<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-50954 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50954</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 returns sensitive information in URL information that could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275776.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31902 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31902</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.   IBM X-Force ID:  289234.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35119 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35119</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in a stack trace.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  290342.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28798 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28798</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  287172.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35022 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35022</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a local user to update projects that they do not have the authorization to access.  IBM X-Force ID:  258254.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28795 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28795</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  286832.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5062 | Reflected XSS through survey redirect parameter in zenml-io/zenml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5062</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in zenml-io/zenml version 0.57.1. The vulnerability exists due to improper neutralization of input during web page generation, specifically within the survey redirect parameter. This flaw allows an attacker to redirect users to a specified URL after completing a survey, without proper validation of the 'redirect' parameter. Consequently, an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of the user's browser session. This vulnerability could be exploited to steal cookies, potentially leading to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6415 | Ingenico Estate Manager New Widget cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6415</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /emgui/rest/preferences/PREF_HOME_PAGE/sponsor/3/ of the component New Widget Handler. The manipulation of the argument URL leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-270001 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 04:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6414 | Parsec Automation TrakSYS Export Page contentpage direct request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6414</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Parsec Automation TrakSYS 11.x.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file TS/export/contentpage of the component Export Page. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to direct request. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-270000. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5926 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27; in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5926</link><description>Path Traversal: '\..\filename' in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 01:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39848 | Internet2 Grouper before 5.6 allows authentication bypass when LDAP authentication is used in certain ways. This is related to internet2.mid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39848</link><description>Internet2 Grouper before 5.6 allows authentication bypass when LDAP authentication is used in certain ways. This is related to internet2.middleware.grouper.ws.security.WsGrouperLdapAuthentication and the use of the UyY29r password for the M3vwHr account. This also affects "Grouper for Web Services" before 4.13.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39846 | NewPass before 1.2.0 stores passwords (rather than password hashes) directly, which makes it easier to obtain unauthorized access to sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39846</link><description>NewPass before 1.2.0 stores passwords (rather than password hashes) directly, which makes it easier to obtain unauthorized access to sensitive information. NOTE: in each case, data at rest is encrypted, but is decrypted within process memory during use.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39840 | Factorio before 1.1.101 allows a crafted server to execute arbitrary code on clients via a custom map that leverages the ability of certain ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39840</link><description>Factorio before 1.1.101 allows a crafted server to execute arbitrary code on clients via a custom map that leverages the ability of certain Lua base module functions to execute bytecode and generate fake objects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2386 | WordPress Plugin for Google Maps – WP MAPS &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2386</link><description>The WordPress Plugin for Google Maps – WP MAPS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'put_wpgm' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25943 | iDRAC9, versions prior to 7.00.00.172 for 14th Generation and 7.10.50.00 for 15th and 16th Generations, contains a session hijacking vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25943</link><description>iDRAC9, versions prior to 7.00.00.172 for 14th Generation and 7.10.50.00 for 15th and 16th Generations, contains a session hijacking vulnerability in IPMI. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to arbitrary code execution on the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4017 | Goya &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.7 - Unauthenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4017</link><description>The Goya theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attra-color’,  'attra-size', and 'product-cata' parameters in versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 11:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5819 | Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features &amp;lt;= 3.2.45 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via HTML Data Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5819</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML data attributes in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.45 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5666 | Extensions for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5666</link><description>The Extensions for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the EE Button widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5790 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.11.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Gradient Heading Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5790</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ attribute within the plugin's Gradient Heading widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6363 | Stock Ticker &amp;lt;= 3.24.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via stock_ticker Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6363</link><description>The Stock Ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's stock_ticker shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5192 | Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp;amp; One Click Upsells &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5192</link><description>The Funnel Builder for WordPress by FunnelKit – Customize WooCommerce Checkout Pages, Create Sales Funnels, Order Bumps &amp; One Click Upsells plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘mimes’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5598 | Advanced File Manager &amp;lt;= 5.2.4 - Sensitive Information Exposure via Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5598</link><description>The Advanced File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.4 via the 'fma_local_file_system' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including backups or other sensitive information if the files have been moved to the built-in Trash folder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5889 | Events Manager &amp;lt;= 6.4.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5889</link><description>The Events Manager – Calendar, Bookings, Tickets, and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘country’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5942 | Page and Post Clone &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5942</link><description>The Page and Post Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.0 via the 'content_clone' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to clone and read private posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6265 | UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp;amp; Members Directory plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;uwp_sort_by&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6265</link><description>The UsersWP – Front-end login form, User Registration, User Profile &amp; Members Directory plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘uwp_sort_by’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6405 | Floating Social Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6405</link><description>The Floating Social Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the floating_social_buttons_option() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugins settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25211 | parseWildcardRules in Gin-Gonic CORS middleware before 1.6.0 mishandles a wildcard at the end of an origin string, e.g., https://example.com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25211</link><description>parseWildcardRules in Gin-Gonic CORS middleware before 1.6.0 mishandles a wildcard at the end of an origin string, e.g., https://example.community/* is allowed when the intention is that only https://example.com/* should be allowed, and http://localhost.example.com/* is allowed when the intention is that only http://localhost/* should be allowed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 23:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37371 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can cause invalid memory reads during GSS message token handling by sending message ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37371</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can cause invalid memory reads during GSS message token handling by sending message tokens with invalid length fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37370 | In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can modify the plaintext Extra Count field of a confidential GSS krb5 wrap token, ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37370</link><description>In MIT Kerberos 5 (aka krb5) before 1.21.3, an attacker can modify the plaintext Extra Count field of a confidential GSS krb5 wrap token, causing the unwrapped token to appear truncated to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39828 | R74n Sandboxels 1.9 through 1.9.5 allows XSS via a message in a modified saved-game file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39828</link><description>R74n Sandboxels 1.9 through 1.9.5 allows XSS via a message in a modified saved-game file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 22:20:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38532 | TEST_KEY used in example dcp_tool reference implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38532</link><description>The NXP Data Co-Processor (DCP) is a built-in hardware module for specific NXP SoCs¹ that implements a dedicated AES cryptographic engine for encryption/decryption operations. The dcp_tool reference implementation included in the repository selected the test key, regardless of its `-t` argument. This issue has been patched in commit 26a7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38533 | ZKsync Era invalid stack addressing conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38533</link><description>ZKsync Era is a layer 2 rollup that uses zero-knowledge proofs to scale Ethereum. There is possible invalid stack access due to the addresses used to access the stack not properly being converted to cells. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38525 | dd-trace-cpp malformed unicode header values may cause crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38525</link><description>dd-trace-cpp is the Datadog distributed tracing for C++. When the library fails to extract trace context due to malformed unicode, it logs the list of audited headers and their values using the `nlohmann` JSON library. However, due to the way the JSON library is invoked, it throws an uncaught exception, which results in a crash. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29040 | Fapi Verify Quote: Does not detect if quote was not generated by TPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29040</link><description>This repository hosts source code implementing the Trusted Computing Group's (TCG) TPM2 Software Stack (TSS). The JSON Quote Info returned by Fapi_Quote has to be deserialized by Fapi_VerifyQuote to the TPM Structure `TPMS_ATTEST`. For the field `TPM2_GENERATED magic` of this structure any number can be used in the JSON structure. The verifier can receive a state which does not represent the actual, possibly malicious state of the device under test. The malicious device might get access to data it shouldn't, or can use services it shouldn't be able to. This 
issue has been patched in version 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39302 | Some bbb-record-core files installed with wrong file permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39302</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom designed to help teachers teach and learners learn. An attacker may be able to exploit the overly elevated file permissions in the `/usr/local/bigbluebutton/core/vendor/bundle/ruby/2.7.0/gems/resque-2.6.0` directory with the goal of privilege escalation, potentially exposing sensitive information on the server. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2.6.18, 2.7.8 and 3.0.0-alpha.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39307 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via crafted ebooks in Kavita</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39307</link><description>Kavita is a cross platform reading server. Opening an ebook with malicious scripts inside leads to code execution inside the browsing context. Kavita doesn't sanitize or sandbox the contents of epubs, allowing scripts inside ebooks to execute. This vulnerability was patched in version 0.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38518 | bbb-web API additional parameters considered</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38518</link><description>BigBlueButton is an open-source virtual classroom designed to help teachers teach and learners learn. An attacker with a valid join link to a meeting can trick BigBlueButton into generating a signed join link with additional parameters. One of those parameters may be "role=moderator", allowing an attacker to join a meeting as moderator using a join link that was originally created for viewer access. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 2.6.18, 2.7.8 and 3.0.0-alpha.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3995 | Command Injection in Helix Sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3995</link><description>In Helix ALM versions prior to 2024.2.0, a local command injection was identified.  Reported by Bryan Riggins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38528 | Unlimited number of NTS-KE connections can crash ntpd-rs server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38528</link><description>nptd-rs is a tool for synchronizing your computer's clock, implementing the NTP and NTS protocols. There is a missing limit for accepted NTS-KE connections. This allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to crash ntpd-rs when an NTS-KE server is configured. Non NTS-KE server configurations, such as the default ntpd-rs configuration, are unaffected. This vulnerability has been patched in version 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5827 | Arbitrary File Write by Prompt Injection via DuckDB SQL in vanna-ai/vanna</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5827</link><description>Vanna v0.3.4 is vulnerable to SQL injection in its DuckDB integration exposed to its Flask Web APIs. Attackers can inject malicious SQL training data and generate corresponding queries to write arbitrary files on the victim's file system, such as backdoor.php with contents ``. This can lead to command execution or the creation of backdoors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5712 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5712</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in stitionai/devika</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27540 | A potential Time-of-Check to Time-of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the HP BIOS for certain HP PC products, which might a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27540</link><description>A potential Time-of-Check to Time-of Use (TOCTOU) vulnerability has been identified in the HP BIOS for certain HP PC products, which might allow arbitrary code execution, denial of service, and information disclosure. HP is releasing BIOS updates to mitigate the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38383 | IBM Cloud Pak for Security information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38383</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak for Security (CP4S) 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 and IBM QRadar Software Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.21.0 allows web pages to be stored locally which can be read by another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  233673.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25041 | IBM Cognos Analytics cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25041</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, and 12.0.2 is potentially vulnerable to cross site scripting (XSS). A remote attacker could execute malicious commands due to improper validation of column headings in Cognos Assistant.  IBM X-Force ID:  282780.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25053 | IBM Cognos Analytics improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25053</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, and 12.0.2 is vulnerable to improper certificate validation when using the IBM Planning Analytics Data Source Connection. This could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted entity by interfering in the communication path between IBM Planning Analytics server and IBM Cognos Analytics server.  IBM X-Force ID:  283364.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38322 | IBM Storage Defender information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38322</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.4 agent username and password error response discrepancy exposes product to brute force enumeration.  IBM X-Force ID:  294869.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25031 | IBM Storage Defender information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25031</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.4 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow an attacker on the network to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  281678.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27628 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DCMTK v.3.6.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the EctEnhancedCT method component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27628</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in DCMTK v.3.6.8 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the EctEnhancedCT method component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27629 | An issue in dc2niix before v.1.0.20240202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the generated file name is not properly esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27629</link><description>An issue in dc2niix before v.1.0.20240202 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the generated file name is not properly escaped and injected into a system call when certain types of compression are used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35116 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35116</link><description>IBM MQ 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS, and 9.3 CD is vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by an error applying configuration changes.  IBM X-Force ID:  290335.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35156 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35156</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  292766.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38514 | NextChat Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38514</link><description>NextChat is a cross-platform ChatGPT/Gemini UI. There is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability due to a lack of validation of the `endpoint` GET parameter on the WebDav API endpoint. This SSRF can be used to perform arbitrary HTTPS request from the vulnerable instance (MKCOL, PUT and GET methods supported), or to target NextChat users and make them execute arbitrary JavaScript code in their browser. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.12.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38374 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in org.cyclonedx:cyclonedx-core-java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38374</link><description>The CycloneDX core module provides a model representation of the SBOM along with utilities to assist in creating, validating, and parsing SBOMs. Before deserializing CycloneDX Bill of Materials in XML format, _cyclonedx-core-java_ leverages XPath expressions to determine the schema version of the BOM. The `DocumentBuilderFactory` used to evaluate XPath expressions was not configured securely, making the library vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) injection. This vulnerability has been fixed in cyclonedx-core-java version 9.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38371 | Insufficient access control for OAuth2 Device Code flow in authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38371</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Access restrictions assigned to an application were not checked when using the OAuth2 Device code flow. This could potentially allow users without the correct authorization to get OAuth tokens for an application and access it. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2024.6.0, 2024.2.4 and 2024.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31912 | IBM MQ privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31912</link><description>IBM MQ 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could allow an authenticated user to escalate their privileges under certain configurations due to incorrect privilege assignment.  IBM X-Force ID:  289894.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35155 | IBM MQ information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35155</link><description>IBM MQ Console 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD could disclose could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  292765.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31919 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31919</link><description>IBM MQ 9.0 LTS, 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS and 9.3 CD, in certain configurations, is vulnerable to a denial of service attack caused by an error processing messages when an API Exit using MQBUFMH is used.  IBM X-Force ID:  290259.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37905 | Improper Access Control and Incorrect Authorization in github.com/goauthentik/authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37905</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider that emphasizes flexibility and versatility. Authentik API-Access-Token mechanism can be exploited to gain admin user privileges. A successful exploit of the issue will result in a user gaining full admin access to the Authentik application, including resetting user passwords and more. This issue has been patched in version(s) 2024.2.4, 2024.4.2 and 2024.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38522 | CSP bypass in Hush Line</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38522</link><description>Hush Line is a free and open-source, anonymous-tip-line-as-a-service for organizations or individuals. The CSP policy applied on the `tips.hushline.app` website and bundled by default in this repository is trivial to bypass. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6402 | Tenda A301 SetOnlineDevName fromSetWirelessRepeat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6402</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromSetWirelessRepeat of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269947. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6403 | Tenda A301 SetOnlineDevName formWifiBasicSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6403</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12. Affected by this issue is the function formWifiBasicSet of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-269948. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29039 | Missing check in tpm2_checkquote allows attackers to misrepresent the TPM state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29039</link><description>tpm2 is the source repository for the Trusted Platform Module (TPM2.0) tools. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate tpm2_checkquote outputs by altering the TPML_PCR_SELECTION in the PCR input file.  As a result, digest values are incorrectly mapped to PCR slots and banks, providing a misleading picture of the TPM state. This issue has been patched in version 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35139 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35139</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to obtain sensitive information from the container due to incorrect default permissions.  IBM X-Force ID:  292415.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35137 | IBM Security Access Manager Docker information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35137</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.7.1 could allow a local user to possibly elevate their privileges due to sensitive configuration information being exposed.   IBM X-Force ID:  292413.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38521 | Persistent Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in hushline inbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38521</link><description>Hush Line is a free and open-source, anonymous-tip-line-as-a-service for organizations or individuals. There is a stored XSS in the Inbox. The input is displayed using the `safe` Jinja2 attribute, and thus not sanitized upon display. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29038 | tpm2 does not detect if quote was not generated by TPM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29038</link><description>tpm2-tools is the source repository for the Trusted Platform Module (TPM2.0) tools. A malicious attacker can generate arbitrary quote data which is not detected by `tpm2 checkquote`. This issue was patched in version 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38531 | Nix sandbox escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38531</link><description>Nix is a package manager for Linux and other Unix systems that makes package management reliable and reproducible. A build process has access to and can change the permissions of the build directory. After creating a setuid binary in a globally accessible location, a malicious local user can assume the permissions of a Nix daemon worker and hijack all future builds. This issue was patched in version(s) 2.23.1, 2.22.2, 2.21.3, 2.20.7, 2.19.5 and 2.18.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3801 | XSS in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3801</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to Reflected XSS via including scripts in one of GET header parameters. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3816 | SQLi in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3816</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to a blind SQL Injection executed using the search bar. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:05:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37741 | OpenPLC 3 through 9cd8f1b allows XSS via an SVG document as a profile picture.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37741</link><description>OpenPLC 3 through 9cd8f1b allows XSS via an SVG document as a profile picture.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39704 | Soft Circle French-Bread Melty Blood: Actress Again: Current Code through 1.07 Rev. 1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39704</link><description>Soft Circle French-Bread Melty Blood: Actress Again: Current Code through 1.07 Rev. 1.4.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on a client's machine via a crafted packet on TCP port 46318.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3800 | XSS in S@M CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3800</link><description>Sites managed in S@M CMS (Concept Intermedia) might be vulnerable to Reflected XSS via including scripts in requested file names. 
Only a part of observed services is vulnerable, but since vendor has not investigated the root problem, it is hard to determine when the issue appears.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5735 | Full Path Disclosure in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5735</link><description>Full Path Disclosure vulnerability in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension in afHelper.php script allows an unauthorised attacker to retrieve location of web root folder.This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5736 | SSRF in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5736</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension in afGdStream.php script allows to access local files or server pages available only from localhost.  This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5737 | HTML Injection in AdmirorFrames Joomla! Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5737</link><description>Script afGdStream.php in AdmirorFrames Joomla! extension doesn’t specify a content type and as a result default (text/html) is used. An attacker may embed HTML tags directly in image data which is rendered by a webpage as HTML. This issue affects AdmirorFrames: before 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5424 | Gallery Blocks with Lightbox. Image Gallery, (HTML5 video , YouTube, Vimeo) Video Gallery and Lightbox for native gallery &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via galleryID and className Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5424</link><description>The Gallery Blocks with Lightbox. Image Gallery, (HTML5 video , YouTube, Vimeo) Video Gallery and Lightbox for native gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘galleryID’ and 'className' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5662 | Ultimate Post Kit Addons For Elementor – (Post Grid, Post Carousel, Post Slider, Category List, Post Tabs, Timeline, Post Ticker, Tag Cloud) &amp;lt;= 3.11.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Count (Static) Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5662</link><description>The Ultimate Post Kit Addons For Elementor – (Post Grid, Post Carousel, Post Slider, Category List, Post Tabs, Timeline, Post Ticker, Tag Cloud) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the Social Count (Static) widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5922 | Scylla lite &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5922</link><description>The Scylla lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5925 | Theron Lite &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5925</link><description>The Theron Lite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30135 | Sensitive Information Disclosure vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30135</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX is potentially impacted by disclosure of sensitive information in the mobile application when a snapshot is taken.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2795 | SEO SIMPLE PACK &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2795</link><description>The SEO SIMPLE PACK plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 via META description. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract limited information about password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39350 | A vulnerability regarding authentication bypass by spoofing is found in the RTSP functionality. This allows man-in-the-middle attackers to o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39350</link><description>A vulnerability regarding authentication bypass by spoofing is found in the RTSP functionality. This allows man-in-the-middle attackers to obtain privileges without consent via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5788 | Silesia &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Button Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5788</link><description>The Silesia theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ attribute within the theme's Button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5796 | Infinite &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via project_url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5796</link><description>The Infinite theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘project_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6288 | Conversios.io - All-in-one Google Analytics, Pixels and Product Feed Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6288</link><description>The Conversios – Google Analytics 4 (GA4), Meta Pixel &amp; more Via Google Tag Manager For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tiktok_user_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30111 | Missing Root Detection vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30111</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX product is impacted by Missing
Root Detection vulnerability in the mobile application. The  mobile app can be installed in the rooted
device due to which malicious users can gain unauthorized access to the rooted
devices, compromising security and potentially leading to data breaches or
other malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30110 | Lack of input validation vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30110</link><description>HCL DRYiCE
AEX product is impacted by lack of input validation vulnerability in a particular web application. A malicious script can be injected into a system which
can cause the system to behave in unexpected ways.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39347 | Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in firewall functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39347</link><description>Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in firewall functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to access highly sensitive intranet resources via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39348 | Download of code without integrity check vulnerability in AirPrint functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39348</link><description>Download of code without integrity check vulnerability in AirPrint functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.2.5-8227-11 and 1.3.1-9346-8 allows man-in-the-middle attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47802 | A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the IP bloc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47802</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the IP block functionality. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47803 | A vulnerability regarding improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') is found in the Language Settings f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47803</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal') is found in the Language Settings functionality. This allows remote attackers to read specific files containing non-sensitive information via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39349 | A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') is found in the libjansson component and it...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39349</link><description>A vulnerability regarding buffer copy without checking size of input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') is found in the libjansson component and it does not affect the upstream library. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39351 | A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the NTP con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39351</link><description>A vulnerability regarding improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') is found in the NTP configuration. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary commands via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39352 | A vulnerability regarding incorrect authorization is found in the firmware upgrade functionality. This allows remote authenticated users wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39352</link><description>A vulnerability regarding incorrect authorization is found in the firmware upgrade functionality. This allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to bypass firmware integrity check via unspecified vectors. The following models with Synology Camera Firmware versions before 1.0.7-0298 may be affected: BC500 and TC500.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5570 | Simple Photoswipe &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5570</link><description>The Simple Photoswipe WordPress plugin through 0.1 does not have authorisation check when updating its settings, which could allow any authenticated users, such as subscriber to update them</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5727 | Widget4Call &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5727</link><description>The Widget4Call WordPress plugin through 1.0.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5728 | Animated AL List &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5728</link><description>The Animated AL List WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5729 | Simple AL Slider &amp;lt;= 1.2.10 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5729</link><description>The Simple AL Slider WordPress plugin through 1.2.10 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5730 | Pagerank Tools &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5730</link><description>The Pagerank tools WordPress plugin through 1.1.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30109 | Lack of Clickjacking Protection vulnerability affects DRYiCE AEX v10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30109</link><description>HCL DRYiCE AEX is impacted by a lack of clickjacking protection in the AEX web application.  An attacker can use multiple transparent or opaque layers to trick a user into clicking on a button or link on another page than the one intended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37282 | It was identified that under certain specific preconditions, an API key that was originally created with a specific privileges could be subs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37282</link><description>It was identified that under certain specific preconditions, an API key that was originally created with a specific privileges could be subsequently used to create new API keys that have elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6296 | Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.13.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6296</link><description>The Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘data-caption’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5863 | Easy Image Collage &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Data Clearance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5863</link><description>The Easy Image Collage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the ajax_image_collage() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to erase all of the content in arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5864 | Easy Affiliate Links &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5864</link><description>The Easy Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the eafl_reset_settings AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37137 | Dell Key Trust Platform, v3.0.6 and prior, contains Use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A local priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37137</link><description>Dell Key Trust Platform, v3.0.6 and prior, contains Use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A local privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privileged information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 02:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39708 | An issue was discovered in the Agent in Delinea Privilege Manager (formerly Thycotic Privilege Manager) before 12.0.1096 on Windows. Sometim...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39708</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Agent in Delinea Privilege Manager (formerly Thycotic Privilege Manager) before 12.0.1096 on Windows. Sometimes, a non-administrator user can copy a crafted DLL file to a temporary directory (used by .NET Shadow Copies) such that privilege escalation can occur if the core agent service loads that file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>