<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-53188 | Unauthenticated Credentials Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53188</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53189 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: from o before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53189</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: from o before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53190 | Unauthenticated Time Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53190</link><description>A vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53191 | Unauthenticated Network Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53191</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7677 | DOS attack possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7677</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: All versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7679 | Session ID Basic Auth Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7679</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ABB Aspect.This issue affects Aspect: All versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25229 | Omnissa Workspace ONE UEM contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability. A malicious actor with user privileges may be able to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25229</link><description>Omnissa Workspace ONE UEM contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability. A malicious actor with user privileges may be able to access restricted internal system information, potentially enabling enumeration of internal network resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25231 | Omnissa Workspace ONE UEM contains a Secondary Context Path Traversal Vulnerability. A malicious actor may be able to gain access to sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25231</link><description>Omnissa Workspace ONE UEM contains a Secondary Context Path Traversal Vulnerability. A malicious actor may be able to gain access to sensitive information by sending crafted GET requests (read-only) to restricted API endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54063 | Cherry Studio One-click Remote Code Execution Vulnerability through Custom URL Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54063</link><description>Cherry Studio is a desktop client that supports for multiple LLM providers. From versions 1.4.8 to 1.5.0, there is a one-click remote code execution vulnerability through the custom URL handling. An attacker can exploit this by hosting a malicious website or embedding a specially crafted URL on any website. If a victim clicks the exploit link in their browser, the app’s custom URL handler is triggered, leading to remote code execution on the victim’s machine. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53187 | Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53187</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in ABB ASPECT.This issue affects ASPECT: before &lt;3.08.04-s01.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 17:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8866 | YugabyteDB Anywhere web server does not properly enforce authentication for the /metamaster/universe API endpoint. An unauthenticated attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8866</link><description>YugabyteDB Anywhere web server does not properly enforce authentication for the /metamaster/universe API endpoint. An unauthenticated attacker could exploit this flaw to obtain server networking configuration details, including private and public IP addresses and DNS records.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38499 | clone_private_mnt(): make sure that caller has CAP_SYS_ADMIN in the right userns</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38499</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clone_private_mnt(): make sure that caller has CAP_SYS_ADMIN in the right userns

What we want is to verify there is that clone won't expose something
hidden by a mount we wouldn't be able to undo.  "Wouldn't be able to undo"
may be a result of MNT_LOCKED on a child, but it may also come from
lacking admin rights in the userns of the namespace mount belongs to.

clone_private_mnt() checks the former, but not the latter.

There's a number of rather confusing CAP_SYS_ADMIN checks in various
userns during the mount, especially with the new mount API; they serve
different purposes and in case of clone_private_mnt() they usually,
but not always end up covering the missing check mentioned above.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45146 | ModelCache for LLM through v0.2.0 was discovered to contain an deserialization vulnerability via the component /manager/data_manager.py. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45146</link><description>ModelCache for LLM through v0.2.0 was discovered to contain an deserialization vulnerability via the component /manager/data_manager.py. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying crafted data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10037 | PhpTax pfilez Parameter Exec Remote Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10037</link><description>PhpTax version 0.8 contains a remote code execution vulnerability in drawimage.php. The pfilez GET parameter is unsafely passed to the exec() function without sanitization. A remote attacker can inject arbitrary shell commands, leading to code execution under the web server's context. No authentication is required.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10038 | Auxilium RateMyPet Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10038</link><description>Auxilium RateMyPet contains an unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability in upload_banners.php. The banner upload feature fails to validate file types or enforce authentication, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files. These files are stored in a web-accessible /banners/ directory and can be executed directly, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10039 | ZEN Load Balancer Filelog Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10039</link><description>ZEN Load Balancer versions 2.0 and 3.0-rc1 contain a command injection vulnerability in content2-2.cgi. The filelog parameter is passed directly into a backtick-delimited exec() call without sanitation. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary shell commands, resulting in remote code execution as the root user. ZEN Load Balancer is the predecessor of ZEVENET and SKUDONET. The affected versions (2.0 and 3.0-rc1) are no longer supported. SKUDONET CE is the current community-maintained successor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10040 | Openfiler v2.x NetworkCard Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10040</link><description>Openfiler v2.x contains a command injection vulnerability in the system.html page. The device parameter is used to instantiate a NetworkCard object, whose constructor in network.inc calls exec() with unsanitized input. An authenticated attacker can exploit this to execute arbitrary commands as the openfiler user. Due to misconfigured sudoers, the openfiler user can escalate privileges to root via sudo /bin/bash without a password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:19:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8859 | code-projects eBlog Site File Upload save-slider.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8859</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects eBlog Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /native/admin/save-slider.php of the component File Upload Module. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8865 | The YugabyteDB tablet server contains a flaw in its YCQL query handling that can trigger a null pointer dereference when processing certain ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8865</link><description>The YugabyteDB tablet server contains a flaw in its YCQL query handling that can trigger a null pointer dereference when processing certain malformed inputs. An authenticated attacker could exploit this issue to crash the YCQL tablet server, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8852 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM API Response upload information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8852</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM 11.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /adminFile/upload of the component API Response Handler. The manipulation leads to information exposure through error message. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8851 | LibTIFF tiffcrop tiffcrop.c readSeparateStripsetoBuffer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8851</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in LibTIFF up to 4.5.1. Affected by this issue is the function readSeparateStripsetoBuffer of the file tools/tiffcrop.c of the component tiffcrop. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The patch is identified as 8a7a48d7a645992ca83062b3a1873c951661e2b3. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8864 | Shared Access Signature token is not masked in the backup configuration response and is also exposed in the yb_backup logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8864</link><description>Shared Access Signature token is not masked in the backup configuration response and is also exposed in the yb_backup logs</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8847 | yangzongzhuan RuoYi edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8847</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yangzongzhuan RuoYi up to 4.8.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Edit of the file /system/notice/edit. The manipulation of the argument noticeTitle/noticeContent leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8863 | YugabyteDB diagnostic information was transmitted over HTTP, which could expose sensitive data during transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8863</link><description>YugabyteDB diagnostic information was transmitted over HTTP, which could expose sensitive data during transmission</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8846 | NASM Netwide Assember parser.c parse_line stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8846</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NASM Netwide Assember 2.17rc0. Affected is the function parse_line of the file parser.c. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8862 | YugabyteDB has been collecting diagnostics information from YugabyteDB servers, which may include sensitive gflag configurations. To mitigat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8862</link><description>YugabyteDB has been collecting diagnostics information from YugabyteDB servers, which may include sensitive gflag configurations. To mitigate this, we recommend upgrading the database to a version where this information is properly redacted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8672 | TCC Bypass via Inherited Permissions in Bundled Interpreter in GIMP.app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8672</link><description>MacOS version of GIMP bundles a Python interpreter that inherits the Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) permissions
granted by the user to the main application bundle. An attacker with local user access can
invoke this interpreter with arbitrary commands or scripts, leveraging the
application's previously granted TCC permissions to access user's files in privacy-protected folders without triggering user prompts. Accessing other resources beyond previously granted TCC permissions will prompt the user for approval in the name of GIMP, potentially disguising attacker's malicious intent.

This issue has been fixed in 3.1.4.2 version of GIMP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8845 | NASM Netwide Assember nasm.c assemble_file stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8845</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in NASM Netwide Assember 2.17rc0. This issue affects the function assemble_file of the file nasm.c. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 12:26:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8844 | NASM Netwide Assember preproc.c parse_smacro_template null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8844</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in NASM Netwide Assember 2.17rc0. This vulnerability affects the function parse_smacro_template of the file preproc.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8843 | NASM Netwide Assember outmacho.c macho_no_dead_strip heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in NASM Netwide Assember 2.17rc0. This affects the function macho_no_dead_strip of the file outmacho.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8842 | NASM Netwide Assember preproc.c do_directive use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8842</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in NASM Netwide Assember 2.17rc0. Affected by this issue is the function do_directive of the file preproc.c. The manipulation leads to use after free. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:42:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8841 | zlt2000 microservices-platform FileController.java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8841</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in zlt2000 microservices-platform up to 6.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Upload of the file zlt-business/file-center/src/main/java/com/central/file/controller/FileController.java. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8840 | jshERP Endpoint deleteBatch improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8840</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jshERP up to 3.5. Affected is an unknown function of the file /jshERP-boot/user/deleteBatch of the component Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Different than CVE-2025-7947.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8853 | 2100 Technology｜Official Document Management System - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8853</link><description>Official Document Management System developed by 2100 Technology has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to obtain any user's connection token and use it to log into the system as that user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8839 | jshERP Endpoint addUser improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8839</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jshERP up to 3.5. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /jshERP-boot/user/addUser of the component Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 09:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8838 | WinterChenS my-site Backend admin preHandle improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8838</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in WinterChenS my-site up to 1f7525f15934d9d6a278de967f6ec9f1757738d8. This vulnerability affects the function preHandle of the file /admin/ of the component Backend Interface. The manipulation of the argument uri leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The code maintainer responded to the issue that "[he] tried it, and using this link automatically redirects to the login page."</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8837 | JasPer JPEG2000 File jpc_dec.c jpc_dec_dump use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8837</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JasPer up to 4.2.5. This affects the function jpc_dec_dump of the file src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_dec.c of the component JPEG2000 File Handler. The manipulation leads to use after free. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 8308060d3fbc1da10353ac8a95c8ea60eba9c25a. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 08:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8661 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Symantec PGP Encryption 11.0.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8661</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability (XSS) occurs when the server does not properly validate or encode the data entered by the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8836 | JasPer JPEG2000 Encoder jpc_enc.c jpc_floorlog2 assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8836</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in JasPer up to 4.2.5. Affected by this issue is the function jpc_floorlog2 of the file src/libjasper/jpc/jpc_enc.c of the component JPEG2000 Encoder. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 79185d32d7a444abae441935b20ae4676b3513d4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8660 | Privilege Escalation in Symantec PGP Encryption 11.0.1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8660</link><description>Privilege escalation occurs when a user gets access to more resources or functionality than they are normally allowed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8747 | Keras safe_mode bypass allows arbitrary code execution when loading a malicious model.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8747</link><description>A safe mode bypass vulnerability in the `Model.load_model` method in Keras versions 3.0.0 through 3.10.0 allows an attacker to achieve arbitrary code execution by convincing a user to load a specially crafted `.keras` model archive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8835 | JasPer Image Color Space Conversion jas_image.c jas_image_chclrspc null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8835</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JasPer up to 4.2.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function jas_image_chclrspc of the file src/libjasper/base/jas_image.c of the component Image Color Space Conversion Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is bb7d62bd0a2a8e0e1fdb4d603f3305f955158c52. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 07:22:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8834 | JCG Link-net LW-N915R Wireless Basic Settings basic.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8834</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JCG Link-net LW-N915R 17s.20.001.908. Affected is an unknown function of the file /wireless/basic.asp of the component Wireless Basic Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument Network Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 06:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8833 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 langSwitchBack stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8833</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This issue affects the function langSwitchBack of the file /goform/langSwitchBack. The manipulation of the argument langSelectionOnly leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 06:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7965 | CBX Restaurant Booking &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Plugin Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7965</link><description>The CBX Restaurant Booking WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 06:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8832 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setDMZ stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8832</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This vulnerability affects the function setDMZ of the file /goform/setDMZ. The manipulation of the argument DMZIPAddress leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8831 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 remoteManagement stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8831</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This affects the function remoteManagement of the file /goform/remoteManagement. The manipulation of the argument portNumber leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8830 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setWan sub_3517C os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8830</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this issue is the function sub_3517C of the file /goform/setWan. The manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8854 | bullet3 VHACD utility: stack-based buffer overflow in OFF parser (LoadOFF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8854</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in LoadOFF in bulletphysics bullet3 before 3.26 on all platforms allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted OFF file with an overlong initial token processed by the VHACD test utility or invoked indirectly through PyBullet's vhacd function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 05:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8829 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_setBasicAuto um_red os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8829</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this vulnerability is the function um_red of the file /goform/RP_setBasicAuto. The manipulation of the argument hname leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8828 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setIpv6 ipv6cmd os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8828</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected is the function ipv6cmd of the file /goform/setIpv6. The manipulation of the argument Ipv6PriDns/Ipv6SecDns/Ipv6StaticGateway/LanIpv6Addr/LanPrefixLen/pppoeUser/pppoePass/pppoeIdleTime/pppoeRedialPeriod/Ipv6in4_PrefixLen/LocalIpv6/RemoteIpv4/LanIPv6_Prefix/LanPrefixLen/ipv6to4Relay/ipv6rdRelay/tunrd_PrefixLen/wan_UseLinkLocal/Ipv6StaticIp/Ipv6PrefixLen leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 04:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24298 | liteos_a has an UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24298</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in tcb through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24844 | communication_dsoftbus has a missing release of memory vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24844</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through missing release of memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24925 | applications_settings has a missing release of memory vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24925</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through missing release of memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25212 | pasteboard has an improper input vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25212</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through  improper input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25278 | liteos_a has a race condition vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25278</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in tcb through race condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26690 | communication dsoftbus has a NULL pointer vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26690</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27128 | liteos_a has an UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27128</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in tcb through use after free.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27536 | arkcompiler_ets_runtime has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27536</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27562 | communication_dsoftbus has a missing release of memory vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27562</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker case DOS through missing release of memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27577 | liteos_a has a race condition vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27577</link><description>in OpenHarmony v5.0.3 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in tcb through race condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8827 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_setBasicAuto um_inspect_cross_band os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8827</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This issue affects the function um_inspect_cross_band of the file /goform/RP_setBasicAuto. The manipulation of the argument staticGateway leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8825 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_setBasicAuto os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8825</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This affects the function RP_setBasicAuto of the file /goform/RP_setBasicAuto. The manipulation of the argument staticIp/staticNetmask leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8826 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_setBasicAuto um_rp_autochannel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8826</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This vulnerability affects the function um_rp_autochannel of the file /goform/RP_setBasicAuto. The manipulation of the argument apcli_AuthMode_2G/apcli_AuthMode_5G leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8823 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setDeviceName os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8823</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setDeviceName of the file /goform/setDeviceName. The manipulation of the argument DeviceName leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8824 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setRIP stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8824</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this issue is the function setRIP of the file /goform/setRIP. The manipulation of the argument RIPmode/RIPpasswd leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 03:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8821 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 RP_setBasic os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8821</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This issue affects the function RP_setBasic of the file /goform/RP_setBasic. The manipulation of the argument bssid leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 01:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8822 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setOpMode algDisable stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8822</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected is the function algDisable of the file /goform/setOpMode. The manipulation of the argument opMode leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 01:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8820 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 wirelessBasic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8820</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This vulnerability affects the function wirelessBasic of the file /goform/wirelessBasic. The manipulation of the argument submit_SSID1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8819 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setWan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8819</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. This affects the function setWan of the file /goform/setWan. The manipulation of the argument staticIp leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8818 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setLan setDFSSetting os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8818</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this issue is the function setDFSSetting of the file /goform/setLan. The manipulation of the argument lanNetmask/lanIp leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 22:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8817 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setLan stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8817</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setLan of the file /goform/setLan. The manipulation of the argument lan2enabled leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 22:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8816 | Linksys RE6250/RE6300/RE6350/RE6500/RE7000/RE9000 setOpMode stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8816</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Linksys RE6250, RE6300, RE6350, RE6500, RE7000 and RE9000 up to 20250801. Affected is the function setOpMode of the file /goform/setOpMode. The manipulation of the argument ethConv leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8815 | 猫宁i Morning Shiro Configuration index path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8815</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 猫宁i Morning up to bc782730c74ff080494f145cc363a0b4f43f7d3e. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index of the component Shiro Configuration. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8814 | atjiu pybbs CookieUtil.java setCookie cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8814</link><description>A vulnerability was found in atjiu pybbs up to 6.0.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function setCookie of the file src/main/java/co/yiiu/pybbs/util/CookieUtil.java. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 8aa2bb1aef3346e49aec6358edf5e47ce905ae7b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8813 | atjiu pybbs IndexController.java changeLanguage redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8813</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in atjiu pybbs up to 6.0.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function changeLanguage of the file src/main/java/co/yiiu/pybbs/controller/front/IndexController.java. The manipulation of the argument referer leads to open redirect. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as edb14ff13e9e05394960ba46c3d31d844ff2deac. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 14:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8812 | atjiu pybbs Admin Panel settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8812</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in atjiu pybbs up to 6.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /api/settings of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 2fe4a51afbce0068c291bc1818bbc8f7f3b01a22. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 14:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8811 | code-projects Simple Art Gallery registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8811</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Simple Art Gallery 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Admin/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 13:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8810 | Tenda AC20 SetFirewallCfg strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8810</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC20 16.03.08.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function strcpy of the file /goform/SetFirewallCfg. The manipulation of the argument firewallEn leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 13:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8809 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide addelidetails.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8809</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addelidetails.php. The manipulation of the argument del leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 13:07:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8808 | xujeff tianti 天梯 com.jeff.tianti.controller save exportOrder csv injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8808</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujeff tianti 天梯 up to 2.3. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function exportOrder of the file /tianti-module-admin/user/ajax/save of the component com.jeff.tianti.controller. The manipulation leads to csv injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 12:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8807 | xujeff tianti 天梯 save authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8807</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujeff tianti 天梯 up to 2.3. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /tianti-module-admin/user/ajax/save. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8806 | zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 treeData sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8806</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 1.0.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /adpweb/a/sys/office/treeData. The manipulation of the argument extId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 11:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8805 | Open5GS SMF gsm-sm.c smf_gsm_state_wait_pfcp_deletion denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8805</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function smf_gsm_state_wait_pfcp_deletion of the file src/smf/gsm-sm.c of the component SMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as c58b8f081986aaf2a312d73a0a17985518b47fe6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8804 | Open5GS AMF ngap_build_downlink_nas_transport assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8804</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ngap_build_downlink_nas_transport of the component AMF. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is bca0a7b6e01d254f4223b83831162566d4626428. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8803 | Open5GS AMF gmm-sm.c gmm_state_exception denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8803</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Affected is the function gmm_state_de_registered/gmm_state_exception of the file src/amf/gmm-sm.c of the component AMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 1f30edac27f69f61cff50162e980fe58fdeb30ca. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 09:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8802 | Open5GS SMF smf-sm.c smf_state_operational denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8802</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This vulnerability affects the function smf_state_operational of the file src/smf/smf-sm.c of the component SMF. The manipulation of the argument stream leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version v2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as f168f7586a4fa536cee95ae60ac437d997f15b97. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 09:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8801 | Open5GS AMF gmm-sm.c gmm_state_exception denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8801</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This affects the function gmm_state_exception of the file src/amf/gmm-sm.c of the component AMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is f47f2bd4f7274295c5fbb19e2f806753d183d09a. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 08:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8800 | Open5GS AMF esm-handler.c esm_handle_pdn_connectivity_request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8800</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function esm_handle_pdn_connectivity_request of the file src/mme/esm-handler.c of the component AMF Component. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 701505102f514cbde2856cd2ebc9bedb7efc820d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 08:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8799 | Open5GS AMF npcf-build.c amf_nsmf_pdusession_build_create_sm_context denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8799</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function amf_npcf_am_policy_control_build_create/amf_nsmf_pdusession_build_create_sm_context of the file src/amf/npcf-build.c of the component AMF. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.7.6 is able to address this issue. The patch is named cf63dd63197bf61a4b041aa364ba6a6199ab15e4. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 07:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8798 | oitcode samarium Create Product product unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in oitcode samarium up to 0.9.6. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/product of the component Create Product Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 07:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8797 | LitmusChaos Litmus LocalStorage permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component LocalStorage Handler. The manipulation leads to permission issues. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8796 | LitmusChaos Litmus Delete Request delete_project authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8796</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /auth/delete_project/ of the component Delete Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument projectID leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8795 | LitmusChaos Litmus login access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8795</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /auth/login. The manipulation of the argument projectID leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8794 | LitmusChaos Litmus LocalStorage authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8794</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component LocalStorage Handler. The manipulation of the argument projectID leads to authorization bypass. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8793 | LitmusChaos Litmus resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8793</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument projectID leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:30:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52136 | In EMQX before 5.8.6, administrators can install arbitrary novel plugins via the Dashboard web interface. NOTE: the Supplier's position is t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52136</link><description>In EMQX before 5.8.6, administrators can install arbitrary novel plugins via the Dashboard web interface. NOTE: the Supplier's position is that this is the intended behavior; however, 5.8.6 adds a defense-in-depth feature in which a plugin's acceptability (for later Dashboard installation) is set by the "emqx ctl plugins allow" CLI command.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8791 | LitmusChaos Litmus list_projects improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8791</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /auth/list_projects. The manipulation of the argument role leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8792 | LitmusChaos Litmus client-side enforcement of server-side security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8792</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in LitmusChaos Litmus up to 3.19.0. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to client-side enforcement of server-side security. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8790 | Portabilis i-Educar API Endpoint pessoa improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8790</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /module/Api/pessoa of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8788 | Portabilis i-Diario Informações adicionais planos-de-aula-por-areas-de-conhecimento cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8788</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Diario up to 1.5.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /planos-de-aula-por-areas-de-conhecimento/ of the component Informações adicionais. The manipulation of the argument Parecer/Conteúdos/Objetivos leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8789 | Portabilis i-Educar API Endpoint Diario authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8789</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /module/Api/Diario of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to authorization bypass. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8787 | Portabilis i-Diario Registro das atividades registros-de-conteudos-por-disciplina cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8787</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Portabilis i-Diario up to 1.5.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /registros-de-conteudos-por-disciplina/ of the component Registro das atividades. The manipulation of the argument Registro de atividades/Conteúdos leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 02:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8786 | Portabilis i-Diario Registro das atividades registros-de-conteudos-por-areas-de-conhecimento cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8786</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Portabilis i-Diario up to 1.5.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /registros-de-conteudos-por-areas-de-conhecimento/ of the component Registro das atividades. The manipulation of the argument Registro de atividades/Conteúdos leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 02:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8785 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_usuario_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8785</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /intranet/educar_usuario_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument nm_pessoa/matricula/matricula_interna leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8784 | Portabilis i-Educar Cadastrar Vínculo funcionario_vinculo_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8784</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /intranet/funcionario_vinculo_cad.php of the component Cadastrar Vínculo Page. The manipulation of the argument nome leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8775 | Qiyuesuo Eelectronic Signature Platform Scheduled Task upload execute unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8775</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Qiyuesuo Eelectronic Signature Platform up to 4.34 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function execute of the file /api/code/upload of the component Scheduled Task Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8774 | riscv-boom SonicBOOM L1 Data Cache timing discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8774</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in riscv-boom SonicBOOM up to 2.2.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component L1 Data Cache Handler. The manipulation leads to observable timing discrepancy. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 20:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8773 | Dinstar Monitoring Platform 甘肃省危险品库监控平台 login_getPasswordErrorNum.action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8773</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Dinstar Monitoring Platform 甘肃省危险品库监控平台 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /itc/$%7BappPath%7D/login_getPasswordErrorNum.action. The manipulation of the argument userBean.loginName leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8773 | Dinstar Monitoring Platform 甘肃省危险品库监控平台 login_getPasswordErrorNum.action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8773</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Dinstar Monitoring Platform 甘肃省危险品库监控平台 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /itc/$%7BappPath%7D/login_getPasswordErrorNum.action. The manipulation of the argument userBean.loginName leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8772 | Vinades NukeViet Module index.php server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8772</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Vinades NukeViet up to 4.5.06. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php?language=en&amp;amp;nv=upload of the component Module Handler. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8765 | Datacom DM955 5GT 1200 Wireless Basic Settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8765</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Datacom DM955 5GT 1200 825.8010.00. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Wireless Basic Settings. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8764 | linlinjava litemall upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8764</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in linlinjava litemall up to 1.8.0. Affected is the function Upload of the file /wx/storage/upload. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8763 | Ruijie EG306MG strongSwan strongswan.conf missing encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8763</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie EG306MG 3.0(1)B11P309. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /etc/strongswan.conf of the component strongSwan. The manipulation of the argument i_dont_care_about_security_and_use_aggressive_mode_psk leads to missing encryption of sensitive data. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8759 | TRENDnet TN-200 Lighttpd hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8759</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TN-200 1.02b02. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Lighttpd. The manipulation of the argument secdownload.secret with the input neV3rUseMe leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:20:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8758 | TRENDnet TEW-822DRE vsftpd least privilege violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8758</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TEW-822DRE FW103B02. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component vsftpd. The manipulation leads to least privilege violation. Attacking locally is a requirement. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8757 | TRENDnet TV-IP110WN Embedded Boa Web Server boa.conf least privilege violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8757</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TRENDnet TV-IP110WN 1.2.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /server/boa.conf of the component Embedded Boa Web Server. The manipulation leads to least privilege violation. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50233 | Bluetooth: eir: Fix using strlen with hdev-&amp;gt;{dev_name,short_name}</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50233</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: eir: Fix using strlen with hdev-&gt;{dev_name,short_name}

Both dev_name and short_name are not guaranteed to be NULL terminated so
this instead use strnlen and then attempt to determine if the resulting
string needs to be truncated or not.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58238 | Bluetooth: btnxpuart: Resolve TX timeout error in power save stress test</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58238</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: btnxpuart: Resolve TX timeout error in power save stress test

This fixes the tx timeout issue seen while running a stress test on
btnxpuart for couple of hours, such that the interval between two HCI
commands coincide with the power save timeout value of 2 seconds.

Test procedure using bash script:

hciconfig hci0 up
//Enable Power Save feature
hcitool -i hci0 cmd 3f 23 02 00 00
while (true)
do
    hciconfig hci0 leadv
    sleep 2
    hciconfig hci0 noleadv
    sleep 2
done

Error log, after adding few more debug prints:
Bluetooth: btnxpuart_queue_skb(): 01 0A 20 01 00
Bluetooth: hci0: Set UART break: on, status=0
Bluetooth: hci0: btnxpuart_tx_wakeup() tx_work scheduled
Bluetooth: hci0: btnxpuart_tx_work() dequeue: 01 0A 20 01 00
Can't set advertise mode on hci0: Connection timed out (110)
Bluetooth: hci0: command 0x200a tx timeout

When the power save mechanism turns on UART break, and btnxpuart_tx_work()
is scheduled simultaneously, psdata-&gt;ps_state is read as PS_STATE_AWAKE,
which prevents the psdata-&gt;work from being scheduled, which is responsible
to turn OFF UART break.

This issue is fixed by adding a ps_lock mutex around UART break on/off as
well as around ps_state read/write.
btnxpuart_tx_wakeup() will now read updated ps_state value. If ps_state is
PS_STATE_SLEEP, it will first schedule psdata-&gt;work, and then it will
reschedule itself once UART break has been turned off and ps_state is
PS_STATE_AWAKE.

Tested above script for 50,000 iterations and TX timeout error was not
observed anymore.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8756 | TDuckCloud tduck-platform manage preHandle improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8756</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TDuckCloud tduck-platform up to 5.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function preHandle of the file /manage/ of the component com.tduck.cloud.api.web.interceptor.AuthorizationInterceptor. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8755 | macrozheng mall com.macro.mall.portal.controller UmsMemberController.java detail authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8755</link><description>A vulnerability was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function detail of the file UmsMemberController.java of the component com.macro.mall.portal.controller. The manipulation of the argument orderId leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7726 | The7 &amp;lt;= 12.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title and data-dt-img-description Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7726</link><description>The The7 theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via its lightbox rendering code in all versions up to, and including, 12.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. The theme’s JavaScript reads user-supplied 'title' and 'data-dt-img-description' attributes directly via jQuery.attr(), concatenates them into an HTML string, and inserts that string into the DOM using methods such as jQuery.html() without escaping or filtering. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8753 | linlinjava litemall File delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8753</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in linlinjava litemall up to 1.8.0. Affected by this issue is the function delete of the file /admin/storage/delete of the component File Handler. The manipulation of the argument key leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7020 | BYD DiLink OS Incorrect encryption Implementation of system log dumps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7020</link><description>An incorrect encryption implementation vulnerability exists in the system log dump feature of BYD's DiLink 3.0 OS (e.g. in the model ATTO3). An attacker with physical access to the vehicle can bypass the encryption of log dumps on the In-Vehicle Infotainment (IVI) unit's storage. This allows the attacker to access and read system logs containing sensitive data, including personally identifiable information (PII) and location data.

This vulnerability was introduced in a patch intended to fix CVE-2024-54728.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8752 | wangzhixuan spring-shiro-training add command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8752</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangzhixuan spring-shiro-training up to 94812c1fd8f7fe796c931f4984ff1aa0671ab562. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /role/add. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8751 | Protected Total WebShield Extension Block Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8751</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Protected Total WebShield Extension up to 3.2.0 on Chrome. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component Block Page. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 07:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8750 | macrozheng mall Add Product Page upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8750</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Upload of the file /minio/upload of the component Add Product Page. The manipulation of the argument File leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8746 | GNU libopts __strstr_sse2 memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8746</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GNU libopts up to 27.6. Affected is the function __strstr_sse2. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This issue was initially reported to the tcpreplay project, but the code maintainer explains, that this "bug appears to be in libopts which is an external library." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 06:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8745 | Weee RICEPO App com.ricepo.app AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8745</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Weee RICEPO App 6.17.77 on Android. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.ricepo.app. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4655 | SSRF vulnerability in FreeMarker templates in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.5, 2024.Q4.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4655</link><description>SSRF vulnerability in FreeMarker templates in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.5, 2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.15, 7.4 GA through update 92 allows template editors to bypass access validations via crafted URLs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4581 | Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.4 ,2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4581</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.132, and Liferay DXP 2025.Q1.0 through 2025.Q1.4 ,2024.Q4.0 through 2024.Q4.7, 2024.Q3.1 through 2024.Q3.13, 2024.Q2.0 through 2024.Q2.13, 2024.Q1.1 through 2024.Q1.15, 7.4 GA through update 92 allows a pre-authentication blind SSRF vulnerability in the portal-settings-authentication-opensso-web due to improper validation of user-supplied URLs. An attacker can exploit this issue to force the server to make arbitrary HTTP requests to internal systems, potentially leading to internal network enumeration or further exploitation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54997 | OpenBao: Privileged Operator May Execute Code on the Underlying Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54997</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 2.3.1 and below, some OpenBao deployments intentionally limit privileged API operators from executing system code or making network connections. However, these operators can bypass both restrictions through the audit subsystem by manipulating log prefixes. This allows unauthorized code execution and network access that violates the intended security model. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.2. To workaround, users can block access to sys/audit/* endpoints using explicit deny policies, but root operators cannot be restricted this way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54998 | OpenBao Userpass and LDAP User Lockout Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54998</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 0.1.0 through 2.3.1, attackers could bypass the automatic user lockout mechanisms in the OpenBao Userpass or LDAP auth systems. This was caused by different aliasing between pre-flight and full login request user entity alias attributions. This is fixed in version 2.3.2. To work around this issue, existing users may apply rate-limiting quotas on the authentication endpoints:, see https://openbao.org/api-docs/system/rate-limit-quotas/.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54999 | OpenBao: Timing Side-Channel in Userpass Auth Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54999</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 0.1.0 through 2.3.1, when using OpenBao's userpass auth method, user enumeration was possible due to timing difference between non-existent users and users with stored credentials. This is independent of whether the supplied credentials were valid for the given user. This issue was fixed in version 2.3.2. To work around this issue, users may use another auth method or apply rate limiting quotas to limit the number of requests in a period of time: https://openbao.org/api-docs/system/rate-limit-quotas/.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55000 | OpenBao TOTP Secrets Engine Enables Code Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55000</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 0.1.0 through 2.3.1, OpenBao's TOTP secrets engine could accept valid codes multiple times rather than strictly-once. This was caused by unexpected normalization in the underlying TOTP library. To work around, ensure that all codes are first normalized before submitting to the OpenBao endpoint. TOTP code verification is a privileged action; only trusted systems should be verifying codes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55001 | OpenBao LDAP MFA Enforcement Bypass When Using Username As Alias</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55001</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 2.3.1 and below, OpenBao allowed the assignment of policies and MFA attribution based upon entity aliases, chosen by the underlying auth method. When the username_as_alias=true parameter in the LDAP auth method was in use, the caller-supplied username was used verbatim without normalization, allowing an attacker to bypass alias-specific MFA requirements. This issue was fixed in version 2.3.2. To work around this, remove all usage of the username_as_alias=true parameter and update any entity aliases accordingly.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55003 | OpenBao Login MFA Bypasses Rate Limiting and TOTP Token Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55003</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 2.3.1 and below, OpenBao's Login Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) system allows enforcing MFA using Time-based One Time Password (TOTP). Due to normalization applied by the underlying TOTP library, codes were accepted which could contain whitespace; this whitespace could bypass internal rate limiting of the MFA method and allow reuse of existing MFA codes. This issue was fixed in version 2.3.2. To work around this, use of rate-limiting quotas can limit an attacker's ability to exploit this: https://openbao.org/api-docs/system/rate-limit-quotas/.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55006 | Frappe Learning Holds Potential for Malicious SVG Upload in Image Upload Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55006</link><description>Frappe Learning is a learning system that helps users structure their content. In versions 2.33.0 and below, the image upload functionality did not adequately sanitize uploaded SVG files. This allowed users to upload SVG files containing embedded JavaScript or other potentially malicious content. Malicious SVG files could be used to execute arbitrary scripts in the context of other users. A fix for this issue is planned for version 2.34.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55008 | AuthKit React Router: Sensitive auth data rendered in HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55008</link><description>The AuthKit library for React Router 7+ provides helpers for authentication and session management using WorkOS &amp; AuthKit with React Router. In versions 0.6.1 and below, @workos-inc/authkit-react-router exposed sensitive authentication artifacts — specifically sealedSession and accessToken by returning them from the authkitLoader. This caused them to be rendered into the browser HTML. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55009 | AuthKit: Sensitive auth data rendered in HTML</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55009</link><description>The AuthKit library for Remix provides convenient helpers for authentication and session management using WorkOS &amp; AuthKit with Remix. In versions 0.14.1 and below, @workos-inc/authkit-remix exposed sensitive authentication artifacts — specifically sealedSession and accessToken — by returning them from the authkitLoader. This caused them to be rendered into the browser HTML.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55013 | Assemblyline 4 Service Client: Arbitrary Write through path traversal in Client code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55013</link><description>The Assemblyline 4 Service Client interfaces with the API to fetch tasks and publish the result for a service in Assemblyline 4. In versions below 4.6.1.dev138, the Assemblyline 4 Service Client (task_handler.py) accepts a SHA-256 value returned by the service server and uses it directly as a local file name.A malicious or compromised server (or any MITM that can speak to client) can return a path-traversal payload such as `../../../etc/cron.d/evil` and force the client to write the downloaded bytes to an arbitrary location on disk. This is fixed in version 4.6.1.dev138.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55149 | Path Traversal Vulnerability in PDF Review Function (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55149</link><description>Tiny-Scientist is a lightweight framework for automating the entire lifecycle of scientific research—from ideation to implementation, writing, and review. In versions 0.1.1 and below, a critical path traversal vulnerability has been identified in the review_paper function in backend/app.py. The vulnerability allows malicious users to access arbitrary PDF files on the server by providing crafted file paths that bypass the intended security restrictions. This vulnerability allows attackers to: read any PDF file accessible to the server process, potentially access sensitive documents outside the intended directory and perform reconnaissance on the server's file system structure. This issue does not currently have a fix.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54417 | Craft contains a theoretical bypass for CVE-2025-23209</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54417</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. Versions 4.13.8 through 4.16.2 and 5.5.8 through 5.8.3 contain a vulnerability that can bypass CVE-2025-23209: "Craft CMS has a potential RCE with a compromised security key". To exploit this vulnerability, the project must meet these requirements: have a compromised security key and create an arbitrary file in Craft's /storage/backups folder. With those criteria in place, attackers could create a specific, malicious request to the /updater/restore-db endpoint and execute CLI commands remotely. This issue is fixed in versions 4.16.3 and 5.8.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54888 | @fedify/fedify: Improper Authentication and Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54888</link><description>Fedify is a TypeScript library for building federated server apps powered by ActivityPub. In versions below 1.3.20, 1.4.0-dev.585 through 1.4.12, 1.5.0-dev.636 through 1.5.4, 1.6.0-dev.754 through 1.6.7, 1.7.0-pr.251.885 through 1.7.8 and 1.8.0-dev.909 through 1.8.4, an authentication bypass vulnerability allows any unauthenticated attacker to impersonate any ActivityPub actor by sending forged activities signed with their own keys. Activities are processed before verifying the signing key belongs to the claimed actor, enabling complete actor impersonation across all Fedify instances. This is fixed in versions 1.3.20, 1.4.13, 1.5.5, 1.6.8, 1.7.9 and 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54996 | OpenBao Root Namespace Operator May Elevate Token Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54996</link><description>OpenBao exists to provide a software solution to manage, store, and distribute sensitive data including secrets, certificates, and keys. In versions 2.3.1 and below, accounts with access to highly-privileged identity entity systems in root namespaces were able to increase their scope directly to the root policy. While the identity system allowed adding arbitrary policies, which in turn could contain capability grants on arbitrary paths, the root policy was restricted to manual generation using unseal or recovery key shares. The global root policy was not accessible from child namespaces. This issue is fixed in version 2.3.2. To workaround this vulnerability, use of denied_parameters in any policy which has access to the affected identity endpoints (on identity entities) may be sufficient to prohibit this type of attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55152 | oak: ReDoS in x-forwarded-proto and x-forwarded-for headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55152</link><description>oak is a middleware framework for Deno's native HTTP server, Deno Deploy, Node.js 16.5 and later, Cloudflare Workers and Bun. In versions 17.1.5 and below, it's possible to significantly slow down an oak server with specially crafted values of the x-forwarded-proto or x-forwarded-for headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>