<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-44195 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44195</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44211 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44211</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44223 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An attacker with physical access to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44223</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An attacker with physical access to a Mac may be able to view protected content from the Login Window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44231 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A person with physical access to a Ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44231</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A person with physical access to a Mac may be able to bypass Login Window during a software update.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44292 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44292</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44293 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A user may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44293</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A user may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44298 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44298</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42867 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of the process entitlement and Team ID. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.9. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42867</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of the process entitlement and Team ID. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.9. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 03:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11776 | PCRecruiter Extensions &amp;lt;= 1.4.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11776</link><description>The PCRecruiter Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'PCRecruiter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32203 | There is a command injection vulnerability in Huawei terminal printer product. Successful exploitation could result in the highest privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32203</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in Huawei terminal printer product. Successful exploitation could result in the highest privileges of the printer. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-51773)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32203.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32204 | There is an improper input verification vulnerability in Huawei printer product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32204</link><description>There is an improper input verification vulnerability in Huawei printer product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause service abnormal. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-87185)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32204.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34159 | Huawei printers have an input verification vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause device service exceptions....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34159</link><description>Huawei printers have an input verification vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause device service exceptions. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-80078)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-34159.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-9250 | There is an insufficient authentication vulnerability in some Huawei smart phone. An unauthenticated, local attacker can crafts software pac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9250</link><description>There is an insufficient authentication vulnerability in some Huawei smart phone. An unauthenticated, local attacker can crafts software package to exploit this vulnerability. Due to insufficient verification, successful exploitation may impact the service. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2019-12302)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2020-9250.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32144 | There is an insufficient input verification vulnerability in Huawei product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32144</link><description>There is an insufficient input verification vulnerability in Huawei product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to service abnormal. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-76192)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32144.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12678 | Nomad Allocations Vulnerable To Privilege Escalation Within A Namespace Using Unredacted Workload Identity Tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12678</link><description>Nomad Community and Nomad Enterprise ("Nomad") allocations are vulnerable to privilege escalation within a namespace through unredacted workload identity tokens. This vulnerability, identified as CVE-2024-12678, is fixed in Nomad Community Edition 1.9.4 and Nomad Enterprise 1.9.4, 1.8.8, and 1.7.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12829 | Arista NG Firewall ExecManagerImpl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12829</link><description>Arista NG Firewall ExecManagerImpl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ExecManagerImpl class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24015.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12830 | Arista NG Firewall custom_handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12830</link><description>Arista NG Firewall custom_handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the custom_handler method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-24019.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12831 | Arista NG Firewall uvm_login Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12831</link><description>Arista NG Firewall uvm_login Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the uvm_login module. The issue results from incorrect authorization. An attacker can leverage this to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-24324.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12832 | Arista NG Firewall ReportEntry SQL Injection Arbitrary File Read and Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12832</link><description>Arista NG Firewall ReportEntry SQL Injection Arbitrary File Read and Write Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files and disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ReportEntry class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-24325.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54538 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54538</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, tvOS 18.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12700 | Tibbo AggreGate Network Manager Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12700</link><description>There is an unrestricted file upload vulnerability where it is possible for an authenticated user (low privileged) to upload an jsp shell and execute code with the privileges of user running the web server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54009 | Remote authentication bypass vulnerability in HPE Alletra Storage MP B10000 in versions prior to version 10.4.5 could be remotely exploited ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54009</link><description>Remote authentication bypass vulnerability in HPE Alletra Storage MP B10000 in versions prior to version 10.4.5 could be remotely exploited to allow disclosure of information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56327 | Malicious plugin names, recipients, or identities can cause arbitrary binary execution in pyrage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56327</link><description>pyrage is a set of Python bindings for the rage file encryption library (age in Rust). `pyrage` uses the Rust `age` crate for its underlying operations, and `age` is vulnerable to GHSA-4fg7-vxc8-qx5w. All details of GHSA-4fg7-vxc8-qx5w are relevant to `pyrage` for the versions specified in this advisory. See GHSA-4fg7-vxc8-qx5w for full details. Versions of `pyrage` before 1.2.0 lack plugin support and are therefore **not affected**. An equivalent issue was fixed in [the reference Go implementation of age](https://github.com/FiloSottile/age), see advisory GHSA-32gq-x56h-299c. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.3 and all users are advised to update. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54663 | An issue was discovered in the Webmail Classic UI in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54663</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Webmail Classic UI in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability exists in the /h/rest endpoint, allowing authenticated remote attackers to include and access sensitive files in the WebRoot directory. Exploitation requires a valid auth token and involves crafting a malicious request targeting specific file paths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:20:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54983 | An issue in Quectel BC95-CNV V100R001C00SPC051 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54983</link><description>An issue in Quectel BC95-CNV V100R001C00SPC051 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:20:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54984 | An issue in Quectel BG96 BG96MAR02A08M1G allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54984</link><description>An issue in Quectel BG96 BG96MAR02A08M1G allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54982 | An issue in Quectel BC25 with firmware version BC25PAR01A06 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54982</link><description>An issue in Quectel BC25 with firmware version BC25PAR01A06 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a crafted NAS message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11364 | Rockwell Automation Third Party Vulnerability in Arena®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11364</link><description>Another “uninitialized variable” code execution vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena® that could allow a threat actor to craft a DOE file and force the software to access a variable prior to it being initialized. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12672 | Rockwell Automation Third Party Vulnerability in Arena®</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12672</link><description>A third-party vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena® that could allow a threat actor to write beyond the boundaries of allocated memory in a DOE file. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12729 | A post-auth SQLi vulnerability in the User Portal allows authenticated users to execute code remotely in Sophos Firewall older than version ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12729</link><description>A post-auth SQLi vulnerability in the User Portal allows authenticated users to execute code remotely in Sophos Firewall older than version 21.0 MR1 (21.0.1).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12175 | Rockwell Automation Code Execution Vulnerability in Arena</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12175</link><description>Another “use after free” code execution vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena® that could allow a threat actor to craft a DOE file and force the software to use a resource that was already used. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:10:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11157 | Rockwell Automation Third Party Vulnerability in Arena</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11157</link><description>A third-party vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Arena® that could allow a threat actor to write beyond the boundaries of allocated memory in a DOE file. If exploited, a threat actor could leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code. To exploit this vulnerability, a legitimate user must execute the malicious code crafted by the threat actor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12728 | A weak credentials vulnerability potentially allows privileged system access via SSH to Sophos Firewall older than version 20.0 MR3 (20.0.3)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12728</link><description>A weak credentials vulnerability potentially allows privileged system access via SSH to Sophos Firewall older than version 20.0 MR3 (20.0.3).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12727 | A pre-auth SQL injection vulnerability in the email protection feature of Sophos Firewall versions older than 21.0 MR1 (21.0.1) allows acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12727</link><description>A pre-auth SQL injection vulnerability in the email protection feature of Sophos Firewall versions older than 21.0 MR1 (21.0.1) allows access to the reporting database and can lead to remote code execution if a specific configuration of Secure PDF eXchange (SPX) is enabled in combination with the firewall running in High Availability (HA) mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2201 | CVE-2024-2201</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2201</link><description>A cross-privilege Spectre v2 vulnerability allows attackers to bypass all deployed mitigations, including the recent Fine(IBT), and to leak arbitrary Linux kernel memory on Intel systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12111 | Potential LDAP authentication vulnerabilities in OpenText Privileged Access Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12111</link><description>In a specific scenario a LDAP user can abuse the authentication process in OpenText Privileged Access Manager that allows authentication bypass. This issue affects Privileged Access Manager version 23.3(4.4); 24.3(4.5)</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7137 | Denial of Service in Silicon Labs RS9116 Bluetooth SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7137</link><description>The L2CAP receive data buffer for L2CAP packets is restricted to packet sizes smaller than the maximum supported packet size. Receiving a packet that exceeds the restricted buffer length may cause a crash. A hard reset is required to recover the crashed device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7138 | Denial of Service in Silicon Labs RS9116 Bluetooth SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7138</link><description>An assert may be triggered, causing a temporary denial of service when a peer device sends a specially crafted malformed L2CAP packet. If a watchdog timer is not enabled, a hard reset is required to recover the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7139 | Denial of Service in Silicon Labs RS9116 Bluetooth SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7139</link><description>Due to an unchecked buffer length, a specially crafted L2CAP packet can cause a buffer overflow. This buffer overflow triggers an assert, which results in a temporary denial of service. 

If a watchdog timer is not enabled, a hard reset is required to recover the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49765 | Bypass of Discourse Connect using other login paths if enabled in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49765</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Sites that are using discourse connect but still have local logins enabled could allow attackers to bypass discourse connect to create accounts and login. This problem is patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users unable to upgrade who are using discourse connect may disable all other login methods as a workaround.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52589 | Moderators can view Screened emails even when the “moderators view emails” option is disabled in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52589</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Moderators can see the Screened emails list in the admin dashboard, and through that can learn the email of a user. This problem is patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users unable to upgrade should remove moderator role from untrusted users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52794 | Magnific lightbox susceptible to Cross-site Scripting in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52794</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Users clicking on the lightbox thumbnails could be affected. This problem is patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53991 | Potential Backup file leaked via Nginx in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53991</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. This vulnerability only impacts Discourse instances configured to use `FileStore::LocalStore` which means uploads and backups are stored locally on disk. If an attacker knows the name of the Discourse backup file, the attacker can trick nginx into sending the Discourse backup file with a well crafted request. This issue is patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed versions of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade can either 1. Download all local backups on to another storage device, disable the `enable_backups` site setting and delete all backups until the site has been upgraded to pull in the fix. Or  2. Change the `backup_location` site setting to `s3` so that backups are stored and downloaded directly from S3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56159 | Server source code is exposed to the public if sourcemaps are enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56159</link><description>Astro is a web framework for content-driven websites. A bug in the build process allows any unauthenticated user to read parts of the server source code. During build, along with client assets such as css and font files, the sourcemap files **for the server code** are moved to a publicly-accessible folder. Any outside party can read them with an unauthorized HTTP GET request to the same server hosting the rest of the website. While some server files are hashed, making their access obscure, the files corresponding to the file system router (those in `src/pages`) are predictably named. For example. the sourcemap file for `src/pages/index.astro` gets named `dist/client/pages/index.astro.mjs.map`. This vulnerability is the root cause of issue #12703, which links to a simple stackblitz project demonstrating the vulnerability. Upon build, notice the contents of the `dist/client` (referred to as `config.build.client` in astro code) folder. All astro servers make the folder in question accessible to the public internet without any authentication. It contains `.map` files corresponding to the code that runs on the server. All **server-output** projects on Astro 5 versions **v5.0.3** through **v5.0.7**, that have **sourcemaps enabled**, either directly or through an add-on such as `sentry`, are affected. The fix for **server-output** projects was released in **astro@5.0.8**. Additionally, all **static-output** projects built using Astro 4 versions **4.16.17 or older**, or Astro 5 versions **5.0.8 or older**, that have **sourcemaps enabled** are also affected. The fix for **static-output** projects was released in **astro@5.0.9**, and backported to Astro v4 in **astro@4.16.18**. The immediate impact is limited to source code. Any secrets or environment variables are not exposed unless they are present verbatim in the source code. There is no immediate loss of integrity within the the vulnerable server. However, it is possible to subsequently discover another vulnerability via the revealed source code . There is no immediate impact to availability of the vulnerable server. However, the presence of an unsafe regular expression, for example, can quickly be exploited to subsequently compromise the availability. The fix for **server-output** projects was released in **astro@5.0.8**, and the fix for **static-output** projects was released in **astro@5.0.9** and backported to Astro v4 in **astro@4.16.18**. Users are advised to update immediately if they are using sourcemaps or an integration that enables sourcemaps.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56200 | Uncontrolled Recursion and Asymmetric Resource Consumption in Altair media/file proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56200</link><description>Altair is a fork of Misskey v12. Affected versions lack of request validation and lack of authentication in the image proxy for compressing and resizing remote files could allow attacks that could affect availability, such as by abnormally increasing the CPU usage of the server on which this software is running or placing a heavy load on the network it is using. This issue has been fixed in v12.24Q4.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54150 | Algorithm Confusion Vulnerability in cjwt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54150</link><description>cjwt is a C JSON Web Token (JWT) Implementation. Algorithm confusion occurs when a system improperly verifies the type of signature used, allowing attackers to exploit the lack of distinction between signing methods.  If the system doesn't differentiate between an HMAC signed token and an RS/EC/PS signed token during verification, it becomes vulnerable to this kind of attack. For instance, an attacker could craft a token with the alg field set to "HS256" while the server expects an asymmetric algorithm like "RS256". The server might mistakenly use the wrong verification method, such as using a public key as the HMAC secret, leading to unauthorised access. For RSA, the key can be computed from a few signatures. For Elliptic Curve (EC), two potential keys can be recovered from one signature. This can be used to bypass the signature mechanism if an application relies on asymmetrically signed tokens. This issue has been addressed in version 2.3.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55196 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in the Mail Server Configuration in GoPhish v0.12.1 allows an attacker to access cleartext passwords fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55196</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials in the Mail Server Configuration in GoPhish v0.12.1 allows an attacker to access cleartext passwords for the configured IMAP and SMTP servers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-6923 | HP Linux Imaging and Printing Software - Potential Memory Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-6923</link><description>The HP Linux Imaging and Printing (HPLIP) software may potentially be affected by memory buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12793 | PbootCMS IndexController.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12793</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PbootCMS up to 5.2.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file apps/home/controller/IndexController.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 5.2.4 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12794 | Codezips E-Commerce Site editorder.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12794</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/editorder.php. The manipulation of the argument dstatus/quantity/ddate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7005 | CVE-2023-7005</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7005</link><description>A specially crafted message can be sent to the TTLock App that downgrades the encryption protocol used for communication, and can be utilized to compromise the lock, such as through revealing the unlockKey field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12791 | Codezips E-Commerce Site signin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12791</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file signin.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12792 | Codezips E-Commerce Site newadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12792</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file newadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49336 | IBM Security Guardium server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49336</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 11.5 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38819 | Applications serving static resources through the functional web frameworks WebMvc.fn or WebFlux.fn are vulnerable to path traversal attacks...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38819</link><description>Applications serving static resources through the functional web frameworks WebMvc.fn or WebFlux.fn are vulnerable to path traversal attacks. An attacker can craft malicious HTTP requests and obtain any file on the file system that is also accessible to the process in which the Spring application is running.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51471 | IBM MQ Appliance denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51471</link><description>IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, and 9.4 LTS web console could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial-of-service when trace is enabled due to information being written into memory outside of the intended buffer size.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52897 | IBM MQ Appliance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52897</link><description>IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, and 9.4 LTS web console could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52896 | IBM MQ Appliance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52896</link><description>IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and 9.4 CD web console could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22501 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText™ Operations Bridge Manager allows Input Data Manipulation. 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22501</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in OpenText™ Operations Bridge Manager allows Input Data Manipulation. 

The vulnerability could be exploited to confidential information

This issue affects Operations Bridge Manager: 2017.05, 2017.11, 2018.05, 2018.11, 2019.05, 2019.11, 2020.05, 2020.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12790 | code-projects Hostel Management Site room-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12790</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hostel Management Site 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file room-details.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12788 | Codezips Technical Discussion Forum signinpost.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12788</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Technical Discussion Forum 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file signinpost.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12789 | PbootCMS IndexController.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12789</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PbootCMS up to 3.2.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file apps/home/controller/IndexController.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to code injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.2.4 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12801 | SaxEventRecorder vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12801</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SaxEventRecorder by QOS.CH logback version 1.5.12 on the Java platform, allows an attacker to 
forge requests by compromising logback configuration files in XML.



The attacks involves the modification of DOCTYPE declaration in  XML configuration files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55081 | An XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in the component /datagrip/upload of Chat2DB v0.3.5 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55081</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability in the component /datagrip/upload of Chat2DB v0.3.5 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted XML input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38864 | User-Readable Private Key in Windows Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38864</link><description>Incorrect permissions on the Checkmk Windows Agent's data directory in Checkmk &lt; 2.3.0p23, &lt; 2.2.0p38 and &lt;= 2.1.0p49 (EOL) allows a local attacker to read sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55082 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the endpoint http://{your-server}/url-to-pdf of Stirling-PDF 0.35.1 allows attackers to access sensi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55082</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the endpoint http://{your-server}/url-to-pdf of Stirling-PDF 0.35.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9154 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9154</link><description>A code injection vulnerability in HMS Networks Ewon Flexy 205 allows executing commands on system level on the device. This issue affects Ewon Flexy 205: through 14.8s0 (#2633).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12787 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System check_student_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12787</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /student/check_student_login.php. The manipulation of the argument student_emailid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12798 | JaninoEventEvaluator vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12798</link><description>ACE vulnerability in JaninoEventEvaluator  by QOS.CH logback-core
      upto and including version 1.5.12 in Java applications allows
      attacker to execute arbitrary code by compromising an existing
      logback configuration file or by injecting an environment variable
      before program execution.





Malicious logback configuration files can allow the attacker to execute 
arbitrary code using the JaninoEventEvaluator extension.



A successful attack requires the user to have write access to a 
configuration file. Alternatively, the attacker could inject a malicious 
environment variable pointing to a malicious configuration file. In both 
cases, the attack requires existing privilege.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12786 | X1a0He Adobe Downloader XPC Service com.x1a0he.macOS.Adobe-Downloader.helper shouldAcceptNewConnection privileges management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12786</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in X1a0He Adobe Downloader up to 1.3.1 on macOS. Affected is the function shouldAcceptNewConnection of the file com.x1a0he.macOS.Adobe-Downloader.helper of the component XPC Service. The manipulation leads to improper privilege management. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is not affiliated with the company Adobe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12785 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System sendmail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12785</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file sendmail.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25131 | Openshift-dedicated: must-gather-operator: yaml template injection leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25131</link><description>A flaw was found in the MustGather.managed.openshift.io Custom Defined Resource (CRD) of OpenShift Dedicated. A non-privileged user on the cluster can create a MustGather object with a specially crafted file and set the most privileged service account to run the job. This can allow a standard developer user to escalate their privileges to a cluster administrator and pivot to the AWS environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47093 | Fix various XSS issues and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47093</link><description>Improper neutralization of input in Nagvis before version 1.9.42 which can lead to XSS</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54790 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /index.php in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54790</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /index.php in PHPGurukul Pre-School Enrollment System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the visittime parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10244 | SQLi in ISDO Software&amp;#x27;s Web Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ISDO Software Web Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Web Software: before 3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12784 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System editbill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12784</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file editbill.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26102 | A relative path traversal vulnerability (CWE-23) in FortiWAN version 4.5.7 and below, 4.4 all versions may allow a remote non-authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26102</link><description>A relative path traversal vulnerability (CWE-23) in FortiWAN version 4.5.7 and below, 4.4 all versions may allow a remote non-authenticated attacker to delete files on the system by sending a crafted POST request. In particular, deleting specific configuration files will reset the Admin password to its default value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9101 | phpLDAPadmin: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in entry_chooser.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9101</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the 'Entry Chooser' of phpLDAPadmin (version 1.2.1 through the latest version, 1.2.6.7) allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the user's browser via the 'element' parameter, which is unsafely passed to the JavaScript 'eval' function. However, exploitation is limited to specific conditions where 'opener' is correctly set.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9102 | phpLDAPadmin: Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9102</link><description>phpLDAPadmin since at least version 1.2.0 through the latest version 1.2.6.7 allows users to export elements from the LDAP directory into a Comma-Separated Value (CSV) file, but it does not neutralize special elements that could be interpreted as a command when the file is opened by a spreadsheet product. Thus, this could lead to CSV Formula Injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-32589 | A use after free in Fortinet FortiManager, FortiAnalyzer allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via &lt;insert attack vector ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32589</link><description>A use after free in Fortinet FortiManager, FortiAnalyzer allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12782 | Fujifilm Apeos C3070/Apeos C5570/Apeos C6580 Web Interface index.html#hashHome improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12782</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Fujifilm Apeos C3070, Apeos C5570 and Apeos C6580 up to 24.8.28 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /home/index.html#hashHome of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12783 | itsourcecode Vehicle Management System billaction.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12783</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Vehicle Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /billaction.php. The manipulation of the argument extra-cost leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 13:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45818 | Deadlock in x86 HVM standard VGA handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45818</link><description>The hypervisor contains code to accelerate VGA memory accesses for HVM
guests, when the (virtual) VGA is in "standard" mode.  Locking involved
there has an unusual discipline, leaving a lock acquired past the
return from the function that acquired it.  This behavior results in a
problem when emulating an instruction with two memory accesses, both of
which touch VGA memory (plus some further constraints which aren't
relevant here).  When emulating the 2nd access, the lock that is already
being held would be attempted to be re-acquired, resulting in a
deadlock.

This deadlock was already found when the code was first introduced, but
was analysed incorrectly and the fix was incomplete.  Analysis in light
of the new finding cannot find a way to make the existing locking
discipline work.

In staging, this logic has all been removed because it was discovered
to be accidentally disabled since Xen 4.7.  Therefore, we are fixing the
locking problem by backporting the removal of most of the feature.  Note
that even with the feature disabled, the lock would still be acquired
for any accesses to the VGA MMIO region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45819 | libxl leaks data to PVH guests via ACPI tables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45819</link><description>PVH guests have their ACPI tables constructed by the toolstack.  The
construction involves building the tables in local memory, which are
then copied into guest memory.  While actually used parts of the local
memory are filled in correctly, excess space that is being allocated is
left with its prior contents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37962 | WordPress Fusion Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37962</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Agency Dominion Fusion allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fusion: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12331 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Filebird Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12331</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ajax_install_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install the Filebird plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12626 | AutomatorWP &amp;lt;= 5.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via a-0-o-search_field_value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12626</link><description>The AutomatorWP – Automator plugin for no-code automations, webhooks &amp; custom integrations in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘a-0-o-search_field_value’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. When used in conjunction with the plugin's import and code action feature, this vulnerability can be leveraged to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12820 | Under non-default configuration, a stack-based buffer overflow in FortiOS version 6.0.10 and below, version 5.6.12 and below may allow a rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12820</link><description>Under non-default configuration, a stack-based buffer overflow in FortiOS version 6.0.10 and below, version 5.6.12 and below may allow a remote attacker authenticated to the SSL VPN to crash the FortiClient NAC daemon (fcnacd) and potentially execute arbitrary code via requesting a large FortiClient file name. We are not aware of proof of concept code successfully achieving the latter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-15934 | An execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability in the VCM engine of FortiClient for Linux versions 6.2.7 and below, version 6.4.0. m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-15934</link><description>An execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability in the VCM engine of FortiClient for Linux versions 6.2.7 and below, version 6.4.0. may allow local users to elevate their privileges to root by creating a malicious script or program on the target machine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26115 | An OS command injection (CWE-78) vulnerability in FortiWAN version 4.5.7 and below Command Line Interface may allow a local, authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26115</link><description>An OS command injection (CWE-78) vulnerability in FortiWAN version 4.5.7 and below Command Line Interface may allow a local, authenticated and unprivileged attacker to escalate their privileges to root via executing a specially-crafted command.An OS command injection (CWE-78) vulnerability in FortiWAN Command Line Interface may allow a local, authenticated and unprivileged attacker to escalate their privileges to root via executing a specially-crafted command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 11:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11616 | Double-fetch heap overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11616</link><description>Netskope was made aware of a security vulnerability in Netskope Endpoint DLP’s Content Control Driver where a double-fetch issue leads to heap overflow. The vulnerability arises from the fact that the NumberOfBytes argument to ExAllocatePoolWithTag, and the Length argument for RtlCopyMemory, both independently dereference their value from the user supplied input buffer inside the EpdlpSetUsbAction function, known as a double-fetch. If this length value grows to a higher value in between these two calls, it will result in the RtlCopyMemory call copying user-supplied memory contents outside the range of the allocated buffer, resulting in a heap overflow. A malicious attacker will need admin privileges to exploit the issue.
This issue affects Endpoint DLP version below R119.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4617 | Gaining remote control over Govee devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4617</link><description>Incorrect authorization vulnerability in HTTP POST method in Govee Home application on Android and iOS allows remote attacker to control devices owned by other users via changing "device", "sku" and "type" fields' values. 
This issue affects Govee Home applications on Android and iOS in versions before 5.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12569 | Sensitive Information in Driver’s Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12569</link><description>Disclosure of sensitive information in HikVision camera driver's log file in XProtect Device Pack allows an attacker to read camera credentials stored in the Recording Server under specific conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 08:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26093 | An access of uninitialized pointer (CWE-824) vulnerability in FortiWLC versions 8.6.0, 8.5.3 and earlier may allow a local and authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26093</link><description>An access of uninitialized pointer (CWE-824) vulnerability in FortiWLC versions 8.6.0, 8.5.3 and earlier may allow a local and authenticated attacker to crash the access point being managed by the controller by executing a crafted CLI command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12819 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the processing of Link Control Protocol messages in FortiGate versions 5.6.12, 6.0.10, 6.2.4 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12819</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the processing of Link Control Protocol messages in FortiGate versions 5.6.12, 6.0.10, 6.2.4 and 6.4.1 and earlier may allow a remote attacker with valid SSL VPN credentials to crash the SSL VPN daemon by sending a large LCP packet, when tunnel mode is enabled. Arbitrary code execution may be theoretically possible, albeit practically very difficult to achieve in this context</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 07:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4230 | External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in Edgecross Basic Software for Windows versions 1.00 and later and Edgecross Basic Soft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4230</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in Edgecross Basic Software for Windows versions 1.00 and later and Edgecross Basic Software for Developers versions 1.00 and later allows a malicious local attacker to execute an arbitrary malicious code, resulting in information disclosure, tampering with and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 07:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4229 | Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Edgecross Basic Software for Windows versions 1.00 and later and Edgecross Basic Software for...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4229</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Edgecross Basic Software for Windows versions 1.00 and later and Edgecross Basic Software for Developers versions 1.00 and later allows a malicious local attacker to execute an arbitrary malicious code, resulting in information disclosure, tampering with and deletion, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, if the product is installed in a folder other than a folder that only users with administrative privilege have permission to modify.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 07:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12560 | Button Block – Get fully customizable &amp;amp; multi-functional buttons &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure via Post Duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12560</link><description>The Button Block – Get fully customizable &amp; multi-functional buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5 via the 'btn_block_duplicate_post' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract potentially sensitive data from draft, scheduled (future), private, and password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11740 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.03 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11740</link><description>The The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.03. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11768 | Download manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.03 - Improper Authorization to Unauthenticated Download of Password-Protected Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11768</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized download of password-protected content due to improper password validation on the checkFilePassword function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.03. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download password-protected files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 05:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11984 | SUNNET Corporate Training Management System - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11984</link><description>A unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in epaper draft function in Corporate Training Management System before 10.13 allows remote authenticated users to bypass file upload restrictions and perform arbitrary system commands with SYSTEM privilege via a crafted ZIP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 04:21:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27595 | QVPN Device Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27595</link><description>An insecure library loading vulnerability has been reported to affect QVPN Device Client. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local attackers who have gained user access to execute unauthorized code or commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QVPN Windows 2.0.0.1316 and later
QVPN Windows 2.0.0.1310 and later</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27600 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27600</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.0.1.2277 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2280 build 20230112 and later
QuTS hero h5.0.1.2277 build 20230112 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2374 build 20230417 and later
QuTScloud c5.0.1.2374 and later</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23354 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23354</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained user access to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuLog Center 1.5.0.738 ( 2023/03/06 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.4.1.691 ( 2023/03/01 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.3.1.645 ( 2023/02/22 ) and later</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23356 | QuFirewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23356</link><description>A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to execute arbitrary commands.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuFirewall 2.3.3 ( 2023/03/27 ) and later
  and later</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23357 | QuLog Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23357</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow remote attackers who have gained administrator access to bypass security mechanisms or read application data.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuLog Center 1.5.0.738 ( 2023/03/06 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.4.1.691 ( 2023/03/01 ) and later
QuLog Center 1.3.1.645 ( 2023/02/22 ) and later</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10548 | WP Project Manager &amp;lt;= 2.6.15 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Project Task List REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10548</link><description>The WP Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.15 via the Project Task List ('/wp-json/pm/v2/projects/1/task-lists') REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the hashed passwords of project owners (e.g. adminstrators).</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12121 | Broken Link Checker | Finder &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12121</link><description>The Broken Link Checker | Finder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the 'moblc_check_link' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51532 | Dell PowerStore contains an Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability. A low privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51532</link><description>Dell PowerStore contains an Improper Neutralization of Argument Delimiters in a Command ('Argument Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to modification of arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30443 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30443</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35141 | IBM Security Verify Access privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35141</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0 through 10.0.6 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to execution of unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 02:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33954 | IBM Robotic Process Automation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33954</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation 21.0.1, 21.0.2, and 21.0.3 could allow a user with psychical access to the system to obtain sensitive information due to insufficiently protected credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-39081 | IBM Cognos Analytics Mobile information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-39081</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics Mobile for Android 1.1.14 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55603 | Insufficient session invalidation in Kanboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55603</link><description>Kanboard is project management software that focuses on the Kanban methodology. In affected versions sessions are still usable even though their lifetime has exceeded. Kanboard implements a cutom session handler (`app/Core/Session/SessionHandler.php`), to store the session data in a database. Therefore, when a `session_id` is given, kanboard queries the data from the `sessions` sql table. At this point, it does not correctly verify, if a given `session_id` has already exceeded its lifetime (`expires_at`).
Thus, a session which's lifetime is already `&gt; time()`, is still queried from the database and hence a valid login. The implemented **SessionHandlerInterface::gc** function, that does remove invalid sessions, is called only **with a certain probability** (_Cleans up expired sessions. Called by `session_start()`, based on `session.gc_divisor`, `session.gc_probability` and `session.gc_maxlifetime` settings_) accordingly to the php documentation. In the official Kanboard docker image these values default to: session.gc_probability=1, session.gc_divisor=1000. Thus, an expired session is only terminated with probability 1/1000. This issue has been addressed in release 1.2.43 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-29827 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-29827</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-20553 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-20553</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 5.2.0.0 through 6.1.1.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21586 | Acrobat Reader | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21586</link><description>Adobe Acrobat Reader versions 22.003.20282 (and earlier), 22.003.20281 (and earlier) and 20.005.30418 (and earlier) are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could leverage this vulnerability to achieve an application denial-of-service in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44512 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44512</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44513 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44513</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44516 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44516</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44517 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44517</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44518 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44518</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by a use-after-free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44519 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44519</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by a use-after-free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44520 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44520</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by a use-after-free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44514 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44514</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by a use-after-free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44515 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44515</link><description>Acrobat Reader DC version 22.001.20085 (and earlier), 20.005.3031x (and earlier) and 17.012.30205 (and earlier) are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56317 | In Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0, the WriteAcl function deletes all existing ACL entries first, and then atte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56317</link><description>In Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0, the WriteAcl function deletes all existing ACL entries first, and then attempts to recreate them based on user input. If input validation fails during decoding, the process stops, and no entries are restored by access-control-server.cpp, i.e., a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56318 | In raw\TCP.cpp in Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0 before 27ca6ec, there is a NULL pointer dereference in TCPBas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56318</link><description>In raw\TCP.cpp in Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0 before 27ca6ec, there is a NULL pointer dereference in TCPBase::ProcessSingleMessage via TCP packets with zero messageSize, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56319 | In Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0 before e3277eb, unlimited user label appends in a userlabel cluster can lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56319</link><description>In Matter (aka connectedhomeip or Project CHIP) through 1.4.0.0 before e3277eb, unlimited user label appends in a userlabel cluster can lead to a denial of service (resource exhaustion).</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41145 | A library injection vulnerability exists in the WebView.app helper app of Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.2813.2770.1094 for macOS. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41145</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in the WebView.app helper app of Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.2813.2770.1094 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Teams's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41159 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft OneNote 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage OneNote's access pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41159</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft OneNote 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage OneNote's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41165 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Word 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Word's access privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41165</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Word 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Word's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42004 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.2813.2770.1094 for macOS. A specially crafted library can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42004</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.2813.2770.1094 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Teams's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42220 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Outlook 16.83.3 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Outlook's access p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42220</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Outlook 16.83.3 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Outlook's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43106 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Excel 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Excel's access privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43106</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft Excel 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Excel's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40732 | An access violation vulnerability exists in the DirectComposition functionality win32kbase.sys driver version 10.0.22000.593 as part of Wind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40732</link><description>An access violation vulnerability exists in the DirectComposition functionality win32kbase.sys driver version 10.0.22000.593 as part of Windows 11 version 22000.593 and version 10.0.20348.643 as part of Windows Server 2022 version 20348.643. A specially-crafted set of syscalls can lead to a reboot. An unprivileged user can run specially-crafted code to trigger Denial Of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40733 | An access violation vulnerability exists in the DirectComposition functionality win32kbase.sys driver version 10.0.22000.593 as part of Wind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40733</link><description>An access violation vulnerability exists in the DirectComposition functionality win32kbase.sys driver version 10.0.22000.593 as part of Windows 11 version 22000.593 and version 10.0.20348.643 as part of Windows Server 2022 version 20348.643. A specially-crafted set of syscalls can lead to a reboot. An unprivileged user can run specially-crafted code to trigger Denial Of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39804 | A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft PowerPoint 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage PowerPoint's acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39804</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in Microsoft PowerPoint 16.83 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage PowerPoint's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41138 | A library injection vulnerability exists in the com.microsoft.teams2.modulehost.app helper app of Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.281...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41138</link><description>A library injection vulnerability exists in the com.microsoft.teams2.modulehost.app helper app of Microsoft Teams (work or school) 24046.2813.2770.1094 for macOS. A specially crafted library can leverage Teams's access privileges, leading to a permission bypass. A malicious application could inject a library and start the program to trigger this vulnerability and then make use of the vulnerable application's permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56115 | A vulnerability in Amiro.CMS before 7.8.4 exists due to the failure to take measures to neutralize special elements. It allows remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56115</link><description>A vulnerability in Amiro.CMS before 7.8.4 exists due to the failure to take measures to neutralize special elements. It allows remote attackers to conduct a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53580 | iperf v3.17.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the iperf_exchange_parameters() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53580</link><description>iperf v3.17.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the iperf_exchange_parameters() function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56116 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Amiro.CMS before 7.8.4 allows remote attackers to create an administrator account.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56116</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Amiro.CMS before 7.8.4 allows remote attackers to create an administrator account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37649 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in SecureSTATION v.2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and before allows a physically proximate attacker to obt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37649</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in SecureSTATION v.2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811A and before allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain sensitive information via the modification of user credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55239 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in the standard documentation upload functionality in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55239</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in the standard documentation upload functionality in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9 allows attacker to craft malicious urls with arbitrary javascript in the 'titulo_documento' parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55461 | SeaCMS &lt;=13.0 is vulnerable to command execution in phome.php via the function Ebak_RepPathFiletext().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55461</link><description>SeaCMS &lt;=13.0 is vulnerable to command execution in phome.php via the function Ebak_RepPathFiletext().</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55506 | An IDOR vulnerability in CodeAstro's Complaint Management System v1.0 (version with 0 updates) enables an attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55506</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability in CodeAstro's Complaint Management System v1.0 (version with 0 updates) enables an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the delete.php file and modifying the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55231 | An IDOR vulnerability in the edit-notes.php module of PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing Management System v1.0 allows unauthorized users to mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55231</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability in the edit-notes.php module of PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing Management System v1.0 allows unauthorized users to modify notes belonging to other accounts due to missing authorization checks. This flaw exposes sensitive data and enables attackers to alter another user's information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55232 | An IDOR vulnerability in the manage-notes.php module in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing Management System v1.0 allows unauthorized users to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55232</link><description>An IDOR vulnerability in the manage-notes.php module in PHPGurukul Online Notes Sharing Management System v1.0 allows unauthorized users to delete notes belonging to other accounts due to missing authorization checks. This flaw enables attackers to delete another user's information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55505 | An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the mess-view.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55505</link><description>An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the mess-view.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12692 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12692</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12693 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12693</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12694 | Use after free in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12694</link><description>Use after free in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12695 | Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12695</link><description>Out of bounds write in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 131.0.6778.204 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45338 | Non-linear parsing of case-insensitive content in golang.org/x/net/html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45338</link><description>An attacker can craft an input to the Parse functions that would be processed non-linearly with respect to its length, resulting in extremely slow parsing. This could cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56140 | Bypass of CSRF Middleware in Astro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56140</link><description>Astro is a web framework for content-driven websites. In affected versions a bug in Astro’s CSRF-protection middleware allows requests to bypass CSRF checks. When the `security.checkOrigin` configuration option is set to `true`, Astro middleware will perform a CSRF check. However, a vulnerability exists that can bypass this security. A semicolon-delimited parameter is allowed after the type in `Content-Type`. Web browsers will treat a `Content-Type` such as `application/x-www-form-urlencoded; abc` as a `simple request` and will not perform preflight validation. In this case, CSRF is not blocked as expected. Additionally, the `Content-Type` header is not required for a request. This issue has been addressed in version 4.16.17 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56145 | RCE when PHP `register_argc_argv` config setting is enabled in craftcms/cms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56145</link><description>Craft is a flexible, user-friendly CMS for creating custom digital experiences on the web and beyond. Users of affected versions are affected by this vulnerability if their php.ini configuration has `register_argc_argv` enabled. For these users an unspecified remote code execution vector is present. Users are advised to update to version 4.13.2 or 5.5.2. Users unable to upgrade should disable `register_argc_argv` to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:51:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12686 | Command Injection vulnerability in Remote Support(RS) &amp;amp; Privilege Remote Access (PRA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12686</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Privileged Remote Access (PRA) and Remote Support (RS) which can allow an attacker with existing administrative privileges to inject commands and run as a site user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51470 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51470</link><description>IBM MQ 9.1 LTS, 9.2 LTS, 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, 9.4 CD, IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 LTS, 9.3 CD, 9.4 LTS, and IBM MQ for HPE NonStop 8.1.0 through 8.1.0.25 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial-of-service due to messages with improperly set values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36694 | OpenCart 4.0.2.3 is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) via the Theme Editor Function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36694</link><description>OpenCart 4.0.2.3 is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) via the Theme Editor Function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49363 | Uncontrolled Recursion and Asymmetric Resource Consumption (Amplification) in media/file proxy in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49363</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. In affected versions FileServerService (media proxy) in github.com/misskey-dev/misskey 2024.10.1 or earlier did not detect proxy loops, which allows remote actors to execute a self-propagating reflected/amplified distributed denial-of-service via a maliciously crafted note. FileServerService.prototype.proxyHandler did not check incoming requests are not coming from another proxy server. An attacker can execute an amplified denial-of-service by sending a nested proxy request to the server and end the request with a malicious redirect back to another nested proxy request.
Leading to unbounded recursion until the original request is timed out. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may configure the reverse proxy to block requests to the proxy with an empty User-Agent header or one containing Misskey/. An attacker can not effectively modify the User-Agent header without making another request to the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52579 | Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability in various APIs in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52579</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. Some APIs using `HttpRequestService` do not properly check the target host. This vulnerability allows an attacker to send POST or GET requests to the internal server, which may result in a SSRF attack.It allows an attacker to send POST or GET requests (with some controllable URL parameters) to private IPs, enabling further attacks on internal servers. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52590 | Missing validation allows spoofed profiles in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52590</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. In affected versions missing validation in `ApRequestService.signedGet` allows an attacker to create fake user profiles that appear to be from a different instance than the one where they actually exist. These profiles can be used to impersonate existing users from the target instance. Vulnerable Misskey instances will accept spoofed users as valid, allowing an attacker to impersonate users on another instance. Attackers have full control of the spoofed user and can post, renote, or otherwise interact like a real account. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12741 | Deserialization Of Untrusted Data Vulnerability In NI DAAQAExpress Project File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12741</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability exists in NI DAQExpress that may result in remote code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted project file. This vulnerability affects DAQExpress 5.1 and prior versions.  Please note that DAQExpress is an EOL product and will not receive any updates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52591 | Missing validation allows spoofed profiles and notes in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52591</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. In affected versions missing validation in `ApRequestService.signedGet` and `HttpRequestService.getActivityJson` allows an attacker to create fake user profiles and forged notes. The spoofed users will appear to be from a different instance than the one where they actually exist, and the forged notes will appear to be posted by a different user. Vulnerable Misskey instances will accept the spoofed objects as valid, allowing an attacker to impersonate other users and instances. The attacker retains full control of the spoofed user / note and can interact like a real account. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52592 | Missing validation allows spoofed poll updates in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52592</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. In affected versions missing validation in `ApInboxService.update` allows an attacker to modify the result of polls belonging to another user. No authentication is required, except for a valid signature from any actor on any remote instance. Vulnerable Misskey instances will accept spoofed updates for remote polls. Local polls are unaffected. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52593 | Missing validation allows spoofed &amp;quot;origin&amp;quot; links in Misskey</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52593</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform.In affected versions missing validation in `NoteCreateService.insertNote`, `ApPersonService.createPerson`, and `ApPersonService.updatePerson` allows an attacker to control the target of any "origin" links (such as the "view on remote instance" banner). Any HTTPS URL can be set, even if it belongs to a different domain than the note / user. Vulnerable Misskey instances will use the unverified URL for several clickable links, allowing an attacker to conduct phishing or other attacks against remote users. This issue has been addressed in version 2024.11.0-alpha.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53269 | Happy Eyeballs: Validate that additional_address are IP addresses instead of crashing when sorting in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53269</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. When additional address are not ip addresses, then the Happy Eyeballs sorting algorithm will crash in data plane. This issue has been addressed in releases 1.32.2, 1.31.4, and 1.30.8. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may disable Happy Eyeballs and/or change the IP configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53270 | HTTP/1: sending overload crashes when the request is reset beforehand in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53270</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. In affected versions `sendOverloadError` is going to assume the active request exists when `envoy.load_shed_points.http1_server_abort_dispatch` is configured. If `active_request` is nullptr, only onMessageBeginImpl() is called. However, the `onMessageBeginImpl` will directly return ok status if the stream is already reset leading to the nullptr reference. The downstream reset can actually happen during the H/2 upstream reset. As a result envoy may crash. This issue has been addressed in releases 1.32.3, 1.31.5, 1.30.9, and 1.29.12. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may disable `http1_server_abort_dispatch` load shed point and/or use a high threshold.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53271 | HTTP/1.1 multiple issues with envoy.reloadable_features.http1_balsa_delay_reset in envoy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53271</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native high-performance edge/middle/service proxy. In affected versions envoy  does not properly handle http 1.1 non-101 1xx responses. This can lead to downstream failures in networked devices. This issue has been addressed in versions 1.31.5 and 1.32.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47039 | OOB Read in the android.hardware.boot.IBootControl/default service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47039</link><description>In isSlotMarkedSuccessful of BootControl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local  information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User  interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47040 | Use After Free in the android.hardware.radio.sap.ISap/slot2 service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47040</link><description>There is a possible UAF due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47038 | In dhd_prot_flowrings_pool_release of dhd_msgbuf.c, there is a possible outcof bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47038</link><description>In dhd_prot_flowrings_pool_release of dhd_msgbuf.c, there is a possible outcof bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to localcescalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. Usercinteraction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56047 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.3 - Subscriber+ SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56047</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56048 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56048</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56053 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.3 - Instructor+ SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56053</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56050 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.3 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56050</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56052 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.2 - Student+ Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56052</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56054 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.2 - Instructor+ Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56054</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56057 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56057</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54381 | WordPress Advance Menu Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54381</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theDotstore Advance Menu Manager.This issue affects Advance Menu Manager: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54383 | WordPress WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.9 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54383</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in wpweb WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a before 4.9.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55952 | Dataease Redshift Data Source JDBC Connection Parameters Not Verified Leads to RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55952</link><description>DataEase is an open source business analytics tool. Authenticated users can remotely execute code through the backend JDBC connection. When constructing the jdbc connection string, the parameters are not filtered. Constructing the host as ip:5432/test/?socketFactory=org.springframework.context.support.ClassPathXmlApplicationContext&amp;amp;socketFactoryArg=http://ip:5432/1.xml&amp;amp;a= can trigger the ClassPathXmlApplicationContext construction method. The vulnerability has been fixed in v1.18.27. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55953 | Dataease Mysql JDBC Connection Parameters Not Verified Leads to Deserialization and Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55953</link><description>DataEase is an open source business analytics tool. Authenticated users can read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. When constructing the jdbc connection string, the parameters are not filtered. This vulnerability has been fixed in v1.18.27. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56049 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.2 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56049</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49202 | Keyfactor Command before 12.5.0 has Incorrect Access Control: access tokens are over permissioned, aka 64099. The fixed versions are 11.5.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49202</link><description>Keyfactor Command before 12.5.0 has Incorrect Access Control: access tokens are over permissioned, aka 64099. The fixed versions are 11.5.1.1, 11.5.2.1, 11.5.3.1, 11.5.4.5, 11.5.6.1, 11.6.0, 12.2.0.1, 12.3.0.1, 12.4.0.1, 12.5.0, and 24.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56051 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5 - Student+ Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56051</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Code Injection.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56055 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.2 - Arbitrary Directory Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56055</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49201 | Keyfactor Remote File Orchestrator (aka remote-file-orchestrator) 2.8 before 2.8.1 allows Information Disclosure: sensitive information coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49201</link><description>Keyfactor Remote File Orchestrator (aka remote-file-orchestrator) 2.8 before 2.8.1 allows Information Disclosure: sensitive information could be exposed at the debug logging level.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55088 | GetSimple CMS CE 3.3.19 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the backend plugin module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55088</link><description>GetSimple CMS CE 3.3.19 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the backend plugin module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55089 | Rhymix 2.1.19 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the background import data function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55089</link><description>Rhymix 2.1.19 is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the background import data function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55086 | In the GetSimple CMS CE 3.3.19 management page, Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) can be achieved in the plug-in download address in the ba...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55086</link><description>In the GetSimple CMS CE 3.3.19 management page, Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) can be achieved in the plug-in download address in the backend management system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55492 | Winmail Server 4.4 is vulnerable to f_user=%22%3E%3Csvg%20onload Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55492</link><description>Winmail Server 4.4 is vulnerable to f_user=%22%3E%3Csvg%20onload Cross Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25042 | IBM Cognos Analytics cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25042</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 and 12.0.0 through 12.0.3 



is potentially vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). A remote attacker could execute malicious commands due to improper validation of column headings in Cognos Explorations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41752 | IBM Cognos Analytics HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41752</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 and 12.0.0 through 12.0.3 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45082 | IBM Cognos Analytics HTTP open redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45082</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 and 12.0.0 through 12.0.3 

could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47810 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.3.0.26795 handles a 3D page object. A specially crafted Javascript code i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47810</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.3.0.26795 handles a 3D page object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49576 | A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.3.0.26795 handles a checkbox CBF_Widget object. A specially crafted Javas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49576</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the way Foxit Reader 2024.3.0.26795 handles a checkbox CBF_Widget object. A specially crafted Javascript code inside a malicious PDF document can trigger this vulnerability, which can lead to memory corruption and result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker needs to trick the user into opening the malicious file to trigger this vulnerability. Exploitation is also possible if a user visits a specially crafted, malicious site if the browser plugin extension is enabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12373 | Rockwell Automation PowerMonitor™ 1000 Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12373</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Power Monitor 1000. The vulnerability results in a buffer-overflow, potentially causing denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50956 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50956</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.9 

could allow a privileged user to obtain highly sensitive user credentials from secret keys that are stored in clear text.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12371 | Rockwell Automation PowerMonitor™ 1000 Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12371</link><description>A device takeover vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Power Monitor 1000. This vulnerability allows configuration of a new Policyholder user without any authentication via API. Policyholder user is the most privileged user that can perform edit operations, creating admin users and performing factory reset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12372 | Rockwell Automation PowerMonitor™ 1000 Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12372</link><description>A denial-of-service and possible remote code execution vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation Power Monitor 1000. The vulnerability results in corruption of the heap memory which may compromise the integrity of the system, potentially allowing for remote code execution or a denial-of-service attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47119 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47119</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.9 does not properly validate a certificate which could allow an attacker to spoof a trusted entity by interfering in the communication path between the host and client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52361 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52361</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0.0 through 2.0.9 



 stores user credentials in plain text which can be read by an authenticated user with access to the pod.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56128 | Apache Kafka: SCRAM authentication vulnerable to replay attacks when used without encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56128</link><description>Incorrect Implementation of Authentication Algorithm in Apache Kafka's SCRAM implementation.

Issue Summary:
Apache Kafka's implementation of the Salted Challenge Response Authentication Mechanism (SCRAM) did not fully adhere to the requirements of RFC 5802 [1].
Specifically, as per RFC 5802, the server must verify that the nonce sent by the client in the second message matches the nonce sent by the server in its first message.
However, Kafka's SCRAM implementation did not perform this validation.

Impact:
This vulnerability is exploitable only when an attacker has plaintext access to the SCRAM authentication exchange. However, the usage of SCRAM over plaintext is strongly
discouraged as it is considered an insecure practice [2]. Apache Kafka recommends deploying SCRAM exclusively with TLS encryption to protect SCRAM exchanges from interception [3].
Deployments using SCRAM with TLS are not affected by this issue.

How to Detect If You Are Impacted:
If your deployment uses SCRAM authentication over plaintext communication channels (without TLS encryption), you are likely impacted.
To check if TLS is enabled, review your server.properties configuration file for listeners property. If you have SASL_PLAINTEXT in the listeners, then you are likely impacted.

Fix Details:
The issue has been addressed by introducing nonce verification in the final message of the SCRAM authentication exchange to ensure compliance with RFC 5802.

Affected Versions:
Apache Kafka versions 0.10.2.0 through 3.9.0, excluding the fixed versions below.

Fixed Versions:
3.9.0
3.8.1
3.7.2

Users are advised to upgrade to 3.7.2 or later to mitigate this issue.

Recommendations for Mitigation:
Users unable to upgrade to the fixed versions can mitigate the issue by:
- Using TLS with SCRAM Authentication:
Always deploy SCRAM over TLS to encrypt authentication exchanges and protect against interception.
- Considering Alternative Authentication Mechanisms:
Evaluate alternative authentication mechanisms, such as PLAIN, Kerberos or OAuth with TLS, which provide additional layers of security.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 13:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34990 | A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and 8.5.0 through 8.5.4 allows attacker to execute unauthorized c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34990</link><description>A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and 8.5.0 through 8.5.4 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted web requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48889 | An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiManager version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48889</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiManager version 7.6.0, version 7.4.4 and below, version 7.2.7 and below, version 7.0.12 and below, version 6.4.14 and below and FortiManager Cloud version 7.4.4 and below, version 7.2.7 to 7.2.1, version 7.0.12 to 7.0.1 may allow an authenticated remote attacker to execute unauthorized code via FGFM crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50570 | A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability [CWE-312] in FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50570</link><description>A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability [CWE-312] in FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.1, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13 and FortiClientLinux 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13 may permit a local authenticated user to retrieve VPN password via memory dump, due to JavaScript's garbage collector</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49677 | WordPress Bootstrap Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49677</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in David Cramer Bootstrap Buttons allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Bootstrap Buttons: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51646 | WordPress Saoshyant Element plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saoshyant Saoshyant Element allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Saoshyant Element: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52485 | WordPress WP Menu Image plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52485</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Yudiz Solutions Ltd. WP Menu Image allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Menu Image: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54270 | WordPress Axeptio plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54270</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in axeptio Axeptio allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Axeptio: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54350 | WordPress hmd theme &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54350</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HJYL hmd allows Stored XSS.This issue affects hmd: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55975 | WordPress Dr Affiliate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55975</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Rohit Urane Dr Affiliate allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Dr Affiliate: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55983 | WordPress PowerFormBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55983</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Derek Hamilton PowerFormBuilder allows SQL Injection.This issue affects PowerFormBuilder: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55984 | WordPress Saksh Escrow System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in susheelhbti Saksh Escrow System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Saksh Escrow System: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55985 | WordPress YDS Support Ticket System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55985</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ydesignservices YDS Support Ticket System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects YDS Support Ticket System: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55997 | WordPress Order Delivery &amp;amp; Pickup Location Date Time plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55997</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Web Chunky Order Delivery &amp; Pickup Location Date Time allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Order Delivery &amp; Pickup Location Date Time: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56008 | WordPress Spreadr Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56008</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spreadr Spreadr Woocommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Spreadr Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56010 | WordPress Device Detector Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56010</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pierre Lannoy / PerfOps One Device Detector allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Device Detector: from n/a through 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56016 | WordPress Image Mapper plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56016</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPTooling Image Mapper allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Image Mapper: from n/a through 0.2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56058 | WordPress VRPConnector plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56058</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Gueststream VRPConnector allows Object Injection.This issue affects VRPConnector: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56059 | WordPress Partners plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56059</link><description>Improperly Controlled Modification of Object Prototype Attributes ('Prototype Pollution') vulnerability in Mighty Digital Partners allows Object Injection.This issue affects Partners: from n/a through 0.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4995 | Protocol Downgrade in Wapro ERP Desktop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4995</link><description>Wapro ERP Desktop is vulnerable to MS SQL protocol downgrade request from a server side, what could lead to an unencrypted communication vulnerable to data interception and modification. This issue affects Wapro ERP Desktop versions before 9.00.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4996 | Hardcoded Password in Wapro ERP Desktop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4996</link><description>Use of a hard-coded password for a database administrator account created during Wapro ERP installation allows an attacker to retrieve embedded sensitive data stored in the database. The password is same among all Wapro ERP installations. This issue affects Wapro ERP Desktop versions before 8.90.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11291 | Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp;amp; Content Restriction &amp;lt;= 2.13.4 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11291</link><description>The Paid Membership Subscriptions – Effortless Memberships, Recurring Payments &amp; Content Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.13.4 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11912 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via order_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11912</link><description>The Travel Booking WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to blind time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11926 | Traveler &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Missing Authorization in Several AJAX Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11926</link><description>The Travel Booking WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the '__stPartnerCreateServiceRental',  'st_delete_order_item', '_st_partner_approve_booking', 'save_order_item', and '__userDenyEachInfo' functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify posts, delete posts and pages, approve arbitrary orders, insert orders with arbitrary prices, and deny user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47104 | IBM i incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47104</link><description>IBM i 7.4 and 7.5 is vulnerable to an authenticated user gaining elevated privilege to a physical file. A user with authority to a view can alter the based-on physical file security attributes without having object management rights to the physical file. A malicious actor can use the elevated privileges to perform actions restricted by their view privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12340 | Animation Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Content Slider and Tabs Widget Elementor Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12340</link><description>The Animation Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 via the 'render' function in widgets/content-slider.php and widgets/tabs.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft Elementor template data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12454 | Affiliate Program Suite — SliceWP Affiliates &amp;lt;= 1.1.23 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12454</link><description>The Affiliate Program Suite — SliceWP Affiliates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.23. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 09:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12554 | Peter’s Custom Anti-Spam &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via cas_register_post Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12554</link><description>The Peter’s Custom Anti-Spam plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.3. This is due to missing nonce validation on the cas_register_post() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to blacklist emails via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11614 | Dpdk: denial of service from malicious guest on hypervisors using dpdk vhost library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11614</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in DPDK's Vhost library checksum offload feature. This issue enables an untrusted or compromised guest to crash the hypervisor's vSwitch by forging Virtio descriptors to cause out-of-bounds reads. This flaw allows an attacker with a malicious VM using a virtio driver to cause the vhost-user side to crash by sending a packet with a Tx checksum offload request and an invalid csum_start offset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 08:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11295 | Simple Page Access Restriction &amp;lt;= 1.0.29 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11295</link><description>The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.29 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as logged-in users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 07:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12287 | Biagiotti Membership &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authentication Bypass via biagiotti_membership_check_facebook_user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12287</link><description>The Biagiotti Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users, such as administrators, granted they have access to an email.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 07:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39703 | In ThreatQuotient ThreatQ before 5.29.3, authenticated users are able to execute arbitrary commands by sending a crafted request to an API e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39703</link><description>In ThreatQuotient ThreatQ before 5.29.3, authenticated users are able to execute arbitrary commands by sending a crafted request to an API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47397 | Weak authentication issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier and AE1021PE firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier. If this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47397</link><description>Weak authentication issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier and AE1021PE firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, the authentication may be bypassed with an undocumented specific string.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53688 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53688</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier and AE1021PE firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier, which may allow a logged-in user to execute an arbitrary OS command using a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54457 | Inclusion of undocumented features or chicken bits issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier and AE1021PE firmware version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54457</link><description>Inclusion of undocumented features or chicken bits issue exists in AE1021 firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier and AE1021PE firmware versions 2.0.10 and earlier, which may allow a logged-in user to enable telnet service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1610 | OPPO Store app include remote account token hijacking and sensitive information leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1610</link><description>In OPPO Store APP, there's a possible escalation of privilege due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21546 | Versions of the package unisharp/laravel-filemanager before 2.9.1 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) through using a valid mimety...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21546</link><description>Versions of the package unisharp/laravel-filemanager before 2.9.1 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) through using a valid mimetype and inserting the . character after the php file extension. This allows the attacker to execute malicious code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21547 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.2 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal due to URI normalisation in the browser where ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21547</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.2 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal due to URI normalisation in the browser where the file:// check can be bypassed with file:\\. An attacker could read any file on the server by exploiting the normalization of \ into /.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21548 | Versions of the package bun before 1.1.30 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can exploit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21548</link><description>Versions of the package bun before 1.1.30 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability through Bun's APIs that accept objects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10892 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt; 3.2.43 - Settings update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10892</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder WordPress plugin before 3.2.43 does not have CSRF checks in some AJAX actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4464 | Authorization bypass through user-controlled key vulnerability in streaming service in Synology Media Server before 1.4-2680, 2.0.5-3152 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4464</link><description>Authorization bypass through user-controlled key vulnerability in streaming service in Synology Media Server before 1.4-2680, 2.0.5-3152 and 2.2.0-3325 allows remote attackers to read specific files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 06:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56173 | In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56173</link><description>In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under specific conditions: XSS from JavaScript in an SVG document.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56174 | In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56174</link><description>In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under specific conditions: XSS from client-side template injection in search history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56175 | In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56175</link><description>In Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408, malicious payloads can be stored and subsequently executed in users' browsers under specific conditions: XSS from client-side template injection in list item names.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12698 | Ose-olm-catalogd-container: incomplete fix for rapid reset (cve-2023-39325/cve-2023-44487)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12698</link><description>An incomplete fix for ose-olm-catalogd-container was issued for the Rapid Reset Vulnerability (CVE-2023-39325/CVE-2023-44487) where only unauthenticated streams were protected, not streams created by authenticated sources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 05:09:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56169 | A validation integrity issue was discovered in Fort through 1.6.4 before 2.0.0. RPKI Relying Parties (such as Fort) are supposed to maintain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56169</link><description>A validation integrity issue was discovered in Fort through 1.6.4 before 2.0.0. RPKI Relying Parties (such as Fort) are supposed to maintain a backup cache of the remote RPKI data. This can be employed as a fallback in case a new fetch fails or yields incorrect files. However, the product currently uses its cache merely as a bandwidth saving tool (because fetching is performed through deltas). If a fetch fails midway or yields incorrect files, there is no viable fallback. This leads to incomplete route origin validation data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56170 | A validation integrity issue was discovered in Fort through 1.6.4 before 2.0.0. RPKI manifests are listings of relevant files that clients a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56170</link><description>A validation integrity issue was discovered in Fort through 1.6.4 before 2.0.0. RPKI manifests are listings of relevant files that clients are supposed to verify. Assuming everything else is correct, the most recent version of a manifest should be prioritized over other versions, to prevent replays, accidental or otherwise. Manifests contain the manifestNumber and thisUpdate fields, which can be used to gauge the relevance of a given manifest, when compared to other manifests. The former is a serial-like sequential number, and the latter is the date on which the manifest was created. However, the product does not compare the up-to-dateness of the most recently fetched manifest against the cached manifest. As such, it's prone to a rollback to a previous version if it's served a valid outdated manifest. This leads to outdated route origin validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 04:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11254 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11254</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the disqus_name parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 due to insufficient input validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12025 | Collapsing Categories &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12025</link><description>The Collapsing Categories plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'taxonomy' parameter of the /wp-json/collapsing-categories/v1/get REST API in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12061 | Events Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12061</link><description>The Events Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3 via the naevents_elementor_template shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12250 | Accept Authorize.NET Payments Using Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12250</link><description>The Accept Authorize.NET Payments Using Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 via the cf7adn-info.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract configuration data which can be used to aid in other attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12259 | CRM WordPress Plugin – RepairBuddy &amp;lt;= 3.8120 - Missing Authorization to Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12259</link><description>The CRM WordPress Plugin – RepairBuddy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.8120. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their email through the wc_update_user_data AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12432 | WPC Shop as a Customer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authentication Bypass Due to Insufficiently Unique Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12432</link><description>The WPC Shop as a Customer for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to account takeover and privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8. This is due to the 'generate_key' function not producing a sufficiently random value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to log in as site administrators, granted they have triggered the ajax_login() function which generates a unique key that can be used to log in.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12449 | Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script &amp;lt;= 2.6.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12449</link><description>The Video Share VOD – Turnkey Video Site Builder Script plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_player_html' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12596 | LifterLMS – WP LMS for eLearning, Online Courses, &amp;amp; Quizzes &amp;lt;= 7.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12596</link><description>The LifterLMS – WP LMS for eLearning, Online Courses, &amp; Quizzes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary post deletion due to a missing capability check on the 'llms_delete_cert' action in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11439 | ScanCircle &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11439</link><description>The ScanCircle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'scancircle' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11748 | Taeggie Feed &amp;lt;= 0.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11748</link><description>The Taeggie Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'taeggie-feed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11881 | Easy Waveform Player &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11881</link><description>The Easy Waveform Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'easywaveformplayer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12500 | Philantro – Donations and Donor Management &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12500</link><description>The Philantro – Donations and Donor Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes like 'donate' in all versions up to, and including, 5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12513 | Contests by Rewards Fuel &amp;lt;= 2.0.65 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12513</link><description>The Contests by Rewards Fuel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'RF_CONTEST' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.65 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47480 | Dell Inventory Collector Client, versions prior to 12.7.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access vulnerability. A low-priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47480</link><description>Dell Inventory Collector Client, versions prior to 12.7.0, contains an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access vulnerability. A low-privilege attacker with local access may exploit this vulnerability, potentially resulting in Elevation of Privileges and unauthorized file system access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 03:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>