<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:43:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-5988 | Reflected XSS in Uyumsoft ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5988</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uyumsoft Information System and Technologies LioXERP allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LioXERP: before v.146.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47265 | Apache Airflow: DAG Params alllow to embed unchecked Javascript</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47265</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions 2.6.0 through 2.7.3 has a stored XSS vulnerability that allows a DAG author to add an unbounded and not-sanitized javascript in the parameter description field of the DAG. This Javascript can be executed on the client side of any of the user who looks at the tasks in the browser sandbox. While this issue does not allow to exit the browser sandbox or manipulation of the server-side data - more than the DAG author already has, it allows to modify what the user looking at the DAG details sees in the browser - which opens up all kinds of possibilities of misleading other users.

Users of Apache Airflow are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48291 | Apache Airflow: Improper access control to DAG resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48291</link><description>Apache Airflow, in versions prior to 2.8.0, contains a security vulnerability that allows an authenticated user with limited access to some DAGs, to craft a request that could give the user write access to various DAG resources for DAGs that the user had no access to, thus, enabling the user to clear DAGs they shouldn't.

This is a missing fix for CVE-2023-42792 in Apache Airflow 2.7.2 

Users of Apache Airflow are strongly advised to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or newer to mitigate the risk associated with this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49920 | Apache Airflow: Missing CSRF protection on DAG/trigger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49920</link><description>Apache Airflow, version 2.7.0 through 2.7.3, has a vulnerability that allows an attacker to trigger a DAG in a GET request without CSRF validation. As a result, it was possible for a malicious website opened in the same browser - by the user who also had Airflow UI opened - to trigger the execution of DAGs without the user's consent.
Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.8.0 or later which is not affected</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50783 | Apache Airflow: Improper access control vulnerability on the &amp;quot;varimport&amp;quot; endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50783</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.0, is affected by a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user without the variable edit permission, to update a variable.
This flaw compromises the integrity of variable management, potentially leading to unauthorized data modification.
Users are recommended to upgrade to 2.8.0, which fixes this issue</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2585 | Client access via device auth request spoof</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2585</link><description>Keycloak's device authorization grant does not correctly validate the device code and client ID. An attacker client could abuse the missing validation to spoof a client consent request and trick an authorization admin into granting consent to a malicious OAuth client or possible unauthorized access to an existing OAuth client.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7026 | Lightxun IPTV Gateway web_upload_template.html unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7026</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Lightxun IPTV Gateway up to 20231208. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ZHGXTV/index.php/admin/index/web_upload_template.html. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248579.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 04:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7025 | KylinSoft hedron-domain-hook DBus init_kcm access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7025</link><description>A vulnerability was found in KylinSoft hedron-domain-hook up to 3.8.0.12-0k0.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function init_kcm of the component DBus Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-248578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7023 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7023</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file general/vehicle/query/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument VU_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 02:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7022 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_all.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7022</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/work_plan/manage/delete_all.php. The manipulation of the argument DELETE_STR leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248569 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29485 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29485</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to bypass network filtering, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via DarkLayer Guard threat prevention module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29486 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before 3.7.0 on Windows, allows attackers to bypass USB access restrictions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29486</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before 3.7.0 on Windows, allows attackers to bypass USB access restrictions, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via Next-Gen Antivirus component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29487 | An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29487</link><description>An issue was discovered in Heimdal Thor agent versions 3.4.2 and before on Windows and 2.6.9 and before on macOS, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the Threat To Process Correlation threat prevention module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28025 | An HTML injection vulnerability can affect HCL BigFix Mobile / Modern Client Management </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28025</link><description>Due to this vulnerability, the Master operator could potentially incorporate an SVG tag into HTML, leading to an alert pop-up displaying a cookie. To mitigate stored XSS vulnerabilities, a preventive measure involves thoroughly sanitizing and validating all user inputs before they are processed and stored in the server storage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7021 | Tongda OA 2017 delete_search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7021</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file general/vehicle/checkup/delete_search.php. The manipulation of the argument VU_ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248568. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 01:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45700 | HCL Launch is susceptible to an HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45700</link><description>HCL Launch is vulnerable to HTML injection. This vulnerability may allow a user to embed arbitrary HTML tags in the Web UI potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7020 | Tongda OA 2017 view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7020</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file general/wiki/cp/ct/view.php. The manipulation of the argument TEMP_ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248567. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49032 | An issue in LTB Self Service Password before v.1.5.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49032</link><description>An issue in LTB Self Service Password before v.1.5.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via hijack of the SMS verification code function to arbitrary phone.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45703 | HCL Launch is susceptible to a Denial of Service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45703</link><description>HCL Launch may mishandle input validation of an uploaded archive file leading to a denial of service due to resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51390 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Journalpump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51390</link><description>journalpump is a daemon that takes log messages from journald and pumps them to a given output. A logging vulnerability was found in journalpump which logs out the configuration of a service integration in plaintext to the supplied logging pipeline, including credential information contained in the configuration if any. The problem has been patched in journalpump 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46131 | Grails® data binding causes JVM crash and/or DoS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46131</link><description>Grails is a framework used to build web applications with the Groovy programming language. A specially crafted web request can lead to a JVM crash or denial of service. Any Grails framework application using Grails data binding is vulnerable. This issue has been patched in version 3.3.17, 4.1.3, 5.3.4, 6.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 23:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41166 | An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) 3.7.0 through 3.7.39, 3.11.0 through 3.11.27, 4.3.0 through 4.3.22, 4.6.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41166</link><description>An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) 3.7.0 through 3.7.39, 3.11.0 through 3.11.27, 4.3.0 through 4.3.22, 4.6.0 through 4.6.9, and 4.7.0 through 4.7.1. It's possible to know if a specific user account exists on the SNS firewall by using remote access commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 23:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47093 | An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) 4.0.0 through 4.3.21, 4.4.0 through 4.6.8, and 4.7.0. Sending a crafted ICMP p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47093</link><description>An issue was discovered in Stormshield Network Security (SNS) 4.0.0 through 4.3.21, 4.4.0 through 4.6.8, and 4.7.0. Sending a crafted ICMP packet may lead to a crash of the ASQ engine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 23:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50992 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ip parameter in the setPing function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50992</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ip parameter in the setPing function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50993 | Ruijie WS6008 v1.x v2.x AC_RGOS11.9(6)W3B2_G2C6-01_10221911 and WS6108 v1.x AC_RGOS11.9(6)W3B2_G2C6-01_10221911 was discovered to contain a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50993</link><description>Ruijie WS6008 v1.x v2.x AC_RGOS11.9(6)W3B2_G2C6-01_10221911 and WS6108 v1.x AC_RGOS11.9(6)W3B2_G2C6-01_10221911 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the function downFiles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:58:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50983 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sysScheduleRebootSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50983</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sysScheduleRebootSet function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50984 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the ip parameter in the spdtstConfigAndStart function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50984</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the ip parameter in the spdtstConfigAndStart function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50985 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the lanGw parameter in the lanCfgSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50985</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the lanGw parameter in the lanCfgSet function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50986 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the time parameter in the sysLogin function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50986</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the time parameter in the sysLogin function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50987 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the time parameter in the sysTimeInfoSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50987</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the time parameter in the sysTimeInfoSet function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50988 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the bandwidth parameter in the wifiRadioSetIndoor function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50988</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the bandwidth parameter in the wifiRadioSetIndoor function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50989 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pingSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50989</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pingSet function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50990 | Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the rebootTime parameter in the sysScheduleRebootSet function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50990</link><description>Tenda i29 v1.0 V1.0.0.5 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the rebootTime parameter in the sysScheduleRebootSet function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50639 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CuteHttpFileServer v.1.0 and v.2.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50639</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CuteHttpFileServer v.1.0 and v.2.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the file upload function in the home page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48433 | Online Voting System Project v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48433</link><description>Online Voting System Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the login_action.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 20:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48434 | Online Voting System Project v1.0 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48434</link><description>Online Voting System Project v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'username' parameter of the reg_action.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 20:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44684 | Windows Local Session Manager (LSM) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44684</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23970 | WordPress Corsa Theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23970</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WooRockets Corsa.This issue affects Corsa: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49270 | Hotel Management v1.0 - Multiple Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49270</link><description>Hotel Management v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'check_in_date' parameter of the reservation.php resource is copied into the HTML document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the application's response.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49271 | Hotel Management v1.0 - Multiple Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49271</link><description>Hotel Management v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'check_out_date' parameter of the reservation.php resource is copied into the HTML document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the application's response.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49272 | Hotel Management v1.0 - Multiple Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49272</link><description>Hotel Management v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'children' parameter of the reservation.php resource is copied into the HTML document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the application's response.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25970 | WordPress Zendrop – Global Dropshipping Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25970</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Zendrop Zendrop – Global Dropshipping.This issue affects Zendrop – Global Dropshipping: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28170 | WordPress Theme Demo Import Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28170</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Themely Theme Demo Import.This issue affects Theme Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29102 | WordPress Olive One Click Demo Import Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29102</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Olive Themes Olive One Click Demo Import.This issue affects Olive One Click Demo Import: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29384 | WordPress WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29384</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in HM Plugin WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP.This issue affects WordPress Job Board and Recruitment Plugin – JobWP: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31215 | WordPress Dropshipping &amp;amp; Affiliation with Amazon Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31215</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in AmaderCode Lab Dropshipping &amp; Affiliation with Amazon.This issue affects Dropshipping &amp; Affiliation with Amazon: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47990 | SQL Injection vulnerability in components/table_manager/html/edit_admin_table.php in CuppaCMS V1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47990</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in components/table_manager/html/edit_admin_table.php in CuppaCMS V1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the table parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31231 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.65 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31231</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates).This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.65.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33318 | WordPress WooCommerce Follow-Up Emails Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.40 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33318</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WooCommerce AutomateWoo.This issue affects AutomateWoo: from n/a through 4.9.40.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34007 | WordPress Download Monitor Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34007</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WPChill Download Monitor.This issue affects Download Monitor: from n/a through 4.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34385 | WordPress Export Import Menus Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34385</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Akshay Menariya Export Import Menus.This issue affects Export Import Menus: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40204 | WordPress Folders Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40204</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Premio Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager.This issue affects Folders – Unlimited Folders to Organize Media Library Folder, Pages, Posts, File Manager: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45603 | WordPress User Submitted Posts Plugin &amp;lt;= 20230902 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45603</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Jeff Starr User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End.This issue affects User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End: from n/a through 20230902.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46149 | WordPress Themify Ultra Theme &amp;lt;= 7.3.5 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46149</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Themify Themify Ultra.This issue affects Themify Ultra: from n/a through 7.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47784 | WordPress Slider Revolution Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.15 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47784</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ThemePunch OHG Slider Revolution.This issue affects Slider Revolution: from n/a through 6.6.15.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49814 | WordPress Symbiostock Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.0 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49814</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Symbiostock symbiostock.This issue affects Symbiostock: from n/a through 6.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47597 | WordPress Popup Maker Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.1 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47597</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Popup Maker Popup Maker – Popup for opt-ins, lead gen, &amp; more.This issue affects Popup Maker – Popup for opt-ins, lead gen, &amp; more: from n/a through 1.17.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47599 | WordPress File Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.7 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47599</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in File Manager by Bit Form Team File Manager – 100% Free &amp; Open Source File Manager Plugin for WordPress | Bit File Manager.This issue affects File Manager – 100% Free &amp; Open Source File Manager Plugin for WordPress | Bit File Manager: from n/a through 5.2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49269 | Hotel Management v1.0 - Multiple Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49269</link><description>Hotel Management v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple authenticated Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerabilities. The 'adults' parameter of the reservation.php resource is copied into the HTML document as plain text between tags. Any input is echoed unmodified in the application's response.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49166 | WordPress MSync Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49166</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Magic Logix MSync.This issue affects MSync: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49752 | WordPress Adifier System Plugin &amp;lt; 3.1.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Spoon themes Adifier - Classified Ads WordPress Theme.This issue affects Adifier - Classified Ads WordPress Theme: from n/a before 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26525 | WordPress Dokan Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in weDevs Dokan – Best WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution – Build Your Own Amazon, eBay, Etsy.This issue affects Dokan – Best WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution – Build Your Own Amazon, eBay, Etsy: from n/a through 3.7.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49161 | WordPress Bravo Translate Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Guelben Bravo Translate.This issue affects Bravo Translate: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28491 | WordPress Slideshow Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28491</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Tribulant Slideshow Gallery LITE.This issue affects Slideshow Gallery LITE: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28788 | WordPress Advanced Page Visit Counter Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28788</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Page Visit Counter Advanced Page Visit Counter – Most Wanted Analytics Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects Advanced Page Visit Counter – Most Wanted Analytics Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 6.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29096 | WordPress Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29096</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in BestWebSoft Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft – Messages Database Plugin For WordPress.This issue affects Contact Form to DB by BestWebSoft – Messages Database Plugin For WordPress: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29432 | WordPress Houzez Theme &amp;lt; 2.8.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29432</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Favethemes Houzez - Real Estate WordPress Theme.This issue affects Houzez - Real Estate WordPress Theme: from n/a before 2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30495 | WordPress Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.23 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30495</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Themefic Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7.This issue affects Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 3.1.23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30750 | WordPress CM Pop-Up banners Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.10 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Popup Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects CM Popup Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30872 | WordPress BSK Forms Blacklist Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30872</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in BannerSky BSK Forms Blacklist.This issue affects BSK Forms Blacklist: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47118 | Heap buffer overflow in T64 codec decompression</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47118</link><description>ClickHouse® is an open-source column-oriented database management system that allows generating analytical data reports in real-time. A heap buffer overflow issue was discovered in ClickHouse server. An attacker could send a specially crafted payload to the native interface exposed by default on port 9000/tcp, triggering a bug in the decompression logic of T64 codec that crashes the ClickHouse server process. This attack does not require authentication. Note that this exploit can also be triggered via HTTP protocol, however, the attacker will need a valid credential as the HTTP authentication take places first. This issue has been fixed in version 23.10.2.13-stable, 23.9.4.11-stable, 23.8.6.16-lts and 23.3.16.7-lts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7018 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in huggingface/transformers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7018</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data in GitHub repository huggingface/transformers prior to 4.36.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31092 | WordPress Easy Bet Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31092</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Foxskav Easy Bet.This issue affects Easy Bet: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32128 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Donation Box – Bitcoin &amp;amp; Crypto Donations Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32128</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Adastra Crypto Cryptocurrency Payment &amp; Donation Box – Accept Payments in any Cryptocurrency on your WP Site for Free.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Payment &amp; Donation Box – Accept Payments in any Cryptocurrency on your WP Site for Free: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32743 | WordPress AutomateWoo Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32743</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WooCommerce AutomateWoo.This issue affects AutomateWoo: from n/a through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5007 | Student Information System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5007</link><description>Student Information System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'id' parameter of the marks.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5010 | Student Information System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5010</link><description>Student Information System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'coursecode' parameter of the marks.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5011 | Student Information System v1.0 - Multiple Authenticated SQL Injections (SQLi)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5011</link><description>Student Information System v1.0 is vulnerable to multiple Authenticated SQL Injection vulnerabilities. The 'coursename' parameter of the marks.php resource does not validate the characters received and they are sent unfiltered to the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33209 | WordPress SEO Change Monitor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33209</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CrawlSpider SEO Change Monitor – Track Website Changes.This issue affects SEO Change Monitor – Track Website Changes: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33330 | WordPress WooCommerce Follow-Up Emails Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.50 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33330</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WooCommerce AutomateWoo.This issue affects AutomateWoo: from n/a through 4.9.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49825 | WordPress Soledad Theme &amp;lt;= 8.4.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49825</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PenciDesign Soledad – Multipurpose, Newspaper, Blog &amp; WooCommerce WordPress Theme.This issue affects Soledad – Multipurpose, Newspaper, Blog &amp; WooCommerce WordPress Theme: from n/a through 8.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49773 | WordPress BCorp Shortcodes Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.23 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49773</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Tim Brattberg BCorp Shortcodes.This issue affects BCorp Shortcodes: from n/a through 0.23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49776 | WordPress Sayfa Sayaç Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49776</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Hakan Demiray Sayfa Sayac.This issue affects Sayfa Sayac: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3742 | Insufficient policy enforcement in ADB in Google Chrome on ChromeOS prior to 114.0.5735.90 allowed a local attacker to bypass device policy ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3742</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in ADB in Google Chrome on ChromeOS prior to 114.0.5735.90 allowed a local attacker to bypass device policy restrictions via physical access to the device. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49772 | WordPress Genesis Simple Love Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49772</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Phpbits Creative Studio Genesis Simple Love.This issue affects Genesis Simple Love: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35914 | WordPress WooCommerce Subscriptions Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35914</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce Woo Subscriptions.This issue affects Woo Subscriptions: from n/a through 5.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35915 | WordPress WooCommerce Payments Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35915</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Automattic WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo.This issue affects WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo: from n/a through 5.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35916 | WordPress WooCommerce Payments Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35916</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Automattic WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo.This issue affects WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo: from n/a through 5.9.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40010 | WordPress HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce (formerly WOOF) Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40010</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in realmag777 HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional.This issue affects HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional: from n/a through 1.3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32590 | WordPress Subscribe to Category Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Daniel Söderström / Sidney van de Stouwe Subscribe to Category.This issue affects Subscribe to Category: from n/a through 2.7.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 15:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28782 | WordPress Gravity Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.3 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28782</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Rocketgenius Inc. Gravity Forms.This issue affects Gravity Forms: from n/a through 2.7.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47852 | WordPress Link Whisper Free Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.5 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47852</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Link Whisper Link Whisper Free.This issue affects Link Whisper Free: from n/a through 0.6.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35876 | WordPress WooCommerce Square Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35876</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce WooCommerce Square.This issue affects WooCommerce Square: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35895 | IBM Informix JDBC code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35895</link><description>IBM Informix JDBC Driver 4.10 and 4.50 is susceptible to remote code execution attack via JNDI injection when passing an unchecked argument to a certain API.  IBM X-Force ID:  259116.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36520 | WordPress Editorial Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.12 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36520</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in MarketingFire Editorial Calendar.This issue affects Editorial Calendar: from n/a through 3.7.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51457 | Stored XSS in `/libs/granite/ui/components/coral/foundation/clientlibs/foundation/js/granite/collection/create.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51457</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51458 | Stored XSS in `libs/cq/gui/components/projects/admin/translation/job/addcontent/clientlibs/js/addcontent.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51458</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51459 | AMS XSS -  /libs/dam/gui/coral/components/admin/folderschemaforms/formbuilder/formfields/v2/dropdownfield (encoded HTML attributes without quotes)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51459</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If a low-privileged attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51460 | Stored XSS in `libs/granite/ui/components/coral/foundation/clientlibs/foundation/js/granite/toggleable/control.js`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51460</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51461 | Admin Account Takeover using Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51461</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51462 | Cloud XSS - /libs/wcm/core/content/sites/createsitefromstarterkitwizard.html</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51462</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.18 and earlier are affected by a reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. If a low-privileged attacker is able to convince a victim to visit a URL referencing a vulnerable page, malicious JavaScript content may be executed within the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37871 | WordPress WooCommerce GoCardless Gateway Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37871</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WooCommerce GoCardless.This issue affects GoCardless: from n/a through 2.5.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6784 | Potential Use of the Sitefinity System for Distribution of Phishing Emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6784</link><description>A malicious user could potentially use the Sitefinity system for the distribution of phishing emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38513 | WordPress Photo Engine Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.5 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38513</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Jordy Meow Photo Engine (Media Organizer &amp; Lightroom).This issue affects Photo Engine (Media Organizer &amp; Lightroom): from n/a through 6.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50249 | Sentry&amp;#x27;s Astro SDK vulnerable to ReDoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50249</link><description>Sentry-Javascript is official Sentry SDKs for JavaScript. A ReDoS (Regular expression Denial of Service) vulnerability has been identified in Sentry's Astro SDK 7.78.0-7.86.0. Under certain conditions, this vulnerability allows an attacker to cause excessive computation times on the server, leading to denial of service (DoS). This vulnerability has been patched in sentry/astro version 7.87.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38519 | WordPress MainWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.3.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38519</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in MainWP MainWP Dashboard – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance.This issue affects MainWP Dashboard – WordPress Manager for Multiple Websites Maintenance: from n/a through 4.4.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40555 | WordPress Flatsome Theme &amp;lt;= 3.17.5 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40555</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in UX-themes Flatsome | Multi-Purpose Responsive WooCommerce Theme.This issue affects Flatsome | Multi-Purpose Responsive WooCommerce Theme: from n/a through 3.17.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41796 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart Plugin &amp;lt; 3.0.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41796</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Galleries for Photographers.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Galleries for Photographers: from n/a before 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46147 | WordPress Themify Ultra Theme &amp;lt;= 7.3.5 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46147</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Themify Themify Ultra.This issue affects Themify Ultra: from n/a through 7.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46311 | WordPress wpDiscuz Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.3 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46311</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in gVectors Team Comments – wpDiscuz.This issue affects Comments – wpDiscuz: from n/a through 7.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47236 | WordPress iPages Flipbook Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Avirtum iPages Flipbook For WordPress.This issue affects iPages Flipbook For WordPress: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47507 | WordPress Master Slider Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47507</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Master Slider Master Slider Pro.This issue affects Master Slider Pro: from n/a through 3.6.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6562 | JPX Fragment List (flst) box vulnerability in Kakadu 7.9 allows an attacker to exfiltrate local and remote files reachable by a server if th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6562</link><description>JPX Fragment List (flst) box vulnerability in Kakadu 7.9 allows an attacker to exfiltrate local and remote files reachable by a server if the server allows the attacker to upload a specially-crafted the image that is displayed back to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 13:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6768 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in Amazing Little Poll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6768</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in Amazing Little Poll affecting versions 1.3 and 1.4. This vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated user to access the admin panel without providing any credentials by simply accessing the "lp_admin.php?adminstep=" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 10:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6769 | Stored XSS vulnerability in Amazing Little Poll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6769</link><description>Stored XSS vulnerability in Amazing Little Poll, affecting versions 1.3 and 1.4. This vulnerability allows a remote attacker to store a malicious JavaScript payload in the "lp_admin.php" file in the "question" and "item" parameters. This vulnerability could lead to malicious JavaScript execution while the page is loading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 10:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6910 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6910</link><description>A vulnerable API method in M-Files Server before 23.12.13195.0 allows for uncontrolled resource consumption. Authenticated attacker can exhaust server storage space to a point where the server can no longer serve requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6912 | Brute force vulnerability in M-Files user authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6912</link><description>Lack of protection against brute force attacks in M-Files Server before 23.12.13205.0 allows an attacker unlimited authentication attempts, potentially compromising targeted M-Files user accounts by guessing passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 09:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50628 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libming version 0.4.8, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via pars...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50628</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libming version 0.4.8, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via parser.c component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 08:54:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50044 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Cesanta MJS version 2.22.0, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (Dos), an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50044</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Cesanta MJS version 2.22.0, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial of service (Dos), and obtain sensitive information via segmentation fault can occur in getprop_builtin_foreign when input string includes a name of Built-in APIs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 08:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37544 | Apache Pulsar WebSocket Proxy: Improper Authentication for WebSocket Proxy Endpoint Allows DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37544</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Apache Pulsar WebSocket Proxy allows an attacker to connect to the /pingpong endpoint without authentication.

This issue affects Apache Pulsar WebSocket Proxy: from 2.8.0 through 2.8.*, from 2.9.0 through 2.9.*, from 2.10.0 through 2.10.4, from 2.11.0 through 2.11.1, 3.0.0.

The known risks include a denial of service due to the WebSocket Proxy accepting any connections, and excessive data transfer due to misuse of the WebSocket ping/pong feature.

2.10 Pulsar WebSocket Proxy users should upgrade to at least 2.10.5.
2.11 Pulsar WebSocket Proxy users should upgrade to at least 2.11.2.
3.0 Pulsar WebSocket Proxy users should upgrade to at least 3.0.1.
3.1 Pulsar WebSocket Proxy users are unaffected.
Any users running the Pulsar WebSocket Proxy for 2.8, 2.9, and earlier should upgrade to one of the above patched versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 08:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0011 | Command Execution through Serial Interface of u-blox TOBY-L2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0011</link><description>A flaw in the input validation in TOBY-L2 allows a user to execute arbitrary operating system commands using specifically crafted AT commands. This vulnerability requires physical access to the serial interface of the module or the ability to modify the system or software which uses its serial interface to send malicious AT commands.




Exploitation of the vulnerability gives full administrative (root) privileges to the attacker to execute any operating system command on TOBY-L2 which can lead to modification of the behavior of the module itself as well as the components connected with it (depending on its rights on other connected systems). It can further provide the ability to read system level files and hamper the availability of the module as well..




This issue affects TOBY-L2 series: TOBY-L200, TOBY-L201, TOBY-L210, TOBY-L220, TOBY-L280.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 08:08:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6977 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6977</link><description>This vulnerability enables malicious users to read sensitive files on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 05:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6974 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6974</link><description>A malicious user could use this issue to access internal HTTP(s) servers and in the worst case (ie: aws instance) it could be abuse to get a remote code execution on the victim machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 05:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6975 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6975</link><description>A malicious user could use this issue to get command execution on the vulnerable machine and get access to data &amp; models information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 05:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6976 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6976</link><description>This vulnerability is capable of writing arbitrary files into arbitrary locations on the remote filesystem in the context of the server process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 05:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47703 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47703</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  271197.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47707 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47707</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  271522.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47702 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47702</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view modify files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  271196.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47705 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47705</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 could allow an authenticated user to manipulate username data due to improper input validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  271228.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47704 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47704</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 contains plain text hard-coded credentials or other secrets in source code repository.  IBM X-Force ID:  271220.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47706 | IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47706</link><description>IBM Security Guardium Key Lifecycle Manager 4.3 could allow an authenticated user to upload files of a dangerous file type.  IBM X-Force ID:  271341.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 01:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27172 | Xpand IT Write-back Manager v2.3.1 uses weak secret keys to sign JWT tokens. This allows attackers to easily obtain the secret key used to s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27172</link><description>Xpand IT Write-back Manager v2.3.1 uses weak secret keys to sign JWT tokens. This allows attackers to easily obtain the secret key used to sign JWT tokens via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42012 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42012</link><description>An IBM UrbanCode Deploy Agent 7.2 through 7.2.3.7, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.2 installed as a Windows service in a non-standard location could be subject to a denial of service attack by local accounts.  IBM X-Force ID:  265509.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47161 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47161</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.1 through 7.1.2.14, 7.2 through 7.2.3.7, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.2 may mishandle input validation of an uploaded archive file leading to a denial of service due to resource exhaustion.  IBM X-Force ID:  270799.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:24:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42013 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42013</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.1 through 7.1.2.14, 7.2 through 7.2.3.7, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.2 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  265510.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50704 | URL Redirection to Untrusted Site (&amp;#x27;Open Redirect&amp;#x27;) in EFACEC UC 500E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50704</link><description>An attacker could construct a URL within the application that causes a redirection to an arbitrary external domain and could be leveraged to facilitate phishing attacks against application users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50705 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in EFACEC UC 500E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50705</link><description>An attacker could create malicious requests to obtain sensitive information about the web server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:51:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50706 |   Improper Access Control in EFACEC UC 500E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50706</link><description>A user without administrator permissions with access to the UC500 windows system could perform a memory dump of the running processes and extract clear credentials or valid session tokens.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50703 |  Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information in EFACEC UC 500E</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50703</link><description>An attacker with network access could perform a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack and capture sensitive information to gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6689 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in EFACEC BCU 500</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6689</link><description>A successful CSRF attack could force the user to perform state changing requests on the application. If the victim is an administrative account, a CSRF attack could compromise the entire web application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45887 | DS Wireless Communication (DWC) with DWC_VERSION_3 and DWC_VERSION_11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on a game-playing cl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45887</link><description>DS Wireless Communication (DWC) with DWC_VERSION_3 and DWC_VERSION_11 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on a game-playing client's machine via a modified GPCM message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50707 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in EFACEC BCU 500</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50707</link><description>Through the exploitation of active user sessions, an attacker could send custom requests to cause a denial-of-service condition on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6928 | Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6928</link><description>EuroTel ETL3100 versions v01c01 and v01x37 does not limit the number of attempts to guess administrative credentials in remote password attacks to gain full control of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6929 | Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key in EuroTel ETL3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6929</link><description>EuroTel ETL3100 versions v01c01 and v01x37 are vulnerable to insecure direct object references that occur when the application provides direct access to objects based on user-supplied input. As a result of this vulnerability, attackers can bypass authorization, access the hidden resources on the system, and execute privileged functionalities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6930 | Improper Access Control in EuroTel ETL3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6930</link><description>EuroTel ETL3100 versions v01c01 and v01x37 suffer from an unauthenticated configuration and log download vulnerability. This enables the attacker to disclose sensitive information and assist in authentication bypass, privilege escalation, and full system access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49147 | An issue was discovered in PDF24 Creator 11.14.0. The configuration of the msi installer file was found to produce a visible cmd.exe window ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49147</link><description>An issue was discovered in PDF24 Creator 11.14.0. The configuration of the msi installer file was found to produce a visible cmd.exe window when using the repair function of msiexec.exe. This allows an unprivileged local attacker to use a chain of actions (e.g., an oplock on faxPrnInst.log) to open a SYSTEM cmd.exe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 22:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45172 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45172</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in AIX windows to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267970.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 22:23:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47146 | IBM QRadar SIEM information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47146</link><description>IBM Qradar SIEM 7.5 could allow a privileged user to obtain sensitive domain information due to data being misidentified.  IBM X-Force ID:  270372.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 22:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49004 | An issue in D-Link DIR-850L v.B1_FW223WWb01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the en parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49004</link><description>An issue in D-Link DIR-850L v.B1_FW223WWb01 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the en parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 22:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38126 | Softing edgeAggregator Restore Configuration Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38126</link><description>Softing edgeAggregator Restore Configuration Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Softing edgeAggregator. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of backup zip files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20543.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50835 | WordPress Advanced Category Template Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50835</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Praveen Goswami Advanced Category Template.This issue affects Advanced Category Template: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49164 | WordPress Ocean Extra Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49164</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OceanWP Ocean Extra.This issue affects Ocean Extra: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46624 | WordPress Parcel Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.11 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46624</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Parcel Pro.This issue affects Parcel Pro: from n/a through 1.6.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43450 | WordPress Stream Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43450</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in XWP Stream.This issue affects Stream: from n/a through 3.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47267 | An issue discovered in TheGreenBow Windows Enterprise Certified VPN Client 6.52, Windows Standard VPN Client 6.87, and Windows Enterprise VP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47267</link><description>An issue discovered in TheGreenBow Windows Enterprise Certified VPN Client 6.52, Windows Standard VPN Client 6.87, and Windows Enterprise VPN Client 6.87 allows attackers to gain escalated privileges via crafted changes to memory mapped file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42940 | A session rendering issue was addressed with improved session tracking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.2.1. A user who shares their ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42940</link><description>A session rendering issue was addressed with improved session tracking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.2.1. A user who shares their screen may unintentionally share the incorrect content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49812 | WordPress WP Photo Album Plus Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.02.005 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49812</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in J.N. Breetvelt a.K.A. OpaJaap WP Photo Album Plus.This issue affects WP Photo Album Plus: from n/a through 8.5.02.005.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48327 | WordPress WC Vendors Marketplace Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48327</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WC Vendors WC Vendors – WooCommerce Multi-Vendor, WooCommerce Marketplace, Product Vendors.This issue affects WC Vendors – WooCommerce Multi-Vendor, WooCommerce Marketplace, Product Vendors: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48738 | WordPress Porto Theme - Functionality Plugin &amp;lt; 2.12.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48738</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Porto Theme Porto Theme - Functionality.This issue affects Porto Theme - Functionality: from n/a before 2.12.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48741 | WordPress ChatBot Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48741</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in QuantumCloud AI ChatBot.This issue affects AI ChatBot: from n/a through 4.7.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48764 | WordPress WordPress Brute Force Protection – Stop Brute Force Attacks Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48764</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GuardGiant Brute Force Protection WordPress Brute Force Protection – Stop Brute Force Attacks.This issue affects WordPress Brute Force Protection – Stop Brute Force Attacks: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49750 | WordPress Couponis Demo Plugin &amp;lt; 2.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Spoonthemes Couponis - Affiliate &amp; Submitting Coupons WordPress Theme.This issue affects Couponis - Affiliate &amp; Submitting Coupons WordPress Theme: from n/a before 2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49764 | WordPress Advanced Database Cleaner Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49764</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Younes JFR. Advanced Database Cleaner.This issue affects Advanced Database Cleaner: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50466 | An authenticated command injection vulnerability in Weintek cMT2078X easyweb Web Version v2.1.3, OS v20220215 allows attackers to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50466</link><description>An authenticated command injection vulnerability in Weintek cMT2078X easyweb Web Version v2.1.3, OS v20220215 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code or access sensitive information via injecting a crafted payload into the HMI Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35883 | WordPress Core Web Vitals &amp;amp; PageSpeed Booster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35883</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Magazine3 Core Web Vitals &amp; PageSpeed Booster.This issue affects Core Web Vitals &amp; PageSpeed Booster: from n/a through 1.0.12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37982 | WordPress Integration for Contact Form 7 and Salesforce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37982</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks Integration for Salesforce and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Ninja Forms.This issue affects Integration for Salesforce and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Ninja Forms: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:17:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38478 | WordPress Integration for WooCommerce and QuickBooks Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38478</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks Integration for WooCommerce and QuickBooks.This issue affects Integration for WooCommerce and QuickBooks: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38481 | WordPress Integration for WooCommerce and Zoho CRM Plugin &amp;lt; 1.3.7 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38481</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in CRM Perks Integration for WooCommerce and Zoho CRM, Books, Invoice, Inventory, Bigin.This issue affects Integration for WooCommerce and Zoho CRM, Books, Invoice, Inventory, Bigin: from n/a before 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40602 | WordPress Doofinder for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.49 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40602</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Doofinder Doofinder WP &amp; WooCommerce Search.This issue affects Doofinder WP &amp; WooCommerce Search: from n/a through 1.5.49.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41648 | WordPress Login and Logout Redirect Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41648</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Swapnil V. Patil Login and Logout Redirect.This issue affects Login and Logout Redirect: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43826 | Apache Guacamole: Integer overflow in handling of VNC image buffers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43826</link><description>Apache Guacamole 1.5.3 and older do not consistently ensure that values received from a VNC server will not result in integer overflow. If a user connects to a malicious or compromised VNC server, specially-crafted data could result in memory corruption, possibly allowing arbitrary code to be executed with the privileges of the running guacd process.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.5.4, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34027 | WordPress Recently Viewed Products Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34027</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Rajnish Arora Recently Viewed Products.This issue affects Recently Viewed Products: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45105 | WordPress affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.9 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45105</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in SERVIT Software Solutions affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin.This issue affects affiliate-toolkit – WordPress Affiliate Plugin: from n/a through 3.3.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34382 | WordPress Dokan Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.19 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34382</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in weDevs Dokan – Best WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution – Build Your Own Amazon, eBay, Etsy.This issue affects Dokan – Best WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution – Build Your Own Amazon, eBay, Etsy: from n/a through 3.7.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49706 | Defective request context handling in Self Service in LinOTP 3.x before 3.2.5 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49706</link><description>Defective request context handling in Self Service in LinOTP 3.x before 3.2.5 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to escalate privileges, thereby allowing them to act as and with the permissions of another user. Attackers must generate repeated API requests to trigger a race condition with concurrent user activity in the self-service portal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 18:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22962 | An attacker can send a specially crafted request which could lead to leakage of sensitive data or potentially a resource-based DoS attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22962</link><description>An attacker can send a specially crafted request which could lead to leakage of sensitive data or potentially a resource-based DoS attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37390 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37390</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor.This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41727 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41727</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46216 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46216</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46217 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46217</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46220 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46220</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46221 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46221</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46222 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46222</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46223 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46223</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46224 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46224</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46225 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46225</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46257 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46257</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46258 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46258</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46259 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46259</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46260 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46260</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46261 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46261</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS) or code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46262 | An unauthenticated attacked could send a specifically crafted web request causing a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Ivanti Avalanche R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46262</link><description>An unauthenticated attacked could send a specifically crafted web request causing a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Ivanti Avalanche Remote Control server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46263 | An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in Avalanche versions 6.4.1 and below that could allow an attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46263</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in Avalanche versions 6.4.1 and below that could allow an attacker to achieve a remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46264 | An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in Avalanche versions 6.4.1 and below that could allow an attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46264</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability exists in Avalanche versions 6.4.1 and below that could allow an attacker to achieve a remove code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46265 | An unauthenticated could abuse a XXE vulnerability in the Smart Device Server to leak data or perform a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46265</link><description>An unauthenticated could abuse a XXE vulnerability in the Smart Device Server to leak data or perform a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46266 | An attacker can send a specially crafted request which could lead to leakage of sensitive data or potentially a resource-based DoS attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46266</link><description>An attacker can send a specially crafted request which could lead to leakage of sensitive data or potentially a resource-based DoS attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46803 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46803</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46804 | An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46804</link><description>An attacker sending specially crafted data packets to the Mobile Device Server can cause memory corruption which could result to a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25715 | WordPress GamiPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25715</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GamiPress GamiPress – The #1 gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress.This issue affects GamiPress – The #1 gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress: from n/a through 2.5.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50272 | A potential security vulnerability has been identified in HPE Integrated Lights-Out 5 (iLO 5) and Integrated Lights-Out 6 (iLO 6). The vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50272</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in HPE Integrated Lights-Out 5 (iLO 5) and Integrated Lights-Out 6 (iLO 6). The vulnerability could be remotely exploited to allow authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44991 | WordPress Media File Renamer Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.9 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44991</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Jordy Meow Media File Renamer: Rename Files (Manual, Auto &amp; AI).This issue affects Media File Renamer: Rename Files (Manual, Auto &amp; AI): from n/a through 5.6.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44983 | WordPress Aruba HiSpeed Cache Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44983</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Aruba.It Aruba HiSpeed Cache.This issue affects Aruba HiSpeed Cache: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43870 | When installing the Net2 software a root certificate is installed into the trusted store. A potential hacker could access the installer batc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43870</link><description>When installing the Net2 software a root certificate is installed into the trusted store. A potential hacker could access the installer batch file or reverse engineer the source code to gain access to the root certificate password. Using the root certificate and password they could then create their own certificates to emulate another site. Then by establishing a proxy service to emulate the site they could monitor traffic passed between the end user and the site allowing access to the data content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6280 | XML External Entity Reference on 52North WPS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6280</link><description>An XXE (XML External Entity) vulnerability has been detected in 52North WPS affecting versions prior to 4.0.0-beta.11. This vulnerability allows the use of external entities in its WebProcessingService servlet for an attacker to retrieve files by making HTTP requests to the internal network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6711 | Vulnerability exists in SCI IEC 60870-5-104 and HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. Specially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6711</link><description>Vulnerability exists in SCI IEC 60870-5-104 and HCI IEC 60870-5-104 that affects the RTU500 series product versions listed below. Specially crafted messages sent to the mentioned components are not validated properly and can result in buffer overflow and as final consequence to a reboot of an RTU500 CMU.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 15:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6913 | Session Hijacking on Imou Life app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6913</link><description>A session hijacking vulnerability has been detected in the Imou Life application affecting version 6.7.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to hijack user accounts due to the QR code functionality not properly filtering codes when scanning a new device and directly running WebView without prompting or displaying it to the user. This vulnerability could trigger phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1514 | A vulnerability exists in the component RTU500 Scripting interface. When a client connects to a server using TLS, the server presents a cert...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1514</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the component RTU500 Scripting interface. When a client connects to a server using TLS, the server presents a certificate. This certificate links a public key to the identity of the service and is signed by a Certification Authority (CA), allowing the client to validate that the remote service can be trusted and is not malicious. If the client does not validate the parameters of the certificate, then attackers could be able to spoof the identity of the service. An attacker could exploit the vulnerability by using faking the identity of a RTU500 device and intercepting the messages initiated via the RTU500 Scripting interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6931 | Out-of-bounds write in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s Performance Events system component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6931</link><description>A heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability in the Linux kernel's Performance Events system component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

A perf_event's read_size can overflow, leading to an heap out-of-bounds increment or write in perf_read_group().

We recommend upgrading past commit 382c27f4ed28f803b1f1473ac2d8db0afc795a1b.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6932 | Use-after-free in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s ipv4: igmp component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6932</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in the Linux kernel's ipv4: igmp component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

A race condition can be exploited to cause a timer be mistakenly registered on a RCU read locked object which is freed by another thread.

We recommend upgrading past commit e2b706c691905fe78468c361aaabc719d0a496f1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50761 | The signature of a digitally signed S/MIME email message may optionally specify the signature creation date and time. If present, Thunderbir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50761</link><description>The signature of a digitally signed S/MIME email message may optionally specify the signature creation date and time. If present, Thunderbird did not compare the signature creation date with the message date and time, and displayed a valid signature despite a date or time mismatch. This could be used to give recipients the impression that a message was sent at a different date or time. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50762 | When processing a PGP/MIME payload that contains digitally signed text, the first paragraph of the text was never shown to the user. This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50762</link><description>When processing a PGP/MIME payload that contains digitally signed text, the first paragraph of the text was never shown to the user. This is because the text was interpreted as a MIME message and the first paragraph was always treated as an email header section. A digitally signed text from a different context, such as a signed GIT commit, could be used to spoof an email message. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 115.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6135 | Multiple NSS NIST curves were susceptible to a side-channel attack known as "Minerva". This attack could potentially allow an attacker to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6135</link><description>Multiple NSS NIST curves were susceptible to a side-channel attack known as "Minerva". This attack could potentially allow an attacker to recover the private key. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6856 | The WebGL `DrawElementsInstanced` method was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow when used on systems with the Mesa VM driver.  This issue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6856</link><description>The WebGL `DrawElementsInstanced` method was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow when used on systems with the Mesa VM driver.  This issue could allow an attacker to perform remote code execution and sandbox escape. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6857 | When resolving a symlink, a race may occur where the buffer passed to `readlink` may actually be smaller than necessary. 
*This bug only aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6857</link><description>When resolving a symlink, a race may occur where the buffer passed to `readlink` may actually be smaller than necessary. 
*This bug only affects Firefox on Unix-based operating systems (Android, Linux, MacOS). Windows is unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6858 | Firefox was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow in `nsTextFragment` due to insufficient OOM handling. This vulnerability affects Firefox E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6858</link><description>Firefox was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow in `nsTextFragment` due to insufficient OOM handling. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6859 | A use-after-free condition affected TLS socket creation when under memory pressure. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6859</link><description>A use-after-free condition affected TLS socket creation when under memory pressure. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6860 | The `VideoBridge` allowed any content process to use textures produced by remote decoders.  This could be abused to escape the sandbox. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6860</link><description>The `VideoBridge` allowed any content process to use textures produced by remote decoders.  This could be abused to escape the sandbox. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6861 | The `nsWindow::PickerOpen(void)` method was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow when running in headless mode. This vulnerability affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6861</link><description>The `nsWindow::PickerOpen(void)` method was susceptible to a heap buffer overflow when running in headless mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6862 | A use-after-free was identified in the `nsDNSService::Init`.  This issue appears to manifest rarely during start-up. This vulnerability affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6862</link><description>A use-after-free was identified in the `nsDNSService::Init`.  This issue appears to manifest rarely during start-up. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6 and Thunderbird &lt; 115.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6863 | The `ShutdownObserver()` was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior due to its reliance on a dynamic type that lacked a virtual destr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6863</link><description>The `ShutdownObserver()` was susceptible to potentially undefined behavior due to its reliance on a dynamic type that lacked a virtual destructor. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6864 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 120, Firefox ESR 115.5, and Thunderbird 115.5. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6864</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 120, Firefox ESR 115.5, and Thunderbird 115.5. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6, Thunderbird &lt; 115.6, and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6865 | `EncryptingOutputStream` was susceptible to exposing uninitialized data.  This issue could only be abused in order to write data to a local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6865</link><description>`EncryptingOutputStream` was susceptible to exposing uninitialized data.  This issue could only be abused in order to write data to a local disk which may have implications for private browsing mode. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6 and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6866 | TypedArrays can be fallible and lacked proper exception handling. This could lead to abuse in other APIs which expect TypedArrays to always ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6866</link><description>TypedArrays can be fallible and lacked proper exception handling. This could lead to abuse in other APIs which expect TypedArrays to always succeed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6867 | The timing of a button click causing a popup to disappear was approximately the same length as the anti-clickjacking delay on permission pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6867</link><description>The timing of a button click causing a popup to disappear was approximately the same length as the anti-clickjacking delay on permission prompts. It was possible to use this fact to surprise users by luring them to click where the permission grant button would be about to appear. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.6 and Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6868 | In some instances, the user-agent would allow push requests which lacked a valid VAPID even though the push manager subscription defined one...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6868</link><description>In some instances, the user-agent would allow push requests which lacked a valid VAPID even though the push manager subscription defined one. This could allow empty messages to be sent from unauthorized parties.
*This bug only affects Firefox on Android.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6869 | A `&amp;lt;dialog&gt;` element could have been manipulated to paint content outside of a sandboxed iframe. This could allow untrusted content to di...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6869</link><description>A `&amp;lt;dialog&gt;` element could have been manipulated to paint content outside of a sandboxed iframe. This could allow untrusted content to display under the guise of trusted content. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6870 | Applications which spawn a Toast notification in a background thread may have obscured fullscreen notifications displayed by Firefox. 
*This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6870</link><description>Applications which spawn a Toast notification in a background thread may have obscured fullscreen notifications displayed by Firefox. 
*This issue only affects Android versions of Firefox and Firefox Focus.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6871 | Under certain conditions, Firefox did not display a warning when a user attempted to navigate to a new protocol handler. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6871</link><description>Under certain conditions, Firefox did not display a warning when a user attempted to navigate to a new protocol handler. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6872 | Browser tab titles were being leaked by GNOME to system logs. This could potentially expose the browsing habits of users running in a privat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6872</link><description>Browser tab titles were being leaked by GNOME to system logs. This could potentially expose the browsing habits of users running in a private tab. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6873 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 120. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6873</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 120. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 121.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25158 | pedroetb tts-api app.js onSpeechDone os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25158</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in pedroetb tts-api up to 2.1.4 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function onSpeechDone of the file app.js. The manipulation leads to os command injection. Upgrading to version 2.2.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 29d9c25415911ea2f8b6de247cb5c4607d13d434. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248278 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 13:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6730 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in huggingface/transformers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6730</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data in GitHub repository huggingface/transformers prior to 4.36.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 12:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6945 | SourceCodester Online Student Management System edit-student-detail.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6945</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Student Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file edit-student-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument notmsg leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-248377 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 11:07:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49734 | Apache Superset: Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49734</link><description>An authenticated Gamma user has the ability to create a dashboard and add charts to it, this user would automatically become one of the owners of the charts allowing him to incorrectly have write permissions to these charts.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 2.1.2, from 3.0.0 before 3.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.2 or 2.1.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49736 | Apache Superset: SQL Injection on where_in JINJA macro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49736</link><description>A where_in JINJA macro allows users to specify a quote, which combined with a carefully crafted statement would allow for SQL injection in Apache Superset.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 2.1.2, from 3.0.0 before 3.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46104 | Apache Superset: Allows for uncontrolled resource consumption via a ZIP bomb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46104</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption can be triggered by authenticated attacker that uploads a malicious ZIP to import database, dashboards or datasets.  
This vulnerability exists in Apache Superset versions up to and including 2.1.2 and versions 3.0.0, 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49006 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Phpsysinfo version 3.4.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49006</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Phpsysinfo version 3.4.3 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted page in the XML.php file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49489 | Reflective Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in KodeExplorer version 4.51, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49489</link><description>Reflective Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in KodeExplorer version 4.51, allows attackers to obtain sensitive information and escalate privileges via the APP_HOST parameter at config/i18n/en/main.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50376 | WordPress Simple Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.8 is vulnerable to Unauth. Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50376</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in smp7, wp.Insider Simple Membership allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Membership: from n/a through 4.3.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 08:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5432 | The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'jquery-news-ticker' shortcode in versions up t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5432</link><description>The Jquery news ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'jquery-news-ticker' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5413 | The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'ihrss-gallery' shortcode i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5413</link><description>The Image horizontal reel scroll slideshow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'ihrss-gallery' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 13.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125107 | Corveda PHPSandbox String protection mechanism</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Corveda PHPSandbox 1.3.4 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component String Handler. The manipulation leads to protection mechanism failure. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.3.5 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 48fde5ffa4d76014bad260a3cbab7ada3744a4cc. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-248270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25157 | Ethex Contracts Monthly Jackpot EthexJackpot.sol access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25157</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ethex Contracts. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file EthexJackpot.sol of the component Monthly Jackpot Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 6b8664b698d3d953e16c284fadc6caeb9e58e3db. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-248271.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42015 | IBM UrbanCode Deploy HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42015</link><description>IBM UrbanCode Deploy (UCD) 7.1 through 7.1.2.14, 7.2 through 7.2.3.7, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.2 is vulnerable to HTML injection. This vulnerability may allow a user to embed arbitrary HTML tags in the Web UI potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure.  IBM X-Force ID:  265512.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6488 | The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'su_button...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6488</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'su_button', 'su_members', and 'su_tabs' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6940 | Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6940</link><description>with only one user interaction(download a malicious config), attackers can gain full command execution on the victim system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 02:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6315 | Out-of-bouds read vulnerability in FPWin Pro version 7.7.0.0 and all previous versions may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6315</link><description>Out-of-bouds read vulnerability in FPWin Pro version 7.7.0.0 and all previous versions may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted project file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44982 | WordPress WP Retina 2x Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.5 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44982</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Jordy Meow Perfect Images (Manage Image Sizes, Thumbnails, Replace, Retina).This issue affects Perfect Images (Manage Image Sizes, Thumbnails, Replace, Retina): from n/a through 6.4.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6314 | Stack-based buffer overflow in FPWin Pro version 7.7.0.0 and all previous versions may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6314</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow in FPWin Pro version 7.7.0.0 and all previous versions may allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a specially crafted project file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>