<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 21:26:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-0514 | Executable hyperlink Windows path targets executed unconditionally on activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0514</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows Windows Executable hyperlink  targets to be executed unconditionally on activation.This issue affects LibreOffice: from 24.8 before &lt; 24.8.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 21:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53878 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause a crash by passing a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53878</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause a crash by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53879 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause a crash by passing a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53879</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause a crash by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27239 | Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs - Divide By Zero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27239</link><description>Use after free in some Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27245 | Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27245</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27246 | Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs - Use After Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27246</link><description>Use after free in some Zoom Workplace Apps and SDKs may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53874 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53874</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53875 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53875</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53876 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53876</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53877 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause a NULL pointer exception by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53877</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause a NULL pointer exception by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53870 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53870</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53871 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53871</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the nvdisasm binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to nvdisasm. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53872 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53872</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for all platforms contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53873 | NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53873</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA toolkit for Windows contains a vulnerability in the cuobjdump binary, where a user could cause an out-of-bounds read by passing a malformed ELF file to cuobjdump. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to a partial denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0148 | NVIDIA Jetson Linux and IGX OS image contains a vulnerability in the UEFI firmware RCM boot mode, where an unprivileged attacker with physic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0148</link><description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux and IGX OS image contains a vulnerability in the UEFI firmware RCM boot mode, where an unprivileged attacker with physical access to the device could load untrusted code. A successful exploit might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, and information disclosure. The scope of the impacts can extend to other components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27148 | Gradle vulnerable to local privilege escalation through system temporary directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27148</link><description>Gradle is a build automation tool, and its native-platform tool provides Java bindings for native APIs. On Unix-like systems, the system temporary directory can be created with open permissions that allow multiple users to create and delete files within it. This library initialization could be vulnerable to a local privilege escalation from an attacker quickly deleting and recreating files in the system temporary directory. Gradle builds that rely on versions of net.rubygrapefruit:native-platform prior to 0.22-milestone-28 could be vulnerable to a local privilege escalation from an attacker quickly deleting and recreating files in the system temporary directory.

In net.rubygrapefruit:native-platform prior to version 0.22-milestone-28, if the `Native.get(Class)` method was called, without calling `Native.init(File)` first, with a non-`null` argument used as working file path, then the library would initialize itself using the system temporary directory and NativeLibraryLocator.java lines 68 through 78. Version 0.22-milestone-28 has been released with changes that fix the problem. Initialization is now mandatory and no longer uses the system temporary directory, unless such a path is passed for initialization. The only workaround for affected versions is to make sure to do a proper initialization, using a location that is safe.

Gradle 8.12, only that exact version, had codepaths where the initialization of the underlying native integration library took a default path, relying on copying the binaries to the system temporary directory. Any execution of Gradle exposed this exploit. Users of Windows or modern versions of macOS are not vulnerable, nor are users of a Unix-like operating system with the "sticky" bit set or `noexec` on their system temporary directory vulnerable. This problem was fixed in Gradle 8.12.1. Gradle 8.13 release also upgrades to a version of the native library that no longer has that bug. Some workarounds are available. On Unix-like operating systems, ensure that the "sticky" bit is set. This only allows the original user (or root) to delete a file. Mounting `/tmp` as `noexec` will prevent Gradle 8.12 from starting. Those who are are unable to change the permissions of the system temporary directory can move the Java temporary directory by setting the System Property java.io.tmpdir. The new path needs to limit permissions to the build user only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27110 | Libmodsecurity3 has possible bypass of encoded HTML entities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27110</link><description>Libmodsecurity is one component of the ModSecurity v3 project. The library codebase serves as an interface to ModSecurity Connectors taking in web traffic and applying traditional ModSecurity processing. A bug that exists only in Libmodsecurity3 version 3.0.13 means that, in 3.0.13, Libmodsecurity3 can't decode encoded HTML entities if they contains leading zeroes. Version 3.0.14 contains a fix. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27142 | LocalSend path traversal vulnerability in the file upload endpoint allows nearby devices to execute arbitrary commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27142</link><description>LocalSend is a free, open-source app that allows users to securely share files and messages with nearby devices over their local network without needing an internet connection. Prior to version 1.17.0, due to the missing sanitization of the path in the `POST /api/localsend/v2/prepare-upload` and the `POST /api/localsend/v2/upload` endpoint, a malicious file transfer request can write files to the arbitrary location on the system, resulting in the remote command execution. A malicious file transfer request sent by nearby devices can write files into an arbitrary directory. This usually allows command execution via the startup folder on Windows or Bash-related files on Linux. If the user enables the `Quick Save` feature, it will silently write files without explicit user interaction. Version 1.17.0 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27146 | Matrix IRC Bridge allows IRC command injection to own puppeted user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27146</link><description>matrix-appservice-irc is a Node.js IRC bridge for Matrix. The matrix-appservice-irc bridge up to version 3.0.3 contains a vulnerability which can lead to arbitrary IRC command execution as the puppeted user. The attacker can only inject commands executed as their own IRC user. The vulnerability has been patched in matrix-appservice-irc version 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45421 | Zoom Apps - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45421</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45417 | Zoom Apps for macOS - Uncontrolled Resource Consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45417</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in the installer for some Zoom apps for macOS before version 6.1.5 may allow a privileged user to conduct a disclosure of information via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45418 | Zoom Apps for macOS - Symbolic Link Following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45418</link><description>Symlink following in the installer for some Zoom apps for macOS before version 6.1.5 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27139 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to stored self Cross-site Scripting in preferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27139</link><description>Combodo iTop is a web based IT service management tool. Versions prior to 2.7.12, 3.1.2, and 3.2.0 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when the preferences page is opened. Versions 2.7.12, 3.1.2, and 3.2.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45425 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Incorrect User Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45425</link><description>Incorrect user management in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45426 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Incorrect Ownership Assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45426</link><description>Incorrect ownership assignment in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45424 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Business Logic Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45424</link><description>Business logic error in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36259 | Improper access control in mail module of Odoo Community 17.0 and Odoo Enterprise 17.0 allows remote authenticated attackers to extract sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36259</link><description>Improper access control in mail module of Odoo Community 17.0 and Odoo Enterprise 17.0 allows remote authenticated attackers to extract sensitive information via an oracle-based (yes/no response) crafted attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27135 | RAGFlow SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27135</link><description>RAGFlow is an open-source RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) engine. Versions 0.15.1 and prior are vulnerable to SQL injection. The ExeSQL component extracts the SQL statement from the input and sends it directly to the database query. As of time of publication, no patched version is available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 18:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12368 | Improper access control in the auth_oauth module of Odoo Community 15.0 and Odoo Enterprise 15.0 allows an internal user to export the OAuth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12368</link><description>Improper access control in the auth_oauth module of Odoo Community 15.0 and Odoo Enterprise 15.0 allows an internal user to export the OAuth tokens of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 18:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25192 | GLPI allows unauthorized access to debug mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25192</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Prior to version 10.0.18, a low privileged user can enable debug mode and access sensitive information. Version 10.0.18 contains a patch. As a workaround, one may delete the `install/update.php` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 18:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23046 | GLPI vulnerable to unauthorized authentication by email using the OAuthIMAP plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23046</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 9.5.0 and prior to version 10.0.18, if a "Mail servers" authentication provider is configured to use an Oauth connection provided by the OauthIMAP plugin, anyone can connect to GLPI using a user name on which an Oauth authorization has already been established. Version 10.0.18 contains a patch. As a workaround, one may disable any "Mail servers" authentication provider configured to use an Oauth connection provided by the OauthIMAP plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 17:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1204 | The "update" binary in the firmware of the affected product sends attempts to mount to a hard-coded, routable IP address, bypassing existing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1204</link><description>The "update" binary in the firmware of the affected product sends attempts to mount to a hard-coded, routable IP address, bypassing existing device network settings to do so. The function triggers if the 'C' button is pressed at a specific time during the boot process. If an attacker is able to control or impersonate this IP address, they could upload and overwrite files on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 17:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1067 | There is a code injection vulnerability in ArcGIS Pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1067</link><description>There is an untrusted search path vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS Pro 3.3 and 3.4 that may allow a low privileged attacker with write privileges to the local file system to introduce a malicious executable to the filesystem. When the victim performs a specific action using ArcGIS 

ArcGIS Pro 

, the file could execute and run malicious commands under the context of the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 16:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1068 | There is a code injection vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS AllSource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1068</link><description>There is an untrusted search path vulnerability in Esri ArcGIS AllSource 1.2 and 1.3 that may allow a low privileged attacker with write privileges to the local file system to introduce a malicious executable to the filesystem. When the victim performs a specific action using ArcGIS AllSource, the file could execute and run malicious commands under the context of the victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 16:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26601 | Xorg: xwayland: use-after-free in syncinittrigger()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26601</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. When changing an alarm, the values of the change mask are evaluated one after the other, changing the trigger values as requested, and eventually, SyncInitTrigger() is called. If one of the changes triggers an error, the function will return early, not adding the new sync object, possibly causing a use-after-free when the alarm eventually triggers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 16:19:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26594 | X.org: xwayland: use-after-free of the root cursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26594</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. The root cursor is referenced in the X server as a global variable. If a client frees the root cursor, the internal reference points to freed memory and causes a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26595 | Xorg: xwayland: buffer overflow in xkbvmodmasktext()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26595</link><description>A buffer overflow flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. The code in XkbVModMaskText() allocates a fixed-sized buffer on the stack and copies the names of the virtual modifiers to that buffer. The code fails to check the bounds of the buffer and would copy the data regardless of the size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26596 | Xorg: xwayland: heap overflow in xkbwritekeysyms()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26596</link><description>A heap overflow flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. The computation of the length in XkbSizeKeySyms() differs from what is written in XkbWriteKeySyms(), which may lead to a heap-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26597 | Xorg: xwayland: buffer overflow in xkbchangetypesofkey()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26597</link><description>A buffer overflow flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. If XkbChangeTypesOfKey() is called with a 0 group, it will resize the key symbols table to 0 but leave the key actions unchanged. If the same function is later called with a non-zero value of groups, this will cause a buffer overflow because the key actions are of the wrong size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26598 | Xorg: xwayland: out-of-bounds write in createpointerbarrierclient()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26598</link><description>An out-of-bounds write flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. The function GetBarrierDevice() searches for the pointer device based on its device ID and returns the matching value, or supposedly NULL, if no match was found. However, the code will return the last element of the list if no matching device ID is found, which can lead to out-of-bounds memory access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26599 | Xorg: xwayland: use of uninitialized pointer in compredirectwindow()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26599</link><description>An access to an uninitialized pointer flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. The function compCheckRedirect() may fail if it cannot allocate the backing pixmap. In that case, compRedirectWindow() will return a BadAlloc error without validating the window tree marked just before, which leaves the validated data partly initialized and the use of an uninitialized pointer later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26600 | Xorg: xwayland: use-after-free in playreleasedevents()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26600</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in X.Org and Xwayland. When a device is removed while still frozen, the events queued for that device remain while the device is freed. Replaying the events will cause a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21627 | GLPI Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21627</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. In versions prior to 10.0.18, a malicious link can be crafted to perform a reflected XSS attack on the search page. If the anonymous ticket creation is enabled, this attack can be performed by an unauthenticated user. Version 10.0.18 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23024 | GLPI: Plugins are disabled accessing one page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23024</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 0.72 and prior to version 10.0.18, an anonymous user can disable all the active plugins. Version 10.0.18 contains a patch. As a workaround, one may delete the `install/update.php` file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21626 | GLPI vulnerable to exposure of sensitive information in the `status.php` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21626</link><description>GLPI is a free asset and IT management software package. Starting in version 0.71 and prior to version 10.0.18, an anonymous user can fetch sensitive information from the `status.php` endpoint. Version 10.0.18 contains a fix for the issue. Some workarounds are available. One may delete the `status.php` file, restrict its access, or remove any sensitive values from the `name` field of the active LDAP directories, mail servers authentication providers and mail receivers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11955 | GLPI index.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11955</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GLPI up to 10.0.17. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument redirect leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 10.0.18 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34036 | An issue was discovered in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC I-Release. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker can disrupt the initial connection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34036</link><description>An issue was discovered in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC I-Release. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker can disrupt the initial connection between a gNB and the Near RT-RIC by inundating the system with a high volume of subscription requests via an xApp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25574 | JupyterHub&amp;#x27;s LTI13Authenticator: JWT signature not validated</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25574</link><description>`jupyterhub-ltiauthenticator` is a JupyterHub authenticator for learning tools interoperability (LTI). LTI13Authenticator that was introduced in `jupyterhub-ltiauthenticator` 1.3.0 wasn't validating JWT signatures. This is believed to allow the LTI13Authenticator to authorize a forged request. Only users that has configured a JupyterHub installation to use the authenticator class `LTI13Authenticator` are affected. `jupyterhub-ltiauthenticator` version 1.4.0 removes LTI13Authenticator to address the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34034 | An issue was discovered in FlexRIC 2.0.0. It crashes during a Subscription Request denial-of-service (DoS) attack, triggered by an assertion...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34034</link><description>An issue was discovered in FlexRIC 2.0.0. It crashes during a Subscription Request denial-of-service (DoS) attack, triggered by an assertion error. An attacker must send a high number of E42 Subscription Requests to the Near-RT RIC component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34035 | An issue was discovered in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC H-Release. To trigger the crashing of the e2mgr, an adversary must flood the system with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34035</link><description>An issue was discovered in O-RAN Near Realtime RIC H-Release. To trigger the crashing of the e2mgr, an adversary must flood the system with a significant quantity of E2 Subscription Requests originating from an xApp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54444 | WordPress Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54444</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elementor Elementor Website Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Elementor Website Builder: from n/a through 3.25.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26751 | WordPress Alphabetic Pagination Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26751</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Alphabetic Pagination allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Alphabetic Pagination: from n/a through 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26752 | WordPress VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26752</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in videowhisper VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration allows Path Traversal. This issue affects VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26753 | WordPress VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26753</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in videowhisper VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration allows Path Traversal. This issue affects VideoWhisper Live Streaming Integration: from n/a through 6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26868 | WordPress Fast Flow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26868</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fastflow Fast Flow allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Fast Flow: from n/a through 1.2.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26871 | WordPress Essential Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26871</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Blocks for Gutenberg allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Essential Blocks for Gutenberg: from n/a through 4.8.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26876 | WordPress Search with Typesense Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26876</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in CodeManas Search with Typesense allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Search with Typesense: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26877 | WordPress Front End Users Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.30 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26877</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rustaurius Front End Users allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Front End Users: from n/a through 3.2.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26878 | WordPress Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in patternsinthecloud Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Autoship Cloud for WooCommerce Subscription Products: from n/a through 2.8.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26881 | WordPress Sticky Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26881</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Sticky Content allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sticky Content: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26882 | WordPress Popup Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.33 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26882</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Popup Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Popup Builder: from n/a through 1.1.33.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26884 | WordPress Greenshift plugin &amp;lt;= 10.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26884</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpsoul Greenshift allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Greenshift: from n/a through 10.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26887 | WordPress EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup plugin &amp;lt;= 5.21.35 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26887</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Eli EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects EZ SQL Reports Shortcode Widget and DB Backup: from n/a through 5.21.35.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26891 | WordPress Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4.9 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26891</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VW THEMES Ibtana allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ibtana: from n/a through 1.2.4.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26893 | WordPress Easy Charts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26893</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiran Potphode Easy Charts allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Easy Charts: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26896 | WordPress PiwigoPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26896</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vpiwigo PiwigoPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PiwigoPress: from n/a through 2.33.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26897 | WordPress List Related Attachments plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26897</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Baden List Related Attachments allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects List Related Attachments: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26900 | WordPress Flexmls® IDX Plugin Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.27 -  PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26900</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in flexmls Flexmls® IDX allows Object Injection. This issue affects Flexmls® IDX: from n/a through 3.14.27.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26904 | WordPress WP Responsive Auto Fit Text plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26904</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gal_op WP Responsive Auto Fit Text allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP Responsive Auto Fit Text: from n/a through 0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26905 | WordPress Estatik plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26905</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Estatik Estatik allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Estatik: from n/a through 4.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26907 | WordPress Estatik Mortgage Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26907</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Estatik Mortgage Calculator Estatik allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mortgage Calculator Estatik: from n/a through 2.0.12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26911 | WordPress System Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.18 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26911</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Bowo System Dashboard allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects System Dashboard: from n/a through 2.8.18.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26912 | WordPress Easy Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26912</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HashThemes Easy Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Elementor Addons: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26913 | WordPress AR for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26913</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webandprint AR For WordPress allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects AR For WordPress: from n/a through 7.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26915 | WordPress Wishlist Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.41 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26915</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in PickPlugins Wishlist allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 1.0.41.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26926 | WordPress Booknetic plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26926</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NotFound Booknetic. This issue affects Booknetic: from n/a through 4.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26928 | WordPress Order Limit for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26928</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in xfinitysoft Order Limit for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Order Limit for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26931 | WordPress Tribulant Gallery Voting plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26931</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tribulant Software Tribulant Gallery Voting allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tribulant Gallery Voting: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26932 | WordPress WPBot plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26932</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in QuantumCloud ChatBot allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects ChatBot: from n/a through 6.3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26935 | WordPress WP Job Portal plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26935</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in wpjobportal WP Job Portal allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WP Job Portal: from n/a through 2.2.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26937 | WordPress Icon List Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Icon List Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Icon List Block: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26938 | WordPress Countdown Timer block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26938</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Countdown Timer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Countdown Timer: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26939 | WordPress Counters Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26939</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Counters Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Counters Block: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26943 | WordPress Easy Quotes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26943</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jürgen Müller Easy Quotes allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Easy Quotes: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26945 | WordPress Info Cards plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26945</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Info Cards – Gutenberg block for creating Beautiful Cards allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Info Cards – Gutenberg block for creating Beautiful Cards: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26946 | WordPress WP Yelp Review Slider Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26946</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in jgwhite33 WP Yelp Review Slider allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Yelp Review Slider: from n/a through 8.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26947 | WordPress Services Section block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26947</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Services Section block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Services Section block: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26948 | WordPress Pie Register Premium plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26948</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Pie Register Premium. This issue affects Pie Register Premium: from n/a through 3.8.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26949 | WordPress Team Section Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26949</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Team Section Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Team Section Block: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26952 | WordPress Business Card Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Business Card Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Business Card Block: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26957 | WordPress Affiliate Coupons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26957</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Deetronix Affiliate Coupons allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Affiliate Coupons: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26960 | WordPress Small Package Quotes – Unishippers Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26960</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Small Package Quotes – Unishippers Edition allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Small Package Quotes – Unishippers Edition: from n/a through 2.4.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26962 | WordPress Contact Form Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26962</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Easy Contact Form Lite  allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Contact Form Lite : from n/a through 1.1.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26963 | WordPress ClickWhale plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26963</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flowdee ClickWhale allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects ClickWhale: from n/a through 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26964 | WordPress Eventin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.20 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26964</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.20.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26965 | WordPress Amelia plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.16 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26965</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in ameliabooking Amelia allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Amelia: from n/a through 1.2.16.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26966 | WordPress PrivateContent plugin &amp;lt;= 8.11.5 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26966</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Aldo Latino PrivateContent. This issue affects PrivateContent: from n/a through 8.11.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26971 | WordPress Poll Maker &amp;lt;= 5.6.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26971</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ays-pro Poll Maker allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Poll Maker: from n/a through 5.6.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26974 | WordPress WP Multi Store Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26974</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPExperts.io WP Multi Store Locator allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Multi Store Locator: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26975 | WordPress Strong Testimonials plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26975</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Chill Strong Testimonials allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Strong Testimonials: from n/a through 3.2.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26977 | WordPress FileBird plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.2.1 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26977</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Ninja Team Filebird allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Filebird: from n/a through 6.4.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26979 | WordPress Funnel Builder by FunnelKit plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26979</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in FunnelKit Funnel Builder by FunnelKit allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Funnel Builder by FunnelKit: from n/a through 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26980 | WordPress Wired Impact Volunteer Management plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26980</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wired Impact Wired Impact Volunteer Management allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Wired Impact Volunteer Management: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26981 | WordPress Web Accessibility By accessiBe plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26981</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in accessiBe Web Accessibility By accessiBe allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Web Accessibility By accessiBe: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26983 | WordPress Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp;amp; Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26983</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPZOOM Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp; Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Recipe Card Blocks for Gutenberg &amp; Elementor: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26985 | WordPress Majestic Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26985</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Majestic Support Majestic Support allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Majestic Support: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26987 | WordPress Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin &amp;lt;= 3.25.17 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26987</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shabti Kaplan Frontend Admin by DynamiApps allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Frontend Admin by DynamiApps: from n/a through 3.25.17.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26991 | WordPress WPPizza plugin &amp;lt;= 3.19.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26991</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ollybach WPPizza allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WPPizza: from n/a through 3.19.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26993 | WordPress Visual Website Collaboration Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26993</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vito Peleg Atarim allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26995 | WordPress Market Exporter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Anton Vanyukov Market Exporter allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Market Exporter: from n/a through 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27000 | WordPress Simple Photo Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27000</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in George Pattichis Simple Photo Feed allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Simple Photo Feed: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51539 | The Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Application and Appliance, versions prior to 5.28, contains a SQL injection vulnerability due to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51539</link><description>The Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) Application and Appliance, versions prior to 5.28, contains a SQL injection vulnerability due to improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command. This vulnerability can only be exploited locally on the affected system. A high-privilege attacker with access to the system could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of non-sensitive information that does not include any customer data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1262 | Advanced Google reCaptcha &amp;lt;= 1.27 - Built-in Math CAPTCHA Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1262</link><description>The Advanced Google reCaptcha plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CAPTCHA Bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.27 . This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the Built-in Math Captcha Verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 12:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1676 | hzmanyun Education and Training System pdf2swf os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1676</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in hzmanyun Education and Training System 3.1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is the function pdf2swf of the file /pdf2swf. The manipulation of the argument file leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13693 | Enfold &amp;lt;= 6.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Disclosure in avia-export-class.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13693</link><description>The Enfold theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check in avia-export-class.php in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export all avia settings which may included sensitive information such as the Mailchimp API Key, reCAPTCHA Secret Key, or Envato private token if they are set.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 09:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13695 | Enfold &amp;lt;= 6.0.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via attachment_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13695</link><description>The Enfold theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.9 via the 'attachment_id' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 09:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13494 | WordPress File Upload &amp;lt;= 4.25.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in wfu_file_details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13494</link><description>The WordPress File Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.25.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'wfu_file_details' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify user data details associated with uploaded files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1674 | Out of bounds read when unpacking DNS answers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1674</link><description>A lack of input validation allows for out of bounds reads caused by malicious or malformed packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1675 | Out of bounds read in dns_copy_qname</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1675</link><description>The function dns_copy_qname in dns_pack.c performs performs a memcpy operation with an untrusted field and does not check if the source buffer is large enough to contain the copied data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1673 | Out of bounds read when calling crc16_ansi and strlen in dns_validate_msg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1673</link><description>A malicious or malformed DNS packet without a payload can cause an out-of-bounds read, resulting in a crash (denial of service) or an incorrect computation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1063 | Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp;amp; Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Unauthenticated Settings Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1063</link><description>The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4 via the rtcl_taxonomy_settings_export function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including API keys and tokens.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1128 | Everest Forms &amp;lt;= 3.0.9.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload, Read, and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1128</link><description>The Everest Forms – Contact Forms, Quiz, Survey, Newsletter &amp; Payment Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file upload, read, and deletion due to missing file type and path validation in the 'format' method of the EVF_Form_Fields_Upload class in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.9.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload, read, and delete arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution, sensitive information disclosure, or a site takeover possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1648 | Yawave &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1648</link><description>The Yawave plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'lbid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10545 | NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt; 3.59.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10545</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and   WordPress plugin before 3.59.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its Image settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22210 | Extension - hikashop.com - SQL injection in Hikashop component version 3.3.0 - 5.1.4 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22210</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the Hikashop component versions 3.3.0-5.1.4 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the category management area in backend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1646 | Lumsoft ERP ASPX File UploadAjaxAPI.ashx unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1646</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Lumsoft ERP 8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Api/TinyMce/UploadAjaxAPI.ashx of the component ASPX File Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 03:06:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1644 | Benner ModernaNet SG_Gravar cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1644</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Benner ModernaNet up to 1.2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /DadosPessoais/SG_Gravar. The manipulation of the argument idItAg leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1645 | Benner Connecta EditarLogado resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1645</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Benner Connecta 1.0.5330. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Usuarios/Usuario/EditarLogado/. The manipulation of the argument Handle leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27145 | copyparty renders unsanitized filenames as HTML when user uploads empty files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27145</link><description>copyparty, a portable file server, has a DOM-based cross-site scripting vulnerability in versions prior to 1.16.15. The vulnerability is considered low-risk. By handing someone a maliciously-named file, and then tricking them into dragging the file into copyparty's Web-UI, an attacker could execute arbitrary javascript with the same privileges as that user. For example, this could give unintended read-access to files owned by that user. The bug is triggered by the drag-drop action itself; it is not necessary to actually initiate the upload. The file must be empty (zero bytes). Note that, as a general-purpose webserver, it is intentionally possible to upload HTML-files with arbitrary javascript in `</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1642 | Benner ModernaNet GetImageMedico resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1642</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Benner ModernaNet up to 1.1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /AGE0000700/GetImageMedico?fooId=1. The manipulation of the argument fooId leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1643 | Benner ModernaNet SG_AlterarSenha cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1643</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Benner ModernaNet up to 1.1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /DadosPessoais/SG_AlterarSenha. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1640 | Benner ModernaNet JS_CarregaCombo sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Benner ModernaNet up to 1.1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Home/JS_CarregaCombo?formName=DADOS_PESSOAIS_PLANO&amp;amp;additionalCondition=&amp;amp;insideParameters=&amp;amp;elementToReturn=DADOS_PESSOAIS_PLANO&amp;amp;ordenarPelaDescricao=true&amp;amp;direcaoOrdenacao=asc&amp;_=1739290047295. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1641 | Benner ModernaNet GetHorariosDoDia sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1641</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Benner ModernaNet up to 1.1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /AGE0000700/GetHorariosDoDia?idespec=0&amp;amp;idproced=1103&amp;amp;data=2025-02-25+19%3A25&amp;amp;agserv=0&amp;amp;convenio=1&amp;amp;localatend=1&amp;amp;idplano=5&amp;amp;pesfis=01&amp;amp;idprofissional=0&amp;amp;target=.horarios--dia--d0&amp;_=1739371223797. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 1.1.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53542 | Incorrect access control in the component /iclock/Settings?restartNCS=1 of NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53542</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component /iclock/Settings?restartNCS=1 of NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 allows attackers to arbitrarily restart the NCServiceManger via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53543 | NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the addProject ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53543</link><description>NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the addProject method in the smarttimeplus/MySQLConnection endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53544 | NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the getCookieNa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53544</link><description>NovaCHRON Zeitsysteme GmbH &amp; Co. KG Smart Time Plus v8.x to v8.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the getCookieNames method in the smarttimeplus/MySQLConnection endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56525 | In Public Knowledge Project (PKP) OJS, OMP, and OPS before 3.3.0.21 and 3.4.x before 3.4.0.8, an XXE attack by the Journal Editor Role can c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56525</link><description>In Public Knowledge Project (PKP) OJS, OMP, and OPS before 3.3.0.21 and 3.4.x before 3.4.0.8, an XXE attack by the Journal Editor Role can create a new role as super admin in the journal context, and insert a backdoor plugin, by uploading a crafted XML document as a User XML Plugin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:53:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57685 | An issue in sparkshop v.1.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted phar file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57685</link><description>An issue in sparkshop v.1.1.7 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted phar file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22974 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SeaCMS v.13.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DoTranExecSql parameter i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22974</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in SeaCMS v.13.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DoTranExecSql parameter in the phome.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27143 | Beter Auth has an Open Redirect via Scheme-Less Callback Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27143</link><description>Better Auth is an authentication and authorization library for TypeScript. Prior to version 1.1.21, the application is vulnerable to an open redirect due to improper validation of the callbackURL parameter in the email verification endpoint and any other endpoint that accepts callback url. While the server blocks fully qualified URLs, it incorrectly allows scheme-less URLs. This results in the browser interpreting the URL as a fully qualified URL, leading to unintended redirection. An attacker can exploit this flaw by crafting a malicious verification link and tricking users into clicking it. Upon successful email verification, the user will be automatically redirected to the attacker's website, which can be used for phishing, malware distribution, or stealing sensitive authentication tokens. This CVE is a bypass of the fix for GHSA-8jhw-6pjj-8723/CVE-2024-56734. Version 1.1.21 contains an updated patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27144 | Go JOSE&amp;#x27;s Parsing Vulnerable to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27144</link><description>Go JOSE provides an implementation of the Javascript Object Signing and Encryption set of standards in Go, including support for JSON Web Encryption (JWE), JSON Web Signature (JWS), and JSON Web Token (JWT) standards. In versions on the 4.x branch prior to version 4.0.5, when parsing compact JWS or JWE input, Go JOSE could use excessive memory. The code used strings.Split(token, ".") to split JWT tokens, which is vulnerable to excessive memory consumption when processing maliciously crafted tokens with a large number of `.` characters.  An attacker could exploit this by sending numerous malformed tokens, leading to memory exhaustion and a Denial of Service. Version 4.0.5 fixes this issue. As a workaround, applications could pre-validate that payloads passed to Go JOSE do not contain an excessive number of `.` characters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57608 | An issue in Via Browser 6.1.0 allows a a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the mark.via.Shell component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57608</link><description>An issue in Via Browser 6.1.0 allows a a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the mark.via.Shell component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25513 | Seacms &lt;=13.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin_members.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25513</link><description>Seacms &lt;=13.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in admin_members.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27141 | Metabase Enterprise Edition allows cached questions to leak data to impersonated users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27141</link><description>Metabase Enterprise Edition is the enterprise version of Metabase business intelligence and data analytics software. Starting in version 1.47.0 and prior to versions 1.50.36, 1.51.14, 1.52.11, and 1.53.2 of Metabase Enterprise Edition, users with impersonation permissions may be able to see results of cached questions, even if their permissions don’t allow them to see the data. If some user runs a question which gets cached, and then an impersonated user runs that question, then the impersonated user sees the same results as the previous user. These cached results may include data the impersonated user should not have access to. This vulnerability only impacts the Enterprise Edition of Metabase and not the Open Source Edition. Versions 1.53.2, 1.52.11, 1.51.14, and 1.50.36 contains a patch. Versions on the 1.49.X, 1.48.X, and 1.47.X branches are vulnerable but do not have a patch available, so users should upgrade to a major version with an available fix. Disabling question caching is a workaround for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27140 | WeGIA vulnerable to OS Command Injection at endpoint &amp;#x27;importar_dump.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;import&amp;#x27; (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27140</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. An OS Command Injection vulnerability was discovered in versions prior to 3.2.15 of the WeGIA application, `importar_dump.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code remotely. The command is basically a command to move a temporary file, so a webshell upload is also possible. Version 3.2.15 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27137 | Dependency-Track vulnerable to local file inclusion via custom notification templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27137</link><description>Dependency-Track is a component analysis platform that allows organizations to identify and reduce risk in the software supply chain. Dependency-Track allows users with the `SYSTEM_CONFIGURATION` permission to customize notification templates. Templates are evaluated using the Pebble template engine. Pebble supports an `include` tag, which allows template authors to include the content of arbitrary files upon evaluation. Prior to version 4.12.6, users of Dependency-Track with the `SYSTEM_CONFIGURATION` permission can abuse the `include` tag by crafting notification templates that `include` sensitive local files, such as `/etc/passwd` or `/proc/1/environ`. By configuring such a template for a notification rule (aka "Alert"), and having it send notifications to a destination controlled by the actor, sensitive information may be leaked. The issue has been fixed in Dependency-Track 4.12.6. In fixed versions, the `include` tag can no longer be used. Usage of the tag will cause template evaluation to fail. As a workaround, avoid assigning the `SYSTEM_CONFIGURATION` permission to untrusted users. The `SYSTEM_CONFIGURATION` permission per default is only granted to members of the `Administrators` team. Assigning this permission to non-administrative users or teams is a security risk in itself, and highly discouraged.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26533 | SQL injection risk in course search module list filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26533</link><description>An SQL injection risk was identified in the module list filter within course search.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:20:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26531 | IDOR in badges allows disabling of arbitrary badges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26531</link><description>Insufficient capability checks made it possible to disable badges a user does not have permission to access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26532 | Teachers can evade trusttext config when restoring glossary entries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26532</link><description>Additional checks were required to ensure trusttext is applied (when enabled) to glossary entries being restored.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26529 | Stored XSS risk in admin live log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26529</link><description>Description information displayed in the site administration live log 
required additional sanitizing to prevent a stored XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26530 | Reflected XSS via question bank filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26530</link><description>The question bank filter required additional sanitizing to prevent a reflected XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26528 | Stored XSS in ddimageortext question type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26528</link><description>The drag-and-drop onto image (ddimageortext) question type required additional sanitizing to prevent a stored XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26527 | Non-searchable tags can still be discovered on the tag search page and in the tags block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26527</link><description>Tags not expected to be visible to a user could still be discovered by them via the tag search page or in the tags block.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26526 | Feedback response viewing and deletions did not respect Separate Groups mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26526</link><description>Separate Groups mode restrictions were not factored into permission 
checks before allowing viewing or deletion of responses in Feedback 
activities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26525 | Arbitrary file read risk through pdfTeX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26525</link><description>Insufficient sanitizing in the TeX notation filter resulted in an 
arbitrary file read risk on sites where pdfTeX is available (such as 
those with TeX Live installed).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27364 | In MITRE Caldera through 4.2.0 and 5.0.0 before 35bc06e, a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was found in the dynamic agent (implant...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27364</link><description>In MITRE Caldera through 4.2.0 and 5.0.0 before 35bc06e, a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was found in the dynamic agent (implant) compilation functionality of the server. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on the server that Caldera is running on via a crafted web request to the Caldera server API used for compiling and downloading of Caldera's Sandcat or Manx agent (implants). This web request can use the gcc -extldflags linker flag with sub-commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27112 | Navidrome has authentication bypass in Subsonic API with non-existent username</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27112</link><description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. Starting in version 0.52.0 and prior to version 0.54.5, in certain Subsonic API endpoints, a flaw in the authentication check process allows an attacker to specify any arbitrary username that does not exist on the system, along with a salted hash of an empty password. Under these conditions, Navidrome treats the request as authenticated, granting access to various Subsonic endpoints without requiring valid credentials. An attacker can use any non-existent username to bypass the authentication system and gain access to various read-only data in Navidrome, such as user playlists. However, any attempt to modify data fails with a "permission denied" error due to insufficient permissions, limiting the impact to unauthorized viewing of information. Version 0.54.5 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27133 | WeGIA has SQL Injection endpoint at &amp;#x27;dao/pet/adicionar_tipo_exame.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;tipo_exame&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27133</link><description>WeGIA is a Web manager for charitable institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application prior to version 3.2.15 at the `adicionar_tipo_exame.php` endpoint. This vulnerability allows an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to sensitive information. Version 3.2.15 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57026 | TawkTo Widget Version &lt;= 1.3.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to processing user input in a way that allows JavaScript exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57026</link><description>TawkTo Widget Version &lt;= 1.3.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) due to processing user input in a way that allows JavaScript execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54820 | XOne Web Monitor v02.10.2024.530 framework 1.0.4.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability in the login page. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54820</link><description>XOne Web Monitor v02.10.2024.530 framework 1.0.4.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability in the login page. This vulnerability allows attackers to extract all usernames and passwords via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26201 | Credential disclosure vulnerability via the /staff route in GreaterWMS &lt;= 2.1.49 allows a remote unauthenticated attackers to bypass authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26201</link><description>Credential disclosure vulnerability via the /staff route in GreaterWMS &lt;= 2.1.49 allows a remote unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22495 | Improper input validation in</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22495</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability was discovered in the NTP server configuration field of the Network-M2 card. This could result in an authenticated high privileged user having the ability to execute arbitrary commands. The vulnerability has been resolved in the version 3.0.4. 
Note - Network-M2 has been declared end-of-life in early 2024 and Network-M3 has been released as a fit-and-functional replacement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26200 | SQL injection in SLIMS v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the month parameter in the visitor_report_day.php compone...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26200</link><description>SQL injection in SLIMS v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the month parameter in the visitor_report_day.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25460 | A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in FlatPress 1.3.1 within the "Add Entry" feature. This vulnerability allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25460</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in FlatPress 1.3.1 within the "Add Entry" feature. This vulnerability allows authenticated attackers to inject malicious JavaScript payloads into blog posts, which are executed when other users view the posts. The issue arises due to improper input sanitization of the "TextArea" field in the blog entry submission form.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26803 | The http parser in Phusion Passenger 6.0.21 through 6.0.25 before 6.0.26 allows a denial of service during parsing of a request with an inva...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26803</link><description>The http parser in Phusion Passenger 6.0.21 through 6.0.25 before 6.0.26 allows a denial of service during parsing of a request with an invalid HTTP method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56897 | Improper access control in the HTTP server in YI Car Dashcam v3.88 allows unrestricted file downloads, uploads, and API commands. API comman...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56897</link><description>Improper access control in the HTTP server in YI Car Dashcam v3.88 allows unrestricted file downloads, uploads, and API commands. API commands can also be made to make unauthorized modifications to the device settings, such as disabling recording, disabling sounds, factory reset.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26883 | WordPress Animated Text Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26883</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bPlugins Animated Text Block allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Animated Text Block: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27316 | WordPress JPG, PNG Compression and Optimization Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.35 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27316</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in hosting.io JPG, PNG Compression and Optimization allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects JPG, PNG Compression and Optimization: from n/a through 1.7.35.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27317 | WordPress RAYS Grid Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27317</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in IT-RAYS RAYS Grid allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects RAYS Grid: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27318 | WordPress Simple Google Sitemap Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27318</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ixiter Simple Google Sitemap allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Google Sitemap: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27320 | WordPress Profile Widget Ninja plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pankaj Mondal Profile Widget Ninja allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Profile Widget Ninja: from n/a through 4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27321 | WordPress Blightly Explorer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27321</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blighty Blightly Explorer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Blightly Explorer: from n/a through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27323 | WordPress WP About Author plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27323</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jon Bishop WP About Author allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP About Author: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27325 | WordPress Video.js HLS Player plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27325</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bruce Video.js HLS Player allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Video.js HLS Player: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27327 | WordPress Live Streaming Video Player – by SRS Player plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.18 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27327</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Winlin Live Streaming Video Player – by SRS Player allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Live Streaming Video Player – by SRS Player: from n/a through 1.0.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27328 | WordPress WP-PostRatings Cheater Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27328</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in queeez WP-PostRatings Cheater allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP-PostRatings Cheater: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27329 | WordPress EZ InLinkz linkup plugin &amp;lt;= 0.18 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27329</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in inlinkz EZ InLinkz linkup allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects EZ InLinkz linkup: from n/a through 0.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27330 | WordPress PlayerJS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.23 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27330</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PlayerJS PlayerJS allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects PlayerJS: from n/a through 2.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27331 | WordPress WooCommerce Display Products by Tags plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27331</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sébastien Dumont WooCommerce Display Products by Tags allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Display Products by Tags: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27332 | WordPress Smart Maintenance &amp;amp; Countdown Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27332</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in gmnazmul Smart Maintenance &amp; Countdown allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Smart Maintenance &amp; Countdown: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27335 | WordPress Auto Tag Links Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27335</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Free plug in by SEO Roma Auto Tag Links allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Auto Tag Links: from n/a through 1.0.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27336 | WordPress Just Variables Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27336</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alex Prokopenko / JustCoded Just Variables allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Just Variables: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27339 | WordPress Minimum Password Strength Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27339</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Will Anderson Minimum Password Strength allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Minimum Password Strength: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27340 | WordPress F12-Profiler Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27340</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marc F12-Profiler allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects F12-Profiler: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27341 | WordPress Reactive Mortgage Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27341</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in afzal_du Reactive Mortgage Calculator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Reactive Mortgage Calculator: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27342 | WordPress WooCommerce Recargo de Equivalencia Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.24 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27342</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in josesan WooCommerce Recargo de Equivalencia allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WooCommerce Recargo de Equivalencia: from n/a through 1.6.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27344 | WordPress Phee&amp;#x27;s LinkPreview Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27344</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in filipstepanov Phee's LinkPreview allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Phee's LinkPreview: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27347 | WordPress Direct Checkout Button for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27347</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in techmix Direct Checkout Button for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Direct Checkout Button for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27348 | WordPress WP Social SEO Booster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Daniel WP Social SEO Booster – Knowledge Graph Social Signals SEO allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Social SEO Booster – Knowledge Graph Social Signals SEO: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27349 | WordPress Get Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nurelm Get Posts allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Get Posts: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27351 | WordPress Local Search SEO Contact Page plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27351</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ExpertBusinessSearch Local Search SEO Contact Page allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Local Search SEO Contact Page: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27352 | WordPress 无觅相关文章插件 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5.7 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27352</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wumii team 无觅相关文章插件 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects 无觅相关文章插件: from n/a through 1.0.5.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27353 | WordPress Namaste! LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27353</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Bob Namaste! LMS allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Namaste! LMS: from n/a through 2.6.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27355 | WordPress Woocommerce – Loi Hamon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27355</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Nicolas GRILLET Woocommerce – Loi Hamon allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Woocommerce – Loi Hamon: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27356 | WordPress Sticky Header On Scroll plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27356</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hardik Sticky Header On Scroll allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Sticky Header On Scroll: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27357 | WordPress Önceki Yazı Link Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27357</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Musa AVCI Önceki Yazı Link allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Önceki Yazı Link: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27265 | WordPress Google Maps for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27265</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aaron D. Campbell Google Maps for WordPress allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Google Maps for WordPress: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27266 | WordPress Hover Image Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27266</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ignacio Perez Hover Image Button allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Hover Image Button: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27272 | WordPress VG PostCarousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27272</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in vinagecko VG PostCarousel allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects VG PostCarousel: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27276 | WordPress Photo Gallery ( Responsive ) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27276</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in lizeipe Photo Gallery ( Responsive ) allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Photo Gallery ( Responsive ): from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27277 | WordPress Add Linked Images To Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27277</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in tiefpunkt Add Linked Images To Gallery allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Add Linked Images To Gallery: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27280 | WordPress Archive Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27280</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alobaidi Archive Page allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Archive Page: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27290 | WordPress Select Erima Zarinpal Donate Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27290</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in seyyed-amir Erima Zarinpal Donate allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Erima Zarinpal Donate: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27294 | WordPress WP-Asambleas plugin &amp;lt;= 2.85.0 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27294</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in platcom WP-Asambleas allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP-Asambleas: from n/a through 2.85.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27296 | WordPress Auto Ad Inserter – Increase Google Adsense and Ad Manager Revenue Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27296</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in revenueflex Auto Ad Inserter – Increase Google Adsense and Ad Manager Revenue allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Auto Ad Inserter – Increase Google Adsense and Ad Manager Revenue: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27297 | WordPress Bravo Search &amp;amp; Replace Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27297</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in guelben Bravo Search &amp; Replace allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Bravo Search &amp; Replace: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27298 | WordPress WP Video Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - CSRF to Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27298</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in cmstactics WP Video Posts allows OS Command Injection. This issue affects WP Video Posts: from n/a through 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27300 | WordPress ADFO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27300</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in giuliopanda ADFO allows Object Injection. This issue affects ADFO: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27301 | WordPress NHR Options Table Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27301</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Nazmul Hasan Robin NHR Options Table Manager allows Object Injection. This issue affects NHR Options Table Manager: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27303 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Star Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themelogger Contact Form 7 Star Rating allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Star Rating: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27304 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Star Rating with font Awesome plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themelogger Contact Form 7 Star Rating with font Awesome allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Star Rating with font Awesome: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27305 | WordPress Table of Contents Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Achal Jain Table of Contents Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Table of Contents Block: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27306 | WordPress Pathomation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27306</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pathomation Pathomation allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Pathomation: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27307 | WordPress Quotes llama plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in oooorgle Quotes llama allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Quotes llama: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27311 | WordPress Bulk Content Creator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27311</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in luk3thomas Bulk Content Creator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Bulk Content Creator: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27312 | WordPress WP Sitemap plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jenst WP Sitemap allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Sitemap: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27315 | WordPress All-In-One Cufon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27315</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wptom All-In-One Cufon allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects All-In-One Cufon: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23017 | WorkOS Hosted AuthKit before 2025-01-07 allows a password authentication MFA bypass (by enrolling a new authentication factor) when the atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23017</link><description>WorkOS Hosted AuthKit before 2025-01-07 allows a password authentication MFA bypass (by enrolling a new authentication factor) when the attacker knows the user's password. No exploitation occurred.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12917 | Improper Access Control in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Health4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12917</link><description>Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in Agito Computer Health4All allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels, Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Health4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12918 | SQLi in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Health4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12918</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Agito Computer Health4All allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Health4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12916 | SQLi in Agito Computer&amp;#x27;s Life4All</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12916</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Agito Computer Life4All allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Life4All: before 10.01.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0545 | XSS in Tekrom Technology&amp;#x27;s T-Soft E-Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tekrom Technology T-Soft E-Commerce allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects T-Soft E-Commerce: before v5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5174 | Broken Authentication in Gliffy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5174</link><description>A flaw in Gliffy results in broken authentication through the reset functionality of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1632 | libarchive bsdunzip.c list null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1632</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libarchive up to 3.7.7. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function list of the file bsdunzip.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1488 | WPO365 | MICROSOFT 365 GRAPH MAILER &amp;lt;= 3.2 - Open Redirect via &amp;#x27;redirect_to&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1488</link><description>The WPO365 | MICROSOFT 365 GRAPH MAILER plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 3.2. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the 'redirect_to' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if 1. they can successfully trick them into performing an action and 2. the plugin is activated but not configured.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 11:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52926 | io_uring/rw: split io_read() into a helper</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52926</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

IORING_OP_READ did not correctly consume the provided buffer list when
read i/o returned &lt; 0 (except for -EAGAIN and -EIOCBQUEUED return).
This can lead to a potential use-after-free when the completion via
io_rw_done runs at separate context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 09:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0690 | Grub2: read: integer overflow may lead to out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0690</link><description>The read command is used to read the keyboard input from the user, while reads it keeps the input length in a 32-bit integer value which is further used to reallocate the line buffer to accept the next character. During this process, with a line big enough it's possible to make this variable to overflow leading to a out-of-bounds write in the heap based buffer. This flaw may be leveraged to corrupt grub's internal critical data and secure boot bypass is not discarded as consequence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20051 | Arbitrary file read via block duplication in Mattermost Boards</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20051</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to properly validate input when patching and duplicating a board, which allows a user to read any arbitrary file on the system via duplicating a specially crafted block in Boards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24490 | SQL Injection in Mattermost Boards via board category ID reordering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24490</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to use prepared statements in the SQL query of boards reordering which allows an attacker to retrieve data from the database, via a SQL injection when reordering specially crafted boards categories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25279 | Arbitrary file read in Mattermost Boards via import &amp;amp; export board archive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25279</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to properly validate board blocks when importing boards which allows an attacker could read any arbitrary file on the system via importing and exporting a specially crafted import archive in Boards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1412 | Session Persistence After User-to-Bot Conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1412</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.6, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1 fail to invalidate all active sessions when converting a user to a bot, with allows the converted user to escalate their privileges depending on the permissions granted to the bot.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24526 | Channel export permitted on archived channel when viewing archived channels is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24526</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.3, 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.7, 10.3.x &lt;= 10.3.2, 10.2.x &lt;= 10.2.2 fail to restrict channel export of archived channels when the "Allow users to view archived channels" is disabled which allows a user to export channel contents when they shouldn't have access to it</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 07:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12308 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.6.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12308</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.6.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13605 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.33 -  Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13605</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13822 | Total Contest Lite &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13822</link><description>The Photo Contest  | Competition | Video Contest WordPress plugin through 2.8.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 06:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1629 | Excitel Broadband Private my Excitel App One-Time Password excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1629</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Excitel Broadband Private my Excitel App 3.13.0 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the component One-Time Password Handler. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 05:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1618 | vTiger CRM index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1618</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in vTiger CRM 6.4.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /modules/Mobile/index.php. The manipulation of the argument _operation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1616 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON Diagnosis os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1616</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Diagnosis. The manipulation of the argument Destination Address leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1617 | Netis WF2780 Wireless 2.4G Menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1617</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Netis WF2780 2.1.41925. This affects an unknown part of the component Wireless 2.4G Menu. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1615 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON NAT Submenu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1615</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component NAT Submenu. The manipulation of the argument Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1613 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON URL Filtering Submenu URL_filterCfg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/URL_filterCfg of the component URL Filtering Submenu. The manipulation of the argument url_IP leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1614 | FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON Port Forwarding Submenu portForwardingCfg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1614</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in FiberHome AN5506-01A ONU GPON RP2511. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/portForwardingCfg of the component Port Forwarding Submenu. The manipulation of the argument pf_Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1612 | Edimax BR-6288ACL wireless5g_basic.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1612</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Edimax BR-6288ACL 1.30. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file wireless5g_basic.asp. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 03:06:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55898 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55898</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 could allow a user with the capability to compile or restore a program to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library call. A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1611 | ShopXO Template ThemeAdminService.php injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1611</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ShopXO up to 6.4.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file app/service/ThemeAdminService.php of the component Template Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1609 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_cmd websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1609</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_cmd. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1610 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_blacklist websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1610</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_blacklist. The manipulation of the argument mac/enable leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1607 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System salary_slip.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1607</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/salary_slip.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1608 | LB-LINK AC1900 Router set_manpwd websGetVar os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1608</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in LB-LINK AC1900 Router 1.0.2. Affected is the function websGetVar of the file /goform/set_manpwd. The manipulation of the argument routepwd  leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1599 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software profile_crud.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1599</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/profile_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument old_cat_img leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1606 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System backups.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1606</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/backup/backups.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1598 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software asset_crud.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1598</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/app/asset_crud.php. The manipulation of the argument photo1 leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1596 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software fpassword.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /fpassword.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1597 | SourceCodester Best Church Management Software redirect.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1597</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Church Management Software 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/redirect.php. The manipulation of the argument a leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22631 | WordPress Marketing Automation Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vbout Marketing Automation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Marketing Automation: from n/a through 1.2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22632 | WordPress WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22632</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in totalsoft WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Pricing – Product Pricing: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22633 | WordPress Give – Divi Donation Modules plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22633</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Matt Cromwell Give – Divi Donation Modules allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Give – Divi Donation Modules: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22635 | WordPress Eventer - WordPress Event &amp;amp; Booking Manager Plugin plugin &amp;lt; 3.9.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22635</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jyothis Joy Eventer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Eventer: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 23:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1595 | Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR getbaseconfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Anhui Xufan Information Technology EasyCVR up to 2.7.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/v1/getbaseconfig. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 22:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1594 | FFmpeg AAC Encoder aacenc_tns.c ff_aac_search_for_tns stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1594</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FFmpeg up to 7.1. This affects the function ff_aac_search_for_tns of the file libavcodec/aacenc_tns.c of the component AAC Encoder. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 21:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1593 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Profile Picture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1593</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /_hr_soft/assets/uploadImage/Profile/ of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 20:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1592 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Add Role Page Role.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1592</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/Operations/Role.php of the component Add Role Page. The manipulation of the argument assign_name/description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1591 | SourceCodester Employee Management System Department Page department.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1591</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /department.php of the component Department Page. The manipulation of the argument Department Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1590 | SourceCodester E-Learning System List of Lessons Page index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/modules/lesson/index.php of the component List of Lessons Page. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1589 | SourceCodester E-Learning System User Registration register.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester E-Learning System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /register.php of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1588 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System manage-nurse.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1588</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/manage-nurse.php. The manipulation of the argument profilepic leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting vulnerability classes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1467 | Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1467</link><description>Versions of the package tarteaucitronjs before 1.17.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the getElemWidth() and getElemHeight(). This is related to [SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-TARTEAUCITRONJS-8366541)</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1587 | SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System Add New Record main.cpp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file main.cpp of the component Add New Record. The manipulation of the argument name leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1586 | code-projects Blood Bank System A-.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1586</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Blood/A-.php. The manipulation of the argument Bloodname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1585 | otale header.html OptionsService cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1585</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in otale tale up to 2.0.5. This issue affects the function OptionsService of the file src/main/resources/templates/themes/default/partial/header.html. The manipulation of the argument logo_url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1584 | opensolon Solon StaticMappings.java path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1584</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in opensolon Solon up to 3.0.8. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file solon-projects/solon-web/solon-web-staticfiles/src/main/java/org/noear/solon/web/staticfiles/StaticMappings.java. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.9 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is f46e47fd1f8455b9467d7ead3cdb0509115b2ef1. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1583 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System search-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/search-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 12:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1582 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System all-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/all-request.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1581 | PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System book-nurse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Nurse Hiring System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /book-nurse.php?bookid=1. The manipulation of the argument contactname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1580 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions contradicting parameter names to be affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 10:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1579 | code-projects Blood Bank System user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1578 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal search-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1578</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument product leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1577 | code-projects Blood Bank System prostatus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1577</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /prostatus.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 07:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13728 | Accept Donations with PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13728</link><description>The Accept Donations with PayPal &amp; Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the rf parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 05:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1576 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System ajax_state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1576</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /ajax_state.php. The manipulation of the argument StateName as part of String leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1575 | Harpia DiagSystem atualatendimento_jpeg.php resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1575</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Harpia DiagSystem 12. Affected is an unknown function of the file /diagsystem/PACS/atualatendimento_jpeg.php. The manipulation of the argument cod/codexame leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>