<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-48948 | Navidrome Transcoding Permission Bypass Vulnerability Report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48948</link><description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. A permission verification flaw in versions prior to 0.56.0 allows any authenticated regular user to bypass authorization checks and perform administrator-only transcoding configuration operations, including creating, modifying, and deleting transcoding settings. In the threat model where administrators are trusted but regular users are not, this vulnerability represents a significant security risk when transcoding is enabled. Version 0.56.0 patches the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1479 | An open debug interface was reported in the Legion Space software included on certain Legion devices that could allow a local attacker to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1479</link><description>An open debug interface was reported in the Legion Space software included on certain Legion devices that could allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2501 | An untrusted search path vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to elevate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2501</link><description>An untrusted search path vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2502 | An improper default permissions vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to elevate privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2502</link><description>An improper default permissions vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to elevate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2503 | An improper permission handling vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to perform arbitrary file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2503</link><description>An improper permission handling vulnerability was reported in Lenovo PC Manager that could allow a local attacker to perform arbitrary file deletions as an elevated user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48946 | liboqs affected by theoretical design flaw in HQC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48946</link><description>liboqs is a C-language cryptographic library that provides implementations of post-quantum cryptography algorithms. liboqs prior to version 0.13.0 supports the HQC algorithm, an algorithm with a theoretical design flaw which leads to large numbers of malformed ciphertexts sharing the same implicit rejection value. Currently, no concrete attack on the algorithm is known. However, prospective users of HQC must take extra care when using the algorithm in protocols involving key derivation. In particular, HQC does not provide the same security guarantees as Kyber or ML-KEM. There is currently no patch for the HQC flaw available in liboqs, so HQC is disabled by default in liboqs starting from version 0.13.0. OQS will update its implementation after the HQC team releases an updated algorithm specification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48883 | Chrome PHP is missing encoding in `CssSelector`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48883</link><description>Chrome PHP allows users to start playing with chrome/chromium in headless mode from PHP. Prior to version 1.14.0, CSS Selector expressions are not properly encoded, which can lead to XSS (cross-site scripting) vulnerabilities. This is patched in v1.14.0. As a workaround, users can apply encoding manually to their selectors if they are unable to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48885 | application-urlshortener users can create arbitrary pages as long as they have view access to them</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48885</link><description>application-urlshortener create shortened URLs for XWiki pages. Versions prior to 1.2.4 are vulnerable to users with view access being able to create arbitrary pages. Any user (even guests) can create these docs, even if they don't exist already. This can enable guest users to denature the structure of wiki pages, by creating 1000's of pages with random name, that then become very difficult to handle by admins. Version 1.2.4 fixes the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48938 | Prevent GitHub CLI and extensions from executing arbitrary commands from compromised GitHub Enterprise Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48938</link><description>go-gh is a collection of Go modules to make authoring GitHub CLI extensions easier. A security vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.12.1 where an attacker-controlled GitHub Enterprise Server could result in executing arbitrary commands on a user's machine by replacing HTTP URLs provided by GitHub with local file paths for browsing. In `2.12.1`, `Browser.Browse()` has been enhanced to allow and disallow a variety of scenarios to avoid opening or executing files on the filesystem without unduly impacting HTTP URLs. No known workarounds are available other than upgrading.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48942 | vLLM DOS: Remotely kill vllm over http with invalid JSON schema</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48942</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In versions 0.8.0 up to but excluding 0.9.0, hitting the  /v1/completions API with a invalid json_schema as a Guided Param kills the vllm server. This vulnerability is similar GHSA-9hcf-v7m4-6m2j/CVE-2025-48943, but for regex instead of a JSON schema. Version 0.9.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48943 | vLLM allows clients to crash the openai server with invalid regex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48943</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). Version 0.8.0 up to but excluding 0.9.0 have a Denial of Service (ReDoS) that causes the vLLM server to crash if an invalid regex was provided while using structured output. This vulnerability is similar to GHSA-6qc9-v4r8-22xg/CVE-2025-48942, but for regex instead of a JSON schema. Version 0.9.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48944 | vLLM Tool Schema allows DoS via Malformed pattern and type Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48944</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In version 0.8.0 up to but excluding 0.9.0, the vLLM backend used with the /v1/chat/completions OpenAPI endpoint fails to validate unexpected or malformed input in the "pattern" and "type" fields when the tools functionality is invoked. These inputs are not validated before being compiled or parsed, causing a crash of the inference worker with a single request. The worker will remain down until it is restarted. Version 0.9.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5359 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System appointment-history.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5359</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /appointment-history.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5358 | PHPGurukul/Campcodes Cyber Cafe Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5358</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul/Campcodes Cyber Cafe Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48887 | vLLM has a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS, Exponential Complexity) Vulnerability in `pythonic_tool_parser.py`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48887</link><description>vLLM, an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs), has a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability in the file `vllm/entrypoints/openai/tool_parsers/pythonic_tool_parser.py` of versions 0.6.4 up to but excluding 0.9.0. The root cause is the use of a highly complex and nested regular expression for tool call detection, which can be exploited by an attacker to cause severe performance degradation or make the service unavailable. The pattern contains multiple nested quantifiers, optional groups, and inner repetitions which make it vulnerable to catastrophic backtracking. Version 0.9.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5054 | Race Condition in Canonical Apport</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5054</link><description>Race condition in Canonical apport up to and including 2.32.0 allows a local attacker to leak sensitive information via PID-reuse by leveraging namespaces.




When handling a crash, the function `_check_global_pid_and_forward`, which detects if the crashing process resided in a container, was being called before `consistency_checks`, which attempts to detect if the crashing process had been replaced. Because of this, if a process crashed and was quickly replaced with a containerized one, apport could be made to forward the core dump to the container, potentially leaking sensitive information. `consistency_checks` is now being called before `_check_global_pid_and_forward`. Additionally, given that the PID-reuse race condition cannot be reliably detected from userspace alone, crashes are only forwarded to containers if the kernel provided a pidfd, or if the crashing process was unprivileged (i.e., if dump mode == 1).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5357 | FreeFloat FTP Server PWD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5357</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PWD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26226 | A use after free memory corruption issue exists in Yandex Browser for Desktop prior to version 24.4.0.682</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26226</link><description>A use after free memory corruption issue exists in Yandex Browser for Desktop prior to version 24.4.0.682</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5356 | FreeFloat FTP Server BYE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5356</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component BYE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42191 | HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to COM hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42191</link><description>HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a COM hijacking vulnerability which could allow an attacker to modify or replace the application with malicious content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42190 | HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to DLL hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42190</link><description>HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a DLL hijacking vulnerability which could allow an attacker to modify or replace the application with malicious content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23589 | HCL Glovius Cloud is susceptible to an Outdated Hash Algorithm vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23589</link><description>Due to outdated Hash algorithm, HCL Glovius Cloud could allow attackers to guess the input data using brute-force or dictionary attacks efficiently using modern hardware such as GPUs or ASICs</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:43:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13915 | Unrestricted Access to Exported Service in com.pri.factorytest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13915</link><description>Android based smartphones from vendors such as Ulefone and Krüger&amp;amp;Matz contain "com.pri.factorytest" application preloaded onto devices during manufacturing process.
The application "com.pri.factorytest" (version name: 1.0, version code: 1) exposes a ”com.pri.factorytest.emmc.FactoryResetService“ service allowing any application to perform a factory reset of the device. 
Application update did not increment the APK version. Instead, it was bundled in OS builds released later than December 2024 (Ulefone) and most probably March 2025 (Krüger&amp;amp;Matz, although the vendor has not confirmed it, so newer releases might be vulnerable as well).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13916 | Exposure of Applications&amp;#x27; Encryption PINs in Kruger&amp;amp;Matz AppLock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13916</link><description>An application "com.pri.applock", which is pre-loaded on Kruger&amp;amp;Matz smartphones, allows a user to encrypt any application using user-provided PIN code or by using biometric data.
Exposed ”com.android.providers.settings.fingerprint.PriFpShareProvider“ content provider's public method query() allows any other malicious application, without any granted Android system permissions, to exfiltrate the PIN code.

Vendor did not provide information about vulnerable versions.
Only version (version name: 13, version code: 33) was tested and confirmed to have this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13917 | Intent Injection in Kruger&amp;amp;Matz AppLock application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13917</link><description>An application "com.pri.applock", which is pre-loaded on Kruger&amp;amp;Matz smartphones, allows a user to encrypt any application using user-provided PIN code or by using biometric data.
Exposed ”com.pri.applock.LockUI“ activity allows any other malicious application, with no granted Android system permissions, to inject an arbitrary intent with system-level privileges to a protected application. One must know the protecting PIN number (it might be revealed by exploiting CVE-2024-13916) or ask the user to provide it.

Vendor did not provide information about vulnerable versions.
Only version (version name: 13, version code: 33) was tested and confirmed to have this vulnerability</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7097 | Incorrect Authorization in Multiple WSO2 Products via SOAP Admin Service Allowing Unauthorized User Signup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7097</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to a flaw in the SOAP admin service, which allows user account creation regardless of the self-registration configuration settings. This vulnerability enables malicious actors to create new user accounts without proper authorization.

Exploitation of this flaw could allow an attacker to create multiple low-privileged user accounts, gaining unauthorized access to the system. Additionally, continuous exploitation could lead to system resource exhaustion through mass user creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7096 | Privilege Escalation in Multiple WSO2 Products via SOAP Admin Service Due to Business Logic Flaw</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7096</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in multiple [Vendor Name] products due to a business logic flaw in SOAP admin services. A malicious actor can create a new user with elevated permissions only when all of the following conditions are met:
  *  SOAP admin services are accessible to the attacker.
  *  The deployment includes an internally used attribute that is not part of the default WSO2 product configuration.
  *  At least one custom role exists with non-default permissions.
  *  The attacker has knowledge of the custom role and the internal attribute used in the deployment.


Exploiting this vulnerability allows malicious actors to assign higher privileges to self-registered users, bypassing intended access control mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1792 | Improper Access Control in Mattermost Channel Member API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1792</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fail to properly enforce access controls for guest users accessing channel member information, allowing authenticated guest users to view metadata about members of public channels via the channel members API endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2571 | Google OAuth Authentication Bypass for Converted Bot Accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2571</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fail to clear Google OAuth credentials when converting user accounts to bot accounts, allowing attackers to gain unauthorized access to bot accounts via the Google OAuth signup flow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3230 | Bypass of System Admin User Deactivation Controls for Personal Access Tokens in Mattermost Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3230</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fails to properly invalidate personal access tokens upon user deactivation, allowing deactivated users to maintain full system access by exploiting access token validation flaws via continued usage of previously issued tokens.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3611 | Improper Access Control in Mattermost allows System Managers to view team details despite role restrictions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3611</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fails to properly enforce access control restrictions for System Manager roles, allowing authenticated users with System Manager privileges to view team details they should not have access to via direct API requests to team endpoints, even when explicitly configured with 'No access' to Teams in the System Console.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0602 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Compare in Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0602</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Compare in Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4983 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting City Referential in City Referential Manager on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4983</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting City Referential  in City Referential Manager on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4984 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting City Discover in City Referential Manager on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4984</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting City Discover in City Referential Manager on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4985 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Risk Management in Project Portfolio Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4985</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Risk Management in Project Portfolio Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4986 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Model Definition in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4986</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Model Definition in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4988 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Results Analytics in Multidisciplinary Optimization Engineer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4988</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Results Analytics in Multidisciplinary Optimization Engineer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4989 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4989</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Requirements in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4990 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Change Governance in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4990</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Change Governance in Product Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4991 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Markup in Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4991</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3D Markup in Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4992 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in Service Process Engineer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4992</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Service Items Management in Service Process Engineer from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2024x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48331 | WordPress WooCommerce Orders &amp;amp; Customers Exporter &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48331</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Vanquish WooCommerce Orders &amp; Customers Exporter allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WooCommerce Orders &amp; Customers Exporter: from n/a through 5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4598 | Systemd-coredump: race condition that allows a local attacker to crash a suid program and gain read access to the resulting core dump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4598</link><description>A vulnerability was found in systemd-coredump. This flaw allows an attacker to force a SUID process to crash and replace it with a non-SUID binary to access the original's privileged process coredump, allowing the attacker to read sensitive data, such as /etc/shadow content, loaded by the original process.

A SUID binary or process has a special type of permission, which allows the process to run with the file owner's permissions, regardless of the user executing the binary. This allows the process to access more restricted data than unprivileged users or processes would be able to. An attacker can leverage this flaw by forcing a SUID process to crash and force the Linux kernel to recycle the process PID before systemd-coredump can analyze the /proc/pid/auxv file. If the attacker wins the race condition, they gain access to the original's SUID process coredump file. They can read sensitive content loaded into memory by the original binary, affecting data confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1484 | A vulnerability exists in the media upload component of the Asset 
Suite versions listed below. If successfully exploited an attacker 
could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1484</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the media upload component of the Asset 
Suite versions listed below. If successfully exploited an attacker 
could impact the confidentiality or integrity of the system. An attacker can use this vulnerability to construct a request that will 
cause JavaScript code supplied by the attacker to execute within 
the user’s browser in the context of that user’s session with the 
application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2500 | A vulnerability exists in the SOAP Web services of the Asset 
Suite versions listed below. If successfully exploited, an attacker 
could gai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2500</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the SOAP Web services of the Asset 
Suite versions listed below. If successfully exploited, an attacker 
could gain unauthorized access to the product and the time window of a possible password attack could be expanded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40909 | Perl threads have a working directory race condition where file operations may target unintended paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40909</link><description>Perl threads have a working directory race condition where file operations may target unintended paths.

If a directory handle is open at thread creation, the process-wide current working directory is temporarily changed in order to clone that handle for the new thread, which is visible from any third (or more) thread already running. 

This may lead to unintended operations such as loading code or accessing files from unexpected locations, which a local attacker may be able to exploit.

The bug was introduced in commit 11a11ecf4bea72b17d250cfb43c897be1341861e and released in Perl version 5.13.6</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4433 | Improper access control in user group management in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a non-administrative user with both "Us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4433</link><description>Improper access control in user group management in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a non-administrative user with both "User Management" and "User Group Management" permissions to perform privilege escalation by adding users to groups with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 12:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4597 | Woo Slider Pro - Drag Drop Slider Builder For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4597</link><description>The Woo Slider Pro – Drag Drop Slider Builder For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the woo_slide_pro_delete_draft_preview AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4944 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Compare and Google Maps Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4944</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Compare and Google Maps widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5190 | Browse As &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Authentication Bypass via Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5190</link><description>The Browse As plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to incorrect authentication checking in the 'IS_BA_Browse_As::notice' function with the 'is_ba_original_user_COOKIEHASH' cookie value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1763 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1763</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE that allows for cross-site-scripting attack and content security policy bypass in a user's browser under specific conditions, affecting all versions from 16.6 before 17.9.7, 17.10 before 17.10.5, and 17.11 before 17.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5142 | Simple Page Access Restriction &amp;lt;= 1.0.31 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via Multiple Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5142</link><description>The Simple Page Access Restriction plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.31. This is due to missing nonce validation and capability checks in the settings save handler in the settings.php script. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to (1) enable or disable access protection on all post types or taxonomies, (2) force every new page/post to be public or private, regardless of meta-box settings, (3) cause a silent wipe of all plugin data when it’s later removed, or (4) to conduct URL redirection attacks via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5235 | OpenSheetMusicDisplay &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via className Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5235</link><description>The OpenSheetMusicDisplay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘className’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48334 | WordPress Woo Slider Pro &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Arbitrary Content Deletion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48334</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BinaryCarpenter Woo Slider Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Woo Slider Pro: from n/a through 1.12. Affected action "woo_slide_pro_delete_slider".</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48912 | Apache Superset: Improper authorization bypass on row level security via SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48912</link><description>An authenticated malicious actor using specially crafted requests could bypass row level security configuration by injecting SQL into 'sqlExpression' fields. This allowed the execution of sub-queries to evade parsing defenses ultimately granting unauthorized access to data.

This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.1.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.1.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4636 | Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4636</link><description>Due to excessive privileges granted to the web user running the airpointer web platform, a malicious actor that gains control of the this user would be able to privilege escalate to the root user</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4633 | Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4633</link><description>Default credentials were present in the web portal for Airpointer 2.4.107-2, allowing an unauthenticated malicious actor to log in via the web portal</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4634 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4634</link><description>The web portal on airpointer 2.4.107-2 was vulnerable local file inclusion. A malicious user with administrative privileges in the web portal would be able to manipulate requests to view files on the filesystem</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4635 | Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4635</link><description>A malicious user with administrative privileges in the web portal would be able to manipulate the Diagnostics module to obtain remote code execution on the local device as a low privileged user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4431 | Featured Image Plus &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Featured Image Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4431</link><description>The Featured Image Plus – Quick &amp; Bulk Edit with Unsplash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the fip_save_attach_featured function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update featured image of any post.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5236 | NinjaTeam Chat for Telegram &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via username Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5236</link><description>The NinjaTeam Chat for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘username’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:30:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4943 | LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data-lakit-element-link Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4943</link><description>The LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘data-lakit-element-link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41385 | An OS Command Injection issue exists in wivia 5 all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41385</link><description>An OS Command Injection issue exists in wivia 5 all versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a logged-in administrative user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41406 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in wivia 5 all versions. If exploited, when a user connects to the affected device with a specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41406</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in wivia 5 all versions. If exploited, when a user connects to the affected device with a specific operation, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the moderator user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47697 | Client-side enforcement of server-side security issue exists in wivia 5 all versions. If exploited, an unauthenticated attacker may bypass a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47697</link><description>Client-side enforcement of server-side security issue exists in wivia 5 all versions. If exploited, an unauthenticated attacker may bypass authentication and operate the affected device as the moderator user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48488 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48488</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, deleting the file .htaccess allows an attacker to upload an HTML file containing malicious JavaScript code to the server, which can result in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48875 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48875</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.181, the system's incorrect validation of last_name and first_name during profile data updates allows for the injection of arbitrary JavaScript code, which will be executed in a flesh-message when the data is deleted, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.181.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48880 | FreeScout has Race Condition When Deleting Users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48880</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.181, when an administrative account is a deleting a user, there is the the possibility of a race condition occurring. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.181.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48936 | ZITADEL Allows Account Takeover via Malicious X-Forwarded-Proto Header Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48936</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. Prior to versions 2.70.12, 2.71.10, and 3.2.2, a potential vulnerability exists in the password reset mechanism. ZITADEL utilizes the Forwarded or X-Forwarded-Host header from incoming requests to construct the URL for the password reset confirmation link. This link, containing a secret code, is then emailed to the user. If an attacker can manipulate these headers (e.g., via host header injection), they could cause ZITADEL to generate a password reset link pointing to a malicious domain controlled by the attacker. If the user clicks this manipulated link in the email, the secret reset code embedded in the URL can be captured by the attacker. This captured code could then be used to reset the user's password and gain unauthorized access to their account. This specific attack vector is mitigated for accounts that have Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) or Passwordless authentication enabled. This issue has been patched in versions 2.70.12, 2.71.10, and 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48485 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48485</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks due to incorrect input validation and sanitization of user-input data when an authenticated user updates the profile of an arbitrary customer. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48486 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48486</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the cross-site scripiting (XSS) vulnerability is caused by the lack of input validation and sanitization in both \Session::flash and __, allowing user input to be executed without proper filtering. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48487 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48487</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, when creating a translation of a phrase that appears in a flash-message after a completed action, it is possible to inject a payload to exploit XSS vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48489 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48489</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks due to insufficient data validation and sanitization during data reception. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48492 | GetSimple CMS RCE in Edit component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48492</link><description>GetSimple CMS is a content management system. In versions starting from 3.3.16 to 3.3.21, an authenticated user with access to the Edit component can inject arbitrary PHP into a component file and execute it via a crafted query string, resulting in Remote Code Execution (RCE). This issue is set to be patched in version 3.3.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48865 | Fabio allows HTTP clients to manipulate custom headers it adds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48865</link><description>Fabio is an HTTP(S) and TCP router for deploying applications managed by consul. Prior to version 1.6.6, Fabio allows clients to remove X-Forwarded headers (except X-Forwarded-For) due to a vulnerability in how it processes hop-by-hop headers. Fabio adds HTTP headers like X-Forwarded-Host and X-Forwarded-Port when routing requests to backend applications. Since the receiving application should trust these headers, allowing HTTP clients to remove or modify them creates potential security vulnerabilities. Some of these custom headers can be removed and, in certain cases, manipulated. The attack relies on the behavior that headers can be defined as hop-by-hop via the HTTP Connection header. This issue has been patched in version 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48889 | Gradio Allows Unauthorized File Copy via Path Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48889</link><description>Gradio is an open-source Python package that allows quick building of demos and web application for machine learning models, API, or any arbitrary Python function. Prior to version 5.31.0, an arbitrary file copy vulnerability in Gradio's flagging feature allows unauthenticated attackers to copy any readable file from the server's filesystem. While attackers can't read these copied files, they can cause DoS by copying large files (like /dev/urandom) to fill disk space. This issue has been patched in version 5.31.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41235 | CVE-2025-41235: Spring Cloud Gateway Server Forwards Headers from Untrusted Proxies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41235</link><description>Spring Cloud Gateway Server forwards the X-Forwarded-For and Forwarded headers from untrusted proxies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4429 | WordPress Gearside Developer Dashboard &amp;lt;= 1.0.72 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4429</link><description>The Gearside Developer Dashboard WordPress plugin through 1.0.72 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 06:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48490 | Laravel Rest Api has a Search Validation Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48490</link><description>Laravel Rest Api is an API generator. Prior to version 2.13.0, a validation bypass vulnerability was discovered where multiple validations defined for the same attribute could be silently overridden. Due to how the framework merged validation rules across multiple contexts (such as index, store, and update actions), malicious actors could exploit this behavior by crafting requests that bypass expected validation rules, potentially injecting unexpected or dangerous parameters into the application. This could lead to unauthorized data being accepted or processed by the API, depending on the context in which the validation was bypassed. This issue has been patched in version 2.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48881 | Valtimo backend libraries allows objects in the object-api to be accessed and modified by unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48881</link><description>Valtimo is a platform for Business Process Automation. In versions starting from 11.0.0.RELEASE to 11.3.3.RELEASE and 12.0.0.RELEASE to 12.12.0.RELEASE, all objects for which an object-management configuration exists can be listed, viewed, edited, created or deleted by unauthorised users. If object-urls are exposed via other channels, the contents of these objects can be viewed independent of object-management configurations. At time of publication, no known patches exist.  A workaround for this issue involves overriding the endpoint security as defined in ObjectenApiHttpSecurityConfigurer and ObjectManagementHttpSecurityConfigurer. Depending on the implementation, this could result in loss of functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4659 | Integration for Salesforce and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable, Ninja Forms &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Unauthenticated Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4659</link><description>The Integration for Salesforce and Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable, Ninja Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5259 | Minimal Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5259</link><description>The Minimal Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48483 | FreeScout Stored XSS leads to CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48483</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks due to incorrect input validation and sanitization of user-input data during mail signature sanitization. An attacker can inject arbitrary HTML code, including JavaScript scripts, into the page processed by the user's browser, allowing them to steal sensitive data, hijack user sessions, or conduct other malicious activities. Additionally, if an administrator accesses one of these emails with a modified signature, it could result in a subsequent Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48484 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48484</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, the application is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks due to incorrect input validation and sanitization of user-input data in the conversation POST data body. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 05:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48476 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48476</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, when adding and editing user records using the fill() method, there is no check for the absence of the password field in the data coming from the user, which leads to a mass-assignment vulnerability. As a result, a user with the right to edit other users of the system can change their password, and then log in to the system using the set password. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48477 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48477</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application's logic requires the user to perform a correct sequence of actions to implement a functional capability, but the application allows access to the functional capability without correctly completing one or more actions in the sequence. The leaves the attributes of Mailbox object able to be changed by the fill method. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48478 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48478</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, insufficient input validation during user creation has resulted in a mass assignment vulnerability, allowing an attacker to manipulate all fields of the object, which are enumerated in the $fillable array (the User object), when creating a new user. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48479 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48479</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the laravel-translation-manager package does not correctly validate user input, enabling the deletion of any directory, given sufficient access rights. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48480 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48480</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, an authorized user with the administrator role or with the privilege User::PERM_EDIT_USERS can create a user, specifying the path to the user's avatar ../.htaccess during creation, and then delete the user's avatar, resulting in the deletion of the file .htaccess in the folder /storage/app/public. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48481 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48481</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, an attacker with an unactivated email invitation containing invite_hash, can exploit this vulnerability to self-activate their account, despite it being blocked or deleted, by leveraging the invitation link from the email to gain initial access to the account. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48482 | FreeScout Has Business Logic Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48482</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, there is a mass assignment vulnerability. The Customer object is updated using the fill() method, which processes fields such as channel and channel_id. However, the fill() method is called with all client-provided data, including unexpected values for channel and channel_id, leading to a mass assignment vulnerability. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48068 | Information exposure in Next.js dev server due to lack of origin verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48068</link><description>Next.js is a React framework for building full-stack web applications. In versions starting from 13.0 to before 15.2.2, Next.js may have allowed limited source code exposure when the dev server was running with the App Router enabled. The vulnerability only affects local development environments and requires the user to visit a malicious webpage while npm run dev is active. This issue has been patched in version 15.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48381 | CVAT has information disclosure via browsable API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48381</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions starting from 2.4.0 to before 2.38.0, an authenticated CVAT user may be able to retrieve the IDs and names of all tasks, projects, labels, and the IDs of all jobs and quality reports on the CVAT instance. In addition, if the instance contains many resources of a particular type, retrieving this information may tie up system resources, denying access to legitimate users. This issue has been patched in version 2.38.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48491 | Project AI API Key Exposure in Source Code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48491</link><description>Project AI is a platform designed to create AI agents. Prior to the pre-beta version, a hardcoded API key was present in the source code. This issue has been patched in the pre-beta version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47952 | Traefik allows path traversal using url encoding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47952</link><description>Traefik (pronounced traffic) is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. Prior to versions 2.11.25 and 3.4.1, there is a potential vulnerability in Traefik managing the requests using a PathPrefix, Path or PathRegex matcher. When Traefik is configured to route the requests to a backend using a matcher based on the path, if the URL contains a URL encoded string in its path, it’s possible to target a backend, exposed using another router, by-passing the middlewares chain. This issue has been patched in versions 2.11.25 and 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44904 | hdf5 v1.14.6 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the H5VM_memcpyvv function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44904</link><description>hdf5 v1.14.6 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the H5VM_memcpyvv function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44905 | hdf5 v1.14.6 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the H5Z__filter_scaleoffset function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44905</link><description>hdf5 v1.14.6 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the H5Z__filter_scaleoffset function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44906 | jhead v3.08 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the ProcessFile function at jhead.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44906</link><description>jhead v3.08 was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the ProcessFile function at jhead.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 03:35:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44612 | Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to transmit sensitive information in plaintext, including control information and device cre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44612</link><description>Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to transmit sensitive information in plaintext, including control information and device credentials, allowing attackers to possibly intercept and access sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44614 | Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to store users' sensitive information, including credentials and mobile phone numbers, in pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44614</link><description>Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to store users' sensitive information, including credentials and mobile phone numbers, in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44619 | Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to be configured to transmit on an open Wi-Fi network, allowing attackers to join the networ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44619</link><description>Tinxy WiFi Lock Controller v1 RF was discovered to be configured to transmit on an open Wi-Fi network, allowing attackers to join the network without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48757 | An insufficient database Row-Level Security policy in Lovable through 2025-04-15 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to read or write to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48757</link><description>An insufficient database Row-Level Security policy in Lovable through 2025-04-15 allows remote unauthenticated attackers to read or write to arbitrary database tables of generated sites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12224 | idna accepts Punycode labels that do not produce any non-ASCII when decoded</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12224</link><description>Improper Validation of Unsafe Equivalence in punycode by the idna crate from Servo rust-url allows an attacker to create a punycode hostname that one part of a system might treat as distinct while another part of that system would treat as equivalent to another hostname.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36846 | IO::Compress::Brotli versions prior to 0.007 for Perl have an integer overflow in the bundled Brotli C library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36846</link><description>A buffer overflow, as described in CVE-2020-8927, exists in the embedded Brotli library.  Versions of IO::Compress::Brotli prior to 0.007 included a version of the brotli library prior to version 1.0.8, where an attacker controlling the input length of a "one-shot" decompression request to a script can trigger a crash, which happens when copying over chunks of data larger than 2 GiB. It is recommended to update your IO::Compress::Brotli module to 0.007 or later. If one cannot update, we recommend to use the "streaming" API as opposed to the "one-shot" API, and impose chunk size limits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 01:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1907 | Instantel Micromate Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1907</link><description>Instantel Micromate lacks authentication on a configuration port which could allow an attacker to execute commands if connected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41438 | Consilium Safety CS5000 Fire Panel Initialization of a Resource with an Insecure Default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41438</link><description>The CS5000 Fire Panel is vulnerable due to a default account that exists
 on the panel. Even though it is possible to change this by SSHing into 
the device, it has remained unchanged on every installed system 
observed. This account is not root but holds high-level permissions that
 could severely impact the device's operation if exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46352 | Consilium Safety CS5000 Fire Panel Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46352</link><description>The CS5000 Fire Panel is vulnerable due to a hard-coded password that 
runs on a VNC server and is visible as a string in the binary 
responsible for running VNC. This password cannot be altered, allowing 
anyone with knowledge of it to gain remote access to the panel. Such 
access could enable an attacker to operate the panel remotely, 
potentially putting the fire panel into a non-functional state and 
causing serious safety issues.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5332 | 1000 Projects Online Notice Board index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Online Notice Board 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5307 | Santesoft Sante DICOM Viewer Pro Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5307</link><description>Santesoft Sante DICOM Viewer Pro contains a memory corruption vulnerability. A local attacker could exploit this issue to potentially disclose information and to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante DICOM Viewer Pro.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5331 | PCMan FTP Server NLST Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5331</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component NLST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 22:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30466 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18.4, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, macO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30466</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in Safari 18.4, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, macOS Sequoia 15.4. A website may be able to bypass Same Origin Policy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31189 | A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31189</link><description>A file quarantine bypass was addressed with additional checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31198 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31198</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5. A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31199 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, macOS Sequoia 15....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31199</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, visionOS 2.4, macOS Sequoia 15.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31231 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4. An app may be able to read sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31231</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4. An app may be able to read sensitive location information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31261 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31261</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31263 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31263</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.4. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31264 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31264</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.5, macOS Sequoia 15.4, macOS Sonoma 14.7.5. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5330 | FreeFloat FTP Server RETR Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5330</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component RETR Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5328 | chshcms mccms Backups.php restore_del path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5328</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chshcms mccms 2.7. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function restore_del of the file /sys/apps/controllers/admin/Backups.php. The manipulation of the argument dirs leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 21:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5327 | chshcms mccms Gf.php index server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5327</link><description>A vulnerability was found in chshcms mccms 2.7. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function index of the file sys/apps/controllers/api/Gf.php. The manipulation of the argument pic leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4967 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4967</link><description>Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and prior allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to bypass the Portal’s SSRF protections.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5326 | zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 verifyToken deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5326</link><description>A vulnerability was found in zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 1.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /adpweb/wechat/verifyToken/. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 20:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54952 | MikroTik RouterOS 6.40.5, the SMB service contains a memory corruption vulnerability. Remote, unauthenticated attackers can exploit this iss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54952</link><description>MikroTik RouterOS 6.40.5, the SMB service contains a memory corruption vulnerability. Remote, unauthenticated attackers can exploit this issue by sending specially crafted packets, triggering a null pointer dereference. This leads to a Remote Denial of Service (DoS), rendering the SMB service unavailable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47933 | Argo CD allows cross-site scripting on repositories page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47933</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. Prior to versions 2.13.8, 2.14.13, and 3.0.4, an attacker can perform arbitrary actions on behalf of the victim via the API. Due to the improper filtering of URL protocols in the repository page, an attacker can achieve cross-site scripting with permission to edit the repository. This issue has been patched in versions 2.13.8, 2.14.13, and 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5325 | zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 testService special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5325</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in zhilink 智互联(深圳)科技有限公司 ADP Application Developer Platform 应用开发者平台 1.0.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /adpweb/a/ica/api/service/rfa/testService. The manipulation leads to improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47288 | Discourse Policy plugin private group members visible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47288</link><description>Discourse Policy plugin gives the ability to confirm users have seen or done something. Prior to version 0.1.1, if there was a policy posted to a public topic that was tied to a private group then the group members could be shown to non-group members. This issue has been patched in version 0.1.1. A workaround involves moving any policy topics with private groups to restricted categories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49350 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49350</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2518 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2518</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 

is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3050 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3050</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.1 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service when using Q replication due to the improper allocation of CPU resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46701 | Apache Tomcat: Security constraint bypass for CGI scripts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46701</link><description>Improper Handling of Case Sensitivity vulnerability in Apache Tomcat's GCI servlet allows security constraint bypass of security constraints that apply to the pathInfo component of a URI mapped to the CGI servlet.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.6, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.40, from 9.0.0.M1 through 9.0.104.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.7, 10.1.41 or 9.0.105, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32752 | Dell ThinOS 2502 and prior contain a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with physical acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32752</link><description>Dell ThinOS 2502 and prior contain a Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with physical access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information Disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48336 | WordPress Course Builder &amp;lt; 3.6.6 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48336</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ThimPress Course Builder allows Object Injection.This issue affects Course Builder: from n/a before 3.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5324 | TechPowerUp GPU-Z 0x8000645C IOCTL GPU-Z.sys sub_140001880 memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5324</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in TechPowerUp GPU-Z 2.23.0. Affected is the function sub_140001880 in the library GPU-Z.sys of the component 0x8000645C IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5323 | fossasia open-event-server Mail Verification mail.py send_email_change_user_email reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5323</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in fossasia open-event-server 1.19.1. This issue affects the function send_email_change_user_email of the file /fossasia/open-event-server/blob/development/app/api/helpers/mail.py of the component Mail Verification Handler. The manipulation leads to reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41591 | An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to create fake IP/MAC addresses and potentially execute a man-in-the-middle...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41591</link><description>An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to create fake IP/MAC addresses and potentially execute a man-in-the-middle attack on communications between fake and real hosts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53423 | An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53423</link><description>An issue in Open Network Foundation ONOS v2.7.0 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via supplying crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46823 | OpenMRS has Vulnerability in FHIR2 Module Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46823</link><description>openmrs-module-fhir2 provides the FHIR REST API and related services for OpenMRS, an open medical records system. In versions of the FHIR2 module prior to 2.5.0, privileges were not always correctly checked, which means that unauthorized users may have been able to add or edit data they were not supposed to be able to. All implementers should update to FHIR2 2.5.0 or newer as soon as is feasible to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29632 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Free5gc v.4.0.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the AMF, NGAP, security.go, handl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29632</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Free5gc v.4.0.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the AMF, NGAP, security.go, handler_generated.go, handleInitialUEMessageMain, DecodePlainNasNoIntegrityCheck, GetSecurityHeaderType components</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51392 | An issue in OpenKnowledgeMaps Headstart v7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the url parameter of the getPDF.php component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51392</link><description>An issue in OpenKnowledgeMaps Headstart v7 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the url parameter of the getPDF.php component</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46722 | vLLM has a Weakness in MultiModalHasher Image Hashing Implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46722</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). In versions starting from 0.7.0 to before 0.9.0, in the file vllm/multimodal/hasher.py, the MultiModalHasher class has a security and data integrity issue in its image hashing method. Currently, it serializes PIL.Image.Image objects using only obj.tobytes(), which returns only the raw pixel data, without including metadata such as the image’s shape (width, height, mode). As a result, two images of different sizes (e.g., 30x100 and 100x30) with the same pixel byte sequence could generate the same hash value. This may lead to hash collisions, incorrect cache hits, and even data leakage or security risks. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:58:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46570 | vLLM’s Chunk-Based Prefix Caching Vulnerable to Potential Timing Side-Channel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46570</link><description>vLLM is an inference and serving engine for large language models (LLMs). Prior to version 0.9.0, when a new prompt is processed, if the PageAttention mechanism finds a matching prefix chunk, the prefill process speeds up, which is reflected in the TTFT (Time to First Token). These timing differences caused by matching chunks are significant enough to be recognized and exploited. This issue has been patched in version 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48475 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48475</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the System does not provide a check on which "clients" of the System an authorized user can view and edit, and which ones they cannot. As a result, an authorized user who does not have access to any of the existing mailboxes, as well as to any of the existing conversations, has the ability to view and edit the System's clients. The limitation of client visibility can be implemented by the limit_user_customer_visibility setting, however, in the specified scenarios, there is no check for the presence of this setting. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48474 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48474</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.180, the application incorrectly checks user access rights for conversations. Users with show_only_assigned_conversations enabled can assign themselves to an arbitrary conversation from the mailbox to which they have access, thereby bypassing the restriction on viewing conversations. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.180.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48473 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48473</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, when creating a conversation from a message in another conversation, there is no check to ensure that the user has the ability to view this message. Thus, the user can view arbitrary messages from other mailboxes or from other conversations to which they do not have access (access restriction to conversations is implemented by the show_only_assigned_conversations setting, which is also not checked). This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3913 | Team Privacy Settings Authorization Bypass in Mattermost Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3913</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.7.x &lt;= 10.7.0, 10.6.x &lt;= 10.6.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.3, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.12 fail to properly validate permissions when changing team privacy settings, allowing team administrators without the 'invite user' permission to access and modify team invite IDs via the /api/v4/teams/:teamId/privacy endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45474 | maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-side request forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45474</link><description>maccms10 v2025.1000.4047 is vulnerable to Server-side request forgery (SSRF) in Email Settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48389 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48389</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, FreeScout is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted data due to insufficient validation. Through the set function, a string with a serialized object can be passed, and when getting an option through the get method, deserialization will occur, which will allow arbitrary code execution This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48390 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48390</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, FreeScout is vulnerable to code injection due to insufficient validation of user input in the php_path parameter. The backticks characters are not removed, as well as tabulation is not removed. When checking user input, the file_exists function is also called to check for the presence of such a file (folder) in the file system. A user with the administrator role can create a translation for the language, which will create a folder in the file system. Further in tools.php, the user can specify the path to this folder as php_path, which will lead to the execution of code in backticks. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48471 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48471</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, the application does not check or performs insufficient checking of files uploaded to the application. This allows files to be uploaded with the phtml and phar extensions, which can lead to remote code execution if the Apache web server is used. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48472 | FreeScout Vulnerable to Insufficient Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48472</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.179, there is no check to ensure that the user is disabling notifications for the mailbox to which they already have access. Moreover, the code explicitly implements functionality that if the user does not have access to the mailbox, then after disabling (enabling) notifications for this mailbox, the user will gain access to it. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.179.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48748 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) through v.10.0.7784.0 has a hard-coded password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48748</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) through v.10.0.7784.0 has a hard-coded password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5321 | aimhubio aim run_view Object query.py RestrictedPythonQuery sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5321</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in aimhubio aim up to 3.29.1. This vulnerability affects the function RestrictedPythonQuery of the file /aim/storage/query.py of the component run_view Object Handler. The manipulation of the argument Query leads to sandbox issue. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5334 | Exposure of private personal information to an unauthorized actor in the user vaults component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager
allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5334</link><description>Exposure of private personal information to an unauthorized actor in the user vaults component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager
allows an authenticated user to gain unauthorized access to private personal information. 



Under specific circumstances, entries may be unintentionally moved from user vaults to shared vaults when edited by their owners, making them accessible to other users.




This issue affects the following versions :

  *  Remote Desktop Manager Windows 2025.1.34.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4081 | TCC Bypass via Dylib Substitution in DaVinci Resolve</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4081</link><description>Use of entitlement "com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation" and lack of launch and library load constraints allows to substitute a legitimate dylib with malicious one. A local attacker with unprivileged access can execute the application with altered dynamic library successfully bypassing Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC). Acquired resource access is limited to previously granted permissions by the user. Access to other resources beyond granted-permissions requires user interaction with a system prompt asking for permission.

This issue affects DaVinci Resolve on macOS in all versions.
Last tested version: 19.1.3</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22653 | yasm commit 9defefae was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the yasm_section_bcs_append function at section.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22653</link><description>yasm commit 9defefae was discovered to contain a NULL pointer dereference via the yasm_section_bcs_append function at section.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22654 | tcpreplay v4.4.4 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the tcprewrite function at get.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22654</link><description>tcpreplay v4.4.4 was discovered to contain an infinite loop via the tcprewrite function at get.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33043 | SMM buffer Integrity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33043</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause an Improper Input Validation locally. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability can potentially impact of integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46080 | HuoCMS V3.5.1 has a File Upload Vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this flaw to bypass whitelist restrictions and craft malicious files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46080</link><description>HuoCMS V3.5.1 has a File Upload Vulnerability. An attacker can exploit this flaw to bypass whitelist restrictions and craft malicious files with specific suffixes, thereby gaining control of the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46078 | HuoCMS V3.5.1 and before is vulnerable to file upload, which allows attackers to take control of the target server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46078</link><description>HuoCMS V3.5.1 and before is vulnerable to file upload, which allows attackers to take control of the target server</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5320 | gradio-app gradio CORS is_valid_origin origin validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5320</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in gradio-app gradio up to 5.29.1. This affects the function is_valid_origin of the component CORS Handler. The manipulation of the argument localhost_aliases leads to origin validation error. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37993 | can: m_can: m_can_class_allocate_dev(): initialize spin lock on device probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37993</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: m_can: m_can_class_allocate_dev(): initialize spin lock on device probe

The spin lock tx_handling_spinlock in struct m_can_classdev is not
being initialized. This leads the following spinlock bad magic
complaint from the kernel, eg. when trying to send CAN frames with
cansend from can-utils:

| BUG: spinlock bad magic on CPU#0, cansend/95
|  lock: 0xff60000002ec1010, .magic: 00000000, .owner: /-1, .owner_cpu: 0
| CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 95 Comm: cansend Not tainted 6.15.0-rc3-00032-ga79be02bba5c #5 NONE
| Hardware name: MachineWare SIM-V (DT)
| Call Trace:
| [] dump_backtrace+0x1c/0x24
| [] show_stack+0x28/0x34
| [] dump_stack_lvl+0x4a/0x68
| [] dump_stack+0x14/0x1c
| [] spin_dump+0x62/0x6e
| [] do_raw_spin_lock+0xd0/0x142
| [] _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x20/0x2c
| [] m_can_start_xmit+0x90/0x34a
| [] dev_hard_start_xmit+0xa6/0xee
| [] sch_direct_xmit+0x114/0x292
| [] __dev_queue_xmit+0x3b0/0xaa8
| [] can_send+0xc6/0x242
| [] raw_sendmsg+0x1a8/0x36c
| [] sock_write_iter+0x9a/0xee
| [] vfs_write+0x184/0x3a6
| [] ksys_write+0xa0/0xc0
| [] __riscv_sys_write+0x14/0x1c
| [] do_trap_ecall_u+0x168/0x212
| [] handle_exception+0x146/0x152

Initializing the spin lock in m_can_class_allocate_dev solves that
problem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37994 | usb: typec: ucsi: displayport: Fix NULL pointer access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37994</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: typec: ucsi: displayport: Fix NULL pointer access

This patch ensures that the UCSI driver waits for all pending tasks in the
ucsi_displayport_work workqueue to finish executing before proceeding with
the partner removal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37995 | module: ensure that kobject_put() is safe for module type kobjects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37995</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

module: ensure that kobject_put() is safe for module type kobjects

In 'lookup_or_create_module_kobject()', an internal kobject is created
using 'module_ktype'. So call to 'kobject_put()' on error handling
path causes an attempt to use an uninitialized completion pointer in
'module_kobject_release()'. In this scenario, we just want to release
kobject without an extra synchronization required for a regular module
unloading process, so adding an extra check whether 'complete()' is
actually required makes 'kobject_put()' safe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37996 | KVM: arm64: Fix uninitialized memcache pointer in user_mem_abort()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37996</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: arm64: Fix uninitialized memcache pointer in user_mem_abort()

Commit fce886a60207 ("KVM: arm64: Plumb the pKVM MMU in KVM") made the
initialization of the local memcache variable in user_mem_abort()
conditional, leaving a codepath where it is used uninitialized via
kvm_pgtable_stage2_map().

This can fail on any path that requires a stage-2 allocation
without transition via a permission fault or dirty logging.

Fix this by making sure that memcache is always valid.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37997 | netfilter: ipset: fix region locking in hash types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37997</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ipset: fix region locking in hash types

Region locking introduced in v5.6-rc4 contained three macros to handle
the region locks: ahash_bucket_start(), ahash_bucket_end() which gave
back the start and end hash bucket values belonging to a given region
lock and ahash_region() which should give back the region lock belonging
to a given hash bucket. The latter was incorrect which can lead to a
race condition between the garbage collector and adding new elements
when a hash type of set is defined with timeouts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37998 | openvswitch: Fix unsafe attribute parsing in output_userspace()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37998</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

openvswitch: Fix unsafe attribute parsing in output_userspace()

This patch replaces the manual Netlink attribute iteration in
output_userspace() with nla_for_each_nested(), which ensures that only
well-formed attributes are processed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37999 | fs/erofs/fileio: call erofs_onlinefolio_split() after bio_add_folio()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37999</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/erofs/fileio: call erofs_onlinefolio_split() after bio_add_folio()

If bio_add_folio() fails (because it is full),
erofs_fileio_scan_folio() needs to submit the I/O request via
erofs_fileio_rq_submit() and allocate a new I/O request with an empty
`struct bio`.  Then it retries the bio_add_folio() call.

However, at this point, erofs_onlinefolio_split() has already been
called which increments `folio-&gt;private`; the retry will call
erofs_onlinefolio_split() again, but there will never be a matching
erofs_onlinefolio_end() call.  This leaves the folio locked forever
and all waiters will be stuck in folio_wait_bit_common().

This bug has been added by commit ce63cb62d794 ("erofs: support
unencoded inodes for fileio"), but was practically unreachable because
there was room for 256 folios in the `struct bio` - until commit
9f74ae8c9ac9 ("erofs: shorten bvecs[] for file-backed mounts") which
reduced the array capacity to 16 folios.

It was now trivial to trigger the bug by manually invoking readahead
from userspace, e.g.:

 posix_fadvise(fd, 0, st.st_size, POSIX_FADV_WILLNEED);

This should be fixed by invoking erofs_onlinefolio_split() only after
bio_add_folio() has succeeded.  This is safe: asynchronous completions
invoking erofs_onlinefolio_end() will not unlock the folio because
erofs_fileio_scan_folio() is still holding a reference to be released
by erofs_onlinefolio_end() at the end.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48046 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Disclosure of Stored Passwords in Cleartext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48046</link><description>An authenticated user can disclose the cleartext password of a configured SMTP server via an HTTP GET request to the /config.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48047 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48047</link><description>An authenticated user can perform command injection via unsanitized input to the NetFax Server’s ping functionality via the /test.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48045 | MICI Network Co. Ltd. NetFax Server Default Administrator Credentials Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48045</link><description>An unauthenticated HTTP GET request to the /client.php endpoint will disclose the default administrator user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48388 | FreeScout Has Insufficient Protection Against CRLF-injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48388</link><description>FreeScout is a free self-hosted help desk and shared mailbox. Prior to version 1.8.178, the application performs insufficient validation of user-supplied data, which is used as arguments to string formatting functions. As a result, an attacker can pass a string containing special symbols (\r, \n, \t)to the application. This issue has been patched in version 1.8.178.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27151 | redis-check-aof may lead to stack overflow and potential RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27151</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. In versions starting from 7.0.0 to before 8.0.2, a stack-based buffer overflow exists in redis-check-aof due to the use of memcpy with strlen(filepath) when copying a user-supplied file path into a fixed-size stack buffer. This allows an attacker to overflow the stack and potentially achieve code execution. This issue has been patched in version 8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52588 | Strapi allows Server-Side Request Forgery in Webhook function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52588</link><description>Strapi is an open-source content management system. Prior to version 4.25.2, inputting a local domain into the Webhooks URL field leads to the application fetching itself, resulting in a server side request forgery (SSRF). This issue has been patched in version 4.25.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4687 | Account pre-hijacking through invite misuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4687</link><description>In Teltonika Networks Remote Management System (RMS), it is possible to perform account pre-hijacking by misusing the invite functionality. If a victim has a pending invite and registers to the platform directly, they are added to the attackers company without their knowledge. The victims account and their company can then be managed by the attacker.This issue affects RMS: before 5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4670 | Easy Digital Downloads &amp;lt;= 3.3.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via edd_receipt Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4670</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's edd_receipt shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5122 | Map Block Leaflet &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5122</link><description>The Map Block Leaflet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5286 | Bold Builder &amp;lt;= 5.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via additional_settings Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5286</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘additional_settings’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5273 | All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties via the get-markdow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5273</link><description>All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties via the get-markdown-file tool. An attacker can craft a prompt that, once accessed by the MCP host, will allow it to read arbitrary files from the host running the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5276 | All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Markdownify.get() function. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5276</link><description>All versions of the package mcp-markdownify-server are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the Markdownify.get() function. An attacker can craft a prompt that, once accessed by the MCP host, can invoke the webpage-to-markdown, bing-search-to-markdown, and youtube-to-markdown tools to issue requests and read the responses to attacker-controlled URLs, potentially leaking sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 05:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3755 | Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service(DoS) Vulnerability in MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3755</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Index, Position, or Offset in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to read information in the product, to cause a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition in MELSOFT connection, or to stop the operation of the CPU module (causing a DoS condtion on the CPU module), by sending specially crafted packets. The product is needed to reset for recovery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4583 | Smash Balloon Instagram Feed &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `data-plugin` Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4583</link><description>The Smash Balloon Social Photo Feed – Easy Social Feeds Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `data-plugin` attribute in all versions up to, and including, 6.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 04:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27706 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27706</link><description>CVE-2025-27706 is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the management
 console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers 
with system administrator permissions can interfere with another system 
administrator’s use of the management console when the second 
administrator visits the page. Attack complexity is low, there are no 
preexisting attack requirements, privileges required are high and active
 user interaction is required. There is no impact on confidentiality, 
the impact on integrity is low and there is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27703 | Privilege escalation in the management console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27703</link><description>CVE-2025-27703 is a privilege escalation vulnerability in the management
 console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers 
with administrative access to a specific subset of privileged features 
in the console can elevate their permissions to access additional 
features in the console. The attack complexity is low, there are no 
preexisting attack requirements; the privileges required are high, and 
there is no user interaction required. The impact to system 
confidentiality is low, the impact to system integrity is high and the 
impact to system availability is low.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27702 | Permissions bypass in the management console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.54</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27702</link><description>CVE-2025-27702 is a vulnerability in the management console of Absolute 
Secure Access prior to version 13.54. Attackers with administrative 
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of 
permissions can bypass those permissions to improperly modify settings. 
The attack complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack 
requirements; the privileges required are high, and there is no user 
interaction required. There is no impact to system confidentiality or 
availability, impact to system integrity is high.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31500 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an Asset name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31500</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an Asset name.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31501 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an RT permalink.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31501</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via JavaScript injection in an RT permalink.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5256 | Open Redirect vulnerability on user unlock path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5256</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses an Open Redirection vulnerability in Mautic's user unlocking endpoint. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to redirect legitimate users to malicious websites, potentially leading to phishing attacks or the delivery of exploit kits.

Open Redirection via returnUrl Parameter: An Open Redirection vulnerability exists in the /s/action/unlock/user.user/0 endpoint. The returnUrl parameter, intended for post-action redirection, is not properly validated. This allows an attacker to craft a URL that, when clicked by a user, redirects them to an arbitrary external website controlled by the attacker.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to a version that properly validates or sanitizes the returnUrl parameter to ensure that redirects only occur to trusted, internal URLs or explicitly whitelisted domains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30087 | Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 4.4 through 4.4.7 and 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via injection of crafted parameters in a search URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30087</link><description>Best Practical RT (Request Tracker) 4.4 through 4.4.7 and 5.0 through 5.0.7 allows XSS via injection of crafted parameters in a search URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47055 | Segment cloning doesn&amp;#x27;t have a proper permission check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47055</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic related to the segment cloning functionality. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to clone segments without proper authorization checks.

Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) / Missing Authorization: A missing authorization vulnerability exists in the cloneAction of the segment management. This allows an authenticated user to bypass intended permission restrictions and clone segments even if they lack the necessary permissions to create new ones.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to a version that implements proper authorization checks for the cloneAction within the ListController.php. Ensure that users attempting to clone segments possess the appropriate creation permissions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47057 | User name enumeration possible due to response time difference on password reset form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47057</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic related to the "Forget your password" functionality. This vulnerability could be exploited by unauthenticated users to enumerate valid usernames.

User Enumeration via Timing Attack: A user enumeration vulnerability exists in the "Forget your password" functionality. Differences in response times for existing and non-existing users, combined with a lack of request limiting, allow an attacker to determine the existence of usernames through a timing-based attack.

MitigationPlease update to a version that addresses this timing vulnerability, where password reset responses are normalized to respond at the same time regardless of user existence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57336 | Incorrect access control in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS affected v7.x to v7.4.3.599 and v8.x to v8.0.3.79 allows unauthorized attackers to o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57336</link><description>Incorrect access control in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS affected v7.x to v7.4.3.599 and v8.x to v8.0.3.79 allows unauthorized attackers to obtain Administrator account access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57337 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the opcode 500 functionality of M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57337</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the opcode 500 functionality of M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57338 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57338</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in M2Soft CROWNIX Report &amp; ERS v5.x to v5.5.14.1070, v7.x to v7.4.3.960, and v8.x to v8.2.0.345 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1461 | Vuetify XSS through &amp;#x27;eventMoreText&amp;#x27; prop of VCalendar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1461</link><description>Improper neutralization of the value of the 'eventMoreText' property of the 'VCalendar' component in Vuetify allows unsanitized HTML to be inserted into the page. This can lead to a  Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/xss  attack. The vulnerability occurs because the default Vuetify translator will return the translation key as the translation, if it can't find an actual translation.

This issue affects Vuetify versions greater than or equal to 2.0.0 and less than 3.0.0.

Note:
Version 2.x of Vuetify is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://v2.vuetifyjs.com/en/about/eol/ .</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48749 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 inserts Sensitive Information into Sent Da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48749</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 inserts Sensitive Information into Sent Data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32803 | Insecure file permissions can result in confidential information leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32803</link><description>In some cases, Kea log files or lease files may be world-readable.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47748 | Netwrix Directory Manager v.11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 contains a hardcoded password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47748</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager v.11.0.0.0 and before &amp; after v.11.1.25134.03 contains a hardcoded password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48747 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) before and including v.11.0.0.0 and after v.11.1.25134.03 has Incorrect Permission Assi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48747</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) before and including v.11.0.0.0 and after v.11.1.25134.03 has Incorrect Permission Assignment for a Critical Resource.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32801 | Loading a malicious hook library can lead to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32801</link><description>Kea configuration and API directives can be used to load a malicious hook library.  Many common configurations run Kea as root, leave the API entry points unsecured by default, and/or place the control sockets in insecure paths.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32802 | Insecure handling of file paths allows multiple local attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32802</link><description>Kea configuration and API directives can be used to overwrite arbitrary files, subject to permissions granted to Kea.  Many common configurations run Kea as root, leave the API entry points unsecured by default, and/or place the control sockets in insecure paths.
This issue affects Kea versions 2.4.0 through 2.4.1, 2.6.0 through 2.6.2, and 2.7.0 through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48746 | Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v.11.0.0.0 and before, as well as after v.11.1.25134.03 lacks Authentication for a Crit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48746</link><description>Netwrix Directory Manager (formerly Imanami GroupID) v.11.0.0.0 and before, as well as after v.11.1.25134.03 lacks Authentication for a Critical Function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48929 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 implements authentication through a long-lived credential (e.g., not a token with a short expirat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48929</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 implements authentication through a long-lived credential (e.g., not a token with a short expiration time) that can be reused at a later date if discovered by an adversary, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48930 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 stores certain cleartext information in memory, even though memory content may be accessible to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48930</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 stores certain cleartext information in memory, even though memory content may be accessible to an adversary through various avenues, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48931 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on MD5 for password hashing, which opens up various attack possibilities (including rainbo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48931</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on MD5 for password hashing, which opens up various attack possibilities (including rainbow tables) with low computational effort.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48927 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 configures Spring Boot Actuator with an exposed heap dump endpoint at a /heapdump URI, as exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48927</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 configures Spring Boot Actuator with an exposed heap dump endpoint at a /heapdump URI, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48928 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 is based on a JSP application in which the heap content is roughly equivalent to a "core dump" in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48928</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 is based on a JSP application in which the heap content is roughly equivalent to a "core dump" in which a password previously sent over HTTP would be included in this dump, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48925 | The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on the client side (e.g., the TM SGNL app) to do MD5 hashing, and then accepts the hash as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48925</link><description>The TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 relies on the client side (e.g., the TM SGNL app) to do MD5 hashing, and then accepts the hash as the authentication credential, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48926 | The admin panel in the TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 allows attackers to discover usernames, e-mail addresses, passwords, and telep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48926</link><description>The admin panel in the TeleMessage service through 2025-05-05 allows attackers to discover usernames, e-mail addresses, passwords, and telephone numbers, as exploited in the wild in May 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47056 | Mautic does not shield .env files from web traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47056</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic where sensitive .env configuration files may be directly accessible via a web browser. This exposure could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information, including database credentials, API keys, and other critical system configurations.

Sensitive Information Disclosure via .env File Exposure: The .env file, which typically contains environment variables and sensitive application configurations, is directly accessible via a web browser due to missing web server configurations that restrict access to such files. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to view the contents of this file by simply navigating to its URL.

MitigationUpdate Mautic to the latest Mautic version.

By default, Mautic does not use .env files for production data.

For Apache users: Ensure your web server is configured to respect .htaccess files.

For Nginx users: As Nginx does not inherently support .htaccess files, you must manually add a configuration block to your Nginx server configuration to deny access to .env files. Add the following to your Nginx configuration for the Mautic site:

location ~ /\.env {
    deny all;
}





After modifying your Nginx configuration, remember to reload or restart your Nginx service for the changes to take effect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5257 | Predictable Page Indexing Might Lead to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5257</link><description>SummaryThis advisory addresses a security vulnerability in Mautic where unpublished page previews could be accessed by unauthenticated users and potentially indexed by search engines. This could lead to the unintended disclosure of draft content or sensitive information.

Unauthorized Access to Unpublished Page Previews: The page preview functionality for unpublished content, accessible via predictable URLs (e.g., /page/preview/1, /page/preview/2), lacked proper authorization checks. This allowed any unauthenticated user to view content that was not yet intended for public release, and allowed search engines to index these private preview URLs, making the content publicly discoverable.

MitigationMautic has patched this vulnerability by enforcing proper permission checks on preview pages. Users should upgrade to the patched version of Mautic or later.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36572 | Dell PowerStore, version(s) 4.0.0.0, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in the PowerStore image file. A low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36572</link><description>Dell PowerStore, version(s) 4.0.0.0, contain(s) an Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in the PowerStore image file. A low privileged attacker with remote access, with the knowledge of the hard-coded credentials, could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized access based on the hardcoded account's privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45343 | An issue in Tenda W18E v.2.0 v.16.01.0.11 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the editing functionality of the account module i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45343</link><description>An issue in Tenda W18E v.2.0 v.16.01.0.11 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the editing functionality of the account module in the goform/setmodules route.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38341 | IBM Sterling Secure Proxy information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38341</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.0.0.0 through 6.0.3.1, 6.1.0.0 through 6.1.0.0, and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51453 | IBM Sterling Secure Proxy directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51453</link><description>IBM Sterling Secure Proxy 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3357 | IBM Tivoli Monitoring code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3357</link><description>IBM Tivoli Monitoring 6.3.0.7 through 6.3.0.7 Service Pack 19 could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code due to improper validation of an index value of a dynamically allocated array.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45997 | Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v.1.0 has a file upload vulnerability. An attacker can upload a PHP file disguis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45997</link><description>Sourcecodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System v.1.0 has a file upload vulnerability. An attacker can upload a PHP file disguised as an image by modifying the Content-Type header to image/jpg.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4134 | Lack of file validation in Avast Business Antivirus for Linux allows writing untrusted update files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4134</link><description>Lack of file validation in do_update_vps in Avast Business Antivirus for Linux 4.5 on Linux allows local user to spoof or tamper with the update file via an unverified file write.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40651 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Real Easy Store</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40651</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Real Easy Store. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the keyword parameter in /index.php?a=search. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48734 | Apache Commons BeanUtils: PropertyUtilsBean does not suppresses an enum&amp;#x27;s declaredClass property by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48734</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in Apache Commons.



A special BeanIntrospector class was added in version 1.9.2. This can be used to stop attackers from using the declared class property of Java enum objects to get access to the classloader. However this protection was not enabled by default. PropertyUtilsBean (and consequently BeanUtilsBean) now disallows declared class level property access by default.





Releases 1.11.0 and 2.0.0-M2 address a potential security issue when accessing enum properties in an uncontrolled way. If an application using Commons BeanUtils passes property paths from an external source directly to the getProperty() method of PropertyUtilsBean, an attacker can access the enum’s class loader via the “declaredClass” property available on all Java “enum” objects. Accessing the enum’s “declaredClass” allows remote attackers to access the ClassLoader and execute arbitrary code. The same issue exists with PropertyUtilsBean.getNestedProperty().
Starting in versions 1.11.0 and 2.0.0-M2 a special BeanIntrospector suppresses the “declaredClass” property. Note that this new BeanIntrospector is enabled by default, but you can disable it to regain the old behavior; see section 2.5 of the user's guide and the unit tests.

This issue affects Apache Commons BeanUtils 1.x before 1.11.0, and 2.x before 2.0.0-M2.Users of the artifact commons-beanutils:commons-beanutils

 1.x are recommended to upgrade to version 1.11.0, which fixes the issue.


Users of the artifact org.apache.commons:commons-beanutils2

 2.x are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.0-M2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5277 | aws-mcp-server MCP server is vulnerable to command injection. An attacker can craft a prompt that once accessed by the MCP client will run a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5277</link><description>aws-mcp-server MCP server is vulnerable to command injection. An attacker can craft a prompt that once accessed by the MCP client will run arbitrary commands on the host system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4493 | Improper privilege assignment in PAM JIT privilege sets in Devolutions 
Server allows a PAM user to perform PAM JIT 
requests on unauthorize...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4493</link><description>Improper privilege assignment in PAM JIT privilege sets in Devolutions 
Server allows a PAM user to perform PAM JIT 
requests on unauthorized groups by exploiting a user interface issue.


This issue affects the following versions : 

  *  Devolutions Server 2025.1.3.0 through 2025.1.7.0
  *  Devolutions Server 2024.3.15.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5299 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System user_order_customer_update.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user_order_customer_update.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file_cancelled leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5297 | SourceCodester Computer Store System main.c Add stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5297</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Store System 1.0. This issue affects the function Add of the file main.c. The manipulation of the argument laptopcompany/RAM/Processor leads to stack-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5298 | Campcodes Online Hospital Management System betweendates-detailsreports.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5298</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/betweendates-detailsreports.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3864 | Connection pool exhaustion in hackney</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3864</link><description>Hackney fails to properly release HTTP connections to the pool after handling 307 Temporary Redirect responses. Remote attackers can exploit this to exhaust connection pools, causing denial of service in applications using the library.
Fix for this issue has been included in 1.24.0 release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5295 | FreeFloat FTP Server PORT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5295</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PORT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40673 | Missing Authorization in DinoRANK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40673</link><description>A Missing Authorization vulnerability has been found in DinoRANK. This 
vulnerability allows an attacker to access invoices of any user via 
accessing endpoint '/facturas/YYYY-MM/SDRYYMM-XXXXX.pdf' because there 
is no access control. The pdf filename can be obtained via OSINT, 
insecure network traffic or brute force.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1753 | Command Injection in LLama-Index CLI in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1753</link><description>LLama-Index CLI version v0.12.20 contains an OS command injection vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the improper handling of the `--files` argument, which is directly passed into `os.system`. An attacker who controls the content of this argument can inject and execute arbitrary shell commands. This vulnerability can be exploited locally if the attacker has control over the CLI arguments, and remotely if a web application calls the LLama-Index CLI with a user-controlled filename. This issue can lead to arbitrary code execution on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4963 | WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4963</link><description>The WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 09:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5287 | Likes and Dislikes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5287</link><description>The Likes and Dislikes Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27522 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability during verification processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27522</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. This vulnerability is a secondary mining bypass for CVE-2024-26579. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1] 

 https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11732</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27526 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability For URLEncode and backspace bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27526</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. This vulnerability which can lead to JDBC Vulnerability URLEncdoe and backspace bypass. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11747</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27528 | Apache InLong: JDBC Vulnerability for Invisible Character Bypass Leading to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27528</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache InLong.

This issue affects Apache InLong: from 1.13.0 through 2.1.0. 

This
vulnerability allows attackers to bypass the security mechanisms of InLong
JDBC and leads to arbitrary file reading. Users are advised to upgrade to Apache InLong's 2.2.0 or cherry-pick [1] to solve it.

[1]  https://github.com/apache/inlong/pull/11747</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22252 | A missing authentication for critical function in Fortinet FortiProxy versions 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiSwitchManager version 7.2.5, and Fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22252</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function in Fortinet FortiProxy versions 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiSwitchManager version 7.2.5, and FortiOS versions 7.4.4 through 7.4.6 and version 7.6.0 may allow an attacker with knowledge of an existing admin account to access the device as a valid admin via an authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24473 | A exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere in Fortinet FortiClientWindows versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24473</link><description>A exposure of sensitive system information to an unauthorized control sphere in Fortinet FortiClientWindows versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 may allow an unauthorized remote attacker to view application information via navigation to a hosted webpage, if Windows is configured to accept incoming connections to port 8053 (non-default setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46777 | A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46777</link><description>A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiPortal versions 7.4.0, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.9 may allow an authenticated attacker with at least read-only admin permissions to view encrypted secrets via the FortiPortal System Log.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47294 | A integer overflow or wraparound in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47294</link><description>A integer overflow or wraparound in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the csfd daemon via a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 08:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54020 | A missing authorization in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.7 may allow an authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54020</link><description>A missing authorization in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.1, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.7 may allow an authenticated attacker to overwrite global threat feeds via crafted update requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25251 | An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiClient Mac 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25251</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiClient Mac 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via crafted XPC messages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47295 | A buffer over-read in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47295</link><description>A buffer over-read in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, and versions 7.0.0 through 7.0.14 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to crash the FGFM daemon via a specially crafted request, under rare conditions that are outside of the attacker's control.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:56:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5082 | WP Attachments &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via attachment_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5082</link><description>The WP Attachments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attachment_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4009 | Unauthenticated Arbitrary Command Injection in Evertz SVDN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4009</link><description>The Evertz SVDN 3080ipx-10G is a High Bandwidth Ethernet Switching Fabric for Video Application. This device exposes a web management interface on port 80. This web management interface can be used by administrators to control product
features, setup network switching, and register license among other features. The application has been developed in PHP with the webEASY SDK, also named ‘ewb’ by Evertz.

This web interface has two endpoints that are vulnerable to arbitrary command injection and the authentication mechanism has a flaw leading to authentication bypass.

Remote unauthenticated attackers can gain arbitrary command execution with elevated privileges ( root ) on affected devices.

This level of access could lead to serious business impact such as the interruption of media streaming, modification of media being streamed, alteration of closed captions being generated, among others.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 07:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4947 | QUIC certificate check skip with wolfSSL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4947</link><description>libcurl accidentally skips the certificate verification for QUIC connections when connecting to a host specified as an IP address in the URL. Therefore, it does not detect impostors or man-in-the-middle attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5025 | No QUIC certificate pinning with wolfSSL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5025</link><description>libcurl supports *pinning* of the server certificate public key for HTTPS transfers. Due to an omission, this check is not performed when connecting with QUIC for HTTP/3, when the TLS backend is wolfSSL. Documentation says the option works with wolfSSL, failing to specify that it does not for QUIC and HTTP/3. Since pinning makes the transfer succeed if the pin is fine, users could unwittingly connect to an impostor server without noticing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4800 | MasterStudy LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 4.7.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4800</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing file type validation in the stm_lms_add_assignment_attachment function in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 05:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25025 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25025</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25026 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25026</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information due to an incorrect authentication check.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25029 | IBM Security Guardium information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25029</link><description>IBM Security Guardium 12.0 could allow a privileged user to download any file on the system due to improper escaping of input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 02:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>