<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:51:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-24912 | hostapd fails to process crafted RADIUS packets properly. When hostapd authenticates wi-fi devices with RADIUS authentication, an attacker i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24912</link><description>hostapd fails to process crafted RADIUS packets properly. When hostapd authenticates wi-fi devices with RADIUS authentication, an attacker in the position between the hostapd and the RADIUS server may inject crafted RADIUS packets and force RADIUS authentications to fail.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1508 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt;= 2.1.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Content Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1508</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the download_data action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to download all of a site's post content when WooCommerce is installed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2076 | binlayerpress &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2076</link><description>The binlayerpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2077 | Simple Amazon Affiliate &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2077</link><description>The Simple Amazon Affiliate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'msg' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2078 | BlogBuzzTime-for-wp &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2078</link><description>The BlogBuzzTime for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2205 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt;= 4.15.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2205</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance – Cookie Banner, Cookie Consent, Cookie Notice – CCPA, DSGVO, RGPD plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2220 | Odyssey CMS reCAPTCHA odyssey_contact_form.php key management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2220</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Odyssey CMS up to 10.34. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /modules/odyssey_contact_form/odyssey_contact_form.php of the component reCAPTCHA Handler. The manipulation of the argument g-recaptcha-response leads to key management error. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2218 | LoveCards LoveCardsV2 Setting other access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2218</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LoveCards LoveCardsV2 up to 2.3.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/system/other of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2219 | LoveCards LoveCardsV2 image unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LoveCards LoveCardsV2 up to 2.3.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/upload/image. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2216 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System SaveCrash.ashx UploadCrash unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2216</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 1.3. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCrash of the file /crash/log/SaveCrash.ashx. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2217 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System getAdyData.ashx ProcessRequest sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2217</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 1.3. This affects the function ProcessRequest of the file /getAdyData.ashx. The manipulation of the argument showid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2214 | Microweber Settings index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2214</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Microweber 2.0.19. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file userfiles/modules/settings/group/website_group/index.php of the component Settings Handler. The manipulation of the argument group leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 23:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2215 | Doufox s=doudou path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2215</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Doufox up to 0.2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?s=doudou&amp;amp;c=file&amp;amp;a=list. The manipulation of the argument dir leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 23:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2213 | Castlenet CBW383G2N Wireless Menu wlanPrimaryNetwork.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2213</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Castlenet CBW383G2N up to 20250301. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /wlanPrimaryNetwork.asp of the component Wireless Menu. The manipulation of the argument SSID with the input &lt;img /&gt;srconerror=prompt(8)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 23:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2212 | Castlenet CBW383G2N RgSwInfo.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2212</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Castlenet CBW383G2N up to 20250301. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /RgSwInfo.asp. The manipulation of the argument Description with the input &lt;img /&gt;srconerror=prompt(8)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2233 | Samsung SmartThings Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2233</link><description>Samsung SmartThings Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Samsung SmartThings. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Hub Local API service, which listens on TCP port 8766 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25615.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2210 | aitangbao springboot-manager add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sysJob/add. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2211 | aitangbao springboot-manager add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /sysDictDetail/add. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27792 | Opal vulnerable to CSRF protection bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27792</link><description>Opal is OBiBa’s core database application for biobanks or epidemiological studies. Prior to version 5.1.1, the protections against cross-site request forgery (CSRF) were insufficient application-wide. The referrer header is checked, and if it is invalid, the server returns 403. However, the referrer header can be dropped from CSRF requests using ``, effectively bypassing this protection. Version 5.1.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27101 | Broken Access Control in Opal filesystem&amp;#x27;s copy functionality exposes all user data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27101</link><description>Opal is OBiBa’s core database application for biobanks or epidemiological studies. Prior to version 5.1.1, when copying any parent directory to a folder in the /temp/ directory, all files in that parent directory are copied, including files which the user should not have access to. All users of the application are impacted, as this is exploitable by any user to reveal all files in the opal filesystem. This also means that low-privilege users such as DataShield users can retrieve the files of other users. Version 5.1.1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2209 | aitangbao springboot-manager add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2209</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysDict/add. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1707 | Review Schema &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Post Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1707</link><description>The Review Schema plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4 via post meta. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28856 | WordPress W3Counter Free Real-Time Web Stats plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28856</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in dangrossman W3Counter Free Real-Time Web Stats allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects W3Counter Free Real-Time Web Stats: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28857 | WordPress Rankchecker.io Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28857</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in rankchecker Rankchecker.io Integration allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Rankchecker.io Integration: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28859 | WordPress Maintenance Notice plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28859</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CodeVibrant Maintenance Notice allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Maintenance Notice: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28860 | WordPress Google News Editors Picks Feed Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28860</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PPDPurveyor Google News Editors Picks Feed Generator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google News Editors Picks Feed Generator: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28861 | WordPress WP jQuery Persian Datepicker plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28861</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in bhzad WP jQuery Persian Datepicker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP jQuery Persian Datepicker: from n/a through 0.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28862 | WordPress Comment Date and Gravatar remover plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28862</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Venugopal Comment Date and Gravatar remover allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Comment Date and Gravatar remover: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28863 | WordPress Delete Original Image plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28863</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Carlos Minatti Delete Original Image allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Delete Original Image: from n/a through 0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28864 | WordPress Builder for Contact Form 7 by Webconstruct plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28864</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Planet Studio Builder for Contact Form 7 by Webconstruct allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Builder for Contact Form 7 by Webconstruct: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28866 | WordPress Login Logger plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28866</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in smerriman Login Logger allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Login Logger: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28867 | WordPress Frontpage category filter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28867</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in stesvis Frontpage category filter allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Frontpage category filter: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28868 | WordPress ZipList Recipe plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28868</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ZipList ZipList Recipe allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects ZipList Recipe: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28870 | WordPress amoCRM WebForm plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28870</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in amocrm amoCRM WebForm allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects amoCRM WebForm: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28871 | WordPress Block Spam By Math Reloaded plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28871</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jwpegram Block Spam By Math Reloaded allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Block Spam By Math Reloaded: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28872 | WordPress Block Spam By Math Reloaded plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28872</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in jwpegram Block Spam By Math Reloaded allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Block Spam By Math Reloaded: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28874 | WordPress BP Email Assign Templates By shanebp plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28874</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in shanebp BP Email Assign Templates allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects BP Email Assign Templates: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28875 | WordPress BP Email Assign Templates By shanebp plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in shanebp BP Email Assign Templates allows Stored XSS. This issue affects BP Email Assign Templates: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28876 | WordPress Skrill Official plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.65 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28876</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Skrill_Team Skrill Official allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Skrill Official: from n/a through 1.0.65.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28878 | WordPress Awesome Surveys plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28878</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Will Brubaker Awesome Surveys allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Awesome Surveys: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28879 | WordPress Bee Layer Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28879</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aumsrini Bee Layer Slider allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Bee Layer Slider: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28881 | WordPress Mobile Themes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28881</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mg12 Mobile Themes allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Mobile Themes: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28883 | WordPress WP Compare Tables plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28883</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Martin WP Compare Tables allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Compare Tables: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28884 | WordPress WP Bulk Post Duplicator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28884</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rajesh Kumar WP Bulk Post Duplicator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Bulk Post Duplicator: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28886 | WordPress REST API TO MiniProgram plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28886</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in xjb REST API TO MiniProgram allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects REST API TO MiniProgram: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28887 | WordPress  Plugins Last Updated Column plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28887</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Fastmover Plugins Last Updated Column allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Plugins Last Updated Column: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28891 | WordPress price-calc plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28891</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in jazzigor price-calc allows Stored XSS. This issue affects price-calc: from n/a through 0.6.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28892 | WordPress FTP Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28892</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in a2rocklobster FTP Sync allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FTP Sync: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28894 | WordPress List of Posts from each Category plugin for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28894</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in frucomerci List of Posts from each Category plugin for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects List of Posts from each Category plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28895 | WordPress Custom top bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28895</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sumanbiswas013 Custom top bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom top bar: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28896 | WordPress AS English Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28896</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Akshar Soft Solutions AS English Admin allows Phishing. This issue affects AS English Admin: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28897 | WordPress Domain Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28897</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Steveorevo Domain Theme allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Domain Theme: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28900 | WordPress TabGarb Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28900</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in webgarb TabGarb Pro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects TabGarb Pro: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28901 | WordPress Members page only for logged in users plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28901</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Naren Members page only for logged in users allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Members page only for logged in users: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28902 | WordPress  Contact Form 7 Select Box Editor Button plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28902</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Benjamin Pick Contact Form 7 Select Box Editor Button allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Select Box Editor Button: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28905 | WordPress Featured Posts Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28905</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chaser324 Featured Posts Grid allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Featured Posts Grid: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28906 | WordPress Skitter Slideshow plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28906</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Thiago S.F. Skitter Slideshow allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Skitter Slideshow: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28907 | WordPress WP Last Modified plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28907</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rahul Arora WP Last Modified allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Last Modified: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28908 | WordPress pipDisqus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28908</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pipdig pipDisqus allows Stored XSS. This issue affects pipDisqus: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28909 | WordPress  WP No-Bot Question plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28909</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in edwardw WP No-Bot Question allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP No-Bot Question: from n/a through 0.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28910 | WordPress WP Hide Admin Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28910</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ravinder Khurana WP Hide Admin Bar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Hide Admin Bar: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28912 | WordPress Custom Dashboard Page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28912</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Muntasir Rahman Custom Dashboard Page allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Custom Dashboard Page: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28913 | WordPress WP Add Active Class To Menu Item plugin &amp;lt;=1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28913</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Aftab Ali Muni WP Add Active Class To Menu Item allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Add Active Class To Menu Item: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28914 | WordPress wordpress login form to anywhere plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28914</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ajay Sharma wordpress login form to anywhere allows Stored XSS. This issue affects wordpress login form to anywhere: from n/a through 0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28915 | WordPress ThemeEgg ToolKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28915</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Theme Egg ThemeEgg ToolKit allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects ThemeEgg ToolKit: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28918 | WordPress Featured Image Thumbnail Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28918</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in A. Jones Featured Image Thumbnail Grid allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Featured Image Thumbnail Grid: from n/a through 6.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28919 | WordPress Easy Image Display plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shellbot Easy Image Display allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy Image Display: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28920 | WordPress Responsive Google Map plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28920</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jogesh Responsive Google Map allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Responsive Google Map: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28922 | WordPress Go To Top plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28922</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Terence D. Go To Top allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Go To Top: from n/a through 0.0.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28923 | WordPress No Disposable Email plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28923</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in philippe No Disposable Email allows Stored XSS. This issue affects No Disposable Email: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28925 | WordPress  WATI Chat and Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28925</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hieu Nguyen WATI Chat and Notification allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WATI Chat and Notification: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28926 | WordPress Post Read Time plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in popeating Post Read Time allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Post Read Time: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28927 | WordPress Display Template Name plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28927</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in A. Chappard Display Template Name allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Display Template Name: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28929 | WordPress Tabbed Login Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28929</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vivek Marakana Tabbed Login Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tabbed Login Widget: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28930 | WordPress List Mixcloud plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28930</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rodolphe MOULIN List Mixcloud allows Stored XSS. This issue affects List Mixcloud: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28931 | WordPress WordPress Hashtags plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28931</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DevriX Hashtags allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Hashtags: from n/a through 0.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28932 | WordPress Insert Code plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28932</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BCS Website Solutions Insert Code allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Insert Code: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28933 | WordPress MaxA/B plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28933</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in maxfoundry MaxA/B allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MaxA/B: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28936 | WordPress Lunar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28936</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sakurapixel Lunar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Lunar: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28937 | WordPress Lava Ajax Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in lavacode Lava Ajax Search allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Lava Ajax Search: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28938 | WordPress WP Performance Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28938</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bjoern WP Performance Pack allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Performance Pack: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28940 | WordPress Back To Top Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28940</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in arkapravamajumder Back To Top allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Back To Top: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28941 | WordPress SPAM-BYBYE Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28941</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ohtan Spam Byebye allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Spam Byebye: from n/a through 2.2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28943 | WordPress DP ALTerminator - Missing ALT manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28943</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mylo2h2s DP ALTerminator - Missing ALT manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects DP ALTerminator - Missing ALT manager: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0900 | PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0900</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25368.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2012 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2012</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25185.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2013 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2013</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25186.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2014 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2014</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VS files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25235.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2015 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2015</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25236.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2016 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2016</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25238.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2017 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2017</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25240.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2018 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2018</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25245.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2019 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2019</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25252.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2020 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2020</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VC6 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25254.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2021 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2021</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before writing to memory. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25264.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2022 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2022</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt VS File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25276.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2023 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2023</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt LI File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of LI files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25348.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2208 | aitangbao springboot-manager Filename upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2208</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /sysFiles/upload of the component Filename Handler. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21170 | Substance3D - Modeler | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21170</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.15.0 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could result in an application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, leading to a denial-of-service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27173 | Substance3D - Modeler | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27173</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.15.0 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27180 | Substance3D - Modeler | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27180</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.15.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27181 | Substance3D - Modeler | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27181</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.15.0 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2206 | aitangbao springboot-manager permission cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2206</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/permission. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2207 | aitangbao springboot-manager dept cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2207</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in aitangbao springboot-manager 3.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /sys/dept. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23360 | NVIDIA Nemo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a relative path traversal issue by arbitrary file write. A successfu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23360</link><description>NVIDIA Nemo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a relative path traversal issue by arbitrary file write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23242 | NVIDIA Riva contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper access control issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23242</link><description>NVIDIA Riva contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper access control issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23243 | NVIDIA Riva contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper access control issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23243</link><description>NVIDIA Riva contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper access control issue. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25927 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET request...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25927</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25928 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /admin/users/user.form of Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25928</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /admin/users/user.form of Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25929 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /legacyui/quickReportServlet of Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25929</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /legacyui/quickReportServlet of Openmrs 2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of a user's browser via a crafted payload injected into the reportType parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25925 | A stored cross-scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openmrs v2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25925</link><description>A stored cross-scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openmrs v2.4.3 Build 0ff0ed allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the personName.middleName parameter at /openmrs/admin/patients/shortPatientForm.form.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27789 | Inefficient RexExp complexity in generated code with .replace when transpiling named capturing groups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27789</link><description>Babel is a compiler for writing next generation JavaScript. When using versions of Babel prior to 7.26.10 and 8.0.0-alpha.17 to compile regular expression named capturing groups, Babel will generate a polyfill for the `.replace` method that has quadratic complexity on some specific replacement pattern strings (i.e. the second argument passed to `.replace`). Generated code is vulnerable if all the following conditions are true: Using Babel to compile regular expression named capturing groups, using the `.replace` method on a regular expression that contains named capturing groups, and the code using untrusted strings as the second argument of `.replace`. This problem has been fixed in `@babel/helpers` and `@babel/runtime` 7.26.10 and 8.0.0-alpha.17. It's likely that individual users do not directly depend on `@babel/helpers`, and instead depend on `@babel/core` (which itself depends on `@babel/helpers`). Upgrading to `@babel/core` 7.26.10 is not required, but it guarantees use of a new enough `@babel/helpers` version. Note that just updating Babel dependencies is not enough; one will also need to re-compile the code. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27773 | SimpleSAMLphp SAML2 library has incorrect signature verification for HTTP-Redirect binding</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27773</link><description>The SimpleSAMLphp SAML2 library is a PHP library for SAML2 related functionality. Prior to versions 4.17.0 and 5.0.0-alpha.20, there is a signature confusion attack in the HTTPRedirect binding. An attacker with any signed SAMLResponse via the HTTP-Redirect binding can cause the application to accept an unsigned message. Versions 4.17.0 and 5.0.0-alpha.20 contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27591 | A privilege escalation vulnerability existed in the Below service prior to v0.9.0 due to the creation of a world-writable directory at /var/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27591</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability existed in the Below service prior to v0.9.0 due to the creation of a world-writable directory at /var/log/below. This could have allowed local unprivileged users to escalate to root privileges through symlink attacks that manipulate files such as /etc/shadow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24201 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved checks to prevent unauthorized actions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3.2, iOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24201</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved checks to prevent unauthorized actions. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.3.2, iOS 18.3.2 and iPadOS 18.3.2, macOS Sequoia 15.3.2. Maliciously crafted web content may be able to break out of Web Content sandbox. This is a supplementary fix for an attack that was blocked in iOS 17.2. (Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited in an extremely sophisticated attack against specific targeted individuals on versions of iOS before iOS 17.2.).</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24431 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24431</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24448 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24448</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24449 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24449</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27158 | Acrobat Reader | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27158</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27159 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27159</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27160 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27160</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27161 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27161</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27162 | Acrobat Reader | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27162</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27163 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27163</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27164 | Acrobat Reader | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27164</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27167 | Illustrator | Untrusted Search Path (CWE-426)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27167</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by an Untrusted Search Path vulnerability that might allow attackers to execute their own programs, access unauthorized data files, or modify configuration in unexpected ways. If the application uses a search path to locate critical resources such as programs, then an attacker could modify that search path to point to a malicious program, which the targeted application would then execute. The problem extends to any type of critical resource that the application trusts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27168 | Illustrator | Stack-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-121)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27168</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27169 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27169</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27170 | Illustrator | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27170</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.2.1, 28.7.4 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could result in an application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, leading to a denial of service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27174 | Acrobat Reader | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27174</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 24.001.30225, 20.005.30748, 25.001.20428 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24452 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24452</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24453 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24453</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27166 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27166</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27171 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27171</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27175 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27175</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27176 | InDesign Desktop | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27176</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could result in an application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, leading to a denial-of-service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27177 | InDesign Desktop | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27177</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27178 | InDesign Desktop | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27178</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27179 | InDesign Desktop | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27179</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions ID20.1, ID19.5.2 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could result in an application denial-of-service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, leading to a denial-of-service condition. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24439 | Substance3D - Sampler | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24439</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24440 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24440</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24441 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24441</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24442 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24442</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24443 | Substance3D - Sampler | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24443</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24444 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24444</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24445 | Substance3D - Sampler | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24445</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-37787 | The unprivileged administrative interface in ABO.CMS version 5.8 through v.5.9.3 is affected by a SQL Injection vulnerability via a HTTP POS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37787</link><description>The unprivileged administrative interface in ABO.CMS version 5.8 through v.5.9.3 is affected by a SQL Injection vulnerability via a HTTP POST request to the TinyMCE module</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24450 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24450</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 10.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24451 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24451</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 10.1.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25748 | A CSRF vulnerability in the gestione_utenti.php endpoint of HotelDruid 3.0.7 allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions (e.g., modifyi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25748</link><description>A CSRF vulnerability in the gestione_utenti.php endpoint of HotelDruid 3.0.7 allows attackers to perform unauthorized actions (e.g., modifying user passwords) on behalf of authenticated users by exploiting the lack of origin or referrer validation and the absence of CSRF tokens.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25749 | An issue in HotelDruid version 3.0.7 and earlier allows users to set weak passwords due to the lack of enforcement of password strength poli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25749</link><description>An issue in HotelDruid version 3.0.7 and earlier allows users to set weak passwords due to the lack of enforcement of password strength policies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26701 | An issue was discovered in Percona PMM Server (OVA) before 3.0.0-1.ova. The default service account credentials can lead to SSH access, use ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26701</link><description>An issue was discovered in Percona PMM Server (OVA) before 3.0.0-1.ova. The default service account credentials can lead to SSH access, use of Sudo to root, and sensitive data exposure. This is fixed in PMM2 2.42.0-1.ova, 2.43.0-1.ova, 2.43.1-1.ova, 2.43.2-1.ova, and 2.44.0-1.ova and in PMM3 3.0.0-1.ova and later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0150 | Zoom Workplace Apps for iOS - Incorrect Behavior Order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0150</link><description>Incorrect behavior order in some Zoom Workplace Apps for iOS before version 6.3.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0151 | Zoom Apps - Use After Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0151</link><description>Use after free in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27439 | Zoom Apps - Buffer Underflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27439</link><description>Buffer underflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27440 | Zoom Apps - Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27440</link><description>Heap overflow in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0149 | Insufficient verification of data authenticity in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an unprivileged user to conduct a denial of service via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0149</link><description>Insufficient verification of data authenticity in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an unprivileged user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21180 | Windows exFAT File System Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21180</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21199 | Azure Agent Installer for Backup and Site Recovery Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21199</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21247 | MapUrlToZone Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21247</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24035 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24035</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24043 | WinDbg Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24043</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24044 | Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24044</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24045 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24045</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24046 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24046</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24048 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24048</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24049 | Azure Command Line Integration (CLI) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24049</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24050 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24050</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24051 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24051</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24054 | NTLM Hash Disclosure Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24054</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24055 | Windows USB Video Class System Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24055</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24056 | Windows Telephony Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24056</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24057 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24057</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24059 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24059</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24061 | Windows Mark of the Web Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24061</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24064 | Windows  Domain Name Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24064</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24066 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24066</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24067 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24067</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24070 | ASP.NET Core and Visual Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24070</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24071 | Microsoft Windows File Explorer Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24071</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24072 | Microsoft Local Security Authority (LSA) Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24072</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24075 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24075</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24076 | Microsoft Windows Cross Device Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24076</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24077 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24077</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24078 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24078</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24079 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24079</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24080 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24080</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24081 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24081</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24082 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24082</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24083 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24083</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24084 | Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL2) Kernel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24084</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24983 | Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24983</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24984 | Windows NTFS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24984</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24985 | Windows Fast FAT File System Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24985</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24986 | Azure Promptflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24986</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24987 | Windows USB Video Class System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24987</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24988 | Windows USB Video Class System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24988</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24991 | Windows NTFS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24991</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24992 | Windows NTFS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24992</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24993 | Windows NTFS Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24993</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24994 | Microsoft Windows Cross Device Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24994</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24995 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24995</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24996 | NTLM Hash Disclosure Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24996</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24997 | DirectX Graphics Kernel File Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24997</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24998 | Visual Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24998</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25003 | Visual Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25003</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25008 | Windows Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25008</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26627 | Azure Arc Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26627</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26629 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26629</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26630 | Microsoft Access Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26630</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26631 | Visual Studio Code Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26631</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26633 | Microsoft Management Console Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26633</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26645 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26645</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26634 | Windows Core Messaging Elevation of Privileges Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26634</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56338 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56338</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.6 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.3 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9157 | Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in CxUIUSvc service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9157</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** 

A privilege escalation vulnerability in CxUIUSvc64.exe and
CxUIUSvc32.exe of Synaptics audio drivers allows a local authorized
attacker to load a DLL in a privileged process.


Out of an abundance of caution, this CVE ID is being
assigned to better serve our customers and ensure all who are still running
this product understand that the product is End-of-Life and should be removed.
For more information on this, refer to the CVE Record’s reference information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21169 | Substance3D - Designer | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21169</link><description>Substance3D - Designer versions 14.1 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27172 | Substance3D - Designer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27172</link><description>Substance3D - Designer versions 14.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22213 | [20250301] - Core - Malicious file uploads via Media Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22213</link><description>Inadequate checks in the Media Manager allowed users with "edit" privileges to change file extension to arbitrary extension, including .php and other potentially executable extensions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25747 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DigitalDruid HotelDruid v.3.0.7 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25747</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DigitalDruid HotelDruid v.3.0.7 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the ripristina_backup parameter in the crea_backup.php endpoint</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25680 | LSC Smart Connect LSC Indoor PTZ Camera 7.6.32 is contains a RCE vulnerability in the tuya_ipc_direct_connect function of the anyka_ipc proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25680</link><description>LSC Smart Connect LSC Indoor PTZ Camera 7.6.32 is contains a RCE vulnerability in the tuya_ipc_direct_connect function of the anyka_ipc process. The vulnerability allows arbitrary code execution through the Wi-Fi configuration process when a specially crafted QR code is presented to the camera.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27602 | Umbraco Allows a Restricted Editor User to Delete Media Item or Access Unauthorized Content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27602</link><description>Umbraco is a free and open source .NET content management system. In versions of Umbraco's web backoffice program prior to versions 10.8.9 and 13.7.1, via manipulation of backoffice API URLs, it's possible for authenticated backoffice users to retrieve or delete content or media held within folders the editor does not have access to. The issue is patched in versions 10.8.9 and 13.7.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27617 | Pimcore Vulnerable to SQL Injection in getRelationFilterCondition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27617</link><description>Pimcore is an open source data and experience management platform. Prior to version 11.5.4, authenticated users can craft a filter string used to cause a SQL injection. Version 11.5.4 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27601 | Umbraco Allows Improper API Access Control to Low-Privilege Users to Data Type Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27601</link><description>Umbraco is a free and open source .NET content management system. An improper API access control issue has been identified Umbraco's API management package prior to versions 15.2.3 and 14.3.3, allowing low-privilege, authenticated users to create and update data type information that should be restricted to users with access to the settings section. The issue is patched in versions 15.2.3 and 14.3.3. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37933 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiADC GUI version 7.4.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37933</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiADC GUI version 7.4.0, 7.2.0 through 7.2.1	and before 7.1.3 allows an authenticated attacker to perform an XSS attack via crafted HTTP or HTTPs requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40723 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 6.7.0 through 6.7.4 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40723</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 6.7.0 through 6.7.4 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and 6.5.0 through 6.5.1 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 and 6.3.0 through 6.3.3 and 6.2.0 through 6.2.1 and 6.1.0 through 6.1.2 and 5.4.0 and 5.3.0 through 5.3.3 and 5.2.5 through 5.2.8 and 5.2.1 through 5.2.2 and 5.1.0 through 5.1.3 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via api request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42784 | An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least verions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42784</link><description>An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least verions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via HTTP/S crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48790 | A cross site request forgery vulnerability [CWE-352] in Fortinet FortiNDR version 7.4.0, 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 and 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and bef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48790</link><description>A cross site request forgery vulnerability [CWE-352] in Fortinet FortiNDR version 7.4.0, 7.2.0 through 7.2.1 and 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and before 7.0.5 may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized actions via crafted HTTP GET requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32123 | Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager, FortiAnalyzer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32123</link><description>Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager, FortiAnalyzer versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2
7.2.0 through 7.2.5 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.12 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.14 and 6.2.0 through 6.2.12 and 6.0.0 through 6.0.12 and 5.6.0 through 5.6.11 and 5.4.0 through 5.4.7 and 5.2.0 through 5.2.10 and 5.0.0 through 5.0.12 and 4.3.4 through 4.3.8 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33501 | Two improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33501</link><description>Two improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.0 through 7.4.2 and before 7.2.5, FortiManager version 7.4.0 through 7.4.2 and before 7.2.5 and FortiAnalyzer-BigData version 7.4.0 and before 7.2.7 allows a privileged attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45324 | A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability [CWE-134] in FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, version 7.2.0 through 7.2.9, ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45324</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability [CWE-134] in FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, version 7.2.0 through 7.2.9, version 7.0.0 through 7.0.15 and before 6.4.15, FortiProxy version 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, version 7.2.0 through 7.2.12 and before 7.0.19, FortiPAM version 1.4.0 through 1.4.2 and before 1.3.1, FortiSRA version 1.4.0 through 1.4.2 and before 1.3.1 and FortiWeb version 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, version 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 and before 7.0.10 allows a privileged attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted HTTP or HTTPS commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45328 | An incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiSandbox 4.4.0 through 4.4.6 may allow a low priviledged administrator to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45328</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiSandbox 4.4.0 through 4.4.6 may allow a low priviledged administrator to execute elevated CLI commands via the GUI console menu.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46663 | A stack-buffer overflow vulnerability [CWE-121] in Fortinet FortiMail CLI version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1 and before 7.4.3 allows a privileged a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46663</link><description>A stack-buffer overflow vulnerability [CWE-121] in Fortinet FortiMail CLI version 7.6.0 through 7.6.1 and before 7.4.3 allows a privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via specifically crafted CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51320 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51320</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution via the /servlet/gsdm_fsave_htmltmp, /servlet/gsdm_btlk_openfile components</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51321 | In Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4, an improper check on the m_cURL parameter allows an attacker to redirect the victim to an attacker-control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51321</link><description>In Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4, an improper check on the m_cURL parameter allows an attacker to redirect the victim to an attacker-controlled website after the authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51322 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51322</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution via the /jsp/home.jsp, /jsp/gsfr_feditorHTML.jsp, /servlet/SPVisualZoom, /jsp/gsmd_container.jsp components</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52960 | A client-side enforcement of server-side security vulnerability [CWE-602] in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 5.0.0, 4.4.0 through 4.4.6 and be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52960</link><description>A client-side enforcement of server-side security vulnerability [CWE-602] in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 5.0.0, 4.4.0 through 4.4.6 and before 4.2.7 allows an authenticated attacker with at least read-only permission to execute unauthorized commands via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52961 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS Command vulnerability [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 5.0.0, 4.4.0 th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52961</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS Command vulnerability [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 5.0.0, 4.4.0 through 4.4.7, 4.2.0 through 4.2.7 and before 4.0.5 allows an authenticated attacker with at least read-only permission to execute unauthorized commands via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54018 | Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS Command vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in FortiSandbox before 4.4.5 allows a pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54018</link><description>Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS Command vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in FortiSandbox before 4.4.5 allows a privileged attacker to execute unauthorized commands via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54026 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') in Fortinet FortiSandbox Cloud version 23.4, FortiSa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54026</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') in Fortinet FortiSandbox Cloud version 23.4, FortiSandbox at least 4.4.0 through 4.4.6 and 4.2.0 through 4.2.7 and 4.0.0 through 4.0.5 and 3.2.0 through 3.2.4 and 3.1.0 through 3.1.5 and 3.0.0 through 3.0.7 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55590 | Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55590</link><description>Multiple improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiIsolator version 2.4.0 through 2.4.5 allows an authenticated attacker with at least read-only admin permission and CLI access to execute unauthorized code via specifically crafted CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55592 | An incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiSIEM 7.2 all versions, 7.1 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.7 all versions, 6.6 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55592</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiSIEM 7.2 all versions, 7.1 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.7 all versions, 6.6 all versions, 6.5 all versions, 6.4 all versions, 6.3 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.1 all versions, 5.4 all versions, 5.3 all versions, may allow an authenticated attacker to perform unauthorized operations on incidents via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55597 | A improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('path traversal') in Fortinet FortiWeb versions 7.0.0 through 7.6.0 allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55597</link><description>A improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('path traversal') in Fortinet FortiWeb versions 7.0.0 through 7.6.0 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51319 | A local file include vulnerability in the /servlet/Report of Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51319</link><description>A local file include vulnerability in the /servlet/Report of Zucchetti Ad Hoc Infinity 2.4 allows an authenticated attacker to achieve Remote Code Execution by uploading a jsp web/reverse shell through /jsp/zimg_upload.jsp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22454 | Insufficiently restrictive permissions in Ivanti Secure Access Client before 22.7R4 allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22454</link><description>Insufficiently restrictive permissions in Ivanti Secure Access Client before 22.7R4 allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27403 | Ratify Azure authentication providers can leak authentication tokens to non-Azure container registries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27403</link><description>Ratify is a verification engine as a binary executable and on Kubernetes which enables verification of artifact security metadata and admits for deployment only those that comply with policies the user creates. In a Kubernetes environment, Ratify can be configured to authenticate to a private Azure Container Registry (ACR). The Azure workload identity and Azure managed identity authentication providers are configured in this setup. Users that configure a private ACR to be used with the Azure authentication providers may be impacted by a vulnerability that exists in versions prior to 1.2.3 and 1.3.2. Both Azure authentication providers attempt to exchange an Entra ID (EID) token for an ACR refresh token. However, Ratify’s Azure authentication providers did not verify that the target registry is an ACR. This could have led to the EID token being presented to a non-ACR registry during token exchange. EID tokens with ACR access can potentially be extracted and abused if a user workload contains an image reference to a malicious registry. As of versions 1.2.3 and 1.3.2, the Azure workload identity and Azure managed identity authentication providers are updated to add new validation prior to EID token exchange. Validation relies upon registry domain validation against a pre-configured list of well-known ACR endpoints. EID token exchange will be executed only if at least one of the configured well-known domain suffixes (wildcard support included) matches the registry domain of the image reference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12546 | Potential iSCSI R2T PDU Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12546</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a user may cause an Integer Overflow or Wraparound by network means. A successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54084 | SMM Arbitrary Write via TOCTOU Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54084</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause a Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition by local means. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54085 | Redfish Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54085</link><description>AMI’s SPx contains
a vulnerability in the BMC where an Attacker may bypass authentication remotely through the Redfish Host Interface. A successful exploitation
of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of confidentiality, integrity, and/or
availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2196 | MRCMS org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController upload.do upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.2. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file /admin/file/upload.do of the component org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController. The manipulation of the argument path leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22366 | Mennekes smart/premium charges systems, Command injection in firmware upgrade</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22366</link><description>The authenticated firmware update capability of the firmware for Mennekes Smart / Premium Chargingpoints can be abused for command execution because OS command are improperly neutralized when certain fields are passed to the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22367 | Mennekes smart/premium charges systems, Command injection in time setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22367</link><description>The authenticated time setting capability of the firmware for Mennekes Smart / Premium Chargingpoints can be abused for command execution because OS command are improperly neutralized when certain fields are passed to the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22368 | Mennekes smart/premium charges systems, Command injection in sCU firmware update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22368</link><description>The authenticated SCU firmware command of the firmware for Mennekes Smart / Premium Chargingpoints can be abused for command execution because OS commands are improperly neutralized when certain fields are passed to the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22369 | Mennekes smart/premium charges systems, Arbitrary file download using ReadFile endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22369</link><description>The ReadFile endpoint of the firmware for Mennekes Smart / Premium Chargingpoints can be abused to read arbitrary files from the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22370 | Mennekes smart/premium charges systems, SQL Injection in web configuration interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22370</link><description>Many fields for the web configuration interface of the firmware for Mennekes Smart / Premium Chargingpoints can be abused to execute arbitrary SQL commands because the values are insufficiently neutralized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27363 | An out of bounds write exists in FreeType versions 2.13.0 and below when attempting to parse font subglyph structures related to TrueType GX...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27363</link><description>An out of bounds write exists in FreeType versions 2.13.0 and below when attempting to parse font subglyph structures related to TrueType GX and variable font files. The vulnerable code assigns a signed short value to an unsigned long and then adds a static value causing it to wrap around and allocate too small of a heap buffer. The code then writes up to 6 signed long integers out of bounds relative to this buffer. This may result in arbitrary code execution. This vulnerability may have been exploited in the wild.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2194 | MRCMS org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController list.do list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2194</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.2 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function list of the file /admin/file/list.do of the component org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController. The manipulation of the argument path leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2195 | MRCMS org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController rename.do rename cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MRCMS 3.1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function rename of the file /admin/file/rename.do of the component org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController. The manipulation of the argument name/path leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2192 | Stoque Zeev.it Login Page redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2192</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Stoque Zeev.it 4.24. This affects an unknown part of the file /Login?inpLostSession=1 of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument inpRedirectURL leads to open redirect. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2193 | MRCMS org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController delete.do delete path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2193</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in MRCMS 3.1.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function delete of the file /admin/file/delete.do of the component org.marker.mushroom.controller.FileController. The manipulation of the argument path/name leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2191 | Claro A7600-A1 Ping6 Diagnóstico form2pingv6.cgi cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Claro A7600-A1 RNR4-A72T-2x16_v2110403_CLA_32_160817. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /form2pingv6.cgi of the component Ping6 Diagnóstico. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr with the input &lt;img /&gt;srconerror=prompt(8)&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2189 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Tinxy Smart Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2189</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Tinxy smart devices due to storage of credentials in plaintext within the device firmware. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and analyzing the binary data to obtain the plaintext credentials stored on the vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 11:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52285 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.8), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52285</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.8), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V6.4.8). Affected devices expose several MQTT URLs without authentication. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to access sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56181 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Field PG M5 (All versions), SIMATIC IPC BX-21A (All versions &lt; V31.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-32A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56181</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Field PG M5 (All versions), SIMATIC IPC BX-21A (All versions &lt; V31.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-32A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-39A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-59A (All versions &lt; V32.01.04), SIMATIC IPC PX-32A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC PX-39A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC PX-39A PRO (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC RC-543B (All versions), SIMATIC IPC RW-543A (All versions), SIMATIC IPC127E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC227E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC227G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277G PRO (All versions), SIMATIC IPC3000 SMART V3 (All versions), SIMATIC IPC327G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC347G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC377G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC427E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC477E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC477E PRO (All versions), SIMATIC IPC527G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC627E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC647E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC677E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC847E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC ITP1000 (All versions). The affected devices have insufficient protection mechanism for the EFI(Extensible Firmware Interface) variables stored on the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker to alter the secure boot configuration without proper authorization by directly communicate with the flash controller.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56182 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Field PG M5 (All versions), SIMATIC Field PG M6 (All versions &lt; V26.01.12), SIMATIC IPC BX-21...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56182</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Field PG M5 (All versions), SIMATIC Field PG M6 (All versions &lt; V26.01.12), SIMATIC IPC BX-21A (All versions &lt; V31.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-32A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-39A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC BX-59A (All versions &lt; V32.01.04), SIMATIC IPC PX-32A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC PX-39A (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC PX-39A PRO (All versions &lt; V29.01.07), SIMATIC IPC RC-543B (All versions), SIMATIC IPC RW-543A (All versions), SIMATIC IPC127E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC227E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC227G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC277G PRO (All versions), SIMATIC IPC3000 SMART V3 (All versions), SIMATIC IPC327G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC347G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC377G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC427E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC477E (All versions), SIMATIC IPC477E PRO (All versions), SIMATIC IPC527G (All versions), SIMATIC IPC627E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC647E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC677E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC IPC847E (All versions &lt; V25.02.15), SIMATIC ITP1000 (All versions). The affected devices have insufficient protection mechanism for the EFI(Extensible Firmware Interface) variables stored on the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker to disable the BIOS password without proper authorization by directly communicate with the flash controller.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56336 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS S200 (All versions with serial number beginning with SZVS8, SZVS9, SZVS0 or SZVSN and the FS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56336</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINAMICS S200 (All versions with serial number beginning with SZVS8, SZVS9, SZVS0 or SZVSN and the FS number is 02). The affected device contains an unlocked bootloader. This security oversight enables attackers to inject malicious code, or install untrusted firmware. The intrinsic security features designed to protect against data manipulation and unauthorized access are compromised when the bootloader is not secured.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23384 | A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23384</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) EU (6GK6108-4AM00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), RUGGEDCOM RM1224 LTE(4G) NAM (6GK6108-4AM00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M804PB (6GK5804-0AP00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M812-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M816-1 ADSL-Router family (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M826-2 SHDSL-Router (6GK5826-2AB00-2AB2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M874-2 (6GK5874-2AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M874-3 (6GK5874-3AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M874-3 3G-Router (CN) (6GK5874-3AA00-2FA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (6GK5876-3AA02-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M876-3 (ROK) (6GK5876-3AA02-2EA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (6GK5876-4AA10-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (EU) (6GK5876-4AA00-2BA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE M876-4 (NAM) (6GK5876-4AA00-2DA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUB852-1 (A1) (6GK5852-1EA10-1AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUB852-1 (B1) (6GK5852-1EA10-1BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (A1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (B1) (6GK5853-2EA10-2BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM853-1 (EU) (6GK5853-2EA00-2DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (A1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (B1) (6GK5856-2EA10-3BA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (CN) (6GK5856-2EA00-3FA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (EU) (6GK5856-2EA00-3DA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE MUM856-1 (RoW) (6GK5856-2EA00-3AA1) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE S615 EEC LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA01-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE S615 LAN-Router (6GK5615-0AA00-2AA2) (All versions &lt; V8.2.1), SCALANCE SC-600 family (All versions). Affected devices improperly validate usernames during OpenVPN authentication. This could allow an attacker to get partial invalid usernames accepted by the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23396 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23396</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected applications contain an out of bounds write vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted WRL file.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23397 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23397</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23398 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23398</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23399 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23399</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23400 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23400</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23401 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23401</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23402 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23402</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected applications contain a use-after-free vulnerability that could be triggered while parsing specially crafted WRL files.
An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25266 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25266</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected application does not properly restrict access to the file deletion functionality.
This could allow an unauthorized attacker to delete files even when access to the system should be prohibited, resulting in potential data loss or unauthorized modification of system files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25267 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25267</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected application does not properly restrict the scope of files accessible to the simulation model. This could allow an unauthorized attacker to compromise the confidentiality of the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27392 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27392</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitize user input when creating new VXLAN configurations.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27393 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27393</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitize user input when creating new users.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27394 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27394</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly sanitize user input when creating new SNMP users.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27395 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27395</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit the scope of files accessible through and the privileges of the SFTP functionality.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to read and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27396 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27396</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit the elevation of privileges required to perform certain valid functionality.
This could allow an authenticated lowly-privileged remote attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27397 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27397</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly limit user controlled paths to which logs are written and from where they are read.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to read and write arbitrary files in the filesystem, if and only if the malicious path ends with 'log' .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27398 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly neutral...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27398</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE LPE9403 (6GK5998-3GS00-2AC2) (All versions &lt; V4.0). Affected devices do not properly neutralize special characters when interpreting user controlled log paths.
This could allow an authenticated highly-privileged remote attacker to execute a limited set of binaries that are already present on the filesystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27438 | A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27438</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Teamcenter Visualization V14.3 (All versions &lt; V14.3.0.13), Teamcenter Visualization V2312 (All versions &lt; V2312.0009), Teamcenter Visualization V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0007), Teamcenter Visualization V2412 (All versions &lt; V2412.0002), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0021), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0010). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27493 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.9), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27493</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.9), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V6.4.9). Affected devices improperly sanitize user input for specific commands on the telnet command line interface. This could allow an authenticated local administrator to escalate privileges by injecting arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27494 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.9), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27494</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated AC5102 (ACC-G2) (All versions &lt; V6.4.9), SiPass integrated ACC-AP (All versions &lt; V6.4.9). Affected devices improperly sanitize input for the pubkey endpoint of the REST API. This could allow an authenticated remote administrator to escalate privileges by injecting arbitrary commands that are executed with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 09:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27893 | In Archer Platform 6 through 6.14.00202.10024, an authenticated user with record creation privileges can manipulate immutable fields, such a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27893</link><description>In Archer Platform 6 through 6.14.00202.10024, an authenticated user with record creation privileges can manipulate immutable fields, such as the creation date, by intercepting and modifying a Copy request via a GenericContent/Record.aspx?id= URI. This enables unauthorized modification of system-generated metadata, compromising data integrity and potentially impacting auditing, compliance, and security controls.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 08:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28607 | The ip-utils package through 2.4.0 for Node.js might allow SSRF because some IP addresses (such as 0x7f.1) are improperly categorized as glo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28607</link><description>The ip-utils package through 2.4.0 for Node.js might allow SSRF because some IP addresses (such as 0x7f.1) are improperly categorized as globally routable via a falsy isPrivate return value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 08:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1550 | Arbitrary Code Execution via Crafted Keras Config for Model Loading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1550</link><description>The Keras Model.load_model function permits arbitrary code execution, even with safe_mode=True, through a manually constructed, malicious .keras archive. By altering the config.json file within the archive, an attacker can specify arbitrary Python modules and functions, along with their arguments, to be loaded and executed during model loading.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 08:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58102 | An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. An insecure default parsing depth limit allows stack consumption when parsing u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58102</link><description>An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. An insecure default parsing depth limit allows stack consumption when parsing user-supplied queries containing deeply nested expressions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27911 | An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. Expansion of identifiers in message templates can be used to bypass the system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27911</link><description>An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. Expansion of identifiers in message templates can be used to bypass the system "Event body limit bytes" setting, leading to increased resource consumption. With sufficiently large events, there can be disk space exhaustion (if saved to disk) or a termination of the server process with an out-of-memory error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27912 | An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. Missing Content-Type validation can lead to CSRF when (1) Entra ID or OpenID Co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27912</link><description>An issue was discovered in Datalust Seq before 2024.3.13545. Missing Content-Type validation can lead to CSRF when (1) Entra ID or OpenID Connect authentication is in use and a user visits a compromised/malicious site, or (2) when username/password or Active Directory authentication is in use and a user visits a compromised/malicious site under the same effective top-level domain as the Seq server. Exploitation of the vulnerability allows the attacker to conduct impersonation attacks and perform actions in Seq on behalf of the targeted user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2176 | libzvbi io-sim.c vbi_capture_sim_load_caption integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2176</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in libzvbi up to 0.2.43. This affects the function vbi_capture_sim_load_caption of the file src/io-sim.c. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.2.44 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is ca1672134b3e2962cd392212c73f44f8f4cb489f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The code maintainer was informed beforehand about the issues. She reacted very fast and highly professional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2177 | libzvbi search.c vbi_search_new integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2177</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in libzvbi up to 0.2.43. This vulnerability affects the function vbi_search_new of the file src/search.c. The manipulation of the argument pat_len leads to integer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.2.44 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as ca1672134b3e2962cd392212c73f44f8f4cb489f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The code maintainer was informed beforehand about the issues. She reacted very fast and highly professional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1434 | XSS in AREAL SAS Topkapi Vision Webserv2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1434</link><description>The Spreadsheet view is vulnerable to a XSS attack, where a remote unauthorised attacker can read a limited amount of values or DoS the affected spreadsheet. Disclosure of secrets or other system settings is not affected as well as other spreadsheets still work as expected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13228 | Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.8.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via qubely_get_content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13228</link><description>The Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.13 via the 'qubely_get_content'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, scheduled, password-protected, draft, and trashed post data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26702 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26702</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Input Data Manipulation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26703 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26703</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2190 | The mobile application (com.transsnet.store) has a man-in-the-middle attack vulnerability, which may lead to code injection risks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2190</link><description>The mobile application (com.transsnet.store) has a man-in-the-middle attack vulnerability, which may lead to code injection risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26704 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26704</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2175 | libzvbi _vbi_strndup_iconv integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libzvbi up to 0.2.43. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function _vbi_strndup_iconv. The manipulation leads to integer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.2.44 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The code maintainer was informed beforehand about the issues. She reacted very fast and highly professional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26705 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26705</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26706 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26706</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.07.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:52:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2173 | libzvbi conv.c vbi_strndup_iconv_ucs2 uninitialized pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2173</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libzvbi up to 0.2.43. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function vbi_strndup_iconv_ucs2 of the file src/conv.c. The manipulation of the argument src_length leads to uninitialized pointer. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.2.44 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 8def647eea27f7fd7ad33ff79c2d6d3e39948dce. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The code maintainer was informed beforehand about the issues. She reacted very fast and highly professional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2174 | libzvbi conv.c vbi_strndup_iconv_ucs2 integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2174</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libzvbi up to 0.2.43. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function vbi_strndup_iconv_ucs2 of the file src/conv.c. The manipulation of the argument src_length leads to integer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.2.44 is able to address this issue. The patch is named ca1672134b3e2962cd392212c73f44f8f4cb489f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The code maintainer was informed beforehand about the issues. She reacted very fast and highly professional.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13574 | XV Random Quotes &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13574</link><description>The XV Random Quotes WordPress plugin through 1.40 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13580 | XV Random Quotes &amp;lt;= 1.40 - Settings Reset via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13580</link><description>The XV Random Quotes WordPress plugin through 1.40 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin reset them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13615 | Social Media Plugin by Social Snap &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13615</link><description>The Social Share Buttons, Social Sharing Icons, Click to Tweet — Social Media Plugin by Social Snap WordPress plugin through 1.3.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13836 | WP Login Control &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13836</link><description>The WP Login Control WordPress plugin through 2.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13853 | SEO Tools &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13853</link><description>The SEO Tools WordPress plugin through 4.0.7 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13862 | S3Bubble Media Streaming &amp;lt;= 8.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13862</link><description>The S3Bubble Media Streaming (AWS|Elementor|YouTube|Vimeo Functionality) WordPress plugin through 8.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13864 | Countdown Timer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13864</link><description>The Countdown Timer WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0629 | Coronavirus (COVID-19) Notice Message &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0629</link><description>The Coronavirus (COVID-19) Notice Message WordPress plugin through 1.1.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 06:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13413 | ProductDyno &amp;lt;= 1.0.24 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;res&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13413</link><description>The ProductDyno plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘res’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts into pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This vulnerability is potentially a duplicate of CVE-2025-22320.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 04:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13436 | Appsero Helper &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13436</link><description>The Appsero Helper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'appsero_helper' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1661 | HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.3.6.5 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1661</link><description>The HUSKY – Products Filter Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6.5 via the 'template' parameter of the woof_text_search AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26707 | Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26707</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in ZTE GoldenDB allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects GoldenDB: from 6.1.03 through 6.1.03.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2169 | WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional &amp;lt;= 1.2.0.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2169</link><description>The The WPCS – WordPress Currency Switcher Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 03:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11253 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "DNSServer” parameter of the diagnostic function in the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11253</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "DNSServer” parameter of the diagnostic function in the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware version V5.50(ABOM.8.5)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12009 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "ZyEE" function of the Zyxel EX5601-T1 firmware version V5.70(ACDZ.3.6)C0 and e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12009</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the "ZyEE" function of the Zyxel EX5601-T1 firmware version V5.70(ACDZ.3.6)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12010 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the ”zyUtilMailSend” function of the Zyxel AX7501-B1 firmware version V5.17(ABPC.5....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12010</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the ”zyUtilMailSend” function of the Zyxel AX7501-B1 firmware version V5.17(ABPC.5.3)C0 and earlier could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 02:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22340 | IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22340</link><description>IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture 7.0.0 through 7.5.51 



could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information during the creation of ECDSA signatures to perform a timing-based attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41760 | IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41760</link><description>IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture 7.0.0 through 7.5.51 

could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information due to a timing attack during certain RSA operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49823 | IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49823</link><description>IBM Common Cryptographic Architecture 7.0.0 through 7.5.51 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service in the Hardware Security Module (HSM) using a specially crafted sequence of valid requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0062 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0062</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform allows an attacker to inject JavaScript code in Web Intelligence reports. This code is then executed in the victim's browser each time the vulnerable page is visited by the victim. On successful exploitation, an attacker could cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity within the scope of victim�s browser. There is no impact on availability. This vulnerability occurs only when script/html execution is enabled by the administrator in Central Management Console.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0071 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Web Dispatcher and Internet Communication Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0071</link><description>SAP Web Dispatcher and Internet Communication Manager allow an attacker with administrative privileges to enable debugging trace mode with a specific parameter value. This exposes unencrypted passwords in the logs, causing a high impact on the confidentiality of the application. There is no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23185 | Information Disclosure in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23185</link><description>Due to improper error handling in SAP Business Objects Business Intelligence Platform, technical details of the application are revealed in exceptions thrown to the user and in stack traces. Only an attacker with administrator level privileges has access to this disclosed information, and they could use it to craft further exploits. There is no impact on the integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23188 | Missing Authorization check in SAP S/4HANA (RBD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23188</link><description>An authenticated user with low privileges can exploit a missing authorization check in an IBS module of FS-RBD, allowing unauthorized access to perform actions beyond their intended permissions. This causes a low impact on integrity with no impact on confidentiality and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23194 | Missing Authentication check in SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal (OBN component)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23194</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal OBN does not perform proper authentication check for a particular configuration setting. As result, a non-authenticated user can set it to an undesired value causing low impact on integrity. There is no impact on confidentiality or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25242 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25242</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP allows malicious scripts to be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application, but it can have some minor impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25244 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Business Warehouse (Process Chains)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25244</link><description>SAP Business Warehouse (Process Chains) allows an attacker to manipulate the process execution due to missing authorization check. An attacker with display authorization for the process chain object could set one or all processes to be skipped. This means corresponding activities, such as data loading, activation, or deletion, will not be executed as initially modeled. This could lead to unexpected results in business reporting leading to a significant impact on integrity. However, there is no impact on confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25245 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25245</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence) contains a deprecated web application endpoint that is not properly secured. An attacker could take advantage of this by injecting a malicious url in the data returned to the user. On successful exploitation, there could be a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity within the scope of victim�s browser. There is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26655 | Missing Authorization check in SAP JIT(Outbound)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26655</link><description>SAP Just In Time(JIT) does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing attacker to escalate privileges that would otherwise be restricted, potentially causing a low impact on the integrity of the application.Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26656 | Missing Authorization check in S/4HANA (Manage Purchasing Info Records)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26656</link><description>OData Service in Manage Purchasing Info Records does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, allowing an attacker to escalate privileges. This has low impact on integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26658 | Broken Authentication in SAP Business One (Service Layer)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26658</link><description>The Service Layer in SAP Business One, allows attackers to potentially gain unauthorized access and impersonate other users in the application to perform unauthorized actions. Due to the improper session management, the attackers can elevate themselves to higher privilege and can read, modify and/or write new data. To gain authenticated sessions of other users, the attacker must invest considerable time and effort. This vulnerability has a high impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application with no effect on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26659 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP (applications based on SAP GUI for HTML)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26659</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, leading to DOM-basedCross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This allows an attacker with no privileges, to craft a malicious web message that exploits WEBGUI functionality. On successful exploitation, the malicious JavaScript payload executes in the scope of victim�s browser potentially compromising their data and/or manipulating browser content. This leads to a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity. There is no impact on availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26660 | Broken Access Control in SAP Fiori apps (Posting Library)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26660</link><description>SAP Fiori applications using the posting library fail to properly configure security settings during the setup process, leaving them at default or inadequately defined. This vulnerability allows an attacker with low privileges to bypass access controls within the application, enabling them to potentially modify data. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26661 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Class Builder)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26661</link><description>Due to missing authorization check, SAP NetWeaver (ABAP Class Builder) allows an attacker to gain higher access levels than they should have, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, this could result in disclosure of highly sensitive information. It could also have a high impact on the integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27430 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in SAP CRM and SAP S/4 HANA (Interaction Center)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27430</link><description>Under certain conditions, an SSRF vulnerability in SAP CRM and SAP S/4HANA (Interaction Center) allows an attacker with low privileges to access restricted information. This flaw enables the attacker to send requests to internal network resources, thereby compromising the application's confidentiality. There is no impact on integrity or availability</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27431 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27431</link><description>User management functionality in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This could enable an attacker to inject malicious payload that gets stored and executed when a user accesses the functionality, hence leading to information disclosure or unauthorized data modifications within the scope of victim�s browser. There is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27432 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Electronic Invoicing for Brazil (eDocument Cockpit)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27432</link><description>The eDocument Cockpit (Inbound NF-e) in SAP Electronic Invoicing for Brazil allows an authenticated attacker with certain privileges to gain unauthorized access to each transaction. By executing the specific ABAP method within the ABAP system, an unauthorized attacker could call each transaction and view the inbound delivery details. This vulnerability has a low impact on the confidentiality with no effect on the integrity and the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27433 | Broken Access Control vulnerabilities in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Bank Statements)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27433</link><description>The Manage Bank Statements in SAP S/4HANA allows authenticated attacker to bypass certain functionality restrictions of the application and upload files to a reversed bank statement. This vulnerability has a low impact on the application's integrity, with no effect on confidentiality and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27434 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Commerce (Swagger UI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27434</link><description>Due to insufficient input validation, SAP Commerce (Swagger UI) allows an unauthenticated attacker to inject the malicious code from remote sources, which can be leveraged by an attacker to execute a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack. This could lead to a high impact on the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of data in SAP Commerce.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27436 | Broken Access Control vulnerabilities in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Bank Statements)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27436</link><description>The Manage Bank Statements in SAP S/4HANA does not perform required access control checks for an authenticated user to confirm whether a request to interact with a resource is legitimate, allowing the attacker to delete the attachment of a posted bank statement. This leads to a low impact on integrity, with no impact on the confidentiality of the data or the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1828 | Perl&amp;#x27;s Crypt::Random module after 1.05 and before 1.56 may use rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1828</link><description>Crypt::Random Perl package 1.05 through 1.55 may use rand() function, which is not cryptographically strong, for cryptographic functions.

Crypt::Random::rand 1.05 through 1.55 uses the rand() function.  If the Provider is not specified and /dev/urandom or an Entropy Gathering Daemon (egd) service is not available Crypt::Random will default to use the insecure Crypt::Random::rand provider.

In particular, Windows versions of perl will encounter this issue by default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 23:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27924 | Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8 has a stored XSS issue associated with the "Navigate to a URL" action.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27924</link><description>Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8 has a stored XSS issue associated with the "Navigate to a URL" action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27925 | Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8 has insecure deserialization of user input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27925</link><description>Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8 has insecure deserialization of user input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27926 | In Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8, the K2 SmartForms Designer folder has configuration files (web.config) containing passwords tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27926</link><description>In Nintex Automation 5.6 and 5.7 before 5.8, the K2 SmartForms Designer folder has configuration files (web.config) containing passwords that are readable by unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27610 | Local File Inclusion in Rack::Static</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27610</link><description>Rack provides an interface for developing web applications in Ruby. Prior to versions 2.2.13, 3.0.14, and 3.1.12, `Rack::Static` can serve files under the specified `root:` even if `urls:` are provided, which may expose other files under the specified `root:` unexpectedly. The vulnerability occurs because `Rack::Static` does not properly sanitize user-supplied paths before serving files. Specifically, encoded path traversal sequences are not correctly validated, allowing attackers to access files outside the designated static file directory. By exploiting this vulnerability, an attacker can gain access to all files under the specified `root:` directory, provided they are able to determine then path of the file. Versions 2.2.13, 3.0.14, and 3.1.12 contain a patch for the issue. Other mitigations include removing usage of `Rack::Static`, or ensuring that `root:` points at a directory path which only contains files which should be accessed publicly. It is likely that a CDN or similar static file server would also mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 22:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25907 | tianti v2.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /user/ajax/save. This vulnerability allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25907</link><description>tianti v2.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /user/ajax/save. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET or POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25908 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tianti v2.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25908</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tianti v2.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the coverImageURL parameter at /article/ajax/save.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27910 | tianti v2.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /user/ajax/upd/status. This vulnerability allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27910</link><description>tianti v2.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /user/ajax/upd/status. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET or POST request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0660 | Stored XSS in Folder Function by Rogue Admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0660</link><description>Concrete CMS versions 9.0.0 through 9.3.9 are affected by a stored XSS in Folder Function.The "Add Folder" functionality lacks input sanitization, allowing a rogue admin to inject XSS payloads as folder names.  The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability a CVSS 4.0 Score of 4.8 with vector: CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:H/UI:P/VC:L/VI:N/VA:N/SC:L/SI:N/SA:N. Versions below 9 are not affected. Thanks, Alfin Joseph for reporting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56191 | In dhd_process_full_gscan_result of dhd_pno.c, there is a possible EoP due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56191</link><description>In dhd_process_full_gscan_result of dhd_pno.c, there is a possible EoP due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56192 | In wl_notify_gscan_event of wl_cfgscan.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56192</link><description>In wl_notify_gscan_event of wl_cfgscan.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1920 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1920</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2135 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2135</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2136 | Use after free in Inspector in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2136</link><description>Use after free in Inspector in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:50:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2137 | Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2137</link><description>Out of bounds read in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 134.0.6998.88 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:50:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27913 | Passbolt API before 5, if the server is misconfigured (with an incorrect installation process and disregarding of Health Check results), can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27913</link><description>Passbolt API before 5, if the server is misconfigured (with an incorrect installation process and disregarding of Health Check results), can send email messages with a domain name taken from an attacker-controlled HTTP Host header.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43454 | A double free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.1, watchOS 9.2, iOS 16.2 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43454</link><description>A double free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.1, watchOS 9.2, iOS 16.2 and iPadOS 16.2, tvOS 16.2. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48610 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.1, watchOS 9.2, iOS 16.2 and iPadOS 16.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48610</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.1, watchOS 9.2, iOS 16.2 and iPadOS 16.2. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44179 | This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44179</link><description>This issue was addressed by restricting options offered on a locked device. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.7 and iPadOS 17.7, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An attacker with physical access to a device may be able to read contact numbers from the lock screen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44192 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, Safari 18, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44192</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, Safari 18, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44227 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44227</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54463 | This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access removable volumes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54463</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved entitlements. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access removable volumes without user consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54467 | A cookie management issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, Safari 18, visi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54467</link><description>A cookie management issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11, macOS Sequoia 15, Safari 18, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, tvOS 18. A malicious website may exfiltrate data cross-origin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54469 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7, visionOS 2, iO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54469</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7, macOS Sequoia 15, macOS Sonoma 14.7, visionOS 2, iOS 18 and iPadOS 18. A local user may be able to leak sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54473 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54473</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54546 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to cause unexpected syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54546</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination or corrupt kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54558 | A clickjacking issue was addressed with improved out-of-process view handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54558</link><description>A clickjacking issue was addressed with improved out-of-process view handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. An app may be able to trick a user into granting access to photos from the user's photo library.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54560 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. A mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54560</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, macOS Sequoia 15. A malicious app may be able to modify other apps without having App Management permission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27616 | Vela Server has Insufficient Webhook Payload Data Verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27616</link><description>Vela is a Pipeline Automation (CI/CD) framework built on Linux container technology written in Golang. Prior to versions 0.25.3 and 0.26.3, by spoofing a webhook payload with a specific set of headers and body data, an attacker could transfer ownership of a repository and its repo level secrets to a separate repository. These secrets could be exfiltrated by follow up builds to the repository. Users with an enabled repository with access to repo level CI secrets in Vela are vulnerable to the exploit, and any user with access to the CI instance and the linked source control manager can perform the exploit. Versions 0.25.3 and 0.26.3 fix the issue. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27615 | umatiGateway&amp;#x27;s UI publicly accessible in provided docker-compose file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27615</link><description>umatiGateway is software for connecting OPC Unified Architecture servers with an MQTT broker utilizing JSON messages. The user interface may possibly be publicly accessible with umatiGateway's provided docker-compose file. With this access, the configuration can be viewed and altered. Commit 5d81a3412bc0051754a3095d89a06d6d743f2b16 uses `127.0.0.1:8080:8080` to limit access to the local network. For those who are unable to use this proposed patch, a firewall on Port 8080 may block remote access, but the workaround may not be perfect because Docker may also bypass a firewall by its iptable based rules for port forwarding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26695 | When requesting an OpenPGP key from a WKD server, an incorrect padding size was used and a network observer could have learned the length of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26695</link><description>When requesting an OpenPGP key from a WKD server, an incorrect padding size was used and a network observer could have learned the length of the requested email address. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 136 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:48:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26696 | Certain crafted MIME email messages that claimed to contain an encrypted OpenPGP message, which instead contained an OpenPGP signed message,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26696</link><description>Certain crafted MIME email messages that claimed to contain an encrypted OpenPGP message, which instead contained an OpenPGP signed message, were wrongly shown as being encrypted. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 136 and Thunderbird &lt; 128.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27136 | LocalS3 CreateBucketConfiguration Endpoint XML External Entity (XXE) Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27136</link><description>LocalS3 is an Amazon S3 mock service for testing and local development. Prior to version 1.21, the LocalS3 service's bucket creation endpoint is vulnerable to XML External Entity (XXE) injection. When processing the CreateBucketConfiguration XML document during bucket creation, the service's XML parser is configured to resolve external entities. This allows an attacker to declare an external entity that references an internal URL, which the server will then attempt to fetch when parsing the XML. The vulnerability specifically occurs in the location constraint processing, where the XML parser resolves external entities without proper validation or restrictions. When the external entity is resolved, the server makes an HTTP request to the specified URL and includes the response content in the parsed XML document. This vulnerability can be exploited to perform server-side request forgery (SSRF) attacks, allowing an attacker to make requests to internal services or resources that should not be accessible from external networks. The server will include the responses from these internal requests in the resulting bucket configuration, effectively leaking sensitive information. The attacker only needs to be able to send HTTP requests to the LocalS3 service to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56184 | In static long dev_send of tipc_dev_ql, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56184</link><description>In static long dev_send of tipc_dev_ql, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56185 | In ProtocolUnsolOnSSAdapter::GetServiceClass() of protocolcalladapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56185</link><description>In ProtocolUnsolOnSSAdapter::GetServiceClass() of protocolcalladapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56186 | In closeChannel of secureelementimpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56186</link><description>In closeChannel of secureelementimpl.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56187 | In ppcfw_deny_sec_dram_access of ppcfw.c, there is a possible arbitrary read from TEE memory due to a logic error in the code. This could le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56187</link><description>In ppcfw_deny_sec_dram_access of ppcfw.c, there is a possible arbitrary read from TEE memory due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56188 | there is a possible way to crash the modem due to a missing null check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56188</link><description>there is a possible way to crash the modem due to a missing null check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22603 | AutoGPT SSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22603</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. Versions prior to autogpt-platform-beta-v0.4.2 contains a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability inside component (or block) `Send Web Request`. The root cause is  that IPV6 address is not restricted or filtered, which allows attackers to perform a server side request forgery to visit an IPV6 service. autogpt-platform-beta-v0.4.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25306 | Misskey&amp;#x27;s Incomplete Patch of CVE-2024-52591 Leads to Forgery of Federated Notes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25306</link><description>Misskey is an open source, federated social media platform. The patch for CVE-2024-52591 did not sufficiently validate the relation between the `id` and `url` fields of ActivityPub objects. An attacker can forge an object where they claim authority in the `url` field even if the specific ActivityPub object type require authority in the `id` field. Version 2025.2.1 addresses the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1296 | Nomad Exposes Sensitive Workload Identity and Client Secret Token in Audit Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1296</link><description>Nomad Community and Nomad Enterprise (“Nomad”) are vulnerable to unintentional exposure of the workload identity token and client secret token in audit logs. This vulnerability, identified as CVE-2025-1296, is fixed in Nomad Community Edition 1.9.7 and Nomad Enterprise 1.9.7, 1.8.11, and 1.7.19.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52812 | LF Edge eKuiper has Stored XSS in Rules Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52812</link><description>LF Edge eKuiper is an internet-of-things data analytics and stream processing engine. Prior to version 2.0.8, auser with rights to modify the service (e.g. kuiperUser role) can inject a cross-site scripting payload into the rule `id` parameter. Then, after any user with access to this service (e.g. admin) tries make any modifications with the rule (update, run, stop, delete), a payload acts in the victim's browser. Version 2.0.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53307 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /mw/ endpoint of Evisions MAPS v6.10.2.267 allows attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53307</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /mw/ endpoint of Evisions MAPS v6.10.2.267 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55199 | A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to store JavaScript code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55199</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to store JavaScript code inside a PDF file through the file upload feature. When the file is rendered, the injected code is executed on the user's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24813 | Apache Tomcat: Potential RCE and/or information disclosure and/or information corruption with partial PUT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24813</link><description>Path Equivalence: 'file.Name' (Internal Dot) leading to Remote Code Execution and/or Information disclosure and/or malicious content added to uploaded files via write enabled Default Servlet in Apache Tomcat.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.2, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.34, from 9.0.0.M1 through 9.0.98.

If all of the following were true, a malicious user was able to view       security sensitive files and/or inject content into those files:
- writes enabled for the default servlet (disabled by default)
- support for partial PUT (enabled by default)
- a target URL for security sensitive uploads that was a sub-directory of a target URL for public uploads
- attacker knowledge of the names of security sensitive files being uploaded
- the security sensitive files also being uploaded via partial PUT

If all of the following were true, a malicious user was able to       perform remote code execution:
- writes enabled for the default servlet (disabled by default)
- support for partial PUT (enabled by default)
- application was using Tomcat's file based session persistence with the default storage location
- application included a library that may be leveraged in a deserialization attack

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 11.0.3, 10.1.35 or 9.0.98, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52905 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52905</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.6 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.3 could disclose sensitive database information to a privileged user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47109 | IBM Sterling File Gateway information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47109</link><description>IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.6 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.3 UI could disclosure the installation path of the server which could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25977 | An issue in canvg v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Constructor of the class StyleElement.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25977</link><description>An issue in canvg v.4.0.2 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Constructor of the class StyleElement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25382 | An issue in the Property Tax Payment Portal in Information Kerala Mission SANCHAYA v3.0.4 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify payment amo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25382</link><description>An issue in the Property Tax Payment Portal in Information Kerala Mission SANCHAYA v3.0.4 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify payment amounts via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25940 | VisiCut 2.1 allows code execution via Insecure XML Deserialization in the loadPlfFile method of VisicutModel.java.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25940</link><description>VisiCut 2.1 allows code execution via Insecure XML Deserialization in the loadPlfFile method of VisicutModel.java.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25614 | Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.0 leads to Privilege Escalation, which allows teachers to update the personal data of fellow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25614</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in Unifiedtransform 2.0 leads to Privilege Escalation, which allows teachers to update the personal data of fellow teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26910 | WordPress WPBookit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26910</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Iqonic Design WPBookit allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WPBookit: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26916 | WordPress Massive Dynamic theme &amp;lt;= 8.2 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26916</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in EPC Massive Dynamic. This issue affects Massive Dynamic: from n/a through 8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26933 | WordPress Place Order Without Payment for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26933</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Nitin Prakash WC Place Order Without Payment allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects WC Place Order Without Payment: from n/a through 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26936 | WordPress Fresh Framework plugin &amp;lt;= 1.70.0 - Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26936</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Fresh Framework allows Code Injection. This issue affects Fresh Framework: from n/a through 1.70.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12604 | Improper Authentication in Tapandsign Technologies&amp;#x27; Tap&amp;amp;Sign App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12604</link><description>Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in an Environment Variable, Weak Password Recovery Mechanism for Forgotten Password vulnerability in Tapandsign Technologies Tap&amp;amp;Sign App allows Password Recovery Exploitation, Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Tap&amp;amp;Sign App: before V.1.025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25620 | Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Create assignment function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25620</link><description>Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the Create assignment function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57492 | An issue in redoxOS relibc before commit 98aa4ea5 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the round_up_to_page funciton.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57492</link><description>An issue in redoxOS relibc before commit 98aa4ea5 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the round_up_to_page funciton.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25615 | Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control which allows viewing attendance list for all class sections.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25615</link><description>Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control which allows viewing attendance list for all class sections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25616 | Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows students to modify rules for exams. The affected endpoint is /e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25616</link><description>Unifiedtransform 2.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control, which allows students to modify rules for exams. The affected endpoint is /exams/edit-rule?exam_rule_id=1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1497 | Remote Code Execution in PlotAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1497</link><description>A vulnerability, that could result in Remote Code Execution (RCE), has been found in PlotAI. Lack of validation of LLM-generated output allows attacker to execute arbitrary Python code.
Vendor commented out vulnerable line, further usage of the software requires uncommenting it and thus accepting the risk. The vendor does not plan to release a patch to fix this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26865 | Apache OFBiz: Server-Side Template Injection affecting the ecommerce plugin leading to possible RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26865</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.

This issue affects Apache OFBiz: from 18.12.17 before 18.12.18.  

It's a regression between 18.12.17 and 18.12.18.
In case you use something like that, which is not recommended!
For security, only official releases should be used.

In other words, if you use 18.12.17 you are still safe.
The version 18.12.17 is not a affected.
But something between 18.12.17 and 18.12.18 is.

In that case, users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.18, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2153 | HDF5 h5 File H5SM.c H5SM_delete heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2153</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in HDF5 1.14.6. Affected is the function H5SM_delete of the file H5SM.c of the component h5 File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2152 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp File BaseImporter.cpp ConvertToUTF8 heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2152</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This issue affects the function Assimp::BaseImporter::ConvertToUTF8 of the file BaseImporter.cpp of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2151 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp File ParsingUtils.h GetNextLine stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2151</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This vulnerability affects the function Assimp::GetNextLine in the library ParsingUtils.h of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2149 | PyTorch Quantized Sigmoid Module nnq_Sigmoid initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2149</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function nnq_Sigmoid of the component Quantized Sigmoid Module. The manipulation of the argument scale/zero_point leads to improper initialization. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:07:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2148 | PyTorch Tuple torch.ops.profiler._call_end_callbacks_on_jit_fut memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2148</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PyTorch 2.6.0+cu124. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function torch.ops.profiler._call_end_callbacks_on_jit_fut of the component Tuple Handler. The manipulation of the argument None leads to memory corruption. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 12:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1945 | picklescan - Zip Flag Bit Exploit Crashes Picklescan But Not PyTorch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1945</link><description>picklescan before 0.0.23 fails to detect malicious pickle files inside PyTorch model archives when certain ZIP file flag bits are modified. By flipping specific bits in the ZIP file headers, an attacker can embed malicious pickle files that remain undetected by PickleScan while still being successfully loaded by PyTorch's torch.load(). This can lead to arbitrary code execution when loading a compromised model.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1944 | picklescan ZIP archive manipulation attack leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1944</link><description>picklescan before 0.0.23 is vulnerable to a ZIP archive manipulation attack that causes it to crash when attempting to extract and scan PyTorch model archives. By modifying the filename in the ZIP header while keeping the original filename in the directory listing, an attacker can make PickleScan raise a BadZipFile error. However, PyTorch's more forgiving ZIP implementation still allows the model to be loaded, enabling malicious payloads to bypass detection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2147 | Beijing Zhide Intelligent Internet Technology Modern Farm Digital Integrated Management System file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Zhide Intelligent Internet Technology Modern Farm Digital Integrated Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13918 | Laravel Reflected XSS via Request Parameter in Debug-Mode Error Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13918</link><description>The Laravel framework versions between 11.9.0 and 11.35.1 are susceptible to reflected cross-site scripting due to an improper encoding of request parameters in the debug-mode error page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13919 | Laravel Reflected XSS via Route Parameter in Debug-Mode Error Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13919</link><description>The Laravel framework versions between 11.9.0 and 11.35.1 are susceptible to reflected cross-site scripting due to an improper encoding of route parameters in the debug-mode error page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24387 | Missing CSRF protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24387</link><description>A vulnerability in OTRS Application Server allows session hijacking due to missing attributes for sensitive 
cookie settings in HTTPS sessions. A request to an OTRS endpoint from a possible malicious web site, would send the authentication cookie, performing an unwanted read operation.
 

This issue affects:

  *  OTRS 7.0.X
  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X
  *  OTRS 2025.x</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27253 | An improper input validation in GE Vernova UR IED family devices from version 7.0 up to 8.60 allows an attacker to provide input that enstab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27253</link><description>An improper input validation in GE Vernova UR IED family devices from version 7.0 up to 8.60 allows an attacker to provide input that enstablishes a TCP connection through a port forwarding. The lack of the IP address and port validation may allow the attacker to bypass firewall rules or to send malicious traffic in the network</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27254 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Authentication Bypass. 
The software's startup authentication ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27254</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Authentication Bypass. 
The software's startup authentication can be disabled by altering a Windows registry setting that any user can modify.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27255 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Privilege Escalation. The local user database is encrypt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27255</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Privilege Escalation. The local user database is encrypted using an hardcoded password retrievable by an attacker analyzing the application code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27256 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in GE Vernova Enervista UR Setup application allows Authentication Bypass due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27256</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in GE Vernova Enervista UR Setup application allows Authentication Bypass due to a missing SSH server authentication. Since the client connection is not authenticated, an attacker may perform a man-in-the-middle attack on the network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27257 | Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in GE Vernova UR IED family devices allows an authenticated user to install a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27257</link><description>Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in GE Vernova UR IED family devices allows an authenticated user to install a modified firmware.
The firmware signature verification is enforced only on the client-side dedicated software Enervista UR Setup, allowing the integration check to be bypassed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2150 | HGiga C&amp;amp;Cm@il - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2150</link><description>The C&amp;amp;Cm@il from HGiga has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to send emails containing malicious JavaScript code, which will be executed in the recipient's browser when they view the email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 07:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11638 | Gtbabel &amp;lt; 6.6.9 - Unauthenticated Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11638</link><description>The Gtbabel WordPress plugin before 6.6.9 does not ensure that the URL to perform code analysis upon belongs to the blog which could allow unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a logged in user (such as admin) cookies by making them open a crafted URL as the request made to analysed the URL contains such cookies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 06:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1926 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) To Post Contents Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1926</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the pagelayer_save_post function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify post contents via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 04:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41724 | Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Command Centre SALTO integration allowed an attacker to spoof the SALTO server. 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41724</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Command Centre SALTO integration allowed an attacker to spoof the SALTO server. 




This issue affects all versions of Gallagher Command Centre prior to 9.20.1043.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43107 | Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Milestone Integration Plugin (MIP) permits unauthenticated messages (e.g. alarm e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43107</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Milestone Integration Plugin (MIP) permits unauthenticated messages (e.g. alarm events) to be sent to the Plugin.
This issue effects Gallagher MIPS Plugin v4.0 prior to v4.0.32, all versions of v3.0 and prior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>