<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:35:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-11195 | Rapid7 AppSpider Project Name Validation Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11195</link><description>Rapid7 AppSpider Pro versions below 7.5.021 suffer from a project name validation vulnerability, whereby an attacker can change the project name directly in the configuration file to a name that already exists. This issue stems from a lack of effective verification of the uniqueness of project names when editing them outside the application in affected versions. This vulnerability was remediated in version 7.5.021 of the product.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56675 | The EKEN video doorbell T6 BT60PLUS_MAIN_V1.0_GC1084_20230531 periodically sends debug logs to the EKEN cloud servers with sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56675</link><description>The EKEN video doorbell T6 BT60PLUS_MAIN_V1.0_GC1084_20230531 periodically sends debug logs to the EKEN cloud servers with sensitive information such as the Wi-Fi SSID and password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23291 | NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an authorized actio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23291</link><description>NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an authorized action. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23292 | NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a SQL injection vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23292</link><description>NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a SQL injection vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an authorized action. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to partial denial of service (UI component).</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23293 | NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an authorized actio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23293</link><description>NVIDIA Delegated Licensing Service for all appliance platforms contains a vulnerability where an User/Attacker may cause an authorized action. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10725 | Openshift-ai: overly permissive clusterrole allows authenticated users to escalate privileges to cluster admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10725</link><description>A flaw was found in Red Hat Openshift AI Service. A low-privileged attacker with access to an authenticated account, for example as a data scientist using a standard Jupyter notebook, can escalate their privileges to a full cluster administrator. This allows for the complete compromise of the cluster's confidentiality, integrity, and availability. The attacker can steal sensitive data, disrupt all services, and take control of the underlying infrastructure, leading to a total breach of the platform and all applications hosted on it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56200 | A URL validation bypass vulnerability exists in validator.js through version 13.15.15. The isURL() function uses '://' as a delimiter to par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56200</link><description>A URL validation bypass vulnerability exists in validator.js through version 13.15.15. The isURL() function uses '://' as a delimiter to parse protocols, while browsers use ':' as the delimiter. This parsing difference allows attackers to bypass protocol and domain validation by crafting URLs leading to XSS and Open Redirect attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56513 | NiceHash QuickMiner 6.12.0 perform software updates over HTTP without validating digital signatures or hash checks. An attacker capable of i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56513</link><description>NiceHash QuickMiner 6.12.0 perform software updates over HTTP without validating digital signatures or hash checks. An attacker capable of intercepting or redirecting traffic to the update url and can hijack the update process and deliver arbitrary executables that are automatically executed, resulting in full remote code execution. This constitutes a critical supply chain attack vector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:32:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57254 | An SQL injection vulnerability in user-login.php and index.php of Karthikg1908 Hospital Management System (HMS) 1.0 allows remote attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57254</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in user-login.php and index.php of Karthikg1908 Hospital Management System (HMS) 1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries via the username and password POST parameters. The application fails to properly sanitize input before embedding it into SQL queries, leading to unauthorized access or potential data breaches. This can result in privilege escalation, account takeover, or exposure of sensitive medical data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56520 | Dify v1.6.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component controllers.console.remote_files.RemoteFileUplo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56520</link><description>Dify v1.6.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the component controllers.console.remote_files.RemoteFileUploadApi. A different vulnerability than CVE-2025-29720.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56207 | A security flaw in the '_transfer' function of a smart contract implementation for Money Making Opportunity (MMO), an Ethereum ERC721 Non-Fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56207</link><description>A security flaw in the '_transfer' function of a smart contract implementation for Money Making Opportunity (MMO), an Ethereum ERC721 Non-Fungible Token (NFT) project, allows users or attackers to transfer NFTs to the zero address, leading to permanent asset loss and non-compliance with the ERC721 standard. The eth address is 0x41d3d86a84c8507a7bc14f2491ec4d188fa944e7, contract name is MoneyMakingOpportunity, and compiler version is v0.8.17+commit.8df45f5f.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:49:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6033 | Memory Corruption issue in XML_Serialize() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6033</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to an out of bounds write in XML_Serialize() when using SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6034 | Out of Bounds Read in DefaultFontOptions() in NI Circuit Design Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6034</link><description>There is a memory corruption vulnerability due to an out of bounds read in DefaultFontOptions() when using SymbolEditor in NI Circuit Design Suite.  This vulnerability may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted .sym file. This vulnerability affects NI Circuit Design Suite 14.3.1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:32:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54476 | Joomla! Core - [20250901] Inadequate content filtering within the checkAttribute filter code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54476</link><description>Improper handling of input could lead to an XSS vector in the checkAttribute method of the input filter framework class.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54477 | Joomla! Core - [20250902] User-Enumeration in passkey authentication method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54477</link><description>Improper handling of authentication requests lead to a user enumeration vector in the passkey authentication method.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55797 | An improper access control vulnerability in FormCms v0.5.4 in the /api/schemas/history/[schemaId] endpoint allows unauthenticated attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55797</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in FormCms v0.5.4 in the /api/schemas/history/[schemaId] endpoint allows unauthenticated attackers to access historical schema data if a valid schemaId is known or guessed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56018 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Category Management via the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56018</link><description>SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System V1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Category Management via the category name field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56571 | Finance.js v4.1.0 contains a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability via the IRR function’s depth parameter. Improper handling of the recursio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56571</link><description>Finance.js v4.1.0 contains a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability via the IRR function’s depth parameter. Improper handling of the recursion/iteration limit can lead to excessive CPU usage, causing application stalls or crashes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56572 | An issue in finance.js v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the seekZero() parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56572</link><description>An issue in finance.js v.4.1.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the seekZero() parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56676 | TitanSystems Zender v3.9.7 contains an account takeover vulnerability in its password reset functionality. A temporary password or reset tok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56676</link><description>TitanSystems Zender v3.9.7 contains an account takeover vulnerability in its password reset functionality. A temporary password or reset token issued to one user can be used to log in as another user, due to improper validation of token-user linkage. This allows remote attackers to gain unauthorized access to any user account by exploiting the password reset mechanism. The vulnerability occurs because the reset token is not correctly bound to the requesting account and is accepted for other user emails during login, enabling privilege escalation and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7493 | Freeipa: idm: privilege escalation from host to domain admin in freeipa</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7493</link><description>A privilege escalation flaw from host to domain administrator was found in FreeIPA. This vulnerability is similar to CVE-2025-4404, where it fails to validate the uniqueness of the krbCanonicalName. While the previously released version added validations for the admin@REALM credential, FreeIPA still does not validate the root@REALM canonical name, which can also be used as the realm administrator's name. This flaw allows an attacker to perform administrative tasks over the REALM, leading to access to sensitive data and sensitive data exfiltration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11178 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (Windows) before buil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11178</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (Windows) before build 42386.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7779 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure XPC service configuration. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7779</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure XPC service configuration. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before build 42389, Acronis True Image for SanDisk (macOS) before build 42198, Acronis True Image for Western Digital (macOS) before build 42197.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56301 | An issue was discovered in Chipsalliance Rocket-Chip commit f517abbf41abb65cea37421d3559f9739efd00a9 (2025-01-29) allowing attackers to corr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56301</link><description>An issue was discovered in Chipsalliance Rocket-Chip commit f517abbf41abb65cea37421d3559f9739efd00a9 (2025-01-29) allowing attackers to corrupt exception handling and privilege state transitions via a flawed interaction between exception handling and MRET return mechanisms in the CSR logic when an exception is triggered during MRET execution. The Control and Status Register (CSR) logic has a flawed interaction between exception handling and exception return (MRET) mechanisms which can cause faulty trap behavior. When the MRET instruction is executed in machine mode without being in an exception state, an Instruction Access Fault may be triggered. This results in both the exception handling logic and the exception return logic activating simultaneously, leading to conflicting updates to the control and status registers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57852 | Openshift-ai: privilege escalation via excessive /etc/passwd permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57852</link><description>A container privilege escalation flaw was found in KServe ModelMesh container images. This issue stems from the /etc/passwd file being created with group-writable permissions during build time. In certain conditions, an attacker who can execute commands within an affected container, even as a non-root user, can leverage their membership in the root group to modify the /etc/passwd file. This could allow the attacker to add a new user with any arbitrary UID, including UID 0, leading to full root privileges within the container.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28016 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28016</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System V3.3. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the fname, lname, and contact parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52043 | In Frappe ERPNext v15.57.5, the function import_coa() at erpnext/accounts/doctype/chart_of_accounts_importer/chart_of_accounts_importer.py i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52043</link><description>In Frappe ERPNext v15.57.5, the function import_coa() at erpnext/accounts/doctype/chart_of_accounts_importer/chart_of_accounts_importer.py is vulnerable to SQL injection, which allows an attacker to extract all information from databases by injecting a SQL query into the company parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52047 | In Frappe ErpNext v15.57.5, the function get_income_account() at erpnext/controllers/queries.py is vulnerable to SQL Injection, which allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52047</link><description>In Frappe ErpNext v15.57.5, the function get_income_account() at erpnext/controllers/queries.py is vulnerable to SQL Injection, which allows an attacker to extract all information from databases by injecting a SQL query into the filters.disabled parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52049 | In Frappe ErpNext v15.57.5, the function get_timesheet_detail_rate() at erpnext/projects/doctype/timesheet/timesheet.py is vulnerable to SQL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52049</link><description>In Frappe ErpNext v15.57.5, the function get_timesheet_detail_rate() at erpnext/projects/doctype/timesheet/timesheet.py is vulnerable to SQL Injection, which allows an attacker to extract all information from databases by injecting SQL query into the timelog parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52050 | In Frappe ERPNext 15.57.5, the function get_loyalty_program_details_with_points() at erpnext/accounts/doctype/loyalty_program/loyalty_progra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52050</link><description>In Frappe ERPNext 15.57.5, the function get_loyalty_program_details_with_points() at erpnext/accounts/doctype/loyalty_program/loyalty_program.py is vulnerable to SQL Injection, which allows an attacker to extract all information from databases by injecting a SQL query into the expiry_date parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34217 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Undocumented Hardcoded SSH Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34217</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (VA/SaaS deployments) contain an undocumented 'printerlogic' user with a hardcoded SSH public key in '~/.ssh/authorized_keys' and a sudoers rule granting the printerlogic_ssh group 'NOPASSWD: ALL'. Possession of the matching private key gives an attacker root access to the appliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9230 | Out-of-bounds read &amp;amp; write in RFC 3211 KEK Unwrap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9230</link><description>Issue summary: An application trying to decrypt CMS messages encrypted using
password based encryption can trigger an out-of-bounds read and write.

Impact summary: This out-of-bounds read may trigger a crash which leads to
Denial of Service for an application. The out-of-bounds write can cause
a memory corruption which can have various consequences including
a Denial of Service or Execution of attacker-supplied code.

Although the consequences of a successful exploit of this vulnerability
could be severe, the probability that the attacker would be able to
perform it is low. Besides, password based (PWRI) encryption support in CMS
messages is very rarely used. For that reason the issue was assessed as
Moderate severity according to our Security Policy.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this
issue, as the CMS implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module
boundary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9231 | Timing side-channel in SM2 algorithm on 64 bit ARM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9231</link><description>Issue summary: A timing side-channel which could potentially allow remote
recovery of the private key exists in the SM2 algorithm implementation on 64 bit
ARM platforms.

Impact summary: A timing side-channel in SM2 signature computations on 64 bit
ARM platforms could allow recovering the private key by an attacker..

While remote key recovery over a network was not attempted by the reporter,
timing measurements revealed a timing signal which may allow such an attack.

OpenSSL does not directly support certificates with SM2 keys in TLS, and so
this CVE is not relevant in most TLS contexts.  However, given that it is
possible to add support for such certificates via a custom provider, coupled
with the fact that in such a custom provider context the private key may be
recoverable via remote timing measurements, we consider this to be a Moderate
severity issue.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this
issue, as SM2 is not an approved algorithm.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9232 | Out-of-bounds read in HTTP client no_proxy handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9232</link><description>Issue summary: An application using the OpenSSL HTTP client API functions may
trigger an out-of-bounds read if the 'no_proxy' environment variable is set and
the host portion of the authority component of the HTTP URL is an IPv6 address.

Impact summary: An out-of-bounds read can trigger a crash which leads to
Denial of Service for an application.

The OpenSSL HTTP client API functions can be used directly by applications
but they are also used by the OCSP client functions and CMP (Certificate
Management Protocol) client implementation in OpenSSL. However the URLs used
by these implementations are unlikely to be controlled by an attacker.

In this vulnerable code the out of bounds read can only trigger a crash.
Furthermore the vulnerability requires an attacker-controlled URL to be
passed from an application to the OpenSSL function and the user has to have
a 'no_proxy' environment variable set. For the aforementioned reasons the
issue was assessed as Low severity.

The vulnerable code was introduced in the following patch releases:
3.0.16, 3.1.8, 3.2.4, 3.3.3, 3.4.0 and 3.5.0.

The FIPS modules in 3.5, 3.4, 3.3, 3.2, 3.1 and 3.0 are not affected by this
issue, as the HTTP client implementation is outside the OpenSSL FIPS module
boundary.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10859 | Cookie storage for non-HTML temporary documents was being shared incorrectly with normal browsing content, allowing information from private...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10859</link><description>Cookie storage for non-HTML temporary documents was being shared incorrectly with normal browsing content, allowing information from private tabs to escape Incognito mode even after the user closed all tabs This vulnerability affects Firefox for iOS &lt; 143.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11152 | This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 143.0.3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11152</link><description>This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 143.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11153 | This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 143.0.3.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11153</link><description>This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 143.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10217 | A vulnerability exists in Asset Suite for an authenticated user to manipulate the content of performance related log data or to inject craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10217</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Asset Suite for an authenticated user to manipulate the content of performance related log data or to inject crafted data in logfile for potentially carrying out further malicious attacks. Performance logging is typically enabled for troubleshooting purposes while resolving application performance related issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41098 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41098</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a  misuse of the general enquiry web service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41091 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41091</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to calendar details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41092 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41092</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to time records details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41093 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41093</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to basic contract details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41094 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41094</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to functional contract details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41095 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41095</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to planning counter details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41096 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41096</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to the dates of the current contract details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41097 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41097</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to basic employee  details using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41099 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in GPS BOLD Workplanner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41099</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in BOLD Workplanner in versions prior to 2.5.25 (4935b438f9b), consisting of a lack of adequate validation of user input, allowing an authenticated user to access to the list of permissions using unauthorised internal identifiers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7063 | Remote Code Execution via Unrestricted File Upload in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7063</link><description>Due to client-controlled permission check parameter, PAD CMS's file upload functionality allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to upload files of any type and extension without restriction, which can then be executed leading to Remote Code Execution. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and ww+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7065 | Remote Code Execution via Unrestricted File Upload in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7065</link><description>Due to client-controlled permission check parameter, PAD CMS's photo upload functionality allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to upload files of any type and extension without restriction, which can then be executed leading to Remote Code Execution. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and ww+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8116 | Reflected XSS in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8116</link><description>PAD CMS is vulnerable to Reflected XSS in printing and save to PDF functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special URL, which will result in arbitrary JavaScript execution in victim's browser, when opened. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and www+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8117 | Account Takeover via Reset Password Functionality in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8117</link><description>PAD CMS improperly initializes parameter used for password recovery, which allows to change password for any user that did not use reset password functionality. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and www+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8118 | Bruteforce Protection Bypass in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8118</link><description>PAD CMS implements weak client-side brute-force protection by utilizing two cookies:  login_count and login_timeout. Information about attempt count or timeout is not stored on the server, which allows a malicious attacker to bypass this brute-force protection by resetting those cookies. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and www+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8119 | Cross-Site Request Forgery in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8119</link><description>PAD CMS is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in reset password's functionality. Malicious attacker can craft special website, which when visited by the victim, will automatically send a POST request changing currently logged user's password to defined by the attacker value. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and www+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8120 | Remote Code Execution via Unrestricted File Upload in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8120</link><description>Due to client-controlled permission check parameter, PAD CMS's upload photo functionality allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to upload files of any type and extension without restriction, which can then be executed leading to Remote Code Execution.This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and ww+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8121 | Blind SQL Injection in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8121</link><description>Improper neutralization of input provided by an authorized user in article positioning functionality allows for Blind SQL Injection attacks. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and ww+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8122 | Blind SQL Injection in PAD CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8122</link><description>Improper neutralization of input provided by an authorized user in article positioning functionality allows for Blind SQL Injection attacks. This issue affects all 3 templates: www, bip and ww+bip.

This product is End-Of-Life and producent will not publish patches for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8877 | AffiliateWP &amp;lt;= 2.28.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8877</link><description>The AffiliateWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ajax_get_affiliate_id_from_login function in all versions up to, and including, 2.28.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 08:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11163 | SmartCrawl SEO checker, analyzer &amp;amp; optimizer &amp;lt;= 3.14.3 - Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11163</link><description>The SmartCrawl SEO checker, analyzer &amp; optimizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update_submodule() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's setttings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 05:35:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11148 | All versions of the package check-branches are vulnerable to Command Injection check-branches is a command-line tool that is interacted with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11148</link><description>All versions of the package check-branches are vulnerable to Command Injection check-branches is a command-line tool that is interacted with locally, or via CI, to confirm no conflicts exist in git branches.&#13;&#13;However, the library follows these conventions which can be abused:&#13;1. It trusts branch names as they are (plain text)&#13;2. It spawns git commands by concatenating user input&#13;&#13;Since a branch name is potentially a user input - as users can create branches remotely via pull requests, or simply due to privileged access to a repository - it can effectively be abused to run any command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 05:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11149 | This affects all versions of the package node-static; all versions of the package @nubosoftware/node-static. The package fails to catch an e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11149</link><description>This affects all versions of the package node-static; all versions of the package @nubosoftware/node-static. The package fails to catch an exception when user input includes null bytes. This allows attackers to access http://host/%00 and crash the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 05:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6815 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.1.94 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6815</link><description>The LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘service[name]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.94 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6941 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.1.94 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6941</link><description>The LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'id' parameter of the 'latepoint_resources' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.94 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7038 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.1.94 - Unauthenticated Authentication Bypass via load_step Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7038</link><description>The LatePoint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to insufficient identity verification within the steps__load_step route of the latepoint_route_call AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.94. The endpoint reads the client-supplied customer email and related customer fields before invoking the internal login handler without verifying login status, capability checks, or a valid AJAX nonce. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log into any customer’s account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7052 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.1.94 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Takeover via change_password() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7052</link><description>The LatePoint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.94. This is due to missing nonce validation on the change_password() function of its customer_cabinet__change_password AJAX route. The plugin hooks this endpoint via wp_ajax and wp_ajax_nopriv but does not verify a nonce or user capability before resetting the user’s password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers who trick a logged-in customer (or, with “WP users as customers” enabled, an administrator) into visiting a malicious link to take over their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59668 | Multiple versions of Central Monitor CNS-6201 contain a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability. When processing a crafted certain UDP packet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59668</link><description>Multiple versions of Central Monitor CNS-6201 contain a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability. When processing a crafted certain UDP packet, the affected device may abnormally terminate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 04:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10000 | Qyrr – simply and modern QR-Code creation &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10000</link><description>The Qyrr – simply and modern QR-Code creation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the blob_to_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10128 | Eulerpool Research Systems &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10128</link><description>The Eulerpool Research Systems plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'aaq' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10130 | Layers &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10130</link><description>The Layers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'webcam' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10131 | All Social Share Options &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10131</link><description>The All Social Share Options plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10168 | Any News Ticker &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10168</link><description>The Any News Ticker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'any-ticker' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10179 | My AskAI &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10179</link><description>The My AskAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'myaskai' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10182 | dbview &amp;lt;= 0.5.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10182</link><description>The dbview plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'dbview' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10189 | BP Direct Menus &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10189</link><description>The BP Direct Menus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bpdm_login' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10191 | Big Post Shipping for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10191</link><description>The Big Post Shipping for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wooboigpost_shipping_status' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10196 | SurveyAnyplace Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10196</link><description>The Survey Anyplace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'surveyanyplace_embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8214 | The Pack Elementor addon &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Typing Letter Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8214</link><description>The The Pack Elementor addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Typing Letter widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8559 | All in One Music Player &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Path Traversal via theme Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8559</link><description>The All in One Music Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 via the 'theme' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8560 | FancyTabs &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via title Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8560</link><description>The FancyTabs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘title’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8566 | GutenBee – Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.18.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8566</link><description>The GutenBee – Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via parameters in the CountUp and Google Maps Blocks in all versions up to, and including, 2.18.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8608 | Mihdan: Elementor Yandex Maps &amp;lt;= 1.6.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Marker Pins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8608</link><description>The Mihdan: Elementor Yandex Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's block attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8623 | WeedMaps Menu for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via weedmaps_menu Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8623</link><description>The WeedMaps Menu for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's weedmaps_menu shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8624 | Nexa Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Google Maps Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8624</link><description>The Nexa Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Google Maps widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8625 | Copypress Rest API 1.1 - 1.2 - Missing Configurable JWT Secret and File-Type Validation to Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8625</link><description>The Copypress Rest API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via copyreap_handle_image() Function in versions 1.1 to 1.2. The plugin falls back to a hard-coded JWT signing key when no secret is defined and does not restrict which file types can be fetched and saved as attachments. As a result, unauthenticated attackers can forge a valid token to gain elevated privileges and upload an arbitrary file (e.g. a PHP script) through the image handler, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8777 | planetcalc &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via language Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8777</link><description>The planetcalc plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘language’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9762 | Post By Email &amp;lt;= 1.0.4b - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via Email Attachments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9762</link><description>The Post By Email plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the save_attachments function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4b. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9852 | Yoga Schedule Momoyoga &amp;lt;= 2.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9852</link><description>The Yoga Schedule Momoyoga plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'momoyoga-schedule' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9946 | LockerPress – WordPress Security Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9946</link><description>The LockerPress – WordPress Security Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9948 | Chat by Chatwee &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9948</link><description>The Chat by Chatwee plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the admin settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9991 | Tiny Bootstrap Elements Light &amp;lt;= 4.3.34 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9991</link><description>The Tiny Bootstrap Elements Light plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.34 via the 'language' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9993 | Bei Fen – WordPress Backup Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9993</link><description>The Bei Fen – WordPress Backup Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 via the 'task'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included. This only affects instances running PHP 7.1 or older.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 03:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61584 | serverless-dns is vulnerable to Command Injection through pr.yml GitHub Action Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61584</link><description>serverless-dns is a RethinkDNS resolver that deploys to Cloudflare Workers, Deno Deploy, Fastly, and Fly.io. Versions through abd including 0.1.30 have a vulnerability where the pr.yml GitHub Action interpolates in an unsafe manner untrusted input, specifically the github.event.pull_request.head.repo.clone_url and github.head_ref, to a command in the runner. Due to the action using the pull_request_target trigger it has permissive permissions by default. An unauthorized attacker can exploit this vulnerability to push arbitrary data to the repository. The subsequent impact on the end-user is executing the attackers' code when running serverless-dns. This is fixed in commit c5537dd, and expected to be released in 0.1.31.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10991 | Root Access via UART</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10991</link><description>The attacker may obtain root access by connecting to the UART port and this vulnerability requires the attacker to have the physical access to the device.

This issue affects Tapo D230S1 V1.20: before 1.2.2 Build 20250907.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 01:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59956 | AgentAPI exposed user chat history via a DNS rebinding attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59956</link><description>AgentAPI is an HTTP API for Claude Code, Goose, Aider, Gemini, Amp, and Codex. Versions 0.3.3 and below are susceptible to a client-side DNS rebinding attack when hosted over plain HTTP on localhost. An attacker can gain access to the /messages endpoint served by the Agent API. This allows for the unauthorized exfiltration of sensitive user data, specifically local message history, which can include secret keys, file system contents, and intellectual property the user was working on locally. This issue is fixed in version 0.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 01:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58040 | Crypt::RandomEncryption for Perl uses insecure rand() function during encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58040</link><description>Crypt::RandomEncryption for Perl version 0.01 uses insecure rand() function during encryption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59954 | Knowage Contains a Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59954</link><description>Knowage is an open source analytics and business intelligence suite. Versions 8.1.26 and below are vulnerable to Remote Code Exection through using an unsafe org.apache.commons.jxpath.JXPathContext in MetaService.java service. This issue is fixed in version 8.1.27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59952 | minio-java Client XML Tag is Vulnerable to Value Substitution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59952</link><description>MinIO Java SDK is a Simple Storage Service (aka S3) client to perform bucket and object operations to any Amazon S3 compatible object storage service. In minio-java versions prior to 8.6.0, XML tag values containing references to system properties or environment variables were automatically substituted with their actual values during processing. This unintended behavior could lead to the exposure of sensitive information, including credentials, file paths, or system configuration details, if such references were present in XML content from untrusted sources. This is fixed in version 8.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59950 | FreshRSS: Double clickjacking can lead to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59950</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. In versions 1.26.3 and below, due to a bypass of double clickjacking protection (confirmation dialog), it is possible to trick the admin into clicking the Promote button in another user's management page after the admin double clicks on a button inside an attacker-controlled website. A successful attack can allow the attacker to promote themselves to "admin" and log into other users' accounts; the attacker has to know the specific instance URL they're targeting. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61586 | FreshRSS is vulnerable to directory enumeration by setting path in its theme field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61586</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below are vulnerable to directory enumeration by setting path in theme field, allowing attackers to gain additional information about the server by checking if certain directories exist. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59948 | FreshRSS is vulnerable to XSS due to lack of CSP on HTML query page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59948</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below do not sanitize certain event handler attributes in feed content, so by finding a page that renders feed entries without CSP, it is possible to execute an XSS payload. The Allow API access authentication setting needs to be enabled by the instance administrator beforehand for the attack to work as it relies on api/query.php. An account takeover is possible by sending a change password request via the XSS payload / setting UserJS for persistence / stealing the autofill password / displaying a phishing page with a spoofed URL using history.replaceState()
If the victim is an administrator, the attacker can also perform administrative actions. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59942 | go-f3 module vulnerable to integer overflow leading to panic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59942</link><description>go-f3 is a Golang implementation of Fast Finality for Filecoin (F3). In versions 0.8.6 and below, go-f3 panics when it validates a "poison" messages causing Filecoin nodes consuming F3 messages to become vulnerable. A "poison" message can can cause integer overflow in the signer index validation, which can cause the whole node to crash. These malicious messages aren't self-propagating since the bug is in the validator. An attacker needs to directly send the message to all targets. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59941 | go-f3 is Vulnerable to Cached Justification Verification Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59941</link><description>go-f3 is a Golang implementation of Fast Finality for Filecoin (F3). In versions 0.8.8 and below, go-f3's justification verification caching mechanism has a vulnerability where verification results are cached without properly considering the context of the message. An attacker can bypass justification verification by submitting a valid message with a correct justification and then reusing the same cached justification in contexts where it would normally be invalid. This occurs because the cached verification does not properly validate the relationship between the justification and the specific message context it's being used with. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36245 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36245</link><description>IBM InfoSphere 11.7.0.0 through 11.7.1.6 Information Server could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on the system due to improper validation of user supplied input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43817 | Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.74 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 throug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43817</link><description>Multiple reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.74 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.6, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 update 74 through update 92 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the `redirect` parameter to (1) Announcements, or (2) Alerts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43813 | Possible path traversal vulnerability and denial-of-service in the ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.107, and older unsuppo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43813</link><description>Possible path traversal vulnerability and denial-of-service in the ComboServlet in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.107, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 7.4 GA through update 92, 7.3 GA through update 35, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to access arbitrary CSS and JSS files and load the files multiple times via the query string in a URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59937 | go-mail has insufficient address encoding when passing mail addresses to the SMTP client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59937</link><description>go-mail is a comprehensive library for sending mails with Go. In versions 0.7.0 and below, due to incorrect handling of the mail.Address values when a sender- or recipient address is passed to the corresponding MAIL FROM or RCPT TO commands of the SMTP client, there is a possibility of wrong address routing or even ESMTP parameter smuggling. For successful exploitation, it is required that the user's code allows for arbitrary mail address input (i. e. through a web form or similar). If only static mail addresses are used (i. e. in a config file) and the mail addresses in use do not consist of quoted local parts, this should not affect users. This issue is fixed in version 0.7.1</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59940 | mkdocs-include-markdown-plugin susceptible to unvalidated input colliding with substitution placeholders</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59940</link><description>mkdocs-include-markdown-plugin is an Mkdocs Markdown includer plugin. In versions 7.1.7 and below, there is a vulnerability where unvalidated input can collide with substitution placeholders. This issue is fixed in version 7.1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43812 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in web content template in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43812</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in web content template in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a web content structure's Name text field</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59933 | libvips is vulnerable to Buffer Over-Read in poppler-based pdfload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59933</link><description>libvips is a demand-driven, horizontally threaded image processing library. For versions 8.17.1 and below, when libvips is compiled with support for PDF input via poppler, the pdfload operation is affected by a buffer read overflow when parsing the header of a crafted PDF with a page that defines a width but not a height. Those using libvips compiled without support for PDF input are unaffected as well as thosewith support for PDF input via PDFium. This issue is fixed in version 8.17.2. A workaround for those affected is to block the VipsForeignLoadPdf operation via vips_operation_block_set, which is available in most language bindings, or to set VIPS_BLOCK_UNTRUSTED environment variable at runtime, which will block all untrusted loaders including PDF input via poppler.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43811 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the related asset selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.50 through 7.4.3.111, and Lif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43811</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the related asset selector in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.50 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.7, and 7.4 update 50 through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into an asset author’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle Name, or (3) Last Name text field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43820 | Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the Calendar widget when inviting users to a event in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43820</link><description>Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in the Calendar widget when inviting users to a event in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.6, 7.4 update 35 through update 92, and 7.3 update 25 through update 35 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a user’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle text, or (3) Last Name text fields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59163 | vet MCP Server SSE Transport DNS Rebinding Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59163</link><description>vet is an open source software supply chain security tool. Versions 1.12.4 and below are vulnerable to a DNS rebinding attack due to lack of HTTP Host and Origin header validation. Data from the vet scan sqlite3 database may be exposed to remote attackers when vet is used as an MCP server in SSE mode with default ports through the sqlite3 query MCP tool. This issue is fixed in version 1.12.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43818 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43818</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.4, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.6, 7.4 update 35 through update 92, and 7.3 update 25 through update 36 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a Calendar's “Name” text field</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57769 | FressRSS: Clickjacking can lead to XSS and/or privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57769</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below contain a vulnerability where a specially crafted page can trick a user into executing arbitrary JS code or promoting a user in FreshRSS by obscuring UI elements in iframes. If embedding an authenticated iframe is possible, this may lead to privilege escalation via obscuring the promote user button in the admin UI or XSS by tricking the user to drag content into the UserJS text area. This is fixed in version 1.27.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:51:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54875 | FreshRSS: Unauthorized creation of admin user when registration is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54875</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. In versions 1.16.0 and above through 1.26.3, an unprivileged attacker can create a new admin user when registration is enabled through the use of a hidden field used only in the user management admin page, new_user_is_admin. This is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54592 | FreshRSS has Incomplete Session Termination on Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54592</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below do not properly terminate the session during logout. After a user logs out, the session cookie remains active and unchanged. The unchanged cookie could be reused by an attacker if a new session were to be started. This failure to invalidate the session can lead to session hijacking and fixation vulnerabilities. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43815 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the page configuration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.102 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43815</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the page configuration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.102 through 7.4.3.110, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.2, and 2023.Q3.5 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the com_liferay_layout_admin_web_portlet_GroupPagesPortlet_backURLTitle parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30247 | An OS command injection vulnerability in user interface in Western Digital My Cloud firmware prior to 5.31.108 on NAS platforms allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30247</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in user interface in Western Digital My Cloud firmware prior to 5.31.108 on NAS platforms allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands via a specially crafted HTTP POST.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54591 | FreshRSS: Unauthenticated users can view default user&amp;#x27;s  information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54591</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Versions 1.26.3 and below expose information about feeds and tags of default admin users, due to lack of access checking in the FreshRSS_Auth::hasAccess() function used by some of the tag/feed related endpoints. FreshRSS controllers usually have a defined firstAction() method with an override to make sure that every action requires access. If one doesn't, then every action has to check for access manually, and certain endpoints use neither the firstAction() method, or do they perform a manual access check. This issue is fixed in version 1.27.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34235 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Weak SSL/TLS Certificate Validation RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34235</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (Windows client deployments) contain a registry key that can be enabled by administrators, causing the client to skip SSL/TLS certificate validation. An attacker who can intercept HTTPS traffic can then inject malicious driver DLLs, resulting in remote code execution with SYSTEM privileges; a local attacker can achieve local privilege escalation via a junction‑point DLL injection. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:52:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34207 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure SSH Client Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34207</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to 22.0.1049 and Application prior to 20.0.2786 (VA and SaaS deployments) configure the SSH client within Docker instances with the following options: `UserKnownHostsFile=/dev/null`, `StrictHostKeyChecking=no`, and `ForwardAgent yes`.  These settings disable verification of the remote host’s SSH key and automatically forward the developer’s SSH‑agent to any host that matches the configured wildcard patterns.  As a result, an attacker who can reach a single compromised container can cause the container to connect to a malicious SSH server, capture the forwarded private keys, and use those keys for unrestricted lateral movement across the environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34212 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Build Pipeline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34212</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.843 and Application prior to version 20.0.1923 (VA/SaaS deployments) possess CI/CD weaknesses: the build pulls an unverified third-party image, downloads the VirtualBox Extension Pack over plain HTTP without signature validation, and grants the jenkins account NOPASSWD for mount/umount. Together these allow supply chain or man-in-the-middle compromise of the build pipeline, injection of malicious firmware, and remote code execution as root on the CI host. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2023-007 — Supply Chain Attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34215 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticate Firmware Update Endpoint RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34215</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1026 and Application prior to version 20.0.2702 (only VA deployments) expose an unauthenticated firmware-upload flow: a public page returns a signed token usable at va-api/v1/update, and every Docker image contains the appliance’s private GPG key and hard-coded passphrase. An attacker who extracts the key and obtains a token can decrypt, modify, re-sign, upload, and trigger malicious firmware, gaining remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34216 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) RCE and Password Leaks via API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34216</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1026 and Application prior to version 20.0.2702 (VA deployments only) expose a set of unauthenticated REST API endpoints that return configuration files and clear‑text passwords. The same endpoints also disclose the Laravel APP_KEY used for cryptographic signing. Because the APP_KEY is required to generate valid signed requests, an attacker who obtains it can craft malicious payloads that are accepted by the application and achieve remote code execution on the appliance. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-018 — RCE &amp; Leaks via API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34220 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated API Leaks Group Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34220</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contains a /api-gateway/identity/search-groups endpoint that does not require authentication. Requests to https://.printercloud10.com/api-gateway/identity/search-groups and adjustments to the `Host` header allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to enumerate every group object stored for that tenant.  The response includes internal identifiers (group ID, source service ID, Azure AD object IDs, creation timestamps, and tenant IDs). This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34221 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34221</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.2.169 and Application prior to version 25.2.1518 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose every internal Docker container to the network because firewall rules allow unrestricted traffic to the Docker bridge network. Because no authentication, ACL or client‑side identifier is required, the attacker can interact with any internal API, bypassing the product’s authentication mechanisms entirely. The result is unauthenticated remote access to internal services, allowing credential theft, configuration manipulation and potential remote code execution. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2025-002 — Authentication Bypass - Docker Instances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34222 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated Admin APIs Used to Modify SSL Certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34222</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose four admin routes – /admin/hp/cert_upload, /admin/hp/cert_delete, /admin/certs/ca, and /admin/certs/serviceclients/{scid} – without any authentication check. The routes are defined in the /var/www/app/routes/web.php file inside the printercloud/pi Docker container and are handled by the HPCertificateController class, which performs no user validation.  An unauthenticated attacker can therefore upload a new TLS/SSL certificate replacing the trusted root used by the appliance, delete an existing certificate causing immediate loss of trust for services that rely on it, or download any stored CA or client certificate via the service‑clients endpoint which also suffers an IDOR that allows enumeration of all client IDs. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-028 — Unauthenticated Admin APIs Used to Modify SSL Certificates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34223 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Installation Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34223</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a default admin account and an installation‑time endpoint at `/admin/query/update_database.php` that can be accessed without authentication. An attacker who can reach the installation web interface can POST arbitrary `root_user` and `root_password` values, causing the script to replace the default admin credentials with attacker‑controlled ones. The script also contains hard‑coded SHA‑512 and SHA‑1 hashes of the default password, allowing the attacker to bypass password‑policy validation. As a result, an unauthenticated remote attacker can obtain full administrative control of the system during the initial setup. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-022 — Insecure Installation Credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34224 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unauthenticated Device Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34224</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose a set of PHP scripts under the `console_release` directory without requiring authentication.  An unauthenticated remote attacker can invoke these endpoints to re‑configure networked printers, add or delete RFID badge devices, or otherwise modify device settings. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-029 — No Authentication to Modify Devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34225 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via console_release Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34225</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The `console_release` directory is reachable from the internet without any authentication.  Inside that directory are dozens of PHP scripts that build URLs from user‑controlled values and then invoke either 'curl_exec()` or `file_get_contents()` without proper validation. Although many files attempt to mitigate SSRF by calling `filter_var', the checks are incomplete. Because the endpoint is unauthenticated, any remote attacker can supply a hostname and cause the server to issue requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, potential pivoting, or data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34228 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via Lexmark update.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34228</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The `/var/www/app/console_release/lexmark/update.php` script is reachable from the internet without any authentication.  The PHP script builds URLs from user‑controlled values and then invokes either 'curl_exec()` or `file_get_contents()` without proper validation. Because the endpoint is unauthenticated, any remote attacker can supply a hostname and cause the server to issue requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, potential pivoting, or data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34229 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via HP installApp.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34229</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/hp/installApp.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34230 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via HP log_off_single_sign_on.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34230</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/hp/log_off_single_sign_on.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34231 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) SSRF via HP badgeSetup.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34231</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind and non-blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The '/var/www/app/console_release/hp/badgeSetup.php' script is reachable from the Internet without any authentication and builds URLs from user‑controlled parameters before invoking either the custom processCurl() function or PHP’s file_get_contents(); in both cases the hostname/URL is taken directly from the request with no whitelist, scheme restriction, IP‑range validation, or outbound‑network filtering. Consequently, any unauthenticated attacker can force the server to issue arbitrary HTTP requests to internal resources. This enables internal network reconnaissance, credential leakage, pivoting, and data exfiltration. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34233 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Use of file_get_contents()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34233</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a protection mechanism failure vulnerability within the file_get_contents() function. When an administrator configures a printer’s hostname (or similar callback field), the value is passed unchecked to PHP’s file_get_contents()/cURL functions, which follow redirects and impose no allow‑list, scheme, or IP‑range restrictions. An admin‑level attacker can therefore point the hostname to a malicious web server that issues a 301 redirect to internal endpoints such as the AWS EC2 metadata service. The server follows the redirect, retrieves the metadata, and returns or stores the credentials, enabling the attacker to steal cloud IAM keys, enumerate internal services, and pivot further into the SaaS infrastructure. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34209 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded GPG Private Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34209</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to 22.0.862 and Application prior to 20.0.2014 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain Docker images with the private GPG key and passphrase for the account *no‑reply+virtual‑appliance@printerlogic.com*. The key is stored in cleartext and the passphrase is hardcoded in files. An attacker with administrative access to the appliance can extract the private key, import it into their own system, and subsequently decrypt GPG-encrypted files and sign arbitrary firmware update packages. A maliciously signed update can be uploaded by an admin‑level attacker and will be executed by the appliance, giving the attacker full control of the virtual appliance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34211 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded SSL Certificate and Private Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34211</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain a private SSL key and matching public certificate stored in cleartext. The key belongs to the hostname `pl‑local.com` and is used by the appliance to terminate TLS connections on ports 80/443. Because the key is hardcoded, any attacker who can gain container-level access can simply read the files and obtain the private key. With the private key, the attacker can decrypt TLS traffic, perform man-in-the-middle attacks, or forge TLS certificates. This enables impersonation of the appliance’s web UI, interception of credentials, and unrestricted access to any services that trust the certificate. The same key is identical across all deployed appliances meaning a single theft compromises the confidentiality of every Vasion Print installation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34218 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Exposed Internal Docker Instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34218</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 22.0.1049 and Application prior to version 20.0.2786 (VA/SaaS deployments) expose internal Docker containers through the gw Docker instance.  The gateway publishes a /meta endpoint which lists every micro‑service container together with version information. These containers are reachable directly over HTTP/HTTPS without any access‑control list (ACL), authentication or rate‑limiting. Consequently, any attacker on the LAN or the Internet can enumerate all internal services and their versions, interact with the exposed APIs of each microservice as an unauthenticated user, or issue malicious requests that may lead to information disclosure, privilege escalation within the container, or denial‑of‑service of the entire appliance. The root cause is the absence of authentication and network‑level restrictions on the API‑gateway’s proxy to internal Docker containers, effectively turning the internal service mesh into a public attack surface. This vulnerability has been identified by the vendor as: V-2024-030 — Exposed Internal Docker Instance (LAN).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34232 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Blind SSRF via Lexmark dellCheck.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34232</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain a blind server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability reachable via the /var/www/app/console_release/lexmark/dellCheck.php script that can be exploited by an unauthenticated user. When a printer is registered, the software stores the printer’s host name in the variable $printer_vo-&gt;str_host_address. The code later builds a URL like 'http://:80/DevMgmt/DiscoveryTree.xml' and sends the request with curl. No validation, whitelist, or private‑network filtering is performed before the request is made. Because the request is blind, an attacker cannot see the data directly, but can still: probe internal services, trigger internal actions, or gather other intelligence. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34234 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded Encryption Private Keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34234</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to version 25.1.102 and Application prior to version 25.1.1413 (VA/SaaS deployments) contain two hardcoded private keys that are shipped in the application containers (printerlogic/pi, printerlogic/printer-admin-api, and printercloud/pi). The keys are stored in clear text under /var/www/app/config/ as keyfile.ppk.dev and keyfile.saasid.ppk.dev. The application uses these keys as the symmetric secret for AES‑256‑CBC encryption/decryption of the “SaaS Id” (external identifier) through the getEncryptedExternalId() / getDecryptedExternalId() methods. Because the secret is embedded in the deployed image, any attacker who can obtain a copy of the Docker image, read the configuration files, or otherwise enumerate the filesystem can recover the encryption key. This vulnerability has been confirmed to be remediated, but it is unclear as to when the patch was introduced.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45376 | Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions 3.4.7 and 3.4.8, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45376</link><description>Dell Repository Manager (DRM), versions 3.4.7 and 3.4.8, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57266 | An issue was discovered in file AssistantController.java in ThriveX Blogging Framework 2.5.9 thru 3.1.3 allowing unauthenticated attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57266</link><description>An issue was discovered in file AssistantController.java in ThriveX Blogging Framework 2.5.9 thru 3.1.3 allowing unauthenticated attackers to gain sensitive information such as API Keys via the /api/assistant/list endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35030 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health cross site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35030</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a cross site request forgery vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to trick administrative users into clicking a crafted URL and perform actions on behalf of that administrative user. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35031 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health includes session token in debug output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35031</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health includes the user's current session token in debug output. An attacker could convince a user to send this output to the attacker, thus allowing the attacker to impersonate that user. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35032 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health arbitrary file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35032</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files. The impact of this behavior depends on how files are accessed. This issue is fixed as of 2025-04-08.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35033 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health CSV injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35033</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a CSV injection vulnerability that allows a remote, authenticated attacker to inject macros in downloadable CSV files. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35034 | Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health reflected cross site scripting via portlet_user_id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35034</link><description>Medical Informatics Engineering Enterprise Health has a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in the 'portlet_user_id' URL parameter. A remote, unauthenticated attacker can craft a URL that can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim's browser. This issue is fixed as of 2025-03-14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56764 | Trivision NC-227WF firmware 5.80 (build 20141010) login mechanism reveals whether a username exists or not by returning different error mess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56764</link><description>Trivision NC-227WF firmware 5.80 (build 20141010) login mechanism reveals whether a username exists or not by returning different error messages ("Unknown user" vs. "Wrong password"), allowing an attacker to enumerate valid usernames.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34196 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Hardcoded PrinterLogic CA Private Key and Hardcoded Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34196</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 25.1.102 and Application prior to 25.1.1413 (Windows client deployments) contain a hardcoded private key for the PrinterLogic Certificate Authority (CA) and a hardcoded password in product configuration files. The Windows client ships the CA certificate and its associated private key (and other sensitive settings such as a configured password) directly in shipped configuration files (for example clientsettings.dat and defaults.ini). An attacker who obtains these files can impersonate the CA, sign arbitrary certificates trusted by the Windows client, intercept or decrypt TLS-protected communications, and otherwise perform man-in-the-middle or impersonation attacks against the product's network communications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41252 | Username enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41252</link><description>Description: VMware NSX contains a username enumeration vulnerability. An unauthenticated malicious actor may exploit this to enumerate valid usernames, potentially leading to unauthorized access attempts.


Impact: Username enumeration → facilitates unauthorized access.


Attack Vector: Remote, unauthenticated.


Severity: Important.


CVSSv3: 7.5 (High).


Acknowledgments: Reported by the National Security Agency.


Affected Products:



  *  VMware NSX 9.x.x.x, 4.2.x, 4.1.x, 4.0.x

  *  NSX-T 3.x

  *  VMware Cloud Foundation (with NSX) 5.x, 4.5.x












Fixed Versions: 



  *  NSX 9.0.1.0;  4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 http://4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 ; 4.1.2.7; NSX-T 3.2.4.3; CCF async patch (KB88287).






Workarounds: None.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41251 | Weak password recovery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41251</link><description>VMware NSX contains a weak password recovery mechanism vulnerability. An unauthenticated malicious actor may exploit this to enumerate valid usernames, potentially enabling brute-force attacks.

Impact: Username enumeration → credential brute force risk.
Attack Vector: Remote, unauthenticated.
Severity: Important.
CVSSv3: 8.1 (High).

Acknowledgments: Reported by the National Security Agency.

Affected Products:VMware NSX 9.x.x.x, 4.2.x, 4.1.x, 4.0.x

NSX-T 3.x
VMware Cloud Foundation (with NSX) 5.x, 4.5.x

Fixed Versions: NSX 9.0.1.0;  4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 http://4.2.2.2/4.2.3.1 ; 4.1.2.7; NSX-T 3.2.4.3; CCF async patch (KB88287).
Workarounds: None.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57424 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MyCourts v3 application within the LTA number profile field. An attacker can...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57424</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the MyCourts v3 application within the LTA number profile field. An attacker can insert arbitrary JavaScript into their profile, which executes in the browser of any user viewing it, including administrators. Due to the absence of the HttpOnly flag on the session cookie, this flaw could be exploited to capture session tokens and hijack user sessions, enabling elevated access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57871 | BUG-000174020 - Reflected XSS vulnerability identified in Portal for ArcGIS. (11.3, 11.1, 10.9.1)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57871</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57872 | BUG-000174150 - Unvalidated redirect in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57872</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57873 | BUG-000175222 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57873</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57874 | BUG-000161627 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.  (11.3, 11.1, 10.9.1)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57874</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57875 | BUG-000164122 - Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57875</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57876 | Stored XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57876</link><description>There is a stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in  Esri Portal for ArcGIS  11.4 and below that may allow a remote, authenticated attacker to inject malicious a file with an embedded xss script which when loaded could potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the victim’s browser. The privileges required to execute this attack are high. The attack could disclose a privileged token which may result in the attacker gaining full control of the Portal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57877 | Reflected XSS vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57877</link><description>There is a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote authenticated attacker with administrative access to supply a crafted string which would execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the  browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57878 | BUG-000174149 - The Portal for ArcGIS has an unvalidated redirect.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57878</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57879 | BUG-000171009 - URL manipulation vulnerability in Portal for ArcGIS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57879</link><description>There is an unvalidated redirect vulnerability in Esri Portal for ArcGIS 11.4 and below that may allow a remote, unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL that could redirect a victim to an arbitrary website, simplifying phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36099 | IBM WebSphere Application Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36099</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially-crafted request. A privileged user could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43400 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.1, macOS Tahoe 26.0.1, ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43400</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.8.1, macOS Tahoe 26.0.1, macOS Sequoia 15.7.1, visionOS 26.0.1, iOS 26.0.1 and iPadOS 26.0.1, iOS 18.7.1 and iPadOS 18.7.1. Processing a maliciously crafted font may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56807 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FairSketch RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 allows an administrator to store a JavaSc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56807</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in FairSketch RISE Ultimate Project Manager &amp; CRM 3.9.4 allows an administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the file explorer in the admin dashboard when creating new folders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41250 | Header injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41250</link><description>VMware vCenter contains an SMTP header injection vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on vCenter who has permission to create scheduled tasks may be able to manipulate the notification emails sent for scheduled tasks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57197 | In the Payeer Android application 2.5.0, an improper access control vulnerability exists in the authentication flow for the PIN change featu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57197</link><description>In the Payeer Android application 2.5.0, an improper access control vulnerability exists in the authentication flow for the PIN change feature. A local attacker with root access to the device can dynamically instrument the app to bypass the current PIN verification check and directly modify the authentication PIN. This allows unauthorized users to change PIN without knowing the original/current PIN.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57483 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tawk.to chatbox widget v4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57483</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in tawk.to chatbox widget v4 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript in the context of the user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the vulnerable parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57412 | An issue in SunOS Omnios v5.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via repeatedly sending crafted TCP packets.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57412</link><description>An issue in SunOS Omnios v5.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via repeatedly sending crafted TCP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56233 | Openindiana, kernel SunOS 5.11 has a denial of service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP packets with RST or SYN flag set, Openindian...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56233</link><description>Openindiana, kernel SunOS 5.11 has a denial of service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP packets with RST or SYN flag set, Openindiana has a wide acceptable range of sequence numbers. It does not require the sequence number to exactly match the next expected sequence value, just to be within the current receive window, which violates RFC5961. This flaw allows attackers to send multiple random TCP RST/SYN packets to hit the acceptable range of sequence numbers, thereby interrupting normal connections and causing a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7104 | Mass Assignment in danny-avila/librechat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7104</link><description>A mass assignment vulnerability exists in danny-avila/librechat, affecting all versions. This vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate sensitive fields by automatically binding user-provided data to internal object properties or database fields without proper filtering. As a result, any extra fields in the request body are included in agentData and passed to the database layer, allowing overwriting of any field in the schema, such as author, access_level, isCollaborative, and projectIds. Additionally, the Object.Prototype can be polluted due to the use of Object.assign with spread operators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51495 | An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the WebSocket component of Mongoose 7.5 thru 7.17. By sending a specially crafted WebSocket requ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51495</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the WebSocket component of Mongoose 7.5 thru 7.17. By sending a specially crafted WebSocket request, an attacker can cause the application to crash. If downstream vendors integrate this component improperly, the issue may lead to a buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56234 | AT_NA2000 from Nanda Automation Technology vendor has a denial-of-service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP RST packets, PLC AT_NA200...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56234</link><description>AT_NA2000 from Nanda Automation Technology vendor has a denial-of-service vulnerability. For the processing of TCP RST packets, PLC AT_NA2000 has a wide acceptable range of sequence numbers. It does not require the sequence number to exactly match the next expected sequence value, just to be within the current receive window, which violates RFC5961. This flaw allows attackers to send multiple random TCP RST packets to hit the acceptable range of sequence numbers, thereby interrupting normal connections and causing a denial-of-service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61659 | bash-git-prompt 2.6.1 through 2.7.1 insecurely uses the /tmp/git-index-private$$ file, which has a predictable name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61659</link><description>bash-git-prompt 2.6.1 through 2.7.1 insecurely uses the /tmp/git-index-private$$ file, which has a predictable name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56795 | Mealie 3.0.1 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the recipe creation functionality. Unsanitized user input in the "no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56795</link><description>Mealie 3.0.1 and earlier is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the recipe creation functionality. Unsanitized user input in the "note" and "text" fields of the "/api/recipes/{recipe_name}" endpoint is rendered in the frontend without proper escaping leading to persistent XSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41245 | VMSA-2025-0015: VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools updates address multiple vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-41244,CVE-2025-41245, CVE-2025-41246)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41245</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges in Aria Operations may exploit this vulnerability to disclose credentials of other users of Aria Operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41244 | VMSA-2025-0015: VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools updates address multiple vulnerabilities (CVE-2025-41244,CVE-2025-41245, CVE-2025-41246)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41244</link><description>VMware Aria Operations and VMware Tools contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious local actor with non-administrative privileges having access to a VM with VMware Tools installed and managed by Aria Operations with SDMP enabled may exploit this vulnerability to escalate privileges to root on the same VM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41246 | Improper authorisation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41246</link><description>VMware Tools for Windows contains an improper authorisation vulnerability due to the way it handles user access controls. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges on a guest VM, who is already authenticated through vCenter or ESX may exploit this issue to access other guest VMs. Successful exploitation requires knowledge of credentials of the targeted VMs and vCenter or ESX.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11155 | WEAK ENCODING FOR PASSWORD IN DEVICE SERVER CONFIGURATION</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11155</link><description>The credentials required to access the device's web server are sent in base64 within the HTTP headers. Since base64 is not considered a strong cipher, an attacker could intercept the web request handling the login and obtain the credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55795 | The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses incremental user IDs and insufficient email ownership verification during e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55795</link><description>The openml/openml.org web application version v2.0.20241110 uses incremental user IDs and insufficient email ownership verification during email update workflows. An authenticated attacker controlling a user account with a lower user ID can update their email address to that of another user with a higher user ID without proper verification. This results in the victim's email being reassigned to the attacker's account, causing the victim to be locked out immediately and unable to log in. The vulnerability leads to denial of service via account lockout but does not grant the attacker direct access to the victim's private data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36351 | IBM License Metric Tool bypass security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36351</link><description>IBM License Metric Tool 9.2.0 through 9.2.40 

could allow an authenticated user to bypass access controls in the REST API interface and perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36352 | IBM License Metric Tool cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36352</link><description>IBM License Metric Tool 9.2.0 through 9.2.40 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57516 | OS Command injection vulnerability in PublicCMS PublicCMS-V5.202506.a, and PublicCMS-V5.202506.b allowing attackers to execute arbitrary com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57516</link><description>OS Command injection vulnerability in PublicCMS PublicCMS-V5.202506.a, and PublicCMS-V5.202506.b allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands via crafted DATABASE, USERNAME, or PASSWORD variables to the backupDB.bat file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56449 | A security vulnerability was identified in Obsidian Scheduler's REST API 5.0.0 thru 6.3.0. If an account is locked out due to not enrolling ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56449</link><description>A security vulnerability was identified in Obsidian Scheduler's REST API 5.0.0 thru 6.3.0. If an account is locked out due to not enrolling in MFA (e.g. after the 7-day enforcement window), the REST API still allows the use of Basic Authentication to authenticate and perform administrative actions. In particular, the default admin account was found to be locked out via the web interface but still usable through the REST API. This allowed creation of a new privileged user, bypassing MFA protections. This undermines the intended security posture of MFA enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57428 | Default credentials in Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRouter.20190211 allows attackers to gain access to the debug shel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57428</link><description>Default credentials in Italy Wireless Mini Router WIRELESS-N 300M v28K.MiniRouter.20190211 allows attackers to gain access to the debug shell exposed via Telnet on Port 23 and execute hardware-level flash and register manipulation commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13150 | SQLi in Fayton Software&amp;#x27;s fayton.pro ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13150</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Fayton Software and Consulting Services fayton.Pro ERP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects fayton.Pro ERP: through 20250929.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9648 | Denial of Service in CivetWeb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9648</link><description>A vulnerability in the CivetWeb library's function mg_handle_form_request allows remote attackers to trigger a denial of service (DoS) condition. By sending a specially crafted HTTP POST request containing a null byte in the payload, the server enters an infinite loop during form data parsing. Multiple malicious requests will result in complete CPU exhaustion and render the service unresponsive to further requests.

This issue was fixed in commit 782e189. This issue affects only the library, standalone executable pre-built by vendor is not affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:50:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8868 | Chef Automate compliance service SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8868</link><description>In Progress Chef Automate, versions earlier than 4.13.295, on Linux x86 platform, an authenticated attacker can gain access to Chef Automate restricted functionality in the compliance service via 

improperly neutralized inputs used in an SQL command using a well-known token.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6724 | Chef Automate SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6724</link><description>In Progress Chef Automate, versions earlier than 4.13.295, on Linux x86 platform, an authenticated attacker can gain access to Chef Automate restricted functionality in multiple services via improperly neutralized inputs used in an SQL command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11150 | asdasdasdasdasdasdasd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11150</link><description>asdasdasdasdasdasdasd</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11146 | Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Apt-Cacher-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11146</link><description>Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) in Apt-Cacher-NG v3.2.1. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts (XSS) in the web management application. The vulnerability is caused by improper handling of GET inputs included in the URL in “/acng-report.html”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11147 | Reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Apt-Cacher-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11147</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) in Apt-Cacher-NG v3.2.1. The vulnerability allows malicious scripts (XSS) to be executed in “/html/.html”.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10346 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10346</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'subject' at the endpoint 'knoewledge_base/article'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10341 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10341</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'company' at the endpoint '/clients/client/x.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10342 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10342</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'name' at the endpoint '/subscriptions/create'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10343 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10343</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameter 'expense_name' at the endpoint '/expenses/expense'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10344 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10344</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'name' and 'clientid' at the endpoint '/projects/project/x'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10345 | HTML injection in Perfex CRM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10345</link><description>HTML injection vulnerability in Perfex CRM v3.2.1 consisting of a 
stored HTML injection due to lack of proper validation of user input by 
sending a POST request in the parameters 'name' and 'address' at the endpoint 'admin/leads/lead'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48006 | Improper restriction of XML external entity reference issue exists in DataSpider Servista 4.4 and earlier. If a specially crafted request is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48006</link><description>Improper restriction of XML external entity reference issue exists in DataSpider Servista 4.4 and earlier. If a specially crafted request is processed, arbitrary files on the file system where the server application for the product is installed may be read, or a denial-of-service (DoS) condition may occur.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5200 | Postie &amp;lt; 1.9.71 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5200</link><description>The Postie WordPress plugin before 1.9.71 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 06:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11141 | Ruijie NBR2100G-E branch_passw.php listAction os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Ruijie NBR2100G-E up to 20250919. Affected by this issue is the function listAction of the file /itbox_pi/branch_passw.php?a=list. Performing manipulation of the argument city results in os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10504 | Heap Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10504</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ABB Terra AC wallbox.This issue affects Terra AC wallbox: through 1.8.33.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11140 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.richclient.RichClientService openForm xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function openForm of the component com.artery.richclient.RichClientService. Such manipulation of the argument contentString leads to xml external entity reference. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11139 | Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP com.artery.form.services.FormStudioUpdater uploadStudioFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Bjskzy Zhiyou ERP up to 11.0. Affected is the function uploadStudioFile of the component com.artery.form.services.FormStudioUpdater. This manipulation of the argument filepath causes path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 03:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11138 | mirweiye wenkucms common.php createPathOne os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mirweiye wenkucms up to 3.4. This impacts the function createPathOne of the file app/common/common.php. The manipulation results in os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11137 | Gstarsoft GstarCAD File Renaming cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Gstarsoft GstarCAD up to 9.4.0. This affects an unknown function of the component File Renaming Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11136 | YiFang CMS Backend File.php webUploader unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11136</link><description>A flaw has been found in YiFang CMS up to 2.0.2. The impacted element is the function webUploader of the file app/app/controller/File.php of the component Backend. Executing manipulation of the argument uploadpath can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11135 | pmTicket Project-Management-Software Cookie class.database.php loadLanguage deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in pmTicket Project-Management-Software up to 2ef379da2075f4761a2c9029cf91d073474e7486. The affected element is the function loadLanguage of the file classes/class.database.php of the component Cookie Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument user_id results in deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 02:53:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11134 | Cudy TR1200 Wireless Settings config cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Cudy TR1200 1.16.3-20230804-164635. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/luci/admin/network/wireless/config/ of the component Wireless Settings Page. Such manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7698 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Pl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7698</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9903 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9903</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerabilities in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9904 | Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Gener...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9904</link><description>Unallocated memory access vulnerability in print processing of Generic Plus PCL6 Printer Driver / Generic Plus UFR II Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPS4 Printer Driver / Generic Plus LIPSLX Printer Driver / Generic Plus PS Printer Driver</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11130 | iHongRen pptp-vpn XPC Service HelperTool.m shouldAcceptNewConnection missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11130</link><description>A weakness has been identified in iHongRen pptp-vpn 1.0/1.0.1 on macOS. This issue affects the function shouldAcceptNewConnection of the file HelpTool/HelperTool.m of the component XPC Service. This manipulation causes missing authentication. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11126 | Apeman ID71 system.ini hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11126</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Apeman ID71 218.53.203.117. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/www/system.ini. The manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11125 | langleyfcu Online Banking System Error Message connection_error.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11125</link><description>A vulnerability was found in langleyfcu Online Banking System up to 57437e6400ce0ae240e692c24e6346b8d0c17d7a. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /connection_error.php of the component Error Message Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument Error results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11124 | code-projects Project Monitoring System postjob.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11124</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Project Monitoring System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /onlineJobSearchEngine/postjob.php. Such manipulation of the argument txtapplyto leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11123 | Tenda AC18 saveAutoQos stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11123</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/saveAutoQos. This manipulation of the argument enable causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11122 | Tenda AC18 WizardHandle stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11122</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/WizardHandle. The manipulation of the argument WANT/mtuvalue results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11121 | Tenda AC18 AdvSetLanip command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11121</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanIp leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11120 | Tenda AC8 SetServerConfig formSetServerConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11120</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. The affected element is the function formSetServerConfig of the file /goform/SetServerConfig. Executing manipulation can lead to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11119 | itsourcecode Hostel Management System POST Request index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11119</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Hostel Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /justines/index.php of the component POST Request Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument from results in cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11118 | CodeAstro Student Grading System adminLogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11118</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CodeAstro Student Grading System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminLogin.php. Such manipulation of the argument staffId leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:21:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11117 | Tenda CH22 GstDhcpSetSer formWrlExtraGet buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11117</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This vulnerability affects the function formWrlExtraGet of the file /goform/GstDhcpSetSer. This manipulation of the argument dips causes buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11116 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System add.home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11116</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add.home.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11115 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addtime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11115</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addtime.php. The manipulation of the argument starttime/endtime leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11114 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application leaveAplicationForm.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11114</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /leaveAplicationForm.php. Executing manipulation of the argument absence[] can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11113 | CodeAstro Online Leave Application signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11113</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Online Leave Application 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /signup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument city results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11112 | PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System myprofile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11112</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Employee Record Management System 1.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /myprofile.php. Such manipulation of the argument First name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11111 | Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System candidates_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11111</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Advanced Online Voting Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/candidates_edit.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11110 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System school_year.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11110</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/school_year.php. The manipulation of the argument school_year results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11109 | Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System us_edit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11109</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Computer Sales and Inventory System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pages/us_edit.php?action=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11108 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11108</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /schedulingsystem/addroom.php. Executing manipulation of the argument room can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11107 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addcourse.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /schedulingsystem/addcourse.php. Performing manipulation of the argument corcode results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11106 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addfaculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11106</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /schedulingsystem/addfaculty.php. Such manipulation of the argument falname leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11105 | code-projects Simple Scheduling System addsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11105</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Scheduling System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /schedulingsystem/addsubject.php. This manipulation of the argument subcode causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11104 | CodeAstro Electricity Billing System bill.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11104</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Electricity Billing System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/bill.php. The manipulation of the argument uid results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 12:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11103 | Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels change-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11103</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Projectworlds Online Tours and Travels 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/change-image.php. The manipulation of the argument packageimage leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 11:17:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11102 | Campcodes Online Learning Management System edit_content.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11102</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Learning Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_content.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Title can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11101 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11101</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /jobportal/admin/company/index.php?view=edit. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 07:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11100 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists uci_set command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11100</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function uci_set of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11099 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_prohibiting uci_del command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11099</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The impacted element is the function uci_del of the file /goform/delete_prohibiting. This manipulation of the argument delvalue causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:35:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11098 | D-Link DIR-823X set_wifi_blacklists command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11098</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_wifi_blacklists. The manipulation of the argument macList results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11097 | D-Link DIR-823X set_device_name command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11097</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/set_device_name. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11096 | D-Link DIR-823X diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11096</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/diag_traceroute. Executing manipulation of the argument target_addr can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11095 | D-Link DIR-823X delete_offline_device command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11095</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/delete_offline_device. Performing manipulation of the argument delvalue results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 04:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11094 | code-projects E-Commerce Website admin_product_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11094</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/admin_product_details.php. Such manipulation of the argument prod_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11092 | D-Link DIR-823X set_switch_settings sub_412E7C command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11092</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is the function sub_412E7C of the file /goform/set_switch_settings. This manipulation of the argument port causes command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11091 | Tenda AC21 SetStaticRouteCfg sscanf buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11091</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda AC21 up to 16.03.08.16. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sscanf of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11090 | itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11090</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Open Source Job Portal 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/employee/index.php?view=edit. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 02:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11089 | kidaze CourseSelectionSystem COUNT3s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11089</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in kidaze CourseSelectionSystem up to 42cd892b40a18d50bd4ed1905fa89f939173a464. This impacts an unknown function of the file /Profilers/PriProfile/COUNT3s4.php. Executing manipulation of the argument cbranch can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:43:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>