<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-42506 | Unauthenticated Command Injection Vulnerabilities in the CLI Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42506</link><description>Command injection vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's Access Point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42507 | Unauthenticated Command Injection Vulnerabilities in the CLI Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42507</link><description>Command injection vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's Access Point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26687 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the product_data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26687</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via the product_data parameter in the PDF Add-on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26689 | An issue discovered in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows attackers to alter arbitrary user account profiles via crafted post request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26689</link><description>An issue discovered in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows attackers to alter arbitrary user account profiles via crafted post request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42505 | Unauthenticated Command Injection Vulnerabilities in the CLI Service Accessed by the PAPI Protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42505</link><description>Command injection vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's Access Point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities results in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45599 | TCC Bypass in Cursor&amp;#x27;s macOS Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45599</link><description>Cursor is an artificial intelligence code editor. Prior to version 0.41.0, if a user on macOS has granted Cursor access to the camera or microphone, any program that is run on the machine is able to access the camera or the microphone without explicitly being granted access, through a DyLib Injection using DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES environment variable. The usage of `com.apple.security.cs.allow-dyld-environment-variables` and `com.apple.security.cs.disable-library-validation` allows an external dynamic library to be injected into the application using DYLD_INSERT_LIBRARIES environment variable. 
Moreover, the entitlement `com.apple.security.device.camera` allows the application to use the host camera and `com.apple.security.device.audio-input` allows the application to use the microphone. This means that untrusted code that is executed on the user's machine can access the camera or the microphone, if the user has already given permission for Cursor to do so. In version 0.41.0, the entitlements have been split by process: the main process gets the camera and microphone entitlements, but not the DyLib entitlements, whereas the extension host process gets the DyLib entitlements but not the camera or microphone entitlements. As a workaround, do not explicitly give Cursor the permission to access the camera or microphone if untrusted users can run arbitrary commands on the affected machine.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 18:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26690 | File Upload vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via File Manager/Editor component in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26690</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via File Manager/Editor component in the vendor or admin menu.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26691 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted zip file when inst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26691</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted zip file when installing a new add-on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42797 | An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/ajax.php?action=delete_playlist in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42797</link><description>An Incorrect Access Control vulnerability was found in /music/ajax.php?action=delete_playlist in Kashipara Music Management System v1.0. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to delete the valid music playlist entries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8067 | Unicode &amp;quot;best fit&amp;quot; argument injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8067</link><description>In versions of Helix Core prior to 2024.1 Patch 2 (2024.1/2655224) a Windows ANSI API Unicode "best fit" argument injection was identified.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26686 | File Upload vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via the image upload feature when cust...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26686</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via the image upload feature when customizing a shop.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26688 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via the product_data pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26688</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CS-Cart MultiVendor 4.16.1 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary code via the product_data parameter of add/edit product in the administration interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8877 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8877</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements results in a SQL Injection vulnerability in Riello Netman 204. It is only limited to the SQLite database of measurement data.This issue affects Netman 204: through 4.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8878 | Unauthenticated Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8878</link><description>The password recovery mechanism for the forgotten password in Riello Netman 204 allows an attacker to reset the admin password and take over control of the device.This issue affects Netman 204: through 4.05.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9148 | Flowise Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9148</link><description>Flowise &lt; 2.1.1 suffers from a Stored Cross-Site vulnerability due to a lack of input sanitization in Flowise Chat Embed &lt; 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8940 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability on Scriptcase</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8940</link><description>Vulnerability in the Scriptcase application version 9.4.019, which involves the arbitrary upload of a file via /scriptcase/devel/lib/third/jquery_plugin/jQuery-File-Upload/server/php/ via a POST request. An attacker could upload malicious files to the server due to the application not properly verifying user input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8941 | Path Traversal vulnerability on Scriptcase</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8941</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in Scriptcase version 9.4.019, in /scriptcase/devel/compat/nm_edit_php_edit.php (in the “subpage” parameter), which allows unauthenticated remote users to bypass SecurityManager's intended restrictions and list and/or read a parent directory via a “/...” or directly into a path used in the POST parameter “field_file” by a web application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8942 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability on Scriptcase</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8942</link><description>Vulnerability in Scriptcase version 9.4.019 that consists of a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), due to the lack of input validation, affecting the “id_form_msg_title” parameter, among others. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted URL to a victim and retrieve their credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8801 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.12.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8801</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.2 via the Content Switcher widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including private, draft, and pending Elementor templates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9141 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Oct8ne</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9141</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Oct8ne system. This flaw could allow an attacker to embed harmful JavaScript code into the body of a chat message. This manipulation occurs when the chat content is intercepted and altered, leading to the execution of the JavaScript payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:58:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38324 | IBM Storage Defender improper certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38324</link><description>IBM Storage Defender 2.0.0 through 2.0.7 on-prem defender-sensor-cmd CLI does not validate server name during registration and unregistration operations which could expose sensitive information to an attacker with access to the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38963 | IBM Aspera Console CSV injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38963</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by a CSV injection vulnerability. By persuading a victim to open a specially crafted file, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43845 | IBM Aspera Console information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43845</link><description>IBM Aspera Console 3.4.0 through 3.4.4 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to set the HTTPOnly flag. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information from the cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9142 | Local File Inclusion (LFI) in Olgu Computer Systems&amp;#x27; e-Belediye</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9142</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path, : Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in Olgu Computer Systems e-Belediye allows Manipulating Web Input to File System Calls.This issue affects e-Belediye: before 2.0.642.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 08:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5359 | W3 Total Cache &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Sensitive Credentials Stored in Plaintext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5359</link><description>The W3 Total Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 via Google OAuth API secrets stored in plaintext in the publicly visible plugin source. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to impersonate W3 Total Cache and gain access to user account information in successful conditions. This would not impact the WordPress users site in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39928 | Apache Linkis Spark EngineConn: Commons Lang&amp;#x27;s RandomStringUtils Random string security vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39928</link><description>In Apache Linkis &lt;= 1.5.0, a Random string security vulnerability in Spark EngineConn, random string generated by the Token when starting Py4j uses the Commons Lang's RandomStringUtils.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.6.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8436 | WP Easy Gallery – WordPress Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8436</link><description>The WP Easy Gallery – WordPress Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'edit_imageId' and 'edit_imageDelete' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8437 | WP Easy Gallery – WordPress Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Gallery Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8437</link><description>The WP Easy Gallery – WordPress Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions hooked via AJAX like wpeg_settings and wpeg_add_gallery in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to modify galleries.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21545 | Proxmox Virtual Environment is an open-source server management platform for enterprise virtualization. Insufficient safeguards against mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21545</link><description>Proxmox Virtual Environment is an open-source server management platform for enterprise virtualization. Insufficient safeguards against malicious API response values allow authenticated attackers with 'Sys.Audit' or 'VM.Monitor' privileges to download arbitrary host files via the API.
When handling the result from a request handler before returning it to the user, the handle_api2_request function will check for the ‘download’ or ‘data’-&gt;’download’ objects inside the request handler call response object. If present, handle_api2_request will read a local file defined by this object and return it to the user.
Two endpoints were identified which can control the object returned by a request handler sufficiently that the ’download’ object is defined and user controlled. This results in arbitrary file read.
The privileges of this file read can result in full compromise of the system by various impacts such as disclosing sensitive files allowing for privileged session forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8103 | WP Category Dropdown &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8103</link><description>The WP Category Dropdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'align' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8267 | Radio Player – Live Shoutcast, Icecast and Any Audio Stream Player for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.0.78 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8267</link><description>The Radio Player – Live Shoutcast, Icecast and Any Audio Stream Player for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'align' attribute within the 'wp:radio-player' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.78 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8914 | Thanh Toán Quét Mã QR Code Tự Động – MoMo, ViettelPay, VNPay và 40 ngân hàng Việt Nam &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8914</link><description>The Thanh Toán Quét Mã QR Code Tự Động – MoMo, ViettelPay, VNPay và 40 ngân hàng Việt Nam plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to incorrect use of the wp_kses_allowed_html function, which allows the 'onclick' attribute for certain HTML elements without sufficient restriction or context validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8917 | AnWP Football Leagues &amp;lt;= 0.16.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8917</link><description>The AnWP Football Leagues plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.16.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8919 | Confetti Fall Animation &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via confetti-fall-animation Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8919</link><description>The Confetti Fall Animation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'confetti-fall-animation' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46957 | Mellium mellium.im/xmpp 0.0.1 through 0.21.4 allows response spoofing because the stanza type is not checked. This is fixed in 0.22.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46957</link><description>Mellium mellium.im/xmpp 0.0.1 through 0.21.4 allows response spoofing because the stanza type is not checked. This is fixed in 0.22.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-2439 | Easy Digital Downloads – Simple eCommerce for Selling Digital Files &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHAR Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-2439</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – Simple eCommerce for Selling Digital Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to deserialization of untrusted input via the 'upload[file]' parameter in versions up to, and including 3.3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated administrative users to call files using a PHAR wrapper, that will deserialize and call arbitrary PHP Objects that can be used to perform a variety of malicious actions granted a POP chain is also present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8628 | Popup, Optin Form &amp;amp; Email Newsletters for Mailchimp, HubSpot, AWeber – MailOptin &amp;lt;= 1.2.70.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8628</link><description>The Popup, Optin Form &amp; Email Newsletters for Mailchimp, HubSpot, AWeber – MailOptin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'post-meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.70.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8671 | WooEvents &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8671</link><description>The WooEvents - Calendar and Event Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file overwrite due to insufficient file path validation in the inc/barcode.php file in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to overwrite arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8623 | MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter &amp;lt;= 1.3.3.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8623</link><description>The The MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3.3. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:04:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8624 | MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter &amp;lt;= 1.3.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8624</link><description>The MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'meta_key' attribute of the 'mdf_select_title' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:04:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8791 | Donation Forms by Charitable – Donations Plugin &amp;amp; Fundraising Platform for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.8.1.14 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8791</link><description>The Donation Forms by Charitable – Donations Plugin &amp; Fundraising Platform for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1.14. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity when the ID parameter is supplied through the update_core_user() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the email address and password of arbitrary user accounts, including administrators, which can then be used to log in to those user accounts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8794 | BA Book Everything &amp;lt;= 1.6.20 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8794</link><description>The BA Book Everything plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary password reset in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.20. This is due to the reset_user_password() function not verifying a user's identity prior to setting a password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset any user's passwords, including administrators. It's important to note that the attacker will not have access to the generated password, therefore, privilege escalation is not possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 03:04:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38269 | An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the USB file-sharing handler of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmwar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38269</link><description>An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the USB file-sharing handler of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware versions through 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause potential memory corruptions, resulting in a thread crash on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8432 | Appointment &amp;amp; Event Booking Calendar Plugin – Webba Booking &amp;lt;= 5.0.48 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) CSS Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8432</link><description>The Appointment &amp; Event Booking Calendar Plugin – Webba Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_appearance() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.48. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify the booking form's CSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8544 | Pixel Cat – Conversion Pixel Manager &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8544</link><description>The Pixel Cat – Conversion Pixel Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8657 | Garden Gnome Package &amp;lt;= 2.2.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8657</link><description>The Garden Gnome Package plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ggpkg shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8662 | Koko Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.3.12 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8662</link><description>The Koko Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8716 | XT Ajax Add To Cart for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8716</link><description>The XT Ajax Add To Cart for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8738 | Seriously Simple Stats &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8738</link><description>The Seriously Simple Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8795 | BA Book Everything &amp;lt;= 1.6.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Email Address Update/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8795</link><description>The BA Book Everything plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.20. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the my_account_update() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update a user's account details via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This can be leveraged to reset a user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38266 | An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the parameter type parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38266</link><description>An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the parameter type parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware versions through 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause potential memory corruptions, resulting in a thread crash on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38267 | An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the IPv6 address parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38267</link><description>An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the IPv6 address parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware versions through 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause potential memory corruptions, resulting in a thread crash on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38268 | An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the MAC address parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38268</link><description>An improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in the MAC address parser of the Zyxel VMG8825-T50K firmware versions through 5.50(ABOM.8)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to cause potential memory corruptions, resulting in a thread crash on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 02:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7024 | Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7024</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 126.0.6478.54 allowed a remote attacker to potentially perform a sandbox escape via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:10:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7023 | Insufficient data validation in Updater in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6537.0 allowed a remote attacker to perform privilege escalation via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7023</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Updater in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6537.0 allowed a remote attacker to perform privilege escalation via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-20072 | Insufficient data validation in PDF in Google Chrome prior to 73.0.3683.75 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-20072</link><description>Insufficient data validation in PDF in Google Chrome prior to 73.0.3683.75 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted PDF file. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38023 | Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 92.0.4515.107 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38023</link><description>Use after free in Extensions in Google Chrome prior to 92.0.4515.107 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7281 | Inappropriate implementation in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7281</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Compositing in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.105 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7282 | Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 113.0.5672.63 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7282</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 113.0.5672.63 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform domain spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7018 | Heap buffer overflow in PDF in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.78 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7018</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in PDF in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.78 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted PDF file. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7019 | Inappropriate implementation in UI in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7019</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in UI in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7020 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7020</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.60 allowed a remote attacker to perform UI spoofing via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7022 | Uninitialized Use in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7022</link><description>Uninitialized Use in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 123.0.6312.58 allowed a remote attacker to perform out of bounds memory access via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 22:07:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42861 | An issue in IEEE 802.1AS linuxptp v.4.2 and before allowing a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Pdelay_Req message ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42861</link><description>An issue in IEEE 802.1AS linuxptp v.4.2 and before allowing a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted Pdelay_Req message to the time synchronization function</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8263 | An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed arbitrary workflows to be committed using an improperly scoped PAT through the use of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8263</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability allowed arbitrary workflows to be committed using an improperly scoped PAT through the use of nested tags. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server and was fixed in version 3.10.17, 3.11.15, 3.12.9, 3.13.4, and 3.14.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8770 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the repository transfer feature of GitHub Enterprise Server, which allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8770</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the repository transfer feature of GitHub Enterprise Server, which allows attackers to steal sensitive user information via social engineering. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server and was fixed in version 3.10.17, 3.11.15, 3.12.9, 3.13.4, and 3.14.1. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44540 | Ubiquiti AirMax firmware version firmware version 8 allows attackers with physical access to gain a privileged command shell via the UART De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44540</link><description>Ubiquiti AirMax firmware version firmware version 8 allows attackers with physical access to gain a privileged command shell via the UART Debugging Port.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37779 | WoodWing Elvis DAM v6.98.1 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Apache Ant script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37779</link><description>WoodWing Elvis DAM v6.98.1 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the Apache Ant script functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43201 | The Planet Fitness Workouts iOS and Android mobile apps prior to version 9.8.12 (released on 2024-07-25) fail to properly validate TLS certi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43201</link><description>The Planet Fitness Workouts iOS and Android mobile apps prior to version 9.8.12 (released on 2024-07-25) fail to properly validate TLS certificates, allowing an attacker with appropriate network access to obtain session tokens and sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46639 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HelpDeskZ v2.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted paylo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46639</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in HelpDeskZ v2.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Name text field of Custom Fields message box.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47222 | New Cloud MyOffice SDK Collaborative Editing Server 2.2.2 through 2.8 allows SSRF via manipulation of requests from external document storag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47222</link><description>New Cloud MyOffice SDK Collaborative Editing Server 2.2.2 through 2.8 allows SSRF via manipulation of requests from external document storage via the MS-WOPI protocol.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39843 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Centreon 24.04.2 allows a remote high-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary SQL command via create user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39843</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Centreon 24.04.2 allows a remote high-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary SQL command via create user form inputs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39842 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Centreon 24.04.2 allows a remote high-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary SQL command via user massive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39842</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Centreon 24.04.2 allows a remote high-privileged attacker to execute arbitrary SQL command via user massive changes inputs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 18:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39341 | Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (On Premise) Software (formerly known as Cardwizard) 6.10.0, 6.9.0, 6.9.1, 6.9.2, and 6.8.x and earlier l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39341</link><description>Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (On Premise) Software (formerly known as Cardwizard) 6.10.0, 6.9.0, 6.9.1, 6.9.2, and 6.8.x and earlier leaves behind a configuration file (i.e. WebAPI.cfg.xml) after the installation process. This file can be accessed without authentication on HTTP port 80 by guessing the correct IIS webroot path. It includes system configuration parameter names and values with sensitive configuration values encrypted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 18:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39342 | Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (formerly known as Cardwizard) 6.10.0, 6.9.0, 6.9.1, 6.9.2, and 6.8.x and earlier uses a DLL library (i.e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39342</link><description>Entrust Instant Financial Issuance (formerly known as Cardwizard) 6.10.0, 6.9.0, 6.9.1, 6.9.2, and 6.8.x and earlier uses a DLL library (i.e. DCG.Security.dll) with a custom AES encryption process that relies on static hard-coded key values. These keys are not uniquely generated per installation of the software. Combined with the encrypted password that can be obtained from "WebAPI.cfg.xml" in CVE-2024-39341, the decryption is trivial and can lead to privilege escalation on the Windows host.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 18:18:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0001 | A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby a local account intended for initial array configuration remains active potentially allowing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0001</link><description>A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby a local account intended for initial array configuration remains active potentially allowing a malicious actor to gain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0005 | A condition exists in FlashArray and FlashBlade Purity whereby a malicious user could execute arbitrary commands remotely through a specific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0005</link><description>A condition exists in FlashArray and FlashBlade Purity whereby a malicious user could execute arbitrary commands remotely through a specifically crafted SNMP configuration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0002 | A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby an attacker can employ a privileged account allowing remote access to the array.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0002</link><description>A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby an attacker can employ a privileged account allowing remote access to the array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0003 | A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby a malicious user could use a remote administrative service to create an account on the array...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0003</link><description>A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby a malicious user could use a remote administrative service to create an account on the array allowing privileged access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0004 | A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby an user with array admin role can execute arbitrary commands remotely to escalate privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0004</link><description>A condition exists in FlashArray Purity whereby an user with array admin role can execute arbitrary commands remotely to escalate privilege on the array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46948 | A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found on Temenos T24 Browser R19.40 that enables a remote attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46948</link><description>A reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found on Temenos T24 Browser R19.40 that enables a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code via the skin parameter in the about.jsp and genrequest.jsp components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9014 | OAuth2 client id and secret exposed through the web browser in pgAdmin 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9014</link><description>pgAdmin versions 8.11 and earlier are vulnerable to a security flaw in OAuth2 authentication. This vulnerability allows an attacker to potentially obtain the client ID and secret, leading to unauthorized access to user data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40441 | An issue in Doccano Open source annotation tools for machine learning practitioners v.1.8.4 and Doccano Auto Labeling Pipeline module to ann...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40441</link><description>An issue in Doccano Open source annotation tools for machine learning practitioners v.1.8.4 and Doccano Auto Labeling Pipeline module to annotate a document automatically v.0.1.23 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the model_attribs parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40442 | An issue in Doccano Open source annotation tools for machine learning practitioners v.1.8.4 and Doccano Auto Labeling Pipeline module to ann...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40442</link><description>An issue in Doccano Open source annotation tools for machine learning practitioners v.1.8.4 and Doccano Auto Labeling Pipeline module to annotate a document automatically v.0.1.23 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted REST Request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34331 | A lack of code signature verification in Parallels Desktop for Mac v19.3.0 and below allows attackers to escalate privileges via a crafted m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34331</link><description>A lack of code signature verification in Parallels Desktop for Mac v19.3.0 and below allows attackers to escalate privileges via a crafted macOS installer, because Parallels Service is setuid root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47068 | DOM Clobbering Gadget found in rollup bundled scripts that leads to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47068</link><description>Rollup is a module bundler for JavaScript. Versions prior to 3.29.5 and 4.22.4 are susceptible to a DOM Clobbering vulnerability when bundling scripts with properties from `import.meta` (e.g., `import.meta.url`) in `cjs`/`umd`/`iife` format. The DOM Clobbering gadget can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) in web pages where scriptless attacker-controlled HTML elements (e.g., an `img` tag with an unsanitized `name` attribute) are present. Versions 3.29.5 and 4.22.4  contain a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47069 | Oveleon Cookiebar reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47069</link><description>Oveleon Cookie Bar is a cookie bar is for the Contao Open Source CMS and allows a visitor to define cookie &amp; privacy settings for the website. Prior to versions 1.16.3 and 2.1.3, the `block/locale` endpoint does not properly sanitize the user-controlled `locale` input before including it in the backend's HTTP response, thereby causing reflected cross-site scripting. Versions 1.16.3 and 2.1.3 contain a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41228 | A symlink following vulnerability in the pouch cp function of AliyunContainerService pouch v1.3.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41228</link><description>A symlink following vulnerability in the pouch cp function of AliyunContainerService pouch v1.3.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46985 | DataEase has an XXE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46985</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization analysis tool. Prior to version 2.10.1, there is an XML external entity injection vulnerability in the static resource upload interface of DataEase. An attacker can construct a payload to implement intranet detection and file reading. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46997 | DataEase&amp;#x27;s H2 datasource has a remote command execution risk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46997</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization analysis tool. Prior to version 2.10.1, an attacker can achieve remote command execution by adding a carefully constructed h2 data source connection string. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47066 | Lobe Chat has insufficient fix for GHSA-mxhq-xw3g-rphc (CVE-2024-32964)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47066</link><description>Lobe Chat is an open-source artificial intelligence chat framework. Prior to version 1.19.13, server-side request forgery protection implemented in `src/app/api/proxy/route.ts` does not consider redirect and could be bypassed when attacker provides an external malicious URL which redirects to internal resources like a private network or loopback address. Version 1.19.13 contains an improved fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23922 | Sony XAV-AX5500 Insufficient Firmware Update Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23922</link><description>Sony XAV-AX5500 Insufficient Firmware Update Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sony XAV-AX5500 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of software updates. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of software update packages. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-22939</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23972 | Sony XAV-AX5500 USB Configuration Descriptor Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23972</link><description>Sony XAV-AX5500 USB Configuration Descriptor Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sony XAV-AX5500 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the USB host driver. A crafted USB configuration descriptor can trigger an overflow of a fixed-length buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23185</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23933 | Sony XAV-AX5500 CarPlay TLV Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23933</link><description>Sony XAV-AX5500 CarPlay TLV Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of 	Sony XAV-AX5500 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the Apple CarPlay protocol. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

Was ZDI-CAN-23238</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23934 | Sony XAV-AX5500 WMV/ASF Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23934</link><description>Sony XAV-AX5500 WMV/ASF Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sony XAV-AX5500 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of WMV/ASF files. A crafted Extended Content Description Object in a WMV media file can trigger an overflow of a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.

. Was ZDI-CAN-22994.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46241 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System v1.1 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the pname parameter in add_product.php and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46241</link><description>PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System v1.1 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via the pname parameter in add_product.php and edit_product.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 13:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7835 | Reflected XSS in Exnet Informatics Software&amp;#x27;s Ferry Reservation System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7835</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Exnet Informatics Software Ferry Reservation System allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ferry Reservation System: before 240805-002.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 11:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7735 | SQLi in Exnet Informatics Software&amp;#x27;s Ferry Reservation System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7735</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Exnet Informatics Software Ferry Reservation System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Ferry Reservation System: before 240805-002.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 11:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46544 | Apache Tomcat Connectors: mod_jk: local users can view and modify configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46544</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Apache Tomcat Connectors allows local users to view and modify shared memory containing mod_jk configuration which may lead to information disclosure and/or denial of service.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat Connectors: from 1.2.9-beta through 1.2.49. Only mod_jk on Unix like systems is affected. Neither the ISAPI redirector nor mod_jk on Windows is affected.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.2.50, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 10:52:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48945 | media: vivid: fix compose size exceed boundary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48945</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: vivid: fix compose size exceed boundary

syzkaller found a bug:

 BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffc9000a3b1000
 #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
 #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
 PGD 100000067 P4D 100000067 PUD 10015f067 PMD 1121ca067 PTE 0
 Oops: 0002 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
 CPU: 0 PID: 23489 Comm: vivid-000-vid-c Not tainted 6.1.0-rc1+ #512
 Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.13.0-1ubuntu1.1 04/01/2014
 RIP: 0010:memcpy_erms+0x6/0x10
[...]
 Call Trace:
  
  ? tpg_fill_plane_buffer+0x856/0x15b0
  vivid_fillbuff+0x8ac/0x1110
  vivid_thread_vid_cap_tick+0x361/0xc90
  vivid_thread_vid_cap+0x21a/0x3a0
  kthread+0x143/0x180
  ret_from_fork+0x1f/0x30
  

This is because we forget to check boundary after adjust compose-&gt;height
int V4L2_SEL_TGT_CROP case. Add v4l2_rect_map_inside() to fix this problem
for this case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 09:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8903 | Local active protection service settings manipulation due to unnecessary privileges assignment. The following products are affected: Acronis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8903</link><description>Local active protection service settings manipulation due to unnecessary privileges assignment. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows, macOS) before build 38565.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 09:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45348 | Xiaomi Router AX9000 has a post-authorization command injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45348</link><description>Xiaomi Router AX9000 has a post-authorization command injection vulnerability. This vulnerability is caused by the lack of validation of user input, and an attacker can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8606 | Fix 2FA bypass via RestAPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8606</link><description>Bypass of two factor authentication in RestAPI in Checkmk &lt; 2.3.0p16 and &lt; 2.2.0p34 allows authenticated users to bypass two factor authentication</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 07:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7846 | YITH WooCommerce Ajax Search &amp;lt; 2.7.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7846</link><description>YITH WooCommerce Ajax Search is vulnerable to a XSS vulnerability due to insufficient sanitization of user supplied block attributes. This makes it possible for Contributors+ attackers to inject arbitrary scripts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 06:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8758 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt; 9.1.3 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8758</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.1.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 06:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47227 | iRedAdmin before 2.6 allows XSS, e.g., via order_name.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47227</link><description>iRedAdmin before 2.6 allows XSS, e.g., via order_name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 03:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9094 | code-projects Blood Bank System o-.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9094</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/blood/update/o-.php. The manipulation of the argument bloodname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43996 | WordPress ElementsKit Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43996</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in ElementsKit ElementsKit Pro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ElementsKit Pro: from n/a through 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44048 | WordPress Product Carousel Slider &amp;amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.10 - Authenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44048</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpWax Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45453 | WordPress Maintenance Redirect  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - IP Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45453</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Peter Hardy-vanDoorn Maintenance Redirect allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Maintenance Redirect: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9092 | SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh Registration Form add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add.php of the component Registration Form. The manipulation of the argument full_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9093 | SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh GET Parameter del.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9093</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file del.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument list leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43989 | WordPress Justified Image Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43989</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Firsh Justified Image Grid allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Justified Image Grid: from n/a through 4.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9091 | code-projects Student Record System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9091</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument regno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9089 | SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System update_loan_record.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9089</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file update_loan_record.php. The manipulation of the argument amount leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9090 | SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System search_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9090</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file search_member.php. The manipulation of the argument searchMember leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9087 | code-projects Vehicle Management edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9087</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit1.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9088 | SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9088</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function login. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9086 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System filter.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9086</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /filter.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "from" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "to" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 21:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40703 | IBM Cognos Analytics information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40703</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, and IBM Cognos Analytics Reports for iOS 11.0.0.7 could allow a local attacker to obtain sensitive information in the form of an API key.  An attacker could use this information to launch further attacks against affected applications.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 12:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9084 | code-projects Blood Bank System bbms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9084</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file bbms.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/age/bloodgroup/city/phno/gender as part of String leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 09:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9083 | SourceCodester Employee Management System add-admin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9083</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/add-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9082 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop User Creation Users.phpf=save improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9082</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Users.phpf=save of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation of the argument type with the input 1 leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9085 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9085</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions sid as affected paramater which is incorrect.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 07:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9081 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop view_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9081</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file view_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 07:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9080 | code-projects Student Record System pincode-verification.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9080</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9079 | code-projects Student Record System marks.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9079</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /marks.php. The manipulation of the argument coursename leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 04:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9078 | code-projects Student Record System course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9078</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /course.php. The manipulation of the argument coursename leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47226 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in NetBox 4.1.0 within the "Configuration History" feature of the "Admin" panel via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47226</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in NetBox 4.1.0 within the "Configuration History" feature of the "Admin" panel via a /core/config-revisions/ Add action. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary JavaScript or HTML into the "Top banner" field.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9077 | dingfangzu Order Checkout order.js cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9077</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in dingfangzu up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. Affected is an unknown function of the file scripts/order.js of the component Order Checkout. The manipulation of the argument address-name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47221 | CheckUser in ScadaServerEngine/MainLogic.cs in Rapid SCADA through 5.8.4 allows an empty password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47221</link><description>CheckUser in ScadaServerEngine/MainLogic.cs in Rapid SCADA through 5.8.4 allows an empty password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47218 | An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows bypassing authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47218</link><description>An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows bypassing authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47219 | An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows shell command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47219</link><description>An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows shell command injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47220 | An issue was discovered in the WEBrick toolkit through 1.8.1 for Ruby. It allows HTTP request smuggling by providing both a Content-Length h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47220</link><description>An issue was discovered in the WEBrick toolkit through 1.8.1 for Ruby. It allows HTTP request smuggling by providing both a Content-Length header and a Transfer-Encoding header, e.g., "GET /admin HTTP/1.1\r\n" inside of a "POST /user HTTP/1.1\r\n" request. NOTE: the supplier's position is "Webrick should not be used in production."</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9076 | DedeCMS article_string_mix.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS up to 5.7.115. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file article_string_mix.php. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>