<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10771 | jeecgboot JimuReport DB2 JDBC testConnection deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10771</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 2.1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /drag/onlDragDataSource/testConnection of the component DB2 JDBC Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument clientRerouteServerListJNDIName can lead to deserialization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10770 | jeecgboot JimuReport MySQL JDBC testConnection deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10770</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jeecgboot JimuReport up to 2.1.2. This impacts an unknown function of the file /drag/onlDragDataSource/testConnection of the component MySQL JDBC Handler. Performing manipulation results in deserialization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 22:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10767 | CosmodiumCS OnlyRAT Configuration File main.py remote_download os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10767</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CosmodiumCS OnlyRAT up to 3.2. The affected element is the function connect/remote_upload/remote_download of the file main.py of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation of the argument configuration["PASSWORD"] results in os command injection. The attack requires a local approach. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53692 | Sitecore Experience Platform Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sitecore Sitecore Experience Manager (XM), Sitecore Experience Platform (XP) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Sitecore Experience Manager (XM): from 9.2 through 10.4; Experience Platform (XP): from 9.2 through 10.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10768 | h2oai h2o-3 IBMDB2 JDBC Driver ImportSQLTable deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10768</link><description>A flaw has been found in h2oai h2o-3 up to 3.46.08. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /99/ImportSQLTable of the component IBMDB2 JDBC Driver. This manipulation of the argument connection_url causes deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10769 | h2oai h2o-3 H2 JDBC Driver ImportSQLTable deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10769</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in h2oai h2o-3 up to 3.46.08. This affects an unknown function of the file /99/ImportSQLTable of the component H2 JDBC Driver. Such manipulation of the argument connection_url leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6544 | Deserialization Vulnerability in h2oai/h2o-3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6544</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability exists in h2oai/h2o-3 versions &lt;= 3.46.0.8, allowing attackers to read arbitrary system files and execute arbitrary code. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of JDBC connection parameters, which can be exploited by bypassing regular expression checks and using double URL encoding. This issue impacts all users of the affected versions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 09:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10766 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS EventViewerController.cs Download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10766</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This issue affects the function Download of the file EventViewerController.cs. Executing manipulation of the argument ID can lead to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 07:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10765 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS SEOSuggestions ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions.dll server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10765</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This vulnerability affects the function CheckPage/Suggestions in the library cms-v4.3\wwwroot\Plugins\ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions\ZKEACMS.SEOSuggestions.dll of the component SEOSuggestions. Performing manipulation results in server-side request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 06:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10764 | SeriaWei ZKEACMS Event Action System PendingTaskController.cs Edit server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10764</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SeriaWei ZKEACMS up to 4.3. This affects the function Edit of the file src/ZKEACMS.EventAction/Controllers/PendingTaskController.cs of the component Event Action System. Such manipulation of the argument Data leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 05:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10763 | academico-sis academico Profile Picture edit-photo unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10763</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in academico-sis academico up to d9a9e2636fbf7e5845ee086bcb03ca62faceb6ab. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit-photo of the component Profile Picture Handler. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 05:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10762 | kuaifan DooTask UsersController.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10762</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kuaifan DooTask up to 1.2.49. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file app/Http/Controllers/Api/UsersController.php. The manipulation of the argument keys[department] results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 04:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10761 | Harness Login Endpoint login excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10761</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Harness 3.3.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/v1/login of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 03:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10760 | Harness lookup_repo.go LookupRepo server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10760</link><description>A flaw has been found in Harness 3.3.0. This impacts the function LookupRepo of the file app/api/controller/gitspace/lookup_repo.go. Executing manipulation of the argument url can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 03:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10759 | Webkul QloApps CSRF Token authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10759</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Webkul QloApps up to 1.7.0. This affects an unknown function of the component CSRF Token Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument token results in authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor explains: "As We are already aware about this vulnerability and our Internal team are already working on this issue. (...) We'll implement the fix for this vulnerability in our next major release."</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10758 | htmly Custom Field post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10758</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in htmly up to 3.1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /htmly/admin/field/post of the component Custom Field Handler. Such manipulation of the argument label leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:07:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10757 | UTT 1200GW formConfigDnsFilterGlobal buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10757</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 1200GW up to 3.0.0-170831. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /goform/formConfigDnsFilterGlobal. This manipulation of the argument GroupName causes buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 23:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10756 | UTT HiPER 840G getOneApConfTempEntry buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10756</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in UTT HiPER 840G up to 3.1.1-190328. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /goform/getOneApConfTempEntry. The manipulation of the argument tempName results in buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 22:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10755 | Selleo Mentingo Content-Type unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10755</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Selleo Mentingo 2025.08.27. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Content-Type Handler. The manipulation of the argument userAvatar results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 21:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40925 | Starch versions 0.14 and earlier generate session ids insecurely</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40925</link><description>Starch versions 0.14 and earlier generate session ids insecurely.

The default session id generator returns a SHA-1 hash seeded with a counter, the epoch time, the built-in rand function, the PID, and internal Perl reference addresses. The PID will come from a small set of numbers, and the epoch time may be guessed, if it is not leaked from the HTTP Date header. The built-in rand function is unsuitable for cryptographic usage.

Predicable session ids could allow an attacker to gain access to systems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10741 | Selleo Mentingo Profile Picture unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10741</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Selleo Mentingo up to 2025.08.27. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation of the argument userAvatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 12:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10658 | SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp;amp; Customer Support Ticket System &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Authentication Bypass to Support Session Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10658</link><description>The SupportCandy – Helpdesk &amp; Customer Support Ticket System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7. This is due to missing rate limiting on the OTP verification for guest login. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to customer support tickets by brute forcing the 6-digit OTP code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9882 | osTicket WP Bridge &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9882</link><description>The osTicket WP Bridge plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9883 | Browser Sniff &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9883</link><description>The Browser Sniff plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9887 | Custom Login And Signup Widget &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9887</link><description>The Custom Login And Signup Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the /frndzk_adminclsw.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the email and username settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 06:50:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10002 | ClickWhale &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10002</link><description>The ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp; Link Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the export_csv() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This may be exploitable by lower level users if access to the plugin is granted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10181 | Draft List &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10181</link><description>The Draft List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'drafts' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10305 | Secure Passkeys &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Passkey Exposure and Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10305</link><description>The Secure Passkeys plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the delete_passkey() and passkeys_list() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view and delete passkeys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10489 | SureForms – Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Form Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10489</link><description>The SureForms – Drag and Drop Contact Form Builder – Multi-step Forms, Conversational Forms and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized creation of forms due to a missing capability check on the register_post_types() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to create forms when the user interface specifically prohibits it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9949 | Internal Links Manager &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9949</link><description>The Internal Links Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the link deletion functionality in the process_bulk_action() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete SEO links via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 04:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10652 | Robcore Netatmo &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via robcore-netatmo Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10652</link><description>The Robcore Netatmo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘module_id’ attribute of the robcore-netatmo shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43808 | The Commerce component in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.112, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43808</link><description>The Commerce component in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.112, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.8, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions saves virtual products uploaded to Documents and Media with guest view permission, which allows remote attackers to access and download virtual products for free via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59689 | Libraesva ESG 4.5 through 5.5.x before 5.5.7 allows command injection via a compressed e-mail attachment. For ESG 5.0 a fix has been release...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59689</link><description>Libraesva ESG 4.5 through 5.5.x before 5.5.7 allows command injection via a compressed e-mail attachment. For ESG 5.0 a fix has been released in 5.0.31. For ESG 5.1 a fix has been released in 5.1.20. For ESG 5.2 a fix has been released in 5.2.31. For ESG 5.4 a fix has been released in 5.4.8. For ESG 5.5. a fix has been released in 5.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56762 | Paracrawl KeOPs v2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in error.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56762</link><description>Paracrawl KeOPs v2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in error.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57396 | Tandoor Recipes 2.0.0-alpha-1, fixed in 2.0.0-alpha-2, is vulnerable to privilege escalation. This is due to the rework of the API, which re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57396</link><description>Tandoor Recipes 2.0.0-alpha-1, fixed in 2.0.0-alpha-2, is vulnerable to privilege escalation. This is due to the rework of the API, which resulted in the User Profile API Endpoint containing two boolean values indicating whether a user is staff or administrative. Consequently, any user can escalate their privileges to the highest level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10568 | HyperX NGENUITY - Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10568</link><description>HyperX NGENUITY software is potentially vulnerable to arbitrary code execution. HP is releasing updated software to address the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52159 | Hardcoded credentials in default configuration of PPress 0.0.9.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52159</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in default configuration of PPress 0.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54761 | An issue was discovered in PPress 0.0.9 allowing attackers to gain escilated privlidges via crafted session cookie.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54761</link><description>An issue was discovered in PPress 0.0.9 allowing attackers to gain escilated privlidges via crafted session cookie.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54815 | Server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in PPress 0.0.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted themes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54815</link><description>Server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability in PPress 0.0.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted themes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9081 | IDOR in board file download allows any user to download any file by UUID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9081</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.8, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.17 fail to properly validate access controls which allows any authenticated user to download sensitive files via board file download endpoint using UUID enumeration</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59431 | MapServer - WFS XML Filter Query SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59431</link><description>MapServer is a system for developing web-based GIS applications. Prior to 8.4.1, the XML Filter Query directive PropertyName is vulnerably to Boolean-based SQL injection. It seems like expression checking is bypassed by introducing double quote characters in the PropertyName. Allowing to manipulate backend database queries. This vulnerability is fixed in 8.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:37:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9079 | Admin RCE via prepackaged plugins by way of misconfigured imports directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9079</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.8.x &lt;= 10.8.3, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.8, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.17, 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.1, 10.9.x &lt;= 10.9.3 fail to validate import directory path configuration which allows admin users to execute arbitrary code via malicious plugin upload to prepackaged plugins directory</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43809 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the server (license) registration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and old...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43809</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in the server (license) registration page in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.7, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.9, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to register a server license via the 'orderUuid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4980 | General Bytes Crypto Application Server (CAS) Unauthenticated Creation of Admin Account via Default-installation/First-admin Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4980</link><description>General Bytes Crypto Application Server (CAS) beginning with version 20201208 prior to 20220531.38 (backport) and 20220725.22 (mainline) contains an authentication bypass in the admin web interface. An unauthenticated attacker could invoke the same URL used by the product's default-installation / first-admin creation page and create a new administrative account remotely. By gaining admin privileges, the attacker can change the ATM configuration resulting in redirected funds. Public vendor advisories and multiple independent writeups describe the vulnerability as a call to the page used for initial/default installation / first administration user creation; General Bytes has not publicly published the exact endpoint/parameter name. The issue was actively exploited in the wild against cloud-hosted and standalone CAS deployments (scanning exposed CAS instances on ports 7777/443), and publicly acknowledged by the General Bytes in September 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13990 | MicroWorld eScan AV Insecure Update Mechanism Allows Man-in-the-Middle Replacement of Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13990</link><description>MicroWorld eScan AV's update mechanism failed to ensure authenticity and integrity of updates: update packages were delivered and accepted without robust cryptographic verification. As a result, an on-path attacker could perform a man-in-the-middle (MitM) attack and substitute malicious update payloads for legitimate ones. The eScan AV client accepted these substituted packages and executed or loaded their components (including sideloaded DLLs and Java/installer payloads), enabling remote code execution on affected systems. MicroWorld eScan confirmed remediation of the update mechanism on 2023-07-31 but versioning details are unavailable. NOTE: MicroWorld eScan disputes the characterization in third-party reports, stating the issue relates to 2018–2019 and that controls were implemented then.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26516 | CVE-2025-26516 Denial of Service Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26516</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly 
StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.8.0.15 and 11.9.0.8 are 
susceptible to a Denial of Service vulnerability. Successful exploit 
could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service on 
the Admin node.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26517 | CVE-2025-26517 Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26517</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly 
StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.8.0.15 and 11.9.0.8 are 
susceptible to a privilege escalation vulnerability. Successful exploit 
could allow an unauthorized authenticated attacker to discover Grid node
 names and IP addresses or modify Storage Grades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34189 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Inter-Process Communication Allows Local Session Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34189</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 1.0.735 and Application versions prior to 20.0.1330 (macOS/Linux client deployments) contain a vulnerability in the local inter-process communication (IPC) mechanism. The software stores IPC request and response files inside /opt/PrinterInstallerClient/tmp with world-readable and world-writable permissions. Any local user can craft malicious request files that are processed by privileged daemons, leading to unauthorized actions being executed in other user sessions. This breaks user session isolation, potentially allowing local attackers to hijack sessions, perform unintended actions in the context of other users, and impact system integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34190 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) PrinterInstallerClientService Authentication Bypass via LD_PRELOAD Hooking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34190</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (macOS/Linux client deployments) are vulnerable to an authentication bypass in PrinterInstallerClientService. The service requires root privileges for certain administrative operations, but these checks rely on calls to geteuid(). By preloading a malicious shared object overriding geteuid(), a local attacker can trick the service into believing it is running with root privileges. This bypass enables execution of administrative commands (e.g., enabling debug mode, managing configurations, or invoking privileged features) without proper authorization. While some actions requiring write access to protected files may still fail, the flaw effectively breaks the intended security model of the inter-process communication (IPC) system, allowing local attackers to escalate privileges and compromise system integrity. NOTE: This vulnerability has been address, but an affected version range is not yet fully determined. We will update this record as soon as the vendor provides confirmed version information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34191 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Arbitrary File Write as Root via Response Path Symlink Follow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34191</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.843 and Application prior to 20.0.1923 (macOS/Linux client deployments) contain an arbitrary file write vulnerability via the response file handling. When tasks produce output the service writes response data into files under /opt/PrinterInstallerClient/tmp/responses/ reusing the requested filename. The service follows symbolic links in the responses directory and writes as the service user (typically root), allowing a local, unprivileged user to cause the service to overwrite or create arbitrary files on the filesystem as root. This can be used to modify configuration files, replace or inject binaries or drivers, and otherwise achieve local privilege escalation and full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34202 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Access to Docker Instances WAN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34202</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host prior to 25.2.169 and Application prior to 25.2.1518 (VA and SaaS deployments) expose Docker internal networks in a way that allows an attacker on the same external L2 segment — or an attacker able to add routes using the appliance as a gateway — to reach container IPs directly. This grants access to internal services (HTTP APIs, Redis, MySQL, etc.) that are intended to be isolated inside the container network. Many of those services are accessible without authentication or are vulnerable to known exploitation chains. As a result, compromise of a single reachable endpoint or basic network access can enable lateral movement, remote code execution, data exfiltration, and full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34205 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Dangerous PHP Dead Code Enables RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34205</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.843 and Application prior to 20.0.1923 (VA and SaaS deployments) contains dangerous PHP dead code present in multiple Docker-hosted PHP instances. A script named /var/www/app/resetroot.php (found in several containers) lacks authentication checks and, when executed, performs a SQL update that sets the database administrator username to 'root' and its password hash to the SHA-512 hash of the string 'password'. Separately, commented-out code in /var/www/app/lib/common/oses.php would unserialize session data (unserialize($_SESSION['osdata']))—a pattern that can enable remote code execution if re-enabled or reached with attacker-controlled serialized data. An attacker able to reach the resetroot.php endpoint can trivially reset the MySQL root password and obtain full database control; combined with deserialization issues this can lead to full remote code execution and system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34206 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Shared Storage Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34206</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (VA and SaaS deployments) mount host configuration and secret material under /var/www/efs_storage into many Docker containers with overly-permissive filesystem permissions. Files such as secrets.env, GPG-encrypted blobs in .secrets, MySQL client keys, and application session files are accessible from multiple containers. An attacker who controls or reaches any container can read or modify these artifacts, leading to credential theft, RCE via Laravel APP_KEY, Portainer takeover, and full compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43803 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Contacts Center widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and older uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43803</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Contacts Center widget in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.119, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.6, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions allows remote attackers to view contact information, including the contact’s name and email address, via the _com_liferay_contacts_web_portlet_ContactsCenterPortlet_entryId parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34188 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Local Log Disclosure of Cleartext Sessions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34188</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 1.0.735 and Application prior to 20.0.1330 (macOS/Linux client deployments) contain a vulnerability in the local logging mechanism. Authentication session tokens, including PHPSESSID, XSRF-TOKEN, and laravel_session, are stored in cleartext within world-readable log files. Any local user with access to the machine can extract these session tokens and use them to authenticate remotely to the SaaS environment, bypassing normal login credentials, potentially leading to unauthorized system access and exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34193 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure Windows Components Lack Modern Memory Protections and Use Outdated Runtimes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34193</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application include Windows client components (PrinterInstallerClientInterface.exe, PrinterInstallerClient.exe, PrinterInstallerClientLauncher.exe) that lack modern compile-time and runtime exploit mitigations and rely on outdated runtimes. These binaries are built as 32-bit, without Data Execution Prevention (DEP), Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR), Control Flow Guard (CFG), or stack-protection, and they incorporate legacy technologies (Pascal/Delphi and Python 2) which are no longer commonly maintained. Several of these processes run with elevated privileges (NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM for PrinterInstallerClient.exe and PrinterInstallerClientLauncher.exe), and the client automatically downloads and installs printer drivers. The absence of modern memory safety mitigations and the use of unmaintained runtimes substantially increase the risk that memory-corruption or other exploit primitives — for example from crafted driver content or maliciously crafted inputs — can be turned into remote or local code execution and privilege escalation to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34194 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Local Privilege Escalation via Insecure Temporary File Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34194</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (Windows client deployments) contain an insecure temporary-file handling vulnerability in the PrinterInstallerClient components. The software creates files as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM inside a directory under the control of the local user (C:\Users\%USER%\AppData\Local\Temp\). An attacker who can place symbolic links or otherwise influence filenames in that directory can cause the service to follow the link and write to arbitrary filesystem locations as SYSTEM. This allows a local, unprivileged user to overwrite or create files as SYSTEM, leading to local privilege escalation and the ability to modify configuration files, replace or inject binaries, or otherwise compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system. NOTE: This vulnerability has been addressed, but an affected version range is not yet fully determined. This record will be updated when the vendor provides confirmed version information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34199 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Insecure SSL Verification Allows Man-in-the-Middle Attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34199</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.1049 and Application versions prior to 20.0.2786 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain insecure defaults and code patterns that disable TLS/SSL certificate verification for communications to printers and internal microservices. In multiple places, the application sets libcurl/PHP transport options such that CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYHOST and CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYPEER are effectively disabled, and environment variables (for example API_*_VERIFYSSL=false) are used to turn off verification for gateway and microservice endpoints. As a result, the client accepts TLS connections without validating server certificates (and, in some cases, uses clear-text HTTP), permitting on-path attackers to perform man-in-the-middle (MitM) attacks. An attacker able to intercept network traffic between the product and printers or microservices can eavesdrop on and modify sensitive data (including print jobs, configuration, and authentication tokens), inject malicious payloads, or disrupt service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34200 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Network Account Password Stored in Cleartext</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34200</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (VA and SaaS deployments)  provision the appliance with the network account credentials in clear-text inside /etc/issue, and the file is world-readable by default. An attacker with local shell access can read /etc/issue to obtain the network account username and password. Using the network account an attacker can change network parameters via the appliance interface, enabling local misconfiguration, network disruption or further escalation depending on deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34201 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Lack of Network Segmentation Between Docker Instances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34201</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (VA and SaaS deployments) run many Docker containers on shared internal networks without firewalling or segmentation between instances. A compromise of any single container allows direct access to internal services (HTTP, Redis, MySQL, etc.) on the overlay network. From a compromised container, an attacker can reach and exploit other services, enabling lateral movement, data theft, and system-wide compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34204 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Processes Running as Root Inside Docker Instances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34204</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host and Application (VA and SaaS deployments) contains multiple Docker containers that run primary application processes (for example PHP workers, Node.js servers and custom binaries) as the root user. This increases the blast radius of a container compromise and enables lateral movement and host compromise when a container is breached.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26514 | CVE-2025-26514 Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26514</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly 
StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.8.0.15 and 11.9.0.8 are 
susceptible to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. 
Successful exploit could allow an attacker to view or modify 
configuration settings or add or modify user accounts but requires the 
attacker to know specific information about the target instance and then
 trick a privileged user into clicking a specially crafted link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26515 | CVE-2025-26515 Server-Side Request Forgery Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26515</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly 
StorageGRID Webscale) versions prior to 11.8.0.15 and 11.9.0.8 without 
Single Sign-on enabled are susceptible to a Server-Side Request Forgery 
(SSRF) vulnerability. Successful exploit could allow an unauthenticated 
attacker to change the password of any Grid Manager or Tenant Manager 
non-federated user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34192 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Usage of Outdated and Unsupported OpenSSL Version</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34192</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.893 and Application versions prior to 20.0.2140 (macOS/Linux client deployments) are built against OpenSSL 1.0.2h-fips (released May 2016), which has been end-of-life since 2019 and is no longer supported by the OpenSSL project. Continued use of this outdated cryptographic library exposes deployments to known vulnerabilities that are no longer patched, weakening the overall security posture. Affected daemons may emit deprecation warnings and rely on cryptographic components with unresolved security flaws, potentially enabling attackers to exploit weaknesses in TLS/SSL processing or cryptographic operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34195 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Unquoted Path During Driver Installation Leads to Execution of C:\Program.exe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34195</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 1.0.735 and Application prior to 20.0.1330 (Windows client deployments) contain a remote code execution vulnerability during driver installation caused by unquoted program paths. The PrinterInstallerClient driver-installation component launches programs using an unquoted path under "C:\Program Files (x86)\Printer Properties Pro\Printer Installer". Because the path is unquoted, the operating system may execute a program located at a short-path location such as C:\Program.exe before the intended binaries in the quoted path. If an attacker can place or cause a program to exist at that location, it will be executed with the privileges of the installer process (which may be elevated), enabling arbitrary code execution and potential privilege escalation. This weakness can be used to achieve remote code execution and full compromise of affected Windows endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34197 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Undocumented Local Account with Hardcoded Password and Passwordless sudo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34197</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.951, Application prior to 20.0.2368 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain an undocumented local user account named ubuntu with a preset password and a sudoers entry granting that account passwordless root privileges (ubuntu ALL=(ALL) NOPASSWD: ALL). Anyone who knows the hardcoded password can obtain root privileges via local console or equivalent administrative access, enabling local privilege escalation. NOTE: The patch for this vulnerability is reported to be incomplete: /etc/shadow was remediated but /etc/sudoers remains vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34198 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Shared / Hardcoded SSH Host Private Keys in Appliance Image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34198</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.951 and Application prior to 20.0.2368 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain shared, hardcoded SSH host private keys in the appliance image. The same private host keys (RSA, ECDSA, and ED25519) are present across installations, rather than being uniquely generated per appliance. An attacker who obtains these private keys (for example from one compromised appliance image or another installation) can impersonate the appliance, decrypt or intercept SSH connections to appliances that use the same keys, and perform man-in-the-middle or impersonation attacks against administrative SSH sessions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34203 | Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Use of Outdated, End-Of-Life, and Vulnerable Third-Party Components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34203</link><description>Vasion Print (formerly PrinterLogic) Virtual Appliance Host versions prior to 22.0.1002 and Application versions prior to 20.0.2614 (VA and SaaS deployments) contain multiple Docker containers that include outdated, end-of-life, unsupported, or otherwise vulnerable third-party components (examples: Nginx 1.17.x, OpenSSL 1.1.1d, various EOL Alpine/Debian/Ubuntu base images, and EOL Laravel/PHP libraries). These components are present across many container images and increase the product's attack surface, enabling exploitation chains when leveraged by an attacker. Multiple distinct EOL versions and unpatched libraries across containers; Nginx binaries date from 2019 in several images and Laravel versions observed include EOL releases (for example Laravel 5.5.x, 5.7.x, 5.8.x).</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48703 | CWP (aka Control Web Panel or CentOS Web Panel) before 0.9.8.1205 allows unauthenticated remote code execution via shell metacharacters in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48703</link><description>CWP (aka Control Web Panel or CentOS Web Panel) before 0.9.8.1205 allows unauthenticated remote code execution via shell metacharacters in the t_total parameter in a filemanager changePerm request. A valid non-root username must be known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10721 | Webull Investing &amp;amp; Trading App AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10721</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Webull Investing &amp; Trading App 11.2.5.63 on Android. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file AndroidManifest.xml. This manipulation causes improper export of android application components. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10722 | SKTLab Mukbee App com.dw.android.mukbee AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10722</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SKTLab Mukbee App 1.01.196 on Android. This affects an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.dw.android.mukbee. The manipulation results in improper export of android application components. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36248 | IBM Copy Services Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36248</link><description>IBM Copy Services Manager 6.3.13 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10718 | Ooma Office Business Phone App com.ooma.office2 improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10718</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ooma Office Business Phone App up to 7.2.2 on Android. This affects an unknown part of the component com.ooma.office2. The manipulation results in improper export of android application components. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56869 | Directory traversal vulnerability in Sync In server thru 1.1.1 allowing authenticated attackers to gain read and write access to the system ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56869</link><description>Directory traversal vulnerability in Sync In server thru 1.1.1 allowing authenticated attackers to gain read and write access to the system via FilesManager.saveMultipart function in backend/src/applications/files/services/files-manager.service.ts, and FilesManager.compress function in backend/src/applications/files/services/files-manager.service.ts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57296 | Tenda AC6 router firmware 15.03.05.19 contains a command injection vulnerability in the formSetIptv function, which processes requests to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57296</link><description>Tenda AC6 router firmware 15.03.05.19 contains a command injection vulnerability in the formSetIptv function, which processes requests to the /goform/SetIPTVCfg web interface. When handling the list and vlanId parameters, the sub_ADBC0 helper function concatenates these user-supplied values into nvram set system commands using doSystemCmd, without validating or sanitizing special characters (e.g., ;, ", #). An unauthenticated or authenticated attacker can exploit this by submitting a crafted POST request, leading to arbitrary system command execution on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59427 | Cloudflare vite plugin exposes secrets over the built-in dev server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59427</link><description>The Cloudflare Vite plugin enables a full-featured integration between Vite and the Workers runtime. When utilising the Cloudflare Vite plugin in its default configuration, all files are exposed by the local dev server, including files in the root directory that contain secret information such as .env and .dev.vars. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39837 | platform/x86: asus-wmi: Fix racy registrations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39837</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

platform/x86: asus-wmi: Fix racy registrations

asus_wmi_register_driver() may be called from multiple drivers
concurrently, which can lead to the racy list operations, eventually
corrupting the memory and hitting Oops on some ASUS machines.
Also, the error handling is missing, and it forgot to unregister ACPI
lps0 dev ops in the error case.

This patch covers those issues by introducing a simple mutex at
acpi_wmi_register_driver() &amp; *_unregister_driver, and adding the
proper call of asus_s2idle_check_unregister() in the error path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39838 | cifs: prevent NULL pointer dereference in UTF16 conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39838</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

cifs: prevent NULL pointer dereference in UTF16 conversion

There can be a NULL pointer dereference bug here. NULL is passed to
__cifs_sfu_make_node without checks, which passes it unchecked to
cifs_strndup_to_utf16, which in turn passes it to
cifs_local_to_utf16_bytes where '*from' is dereferenced, causing a crash.

This patch adds a check for NULL 'src' in cifs_strndup_to_utf16 and
returns NULL early to prevent dereferencing NULL pointer.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39839 | batman-adv: fix OOB read/write in network-coding decode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39839</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

batman-adv: fix OOB read/write in network-coding decode

batadv_nc_skb_decode_packet() trusts coded_len and checks only against
skb-&gt;len. XOR starts at sizeof(struct batadv_unicast_packet), reducing
payload headroom, and the source skb length is not verified, allowing an
out-of-bounds read and a small out-of-bounds write.

Validate that coded_len fits within the payload area of both destination
and source sk_buffs before XORing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39840 | audit: fix out-of-bounds read in audit_compare_dname_path()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39840</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

audit: fix out-of-bounds read in audit_compare_dname_path()

When a watch on dir=/ is combined with an fsnotify event for a
single-character name directly under / (e.g., creating /a), an
out-of-bounds read can occur in audit_compare_dname_path().

The helper parent_len() returns 1 for "/". In audit_compare_dname_path(),
when parentlen equals the full path length (1), the code sets p = path + 1
and pathlen = 1 - 1 = 0. The subsequent loop then dereferences
p[pathlen - 1] (i.e., p[-1]), causing an out-of-bounds read.

Fix this by adding a pathlen &gt; 0 check to the while loop condition
to prevent the out-of-bounds access.

[PM: subject tweak, sign-off email fixes]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39841 | scsi: lpfc: Fix buffer free/clear order in deferred receive path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39841</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: lpfc: Fix buffer free/clear order in deferred receive path

Fix a use-after-free window by correcting the buffer release sequence in
the deferred receive path. The code freed the RQ buffer first and only
then cleared the context pointer under the lock. Concurrent paths (e.g.,
ABTS and the repost path) also inspect and release the same pointer under
the lock, so the old order could lead to double-free/UAF.

Note that the repost path already uses the correct pattern: detach the
pointer under the lock, then free it after dropping the lock. The
deferred path should do the same.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39842 | ocfs2: prevent release journal inode after journal shutdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39842</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: prevent release journal inode after journal shutdown

Before calling ocfs2_delete_osb(), ocfs2_journal_shutdown() has already
been executed in ocfs2_dismount_volume(), so osb-&gt;journal must be NULL. 
Therefore, the following calltrace will inevitably fail when it reaches
jbd2_journal_release_jbd_inode().

ocfs2_dismount_volume()-&gt;
  ocfs2_delete_osb()-&gt;
    ocfs2_free_slot_info()-&gt;
      __ocfs2_free_slot_info()-&gt;
        evict()-&gt;
          ocfs2_evict_inode()-&gt;
            ocfs2_clear_inode()-&gt;
	      jbd2_journal_release_jbd_inode(osb-&gt;journal-&gt;j_journal,

Adding osb-&gt;journal checks will prevent null-ptr-deref during the above
execution path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39843 | mm: slub: avoid wake up kswapd in set_track_prepare</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39843</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: slub: avoid wake up kswapd in set_track_prepare

set_track_prepare() can incur lock recursion.
The issue is that it is called from hrtimer_start_range_ns
holding the per_cpu(hrtimer_bases)[n].lock, but when enabled
CONFIG_DEBUG_OBJECTS_TIMERS, may wake up kswapd in set_track_prepare,
and try to hold the per_cpu(hrtimer_bases)[n].lock.

Avoid deadlock caused by implicitly waking up kswapd by passing in
allocation flags, which do not contain __GFP_KSWAPD_RECLAIM in the
debug_objects_fill_pool() case. Inside stack depot they are processed by
gfp_nested_mask().
Since ___slab_alloc() has preemption disabled, we mask out
__GFP_DIRECT_RECLAIM from the flags there.

The oops looks something like:

BUG: spinlock recursion on CPU#3, swapper/3/0
 lock: 0xffffff8a4bf29c80, .magic: dead4ead, .owner: swapper/3/0, .owner_cpu: 3
Hardware name: Qualcomm Technologies, Inc. Popsicle based on SM8850 (DT)
Call trace:
spin_bug+0x0
_raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x80
hrtimer_try_to_cancel+0x94
task_contending+0x10c
enqueue_dl_entity+0x2a4
dl_server_start+0x74
enqueue_task_fair+0x568
enqueue_task+0xac
do_activate_task+0x14c
ttwu_do_activate+0xcc
try_to_wake_up+0x6c8
default_wake_function+0x20
autoremove_wake_function+0x1c
__wake_up+0xac
wakeup_kswapd+0x19c
wake_all_kswapds+0x78
__alloc_pages_slowpath+0x1ac
__alloc_pages_noprof+0x298
stack_depot_save_flags+0x6b0
stack_depot_save+0x14
set_track_prepare+0x5c
___slab_alloc+0xccc
__kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x470
__set_page_owner+0x2bc
post_alloc_hook[jt]+0x1b8
prep_new_page+0x28
get_page_from_freelist+0x1edc
__alloc_pages_noprof+0x13c
alloc_slab_page+0x244
allocate_slab+0x7c
___slab_alloc+0x8e8
kmem_cache_alloc_noprof+0x450
debug_objects_fill_pool+0x22c
debug_object_activate+0x40
enqueue_hrtimer[jt]+0xdc
hrtimer_start_range_ns+0x5f8
...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39844 | mm: move page table sync declarations to linux/pgtable.h</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39844</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: move page table sync declarations to linux/pgtable.h

During our internal testing, we started observing intermittent boot
failures when the machine uses 4-level paging and has a large amount of
persistent memory:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffe70000000034
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  PGD 0 P4D 0 
  Oops: 0002 [#1] SMP NOPTI
  RIP: 0010:__init_single_page+0x9/0x6d
  Call Trace:
   
   __init_zone_device_page+0x17/0x5d
   memmap_init_zone_device+0x154/0x1bb
   pagemap_range+0x2e0/0x40f
   memremap_pages+0x10b/0x2f0
   devm_memremap_pages+0x1e/0x60
   dev_dax_probe+0xce/0x2ec [device_dax]
   dax_bus_probe+0x6d/0xc9
   [... snip ...]
   

It turns out that the kernel panics while initializing vmemmap (struct
page array) when the vmemmap region spans two PGD entries, because the new
PGD entry is only installed in init_mm.pgd, but not in the page tables of
other tasks.

And looking at __populate_section_memmap():
  if (vmemmap_can_optimize(altmap, pgmap))                                
          // does not sync top level page tables
          r = vmemmap_populate_compound_pages(pfn, start, end, nid, pgmap);
  else                                                                    
          // sync top level page tables in x86
          r = vmemmap_populate(start, end, nid, altmap);

In the normal path, vmemmap_populate() in arch/x86/mm/init_64.c
synchronizes the top level page table (See commit 9b861528a801 ("x86-64,
mem: Update all PGDs for direct mapping and vmemmap mapping changes")) so
that all tasks in the system can see the new vmemmap area.

However, when vmemmap_can_optimize() returns true, the optimized path
skips synchronization of top-level page tables.  This is because
vmemmap_populate_compound_pages() is implemented in core MM code, which
does not handle synchronization of the top-level page tables.  Instead,
the core MM has historically relied on each architecture to perform this
synchronization manually.

We're not the first party to encounter a crash caused by not-sync'd top
level page tables: earlier this year, Gwan-gyeong Mun attempted to address
the issue [1] [2] after hitting a kernel panic when x86 code accessed the
vmemmap area before the corresponding top-level entries were synced.  At
that time, the issue was believed to be triggered only when struct page
was enlarged for debugging purposes, and the patch did not get further
updates.

It turns out that current approach of relying on each arch to handle the
page table sync manually is fragile because 1) it's easy to forget to sync
the top level page table, and 2) it's also easy to overlook that the
kernel should not access the vmemmap and direct mapping areas before the
sync.

# The solution: Make page table sync more code robust and harder to miss

To address this, Dave Hansen suggested [3] [4] introducing
{pgd,p4d}_populate_kernel() for updating kernel portion of the page tables
and allow each architecture to explicitly perform synchronization when
installing top-level entries.  With this approach, we no longer need to
worry about missing the sync step, reducing the risk of future
regressions.

The new interface reuses existing ARCH_PAGE_TABLE_SYNC_MASK,
PGTBL_P*D_MODIFIED and arch_sync_kernel_mappings() facility used by
vmalloc and ioremap to synchronize page tables.

pgd_populate_kernel() looks like this:
static inline void pgd_populate_kernel(unsigned long addr, pgd_t *pgd,
                                       p4d_t *p4d)
{
        pgd_populate(&amp;amp;init_mm, pgd, p4d);
        if (ARCH_PAGE_TABLE_SYNC_MASK &amp; PGTBL_PGD_MODIFIED)
                arch_sync_kernel_mappings(addr, addr);
}

It is worth noting that vmalloc() and apply_to_range() carefully
synchronizes page tables by calling p*d_alloc_track() and
arch_sync_kernel_mappings(), and thus they are not affected by
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39845 | x86/mm/64: define ARCH_PAGE_TABLE_SYNC_MASK and arch_sync_kernel_mappings()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39845</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/mm/64: define ARCH_PAGE_TABLE_SYNC_MASK and arch_sync_kernel_mappings()

Define ARCH_PAGE_TABLE_SYNC_MASK and arch_sync_kernel_mappings() to ensure
page tables are properly synchronized when calling p*d_populate_kernel().

For 5-level paging, synchronization is performed via
pgd_populate_kernel().  In 4-level paging, pgd_populate() is a no-op, so
synchronization is instead performed at the P4D level via
p4d_populate_kernel().

This fixes intermittent boot failures on systems using 4-level paging and
a large amount of persistent memory:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffe70000000034
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  PGD 0 P4D 0
  Oops: 0002 [#1] SMP NOPTI
  RIP: 0010:__init_single_page+0x9/0x6d
  Call Trace:
   
   __init_zone_device_page+0x17/0x5d
   memmap_init_zone_device+0x154/0x1bb
   pagemap_range+0x2e0/0x40f
   memremap_pages+0x10b/0x2f0
   devm_memremap_pages+0x1e/0x60
   dev_dax_probe+0xce/0x2ec [device_dax]
   dax_bus_probe+0x6d/0xc9
   [... snip ...]
   

It also fixes a crash in vmemmap_set_pmd() caused by accessing vmemmap
before sync_global_pgds() [1]:

  BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffeb3ff1200000
  #PF: supervisor write access in kernel mode
  #PF: error_code(0x0002) - not-present page
  PGD 0 P4D 0
  Oops: Oops: 0002 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
  Tainted: [W]=WARN
  RIP: 0010:vmemmap_set_pmd+0xff/0x230
   
   vmemmap_populate_hugepages+0x176/0x180
   vmemmap_populate+0x34/0x80
   __populate_section_memmap+0x41/0x90
   sparse_add_section+0x121/0x3e0
   __add_pages+0xba/0x150
   add_pages+0x1d/0x70
   memremap_pages+0x3dc/0x810
   devm_memremap_pages+0x1c/0x60
   xe_devm_add+0x8b/0x100 [xe]
   xe_tile_init_noalloc+0x6a/0x70 [xe]
   xe_device_probe+0x48c/0x740 [xe]
   [... snip ...]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39846 | pcmcia: Fix a NULL pointer dereference in __iodyn_find_io_region()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39846</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

pcmcia: Fix a NULL pointer dereference in __iodyn_find_io_region()

In __iodyn_find_io_region(), pcmcia_make_resource() is assigned to
res and used in pci_bus_alloc_resource(). There is a dereference of res
in pci_bus_alloc_resource(), which could lead to a NULL pointer
dereference on failure of pcmcia_make_resource().

Fix this bug by adding a check of res.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39847 | ppp: fix memory leak in pad_compress_skb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39847</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ppp: fix memory leak in pad_compress_skb

If alloc_skb() fails in pad_compress_skb(), it returns NULL without
releasing the old skb. The caller does:

    skb = pad_compress_skb(ppp, skb);
    if (!skb)
        goto drop;

drop:
    kfree_skb(skb);

When pad_compress_skb() returns NULL, the reference to the old skb is
lost and kfree_skb(skb) ends up doing nothing, leading to a memory leak.

Align pad_compress_skb() semantics with realloc(): only free the old
skb if allocation and compression succeed.  At the call site, use the
new_skb variable so the original skb is not lost when pad_compress_skb()
fails.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39848 | ax25: properly unshare skbs in ax25_kiss_rcv()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39848</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ax25: properly unshare skbs in ax25_kiss_rcv()

Bernard Pidoux reported a regression apparently caused by commit
c353e8983e0d ("net: introduce per netns packet chains").

skb-&gt;dev becomes NULL and we crash in __netif_receive_skb_core().

Before above commit, different kind of bugs or corruptions could happen
without a major crash.

But the root cause is that ax25_kiss_rcv() can queue/mangle input skb
without checking if this skb is shared or not.

Many thanks to Bernard Pidoux for his help, diagnosis and tests.

We had a similar issue years ago fixed with commit 7aaed57c5c28
("phonet: properly unshare skbs in phonet_rcv()").</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39849 | wifi: cfg80211: sme: cap SSID length in __cfg80211_connect_result()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39849</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: cfg80211: sme: cap SSID length in __cfg80211_connect_result()

If the ssid-&gt;datalen is more than IEEE80211_MAX_SSID_LEN (32) it would
lead to memory corruption so add some bounds checking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39850 | vxlan: Fix NPD in {arp,neigh}_reduce() when using nexthop objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39850</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vxlan: Fix NPD in {arp,neigh}_reduce() when using nexthop objects

When the "proxy" option is enabled on a VXLAN device, the device will
suppress ARP requests and IPv6 Neighbor Solicitation messages if it is
able to reply on behalf of the remote host. That is, if a matching and
valid neighbor entry is configured on the VXLAN device whose MAC address
is not behind the "any" remote (0.0.0.0 / ::).

The code currently assumes that the FDB entry for the neighbor's MAC
address points to a valid remote destination, but this is incorrect if
the entry is associated with an FDB nexthop group. This can result in a
NPD [1][3] which can be reproduced using [2][4].

Fix by checking that the remote destination exists before dereferencing
it.

[1]
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
[...]
CPU: 4 UID: 0 PID: 365 Comm: arping Not tainted 6.17.0-rc2-virtme-g2a89cb21162c #2 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.17.0-4.fc41 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:vxlan_xmit+0xb58/0x15f0
[...]
Call Trace:
 
 dev_hard_start_xmit+0x5d/0x1c0
 __dev_queue_xmit+0x246/0xfd0
 packet_sendmsg+0x113a/0x1850
 __sock_sendmsg+0x38/0x70
 __sys_sendto+0x126/0x180
 __x64_sys_sendto+0x24/0x30
 do_syscall_64+0xa4/0x260
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53

[2]
 #!/bin/bash

 ip address add 192.0.2.1/32 dev lo

 ip nexthop add id 1 via 192.0.2.2 fdb
 ip nexthop add id 10 group 1 fdb

 ip link add name vx0 up type vxlan id 10010 local 192.0.2.1 dstport 4789 proxy

 ip neigh add 192.0.2.3 lladdr 00:11:22:33:44:55 nud perm dev vx0

 bridge fdb add 00:11:22:33:44:55 dev vx0 self static nhid 10

 arping -b -c 1 -s 192.0.2.1 -I vx0 192.0.2.3

[3]
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
[...]
CPU: 13 UID: 0 PID: 372 Comm: ndisc6 Not tainted 6.17.0-rc2-virtmne-g6ee90cb26014 #3 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1v996), BIOS 1.17.0-4.fc41 04/01/2x014
RIP: 0010:vxlan_xmit+0x803/0x1600
[...]
Call Trace:
 
 dev_hard_start_xmit+0x5d/0x1c0
 __dev_queue_xmit+0x246/0xfd0
 ip6_finish_output2+0x210/0x6c0
 ip6_finish_output+0x1af/0x2b0
 ip6_mr_output+0x92/0x3e0
 ip6_send_skb+0x30/0x90
 rawv6_sendmsg+0xe6e/0x12e0
 __sock_sendmsg+0x38/0x70
 __sys_sendto+0x126/0x180
 __x64_sys_sendto+0x24/0x30
 do_syscall_64+0xa4/0x260
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53
RIP: 0033:0x7f383422ec77

[4]
 #!/bin/bash

 ip address add 2001:db8:1::1/128 dev lo

 ip nexthop add id 1 via 2001:db8:1::1 fdb
 ip nexthop add id 10 group 1 fdb

 ip link add name vx0 up type vxlan id 10010 local 2001:db8:1::1 dstport 4789 proxy

 ip neigh add 2001:db8:1::3 lladdr 00:11:22:33:44:55 nud perm dev vx0

 bridge fdb add 00:11:22:33:44:55 dev vx0 self static nhid 10

 ndisc6 -r 1 -s 2001:db8:1::1 -w 1 2001:db8:1::3 vx0</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39851 | vxlan: Fix NPD when refreshing an FDB entry with a nexthop object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39851</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

vxlan: Fix NPD when refreshing an FDB entry with a nexthop object

VXLAN FDB entries can point to either a remote destination or an FDB
nexthop group. The latter is usually used in EVPN deployments where
learning is disabled.

However, when learning is enabled, an incoming packet might try to
refresh an FDB entry that points to an FDB nexthop group and therefore
does not have a remote. Such packets should be dropped, but they are
only dropped after dereferencing the non-existent remote, resulting in a
NPD [1] which can be reproduced using [2].

Fix by dropping such packets earlier. Remove the misleading comment from
first_remote_rcu().

[1]
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
[...]
CPU: 13 UID: 0 PID: 361 Comm: mausezahn Not tainted 6.17.0-rc1-virtme-g9f6b606b6b37 #1 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.17.0-4.fc41 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:vxlan_snoop+0x98/0x1e0
[...]
Call Trace:
 
 vxlan_encap_bypass+0x209/0x240
 encap_bypass_if_local+0xb1/0x100
 vxlan_xmit_one+0x1375/0x17e0
 vxlan_xmit+0x6b4/0x15f0
 dev_hard_start_xmit+0x5d/0x1c0
 __dev_queue_xmit+0x246/0xfd0
 packet_sendmsg+0x113a/0x1850
 __sock_sendmsg+0x38/0x70
 __sys_sendto+0x126/0x180
 __x64_sys_sendto+0x24/0x30
 do_syscall_64+0xa4/0x260
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53

[2]
 #!/bin/bash

 ip address add 192.0.2.1/32 dev lo
 ip address add 192.0.2.2/32 dev lo

 ip nexthop add id 1 via 192.0.2.3 fdb
 ip nexthop add id 10 group 1 fdb

 ip link add name vx0 up type vxlan id 10010 local 192.0.2.1 dstport 12345 localbypass
 ip link add name vx1 up type vxlan id 10020 local 192.0.2.2 dstport 54321 learning

 bridge fdb add 00:11:22:33:44:55 dev vx0 self static dst 192.0.2.2 port 54321 vni 10020
 bridge fdb add 00:aa:bb:cc:dd:ee dev vx1 self static nhid 10

 mausezahn vx0 -a 00:aa:bb:cc:dd:ee -b 00:11:22:33:44:55 -c 1 -q</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39852 | net/tcp: Fix socket memory leak in TCP-AO failure handling for IPv6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39852</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/tcp: Fix socket memory leak in TCP-AO failure handling for IPv6

When tcp_ao_copy_all_matching() fails in tcp_v6_syn_recv_sock() it just
exits the function. This ends up causing a memory-leak:

unreferenced object 0xffff0000281a8200 (size 2496):
  comm "softirq", pid 0, jiffies 4295174684
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    7f 00 00 06 7f 00 00 06 00 00 00 00 cb a8 88 13  ................
    0a 00 03 61 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ...a............
  backtrace (crc 5ebdbe15):
    kmemleak_alloc+0x44/0xe0
    kmem_cache_alloc_noprof+0x248/0x470
    sk_prot_alloc+0x48/0x120
    sk_clone_lock+0x38/0x3b0
    inet_csk_clone_lock+0x34/0x150
    tcp_create_openreq_child+0x3c/0x4a8
    tcp_v6_syn_recv_sock+0x1c0/0x620
    tcp_check_req+0x588/0x790
    tcp_v6_rcv+0x5d0/0xc18
    ip6_protocol_deliver_rcu+0x2d8/0x4c0
    ip6_input_finish+0x74/0x148
    ip6_input+0x50/0x118
    ip6_sublist_rcv+0x2fc/0x3b0
    ipv6_list_rcv+0x114/0x170
    __netif_receive_skb_list_core+0x16c/0x200
    netif_receive_skb_list_internal+0x1f0/0x2d0

This is because in tcp_v6_syn_recv_sock (and the IPv4 counterpart), when
exiting upon error, inet_csk_prepare_forced_close() and tcp_done() need
to be called. They make sure the newsk will end up being correctly
free'd.

tcp_v4_syn_recv_sock() makes this very clear by having the put_and_exit
label that takes care of things. So, this patch here makes sure
tcp_v4_syn_recv_sock and tcp_v6_syn_recv_sock have similar
error-handling and thus fixes the leak for TCP-AO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39853 | i40e: Fix potential invalid access when MAC list is empty</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39853</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i40e: Fix potential invalid access when MAC list is empty

list_first_entry() never returns NULL - if the list is empty, it still
returns a pointer to an invalid object, leading to potential invalid
memory access when dereferenced.

Fix this by using list_first_entry_or_null instead of list_first_entry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39854 | ice: fix NULL access of tx-&amp;gt;in_use in ice_ll_ts_intr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39854</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: fix NULL access of tx-&gt;in_use in ice_ll_ts_intr

Recent versions of the E810 firmware have support for an extra interrupt to
handle report of the "low latency" Tx timestamps coming from the
specialized low latency firmware interface. Instead of polling the
registers, software can wait until the low latency interrupt is fired.

This logic makes use of the Tx timestamp tracking structure, ice_ptp_tx, as
it uses the same "ready" bitmap to track which Tx timestamps complete.

Unfortunately, the ice_ll_ts_intr() function does not check if the
tracker is initialized before its first access. This results in NULL
dereference or use-after-free bugs similar to the issues fixed in the
ice_ptp_ts_irq() function.

Fix this by only checking the in_use bitmap (and other fields) if the
tracker is marked as initialized. The reset flow will clear the init field
under lock before it tears the tracker down, thus preventing any
use-after-free or NULL access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39855 | ice: fix NULL access of tx-&amp;gt;in_use in ice_ptp_ts_irq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39855</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ice: fix NULL access of tx-&gt;in_use in ice_ptp_ts_irq

The E810 device has support for a "low latency" firmware interface to
access and read the Tx timestamps. This interface does not use the standard
Tx timestamp logic, due to the latency overhead of proxying sideband
command requests over the firmware AdminQ.

The logic still makes use of the Tx timestamp tracking structure,
ice_ptp_tx, as it uses the same "ready" bitmap to track which Tx
timestamps complete.

Unfortunately, the ice_ptp_ts_irq() function does not check if the tracker
is initialized before its first access. This results in NULL dereference or
use-after-free bugs similar to the following:

[245977.278756] BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
[245977.278774] RIP: 0010:_find_first_bit+0x19/0x40
[245977.278796] Call Trace:
[245977.278809]  ? ice_misc_intr+0x364/0x380 [ice]

This can occur if a Tx timestamp interrupt races with the driver reset
logic.

Fix this by only checking the in_use bitmap (and other fields) if the
tracker is marked as initialized. The reset flow will clear the init field
under lock before it tears the tracker down, thus preventing any
use-after-free or NULL access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39856 | net: ethernet: ti: am65-cpsw-nuss: Fix null pointer dereference for ndev</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39856</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: ethernet: ti: am65-cpsw-nuss: Fix null pointer dereference for ndev

In the TX completion packet stage of TI SoCs with CPSW2G instance, which
has single external ethernet port, ndev is accessed without being
initialized if no TX packets have been processed. It results into null
pointer dereference, causing kernel to crash. Fix this by having a check
on the number of TX packets which have been processed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39857 | net/smc: fix one NULL pointer dereference in smc_ib_is_sg_need_sync()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39857</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/smc: fix one NULL pointer dereference in smc_ib_is_sg_need_sync()

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 00000000000002ec
PGD 0 P4D 0
Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] SMP PTI
CPU: 28 UID: 0 PID: 343 Comm: kworker/28:1 Kdump: loaded Tainted: G        OE       6.17.0-rc2+ #9 NONE
Tainted: [O]=OOT_MODULE, [E]=UNSIGNED_MODULE
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
Workqueue: smc_hs_wq smc_listen_work [smc]
RIP: 0010:smc_ib_is_sg_need_sync+0x9e/0xd0 [smc]
...
Call Trace:
 
 smcr_buf_map_link+0x211/0x2a0 [smc]
 __smc_buf_create+0x522/0x970 [smc]
 smc_buf_create+0x3a/0x110 [smc]
 smc_find_rdma_v2_device_serv+0x18f/0x240 [smc]
 ? smc_vlan_by_tcpsk+0x7e/0xe0 [smc]
 smc_listen_find_device+0x1dd/0x2b0 [smc]
 smc_listen_work+0x30f/0x580 [smc]
 process_one_work+0x18c/0x340
 worker_thread+0x242/0x360
 kthread+0xe7/0x220
 ret_from_fork+0x13a/0x160
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
 

If the software RoCE device is used, ibdev-&gt;dma_device is a null pointer.
As a result, the problem occurs. Null pointer detection is added to
prevent problems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39858 | eth: mlx4: Fix IS_ERR() vs NULL check bug in mlx4_en_create_rx_ring</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39858</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

eth: mlx4: Fix IS_ERR() vs NULL check bug in mlx4_en_create_rx_ring

Replace NULL check with IS_ERR() check after calling page_pool_create()
since this function returns error pointers (ERR_PTR).
Using NULL check could lead to invalid pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39859 | ptp: ocp: fix use-after-free bugs causing by ptp_ocp_watchdog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39859</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ptp: ocp: fix use-after-free bugs causing by ptp_ocp_watchdog

The ptp_ocp_detach() only shuts down the watchdog timer if it is
pending. However, if the timer handler is already running, the
timer_delete_sync() is not called. This leads to race conditions
where the devlink that contains the ptp_ocp is deallocated while
the timer handler is still accessing it, resulting in use-after-free
bugs. The following details one of the race scenarios.

(thread 1)                           | (thread 2)
ptp_ocp_remove()                     |
  ptp_ocp_detach()                   | ptp_ocp_watchdog()
    if (timer_pending(&amp;amp;bp-&gt;watchdog))|   bp = timer_container_of()
      timer_delete_sync()            |
                                     |
  devlink_free(devlink) //free       |
                                     |   bp-&gt; //use

Resolve this by unconditionally calling timer_delete_sync() to ensure
the timer is reliably deactivated, preventing any access after free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39860 | Bluetooth: Fix use-after-free in l2cap_sock_cleanup_listen()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39860</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Fix use-after-free in l2cap_sock_cleanup_listen()

syzbot reported the splat below without a repro.

In the splat, a single thread calling bt_accept_dequeue() freed sk
and touched it after that.

The root cause would be the racy l2cap_sock_cleanup_listen() call
added by the cited commit.

bt_accept_dequeue() is called under lock_sock() except for
l2cap_sock_release().

Two threads could see the same socket during the list iteration
in bt_accept_dequeue():

  CPU1                        CPU2 (close())
  ----                        ----
  sock_hold(sk)               sock_hold(sk);
  lock_sock(sk)   &lt;-- block close()
  sock_put(sk)
  bt_accept_unlink(sk)
    sock_put(sk)  &lt;-- refcnt by bt_accept_enqueue()
  release_sock(sk)
                              lock_sock(sk)
                              sock_put(sk)
                              bt_accept_unlink(sk)
                                sock_put(sk)        &lt;-- last refcnt
                              bt_accept_unlink(sk)  &lt;-- UAF

Depending on the timing, the other thread could show up in the
"Freed by task" part.

Let's call l2cap_sock_cleanup_listen() under lock_sock() in
l2cap_sock_release().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in debug_spin_lock_before kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:86 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in do_raw_spin_lock+0x26f/0x2b0 kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:115
Read of size 4 at addr ffff88803b7eb1c4 by task syz.5.3276/16995
CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 16995 Comm: syz.5.3276 Not tainted syzkaller #0 PREEMPT(full)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2~bpo12+1 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0x116/0x1f0 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0xcd/0x630 mm/kasan/report.c:482
 kasan_report+0xe0/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:595
 debug_spin_lock_before kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:86 [inline]
 do_raw_spin_lock+0x26f/0x2b0 kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:115
 spin_lock_bh include/linux/spinlock.h:356 [inline]
 release_sock+0x21/0x220 net/core/sock.c:3746
 bt_accept_dequeue+0x505/0x600 net/bluetooth/af_bluetooth.c:312
 l2cap_sock_cleanup_listen+0x5c/0x2a0 net/bluetooth/l2cap_sock.c:1451
 l2cap_sock_release+0x5c/0x210 net/bluetooth/l2cap_sock.c:1425
 __sock_release+0xb3/0x270 net/socket.c:649
 sock_close+0x1c/0x30 net/socket.c:1439
 __fput+0x3ff/0xb70 fs/file_table.c:468
 task_work_run+0x14d/0x240 kernel/task_work.c:227
 resume_user_mode_work include/linux/resume_user_mode.h:50 [inline]
 exit_to_user_mode_loop+0xeb/0x110 kernel/entry/common.c:43
 exit_to_user_mode_prepare include/linux/irq-entry-common.h:225 [inline]
 syscall_exit_to_user_mode_work include/linux/entry-common.h:175 [inline]
 syscall_exit_to_user_mode include/linux/entry-common.h:210 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x3f6/0x4c0 arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:100
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f
RIP: 0033:0x7f2accf8ebe9
Code: ff ff c3 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 40 00 48 89 f8 48 89 f7 48 89 d6 48 89 ca 4d 89 c2 4d 89 c8 4c 8b 4c 24 08 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 c7 c1 a8 ff ff ff f7 d8 64 89 01 48
RSP: 002b:00007ffdb6cb1378 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 00000000000001b4
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 00000000000426fb RCX: 00007f2accf8ebe9
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 000000000000001e RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00007f2acd1b7da0 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: 00000012b6cb166f
R10: 0000001b30e20000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 00007f2acd1b609c
R13: 00007f2acd1b6090 R14: ffffffffffffffff R15: 00007ffdb6cb1490
 

Allocated by task 5326:
 kasan_save_stack+0x33/0x60 mm/kasan/common.c:47
 kasan_save_track+0x14/0x30 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:388 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0xaa/0xb0 mm/kasan/common.c:405
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __do_kmalloc_node mm/slub.c:4365 [inline]
 __kmalloc_nopro
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39861 | Bluetooth: vhci: Prevent use-after-free by removing debugfs files early</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39861</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: vhci: Prevent use-after-free by removing debugfs files early

Move the creation of debugfs files into a dedicated function, and ensure
they are explicitly removed during vhci_release(), before associated
data structures are freed.

Previously, debugfs files such as "force_suspend", "force_wakeup", and
others were created under hdev-&gt;debugfs but not removed in
vhci_release(). Since vhci_release() frees the backing vhci_data
structure, any access to these files after release would result in
use-after-free errors.

Although hdev-&gt;debugfs is later freed in hci_release_dev(), user can
access files after vhci_data is freed but before hdev-&gt;debugfs is
released.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39862 | wifi: mt76: mt7915: fix list corruption after hardware restart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39862</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mt76: mt7915: fix list corruption after hardware restart

Since stations are recreated from scratch, all lists that wcids are added
to must be cleared before calling ieee80211_restart_hw.
Set wcid-&gt;sta = 0 for each wcid entry in order to ensure that they are
not added again before they are ready.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39863 | wifi: brcmfmac: fix use-after-free when rescheduling brcmf_btcoex_info work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39863</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: brcmfmac: fix use-after-free when rescheduling brcmf_btcoex_info work

The brcmf_btcoex_detach() only shuts down the btcoex timer, if the
flag timer_on is false. However, the brcmf_btcoex_timerfunc(), which
runs as timer handler, sets timer_on to false. This creates critical
race conditions:

1.If brcmf_btcoex_detach() is called while brcmf_btcoex_timerfunc()
is executing, it may observe timer_on as false and skip the call to
timer_shutdown_sync().

2.The brcmf_btcoex_timerfunc() may then reschedule the brcmf_btcoex_info
worker after the cancel_work_sync() has been executed, resulting in
use-after-free bugs.

The use-after-free bugs occur in two distinct scenarios, depending on
the timing of when the brcmf_btcoex_info struct is freed relative to
the execution of its worker thread.

Scenario 1: Freed before the worker is scheduled

The brcmf_btcoex_info is deallocated before the worker is scheduled.
A race condition can occur when schedule_work(&amp;amp;bt_local-&gt;work) is
called after the target memory has been freed. The sequence of events
is detailed below:

CPU0                           | CPU1
brcmf_btcoex_detach            | brcmf_btcoex_timerfunc
                               |   bt_local-&gt;timer_on = false;
  if (cfg-&gt;btcoex-&gt;timer_on)   |
    ...                        |
  cancel_work_sync();          |
  ...                          |
  kfree(cfg-&gt;btcoex); // FREE  |
                               |   schedule_work(&amp;amp;bt_local-&gt;work); // USE

Scenario 2: Freed after the worker is scheduled

The brcmf_btcoex_info is freed after the worker has been scheduled
but before or during its execution. In this case, statements within
the brcmf_btcoex_handler() — such as the container_of macro and
subsequent dereferences of the brcmf_btcoex_info object will cause
a use-after-free access. The following timeline illustrates this
scenario:

CPU0                            | CPU1
brcmf_btcoex_detach             | brcmf_btcoex_timerfunc
                                |   bt_local-&gt;timer_on = false;
  if (cfg-&gt;btcoex-&gt;timer_on)    |
    ...                         |
  cancel_work_sync();           |
  ...                           |   schedule_work(); // Reschedule
                                |
  kfree(cfg-&gt;btcoex); // FREE   |   brcmf_btcoex_handler() // Worker
  /*                            |     btci = container_of(....); // USE
   The kfree() above could      |     ...
   also occur at any point      |     btci-&gt; // USE
   during the worker's execution|
   */                           |

To resolve the race conditions, drop the conditional check and call
timer_shutdown_sync() directly. It can deactivate the timer reliably,
regardless of its current state. Once stopped, the timer_on state is
then set to false.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39864 | wifi: cfg80211: fix use-after-free in cmp_bss()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39864</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: cfg80211: fix use-after-free in cmp_bss()

Following bss_free() quirk introduced in commit 776b3580178f
("cfg80211: track hidden SSID networks properly"), adjust
cfg80211_update_known_bss() to free the last beacon frame
elements only if they're not shared via the corresponding
'hidden_beacon_bss' pointer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39865 | tee: fix NULL pointer dereference in tee_shm_put</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39865</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tee: fix NULL pointer dereference in tee_shm_put

tee_shm_put have NULL pointer dereference:

__optee_disable_shm_cache --&gt;
	shm = reg_pair_to_ptr(...);//shm maybe return NULL
        tee_shm_free(shm); --&gt;
		tee_shm_put(shm);//crash

Add check in tee_shm_put to fix it.

panic log:
Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address 0000000000100cca
Mem abort info:
ESR = 0x0000000096000004
EC = 0x25: DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
SET = 0, FnV = 0
EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
FSC = 0x04: level 0 translation fault
Data abort info:
ISV = 0, ISS = 0x00000004, ISS2 = 0x00000000
CM = 0, WnR = 0, TnD = 0, TagAccess = 0
GCS = 0, Overlay = 0, DirtyBit = 0, Xs = 0
user pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp=0000002049d07000
[0000000000100cca] pgd=0000000000000000, p4d=0000000000000000
Internal error: Oops: 0000000096000004 [#1] SMP
CPU: 2 PID: 14442 Comm: systemd-sleep Tainted: P OE ------- ----
6.6.0-39-generic #38
Source Version: 938b255f6cb8817c95b0dd5c8c2944acfce94b07
Hardware name: greatwall GW-001Y1A-FTH, BIOS Great Wall BIOS V3.0
10/26/2022
pstate: 80000005 (Nzcv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : tee_shm_put+0x24/0x188
lr : tee_shm_free+0x14/0x28
sp : ffff001f98f9faf0
x29: ffff001f98f9faf0 x28: ffff0020df543cc0 x27: 0000000000000000
x26: ffff001f811344a0 x25: ffff8000818dac00 x24: ffff800082d8d048
x23: ffff001f850fcd18 x22: 0000000000000001 x21: ffff001f98f9fb88
x20: ffff001f83e76218 x19: ffff001f83e761e0 x18: 000000000000ffff
x17: 303a30303a303030 x16: 0000000000000000 x15: 0000000000000003
x14: 0000000000000001 x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 0101010101010101
x11: 0000000000000001 x10: 0000000000000001 x9 : ffff800080e08d0c
x8 : ffff001f98f9fb88 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 0000000000000000
x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000000
x2 : ffff001f83e761e0 x1 : 00000000ffff001f x0 : 0000000000100cca
Call trace:
tee_shm_put+0x24/0x188
tee_shm_free+0x14/0x28
__optee_disable_shm_cache+0xa8/0x108
optee_shutdown+0x28/0x38
platform_shutdown+0x28/0x40
device_shutdown+0x144/0x2b0
kernel_power_off+0x3c/0x80
hibernate+0x35c/0x388
state_store+0x64/0x80
kobj_attr_store+0x14/0x28
sysfs_kf_write+0x48/0x60
kernfs_fop_write_iter+0x128/0x1c0
vfs_write+0x270/0x370
ksys_write+0x6c/0x100
__arm64_sys_write+0x20/0x30
invoke_syscall+0x4c/0x120
el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0x44/0xf0
do_el0_svc+0x24/0x38
el0_svc+0x24/0x88
el0t_64_sync_handler+0x134/0x150
el0t_64_sync+0x14c/0x15</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39866 | fs: writeback: fix use-after-free in __mark_inode_dirty()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39866</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs: writeback: fix use-after-free in __mark_inode_dirty()

An use-after-free issue occurred when __mark_inode_dirty() get the
bdi_writeback that was in the progress of switching.

CPU: 1 PID: 562 Comm: systemd-random- Not tainted 6.6.56-gb4403bd46a8e #1
......
pstate: 60400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : __mark_inode_dirty+0x124/0x418
lr : __mark_inode_dirty+0x118/0x418
sp : ffffffc08c9dbbc0
........
Call trace:
 __mark_inode_dirty+0x124/0x418
 generic_update_time+0x4c/0x60
 file_modified+0xcc/0xd0
 ext4_buffered_write_iter+0x58/0x124
 ext4_file_write_iter+0x54/0x704
 vfs_write+0x1c0/0x308
 ksys_write+0x74/0x10c
 __arm64_sys_write+0x1c/0x28
 invoke_syscall+0x48/0x114
 el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0xc0/0xe0
 do_el0_svc+0x1c/0x28
 el0_svc+0x40/0xe4
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x120/0x12c
 el0t_64_sync+0x194/0x198

Root cause is:

systemd-random-seed                         kworker
----------------------------------------------------------------------
___mark_inode_dirty                     inode_switch_wbs_work_fn

  spin_lock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock);
  inode_attach_wb
  locked_inode_to_wb_and_lock_list
     get inode-&gt;i_wb
     spin_unlock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock);
     spin_lock(&amp;amp;wb-&gt;list_lock)
  spin_lock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock)
  inode_io_list_move_locked
  spin_unlock(&amp;amp;wb-&gt;list_lock)
  spin_unlock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock)
                                    spin_lock(&amp;amp;old_wb-&gt;list_lock)
                                      inode_do_switch_wbs
                                        spin_lock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock)
                                        inode-&gt;i_wb = new_wb
                                        spin_unlock(&amp;amp;inode-&gt;i_lock)
                                    spin_unlock(&amp;amp;old_wb-&gt;list_lock)
                                    wb_put_many(old_wb, nr_switched)
                                      cgwb_release
                                      old wb released
  wb_wakeup_delayed() accesses wb,
  then trigger the use-after-free
  issue

Fix this race condition by holding inode spinlock until
wb_wakeup_delayed() finished.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55910 | CMSEasy v7.7.8.0 and before is vulnerable to Arbitrary file deletion in database_admin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55910</link><description>CMSEasy v7.7.8.0 and before is vulnerable to Arbitrary file deletion in database_admin.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59344 | AliasVault Vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery via Favicon Extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59344</link><description>AliasVault is a privacy-first password manager with built-in email aliasing. A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the favicon extraction feature of AliasVault API versions 0.23.0 and lower. The extractor fetches a user-supplied URL, parses the returned HTML, and follows . Although the initial URL is validated to allow only HTTP/HTTPS with default ports, the extractor automatically follows redirects and does not block requests to loopback or internal IP ranges. An authenticated, low-privileged user can exploit this behavior to coerce the backend into making HTTP(S) requests to arbitrary internal hosts and non-default ports. If the target host serves a favicon or any other valid image, the response is returned to the attacker in Base64 form. Even when no data is returned, timing and error behavior can be abused to map internal services. This vulnerability only affects self-hosted AliasVault instances that are reachable from the public internet with public user registration enabled. Private/internal deployments without public sign-ups are not directly exploitable. This issue has been fixed in AliasVault release 0.23.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57644 | Accela Automation Platform 22.2.3.0.230103 contains multiple vulnerabilities in the Test Script feature. An authenticated administrative use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57644</link><description>Accela Automation Platform 22.2.3.0.230103 contains multiple vulnerabilities in the Test Script feature. An authenticated administrative user can execute arbitrary Java code on the server, resulting in remote code execution. In addition, improper input validation allows for arbitrary file write and server-side request forgery (SSRF), enabling interaction with internal or external systems. Successful exploitation can lead to full server compromise, unauthorized access to sensitive data, and further network exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8664 | XSS in Saysis Computer Systems&amp;#x27; StarCities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saysis Computer Systems Trade Ltd. Co. StarCities E-Municipality Management allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects StarCities E-Municipality Management: before 20250825.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:55:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10716 | Creality Cloud App com.cxsw.sdprinter AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10716</link><description>A flaw has been found in Creality Cloud App up to 6.1.0 on Android. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.cxsw.sdprinter. Executing manipulation can lead to improper export of android application components. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10717 | intsig CamScanner App com.intsig.camscanner AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10717</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in intsig CamScanner App 6.91.1.5.250711 on Android. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.intsig.camscanner. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:46:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57528 | An issue was discovered in Tenda AC6 US_AC6V1.0BR_V15.03.05.16_multi_TD01 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service via the funcname, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57528</link><description>An issue was discovered in Tenda AC6 US_AC6V1.0BR_V15.03.05.16_multi_TD01 allowing attackers to cause a denial of service via the funcname, funcpara1, funcpara2 parameters to the formSetCfm function (uri path: SetCfm).</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8532 | IDOR in Bimser&amp;#x27;s eBA Document and Workflow Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8532</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key, CWE - 862 - Missing Authorization, – Improper Authorization vulnerability in Bimser Solution Software Trade Inc. EBA Document and Workflow Management System allows – Exploitation of Trusted Identifiers, – Exploitation of Authorization, – Variable Manipulation.This issue affects eBA Document and Workflow Management System: from 6.7.164 before 6.7.166.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10712 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10712</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 20250831. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php/Login/login. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10715 | APEUni PTE Exam Practice App com.ape_edication AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10715</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in APEUni PTE Exam Practice App up to 10.8.0 on Android. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.ape_edication. The manipulation results in improper export of android application components. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46703 | Potential XSS in Extension:AtMentions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46703</link><description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Hallo Welt! GmbH BlueSpice (Extension:AtMentions) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).
This issue affects BlueSpice: from 5 through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48007 | Potential XSS in Extension:BlueSpiceAvatars</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48007</link><description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Hallo Welt! GmbH BlueSpice (Extension:BlueSpiceAvatars) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).
This issue affects BlueSpice: from 5 through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57880 | Potential XSS in Extension:BlueSpiceWhoIsOnline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57880</link><description>Improper Encoding or Escaping of Output vulnerability in Hallo Welt! GmbH BlueSpice (Extension:BlueSpiceWhoIsOnline) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).
This issue affects BlueSpice: from 5 through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58114 | Potential XSS in Extension:CognitiveProcessDesigner</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58114</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Hallo Welt! GmbH BlueSpice (Extension:CognitiveProcessDesigner) allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects BlueSpice: from 5 through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10710 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10710</link><description>A flaw has been found in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 20250831. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. This manipulation of the argument Name causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10711 | 07FLYCMS/07FLY-CMS/07FlyCRM Login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10711</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 07FLYCMS, 07FLY-CMS and 07FlyCRM up to 20250831. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php/sysmanage/Login. Such manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is published under multiple names. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7665 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase 3.1.0 - 3.6.2 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7665</link><description>The Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_mofirebase_form_options' function in versions 3.1.0 to 3.6.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the default role to Administrator. Premium features must be enabled in order to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10709 | Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform historyDownload.do;otheruserLogin.do;getfile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10709</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /history/historyDownload.do;otheruserLogin.do;getfile. The manipulation of the argument fileName results in path traversal. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10707 | JeecgBoot sendMsg improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10707</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.8.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /message/sysMessageTemplate/sendMsg. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10708 | Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform historyDownload.do;usrlogout.do path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10708</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Four-Faith Water Conservancy Informatization Platform 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /history/historyDownload.do;usrlogout.do. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9969 | Reflected XSS in Vizly Web Design&amp;#x27;s Real Estate Packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9969</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vizly Web Design Real Estate Packages allows Content Spoofing, CAPEC - 593 - Session Hijacking, CAPEC - 591 - Reflected XSS.This issue affects Real Estate Packages: before 5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10468 | Path Traversal in Beyaz Computer&amp;#x27;s CityPLus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10468</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Beyaz Computer CityPlus allows Path Traversal.This issue affects CityPlus: before 24.29375.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10719 | WisdomGarden｜Tronclass - Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10719</link><description>Tronclass developed by WisdomGarden has an Insecure Direct object Reference vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to modify a specific parameter to access other users' files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10630 | Regex DoS in Grafana Zabbix Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10630</link><description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. Grafana-Zabbix is a plugin for Grafana allowing to visualize monitoring data from Zabbix and create dashboards for analyzing metrics and realtime monitoring. 



Versions 5.2.1 and below contained a ReDoS vulnerability via user-supplied regex query which could causes CPU usage to max out. This vulnerability is fixed in version 6.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8531 | Improper Handling of Length Parameter Inconsistency vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series Q03UDVCPU, Q04UDVCPU, Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8531</link><description>Improper Handling of Length Parameter Inconsistency vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-Q Series Q03UDVCPU, Q04UDVCPU, Q06UDVCPU, Q13UDVCPU, Q26UDVCPU, Q04UDPVCPU, Q06UDPVCPU, Q13UDPVCPU, and Q26UDPVCPU with the first 5 digits of serial No. "24082" to "27081" allows a remote attacker to cause an integer underflow by sending specially crafted packets to the affected product to stop Ethernet communication and the execution of control programs on the product, when the user authentication function is enabled. The user authentication function is enabled by default only when settings are configured by GX Works2, which complies with the Cybersecurity Law of the People's Republic of China, and is normally disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10647 | Embed PDF for WPForms &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10647</link><description>The Embed PDF for WPForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ajax_handler_download_pdf_media function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9905 | Arbitary Code execution in Keras load_model()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9905</link><description>The Keras Model.load_model method can be exploited to achieve arbitrary code execution, even with safe_mode=True.

One can create a specially crafted .h5/.hdf5 model archive that, when loaded via Model.load_model, will trigger arbitrary code to be executed.

This is achieved by crafting a special .h5 archive file that uses the Lambda layer feature of keras which allows arbitrary Python code in the form of pickled code. The vulnerability comes from the fact that the safe_mode=True option is not honored when reading .h5 archives.

Note that the .h5/.hdf5 format is a legacy format supported by Keras 3 for backwards compatibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9906 | Arbitrary Code execution in Keras Safe Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9906</link><description>The Keras Model.load_model method can be exploited to achieve arbitrary code execution, even with safe_mode=True.

One can create a specially crafted .keras model archive that, when loaded via Model.load_model, will trigger arbitrary code to be executed. This is achieved by crafting a special config.json (a file within the .keras archive) that will invoke keras.config.enable_unsafe_deserialization() to disable safe mode. Once safe mode is disable, one can use the Lambda layer feature of keras, which allows arbitrary Python code in the form of pickled code. Both can appear in the same archive. Simply the keras.config.enable_unsafe_deserialization() needs to appear first in the archive and the Lambda with arbitrary code needs to be second.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7702 | Open Redirect in PUSULA&amp;#x27;s Manageable Email Sending System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7702</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Pusula Communication Information Internet Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Manageable Email Sending System allows Exploiting Trust in Client.This issue affects Manageable Email Sending System: from &lt;=2025.06 before 2025.08.06.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 08:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10456 | Bluetooth: Semi-Arbitrary ability to make the BLE Target send disconnection requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10456</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the handling of Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) fixed channels (such as SMP or ATT). Specifically, an attacker could exploit a flaw that causes the BLE target (i.e., the device under attack) to attempt to disconnect a fixed channel, which is not allowed per the Bluetooth specification. This leads to undefined behavior, including potential assertion failures, crashes, or memory corruption, depending on the BLE stack implementation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5948 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via claim_business</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5948</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to claiming a business when using the claim_business AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as any user including admins. Please note that subscriber privileges or brute-forcing are needed when completing the business takeover. The claim_id is needed to takeover the admin account, but brute-forcing is a practical approach to obtaining valid IDs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10457 | Bluetooth: Out-Of-Context le_conn_rsp Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10457</link><description>The function responsible for handling BLE connection responses, fails to verify whether a connection response is actually expected—i.e., whether the device initiated a connection request. Instead, it only checks if the identifier matches</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10458 | Bluetooth: le_conn_rsp does not sanitize CID, MTU, MPS values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10458</link><description>Parameters are not validated or sanitized, and are later used in various internal operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7403 | Bluetooth: bt_conn_tx_processor unsafe handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7403</link><description>Unsafe handling in bt_conn_tx_processor causes a use-after-free, resulting in a write-before-zero. The written 4 bytes are attacker-controlled, enabling precise memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 05:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10146 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.23 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via `user_ids` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10146</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘user_ids’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5955 | Service Finder SMS System &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5955</link><description>The Service Finder SMS System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to the plugin not verifying a user's phone number before logging them in. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as arbitrary users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8487 | Kubio AI Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8487</link><description>The Kubio AI Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the kubio-image-hub-install-plugin AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install the Image Hub plugin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 03:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59717 | In the @digitalocean/do-markdownit package through 1.16.1 (in npm), the callout and fence_environment plugins perform .includes substring ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59717</link><description>In the @digitalocean/do-markdownit package through 1.16.1 (in npm), the callout and fence_environment plugins perform .includes substring matching if allowedClasses or allowedEnvironments is a string (instead of an array).</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59715 | SMSEagle before 6.11 allows reflected XSS via a username or contact phone number.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59715</link><description>SMSEagle before 6.11 allows reflected XSS via a username or contact phone number.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10690 | Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10690</link><description>The Goza - Nonprofit Charity WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check on the 'beplus_import_pack_install_plugin' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload zip files containing webshells disguised as plugins from remote locations to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59712 | Snipe-IT before 8.1.18 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59712</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.1.18 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59713 | Snipe-IT before 8.1.18 allows unsafe deserialization.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59713</link><description>Snipe-IT before 8.1.18 allows unsafe deserialization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59714 | In Internet2 Grouper 5.17.1 before 5.20.5, group admins who are not Grouper sysadmins can configure loader jobs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59714</link><description>In Internet2 Grouper 5.17.1 before 5.20.5, group admins who are not Grouper sysadmins can configure loader jobs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7937 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7937</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X12STW . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6198 | Supermicro BMC firmware update validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6198</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the Supermicro BMC firmware validation logic at Supermicro MBD-X13SEM-F . An attacker can update the system firmware with a specially crafted image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:51:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>