<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:19:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-8380 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System add_query_account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8380</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add_query_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8379 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System edit_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_room.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2813 | HTTP Service DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2813</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can cause a Denial of Service by sending a large number of requests to the http service on port 80.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41688 | High Privilege RCE via LUA Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41688</link><description>A high privileged remote attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands using an undocumented method allowing to escape the implemented LUA sandbox.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8378 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8378</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40980 | ddd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40980</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in UltimatePOS by UltimateFosters. This vulnerability is due to the lack of proper validation of user inputs via ‘/products//edit’, affecting to ‘name’ parameter via POST. The vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal his/her session cookies details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8376 | code-projects Vehicle Management updatebal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8376</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /updatebal.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8375 | code-projects Vehicle Management addvehicle.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8375</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /addvehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument vehicle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24853 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in JSPWiki Header Link processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24853</link><description>A carefully crafted request when creating a header link using the 
wiki markup syntax, which could allow the attacker to execute javascript
 in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the 
victim.



Further research by the JSPWiki team showed that the markdown parser allowed this kind of attack too.

Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.3 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24854 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in JSPWiki Image plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24854</link><description>A carefully crafted request using the Image plugin could trigger an XSS 
vulnerability on Apache JSPWiki, which could allow the attacker to 
execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive 
information about the victim.





Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.3 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8374 | code-projects Vehicle Management addcompany.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8374</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addcompany.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8192 | Race condition in AndroidTV TvSettings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8192</link><description>There exists a TOCTOU race condition in TvSettings AppRestrictionsFragment.java that lead to start of attacker supplied activity in Settings’ context, i.e. system-uid context, thus lead to launchAnyWhere. The core idea is to utilize the time window between the check of Intent and the use to Intent to change the target component’s state, thus bypass the original security sanitize function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8373 | code-projects Vehicle Management print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8373</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /print.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36563 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product administrator accesses a crafted URL, an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36563</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product administrator accesses a crafted URL, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41391 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product user accesses a malicious page, an arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41391</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product user accesses a malicious page, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41396 | A path traversal issue exists in file uploading feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. Arbitrary files may be overwritten by a product us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41396</link><description>A path traversal issue exists in file uploading feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. Arbitrary files may be overwritten by a product user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46359 | A path traversal issue exists in backup and restore feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. A product administrator may execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46359</link><description>A path traversal issue exists in backup and restore feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. A product administrator may execute arbitrary code by restoring a crafted backup file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54752 | Multiple versions of PowerCMS improperly neutralize formula elements in a CSV file.  If a product user creates a malformed entry and a victi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54752</link><description>Multiple versions of PowerCMS improperly neutralize formula elements in a CSV file.  If a product user creates a malformed entry and a victim user downloads it as a CSV file and opens it in the user's environment, the embedded code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7205 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (GiveWP worker+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7205</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the donor notes parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with GiveWP worker-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Additionally, they need to trick an administrator into visiting the legacy version of the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8372 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s7.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8372</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_s7.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54757 | Multiple versions of PowerCMS allow unrestricted upload of dangerous files. If a product administrator accesses a malicious file uploaded by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54757</link><description>Multiple versions of PowerCMS allow unrestricted upload of dangerous files. If a product administrator accesses a malicious file uploaded by a product user, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8371 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8371</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_s5.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8370 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_escolaridade_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8370</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. Affected is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_escolaridade_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument descricao leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8369 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_avaliacao_desempenho_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8369</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /intranet/educar_avaliacao_desempenho_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument titulo_avaliacao leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53558 | ZXHN-F660T and ZXHN-F660A provided by ZTE Japan K.K. use a common credential for all installations. With the knowledge of the credential, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53558</link><description>ZXHN-F660T and ZXHN-F660A provided by ZTE Japan K.K. use a common credential for all installations. With the knowledge of the credential, an attacker may log in to the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8368 | Portabilis i-Educar pesquisa_pessoa_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8368</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /intranet/pesquisa_pessoa_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument campo_busca/cpf leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8367 | Portabilis i-Educar funcionario_vinculo_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8367</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /intranet/funcionario_vinculo_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument nome leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8366 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_servidor_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /intranet/educar_servidor_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument nome/matricula_servidor leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5720 | Customer Reviews for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.80.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `author` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5720</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.80.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7847 | AI Engine 2.9.3 - 2.9.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7847</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the rest_simpleFileUpload() function in versions 2.9.3 and 2.9.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server when the REST API is enabled, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8365 | Portabilis i-Educar atendidos_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.10. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file atendidos_cad.php. The manipulation of the argument nome/nome_social/email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8348 | Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform home improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8348</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /home. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8347 | Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform findAllTask sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8347</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/task/findAllTask. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8345 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM yunzhijiaApi.php delete_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8345</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.4.7. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_user of the file crm/WeiXinApp/yunzhijia/yunzhijiaApi.php. The manipulation of the argument function leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 8.6.5.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8346 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_aluno_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8346</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /educar_aluno_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument ref_cod_matricula with the input "&gt;&lt;img /&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8344 | openviglet shio ShStaticFileAPI.java shStaticFileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8344</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in openviglet shio up to 0.3.8. Affected is the function shStaticFileUpload of the file shio-app/src/main/java/com/viglet/shio/api/staticfile/ShStaticFileAPI.java. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8343 | openviglet shio ShStaticFileAPI.java shStaticFilePreUpload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8343</link><description>A vulnerability was found in openviglet shio up to 0.3.8. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function shStaticFilePreUpload of the file shio-app/src/main/java/com/viglet/shio/api/staticfile/ShStaticFileAPI.java. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8339 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System student_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /student_login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8340 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System Error Message fill_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file fill_details.php of the component Error Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36039 | IBM Aspera Faspex bypass security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36039</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12.1 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to client-side enforcement of sever side security mechanisms,</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36040 | IBM Aspera Faspex session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36040</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12.1 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to client-side enforcement of sever side security mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49082 | Permissions bypass vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49082</link><description>CVE-2025-49082 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of permissions
can bypass those permissions to improperly read other settings. The attack
complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack requirements; the privileges
required are high, and there is no user interaction required. The impact to
system confidentiality is low, there is no impact to system availability or
integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54085 | Elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54085</link><description>CVE-2025-54085 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of permissions
can bypass those permissions to improperly read or change other settings. The
attack complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack requirements; the
privileges required are high, and there is no user interaction required. The
impact to system confidentiality and integrity is low, there is no impact to
system availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49083 | Data deserialization vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49083</link><description>CVE-2025-49083 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access after version 12.00 and prior to version 13.56.
Attackers with administrative access to the console can cause unsafe content to
be deserialized and executed in the security context of the console. The attack
complexity is low and there are no attack requirements. Privileges required are
high and there is no user interaction required. The impact to confidentiality
is low, impact to integrity is high and there is no impact to availability. The
impact to the confidentiality and integrity of subsequent systems is low and
there is no subsequent system impact to availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49084 | Elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49084</link><description>CVE-2025-49084 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access can overwrite policy rules without the requisite permissions. The attack
complexity is low, attack requirements are present, privileges required are
high and no user interaction is required. There is no impact to
confidentiality, the impact to integrity is low, and there is no impact to
availability. The impact to confidentiality and availability of subsequent systems
is high and the impact to the integrity of subsequent systems is low.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8338 | projectworlds Online Admission System adminac.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /adminac.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8337 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System add_vehicles.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/add_vehicles.php. The manipulation of the argument car_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8336 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_user. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8335 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8334 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_recruitment_status. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54586 | GitProxy is susceptible to a hidden commits injection attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54586</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint. In versions 1.19.1 and below,   attackers can inject extra commits into the pack sent to GitHub, commits that aren’t pointed to by any branch. Although these “hidden” commits never show up in the repository’s visible history, GitHub still serves them at their direct commit URLs. This lets an attacker exfiltrate sensitive data without ever leaving a trace in the branch view. We rate this a High‑impact vulnerability because it completely compromises repository confidentiality. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8333 | code-projects Online Farm System categoryvalue.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8333</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /categoryvalue.php. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8332 | code-projects Online Farm System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54585 | GitProxy is vulnerable to a new branch approval exploit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54585</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint. In versions 1.19.1 and below, attackers can exploit the way GitProxy handles new branch creation to bypass the approval of prior commits on the parent branch. The vulnerability impacts all users or organizations relying on GitProxy to enforce policy and prevent unapproved changes. It requires no elevated privileges beyond regular push access, and no extra user interaction. It does however, require a GitProxy administrator or designated user (canUserApproveRejectPush) to approve pushes to the child branch. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54581 | vproxy is vulnerable to a divide by zero DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54581</link><description>vproxy is an HTTP/HTTPS/SOCKS5 proxy server. In versions 2.3.3 and below, untrusted data is extracted from the user-controlled HTTP Proxy-Authorization header and passed to Extension::try_from and flows into parse_ttl_extension where it is parsed as a TTL value. If an attacker supplies a TTL of zero (e.g. by using a username such as 'configuredUser-ttl-0'), the modulo operation 'timestamp % ttl' will cause a division by zero panic, causing the server to crash causing a denial-of-service. This is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54583 | GitProxy bypasses approvals when pushing multiple branches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54583</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint (e.g., github.com). Versions 1.19.1 and below allow users to push to remote repositories while bypassing policies and explicit approvals. Since checks and plugins are skipped, code containing secrets or unwanted changes could be pushed into a repository. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54584 | GitProxy is vulnerable to a packfile parsing exploit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54584</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint (e.g., github.com). In versions 1.19.1 and below, an attacker can craft a malicious Git packfile to exploit the PACK signature detection in the parsePush.ts file. By embedding a misleading PACK signature within commit content and carefully constructing the packet structure, the attacker can trick the parser into treating invalid or unintended data as the packfile. Potentially, this would allow bypassing approval or hiding commits. This issue is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8331 | code-projects Online Farm System forgot_pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /forgot_pass.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54575 | ImageSharp Triggers an Infinite Loop in its GIF Decoder When Skipping Malformed Comment Extension Blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54575</link><description>ImageSharp is a 2D graphics library. In versions below 2.1.11 and 3.0.0 through 3.1.10, a specially crafted GIF file containing a malformed comment extension block (with a missing block terminator) can cause the ImageSharp GIF decoder to enter an infinite loop while attempting to skip the block. This leads to a denial of service. Applications processing untrusted GIF input should upgrade to a patched version. This issue is fixed in versions 2.1.11 and 3.1.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48916 | Ceph is vulnerable to authentication bypass through RadosGW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48916</link><description>Ceph is a distributed object, block, and file storage platform. In versions 19.2.3 and below, it is possible to send an JWT that has "none" as JWT alg. And by doing so the JWT signature is not checked. The vulnerability is most likely in the RadosGW OIDC provider. As of time of publication, a known patched version has yet to be published.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54576 | OAuth2-Proxy has authentication bypass in oauth2-proxy skip_auth_routes due to Query Parameter inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54576</link><description>OAuth2-Proxy is an open-source tool that can act as either a standalone reverse proxy or a middleware component integrated into existing reverse proxy or load balancer setups. In versions 7.10.0 and below, oauth2-proxy deployments are vulnerable when using the skip_auth_routes configuration option with regex patterns. Attackers can bypass authentication by crafting URLs with query parameters that satisfy configured regex patterns, allowing unauthorized access to protected resources. The issue stems from skip_auth_routes matching against the full request URI. Deployments using skip_auth_routes with regex patterns containing wildcards or broad matching patterns are most at risk. This issue is fixed in version 7.11.0. Workarounds include: auditing all skip_auth_routes configurations for overly permissive patterns, replacing wildcard patterns with exact path matches where possible, ensuring regex patterns are properly anchored (starting with ^ and ending with $), or implementing custom validation that strips query parameters before regex matching.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8330 | code-projects Vehicle Management edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8330</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit1.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53022 | TrustedFirmware-M (aka Trusted Firmware for M profile Arm CPUs) before 2.1.3 and 2.2.x before 2.2.1 lacks length validation during a firmwar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53022</link><description>TrustedFirmware-M (aka Trusted Firmware for M profile Arm CPUs) before 2.1.3 and 2.2.x before 2.2.1 lacks length validation during a firmware upgrade. While processing a new image, the Firmware Upgrade (FWU) module does not validate the length field of the Type-Length-Value (TLV) structure for dependent components against the maximum allowed size. If the length specified in the TLV exceeds the size of the buffer allocated on the stack, the FWU module will overwrite the buffer (and potentially other stack data) with the TLV's value content. An attacker could exploit this by crafting a malicious TLV entry in the unprotected section of the MCUBoot upgrade image. By setting the length field to exceed the expected structure size, the attacker can manipulate the stack memory of the system during the upgrade process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51954 | playground.electronhub.ai v1.1.9 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51954</link><description>playground.electronhub.ai v1.1.9 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52187 | GetProjectsIdea Create School Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in my_profile_update_form1.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52187</link><description>GetProjectsIdea Create School Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in my_profile_update_form1.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50464 | A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the upload.cgi module of the iptime NAS firmware v1.5.04. The vulnerability arises due to the unsa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50464</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the upload.cgi module of the iptime NAS firmware v1.5.04. The vulnerability arises due to the unsafe use of the strcpy function to copy attacker-controlled data from the CONTENT_TYPE HTTP header into a fixed-size stack buffer (v8, allocated 8 bytes) without bounds checking. Since this operation occurs before authentication logic is executed, the vulnerability is exploitable pre-authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51951 | andisearch v0.5.249 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51951</link><description>andisearch v0.5.249 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8329 | code-projects Vehicle Management filter3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8329</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /filter3.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50777 | The firmware of the AZIOT 2MP Full HD Smart Wi-Fi CCTV Home Security Camera (version V1.00.02) contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50777</link><description>The firmware of the AZIOT 2MP Full HD Smart Wi-Fi CCTV Home Security Camera (version V1.00.02) contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability that allows local attackers to gain root shell access. Once accessed, the device exposes critical data including Wi-Fi credentials and ONVIF service credentials stored in plaintext, enabling further compromise of the network and connected systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30103 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5 contains a Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. A l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30103</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5 contains a Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Filesystem access for attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36608 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36608</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36609 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36609</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30480 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, versions prior to 19.19, contain(s) an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in PowerProtect Data Manager....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30480</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, versions prior to 19.19, contain(s) an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in PowerProtect Data Manager. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8328 | code-projects Exam Form Submission register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8328</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument USN leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26332 | TechAdvisor versions 2.6 through 3.37-30 for Dell XtremIO X2, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26332</link><description>TechAdvisor versions 2.6 through 3.37-30 for Dell XtremIO X2, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30105 | Dell XtremIO, version(s) 6.4.0-22, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30105</link><description>Dell XtremIO, version(s) 6.4.0-22, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8327 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s8.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8327</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s8.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45955 | Rocket Software Rocket Zena 4.4.1.26 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the filter parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45955</link><description>Rocket Software Rocket Zena 4.4.1.26 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the filter parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45619 | An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 firmware v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SendAction function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45619</link><description>An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 firmware v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SendAction function</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25691 | A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the component /themes/import of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25691</link><description>A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the component /themes/import of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45620 | An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45620</link><description>An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25692 | A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the _getHeaders function of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25692</link><description>A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the _getHeaders function of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36611 | Dell Encryption and Dell Security Management Server, versions prior to 11.11.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36611</link><description>Dell Encryption and Dell Security Management Server, versions prior to 11.11.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') Vulnerability. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8312 | Deadlock in PAM automatic check-in feature in Devolutions Server allows a password to remain valid beyond the end of its intended check-out ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8312</link><description>Deadlock in PAM automatic check-in feature in Devolutions Server allows a password to remain valid beyond the end of its intended check-out period due to a deadlock occurring in the scheduling service.This issue affects the following version(s) :

  *  
Devolutions Server 2025.2.5.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8353 | UI synchronization issue in the Just-in-Time (JIT) access request approval interface in Devolutions Server 2025.2.4.0 and earlier allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8353</link><description>UI synchronization issue in the Just-in-Time (JIT) access request approval interface in Devolutions Server 2025.2.4.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to gain unauthorized access to deleted JIT Groups via stale UI state during standard checkout request processing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54656 | Apache Struts Extras: Improper Output Neutralization for Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54656</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Output Neutralization for Logs vulnerability in Apache Struts.

This issue affects Apache Struts Extras: before 2.

When using LookupDispatchAction, in some cases, Struts may print untrusted input to the logs without any filtering. Specially-crafted input may lead to log output where part of the message masquerades as a separate log line, confusing consumers of the logs (either human or automated). 

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2593 | Kernel: ksmbd memory exhaustion denial-of-service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2593</link><description>A flaw exists within the Linux kernel's handling of new TCP connections. The issue results from the lack of memory release after its effective lifetime. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to create a denial of service condition on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50578 | LinuxServer.io heimdall 2.6.3-ls307 contains a vulnerability in how it handles user-supplied HTTP headers, specifically `X-Forwarded-Host` a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50578</link><description>LinuxServer.io heimdall 2.6.3-ls307 contains a vulnerability in how it handles user-supplied HTTP headers, specifically `X-Forwarded-Host` and `Referer`. An unauthenticated remote attacker can manipulate these headers to perform Host Header Injection and Open Redirect attacks. This allows the loading of external resources from attacker-controlled domains and unintended redirection of users, potentially enabling phishing, UI redress, and session theft. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation and trust of untrusted input, affecting the integrity and trustworthiness of the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43018 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro Printers – Potential Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43018</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro printers may be vulnerable to information disclosure when a non-authenticated user queries a device’s local address book.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53944 | AutoGPT Platform Exposes Graph Execution Results via Authorization Gap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53944</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents. In v0.6.15 and below, the external API's get_graph_execution_results endpoint has an authorization bypass vulnerability. While it correctly validates user access to the graph_id, it fails to verify ownership of the graph_exec_id parameter, allowing authenticated users to access any execution results by providing arbitrary execution IDs. The internal API implements proper validation for both parameters. This is fixed in v0.6.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54433 | Bugsink is vulnerable to Path Traversal attacks via event_id in ingestion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54433</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking service. In versions 1.4.2 and below, 1.5.0 through 1.5.4, 1.6.0 through 1.6.3, and 1.7.0 through 1.7.3,  ingestion paths construct file locations directly from untrusted event_id input without validation. A specially crafted event_id can result in paths outside the intended directory, potentially allowing file overwrite or creation in arbitrary locations. Submitting such input requires access to a valid DSN, potentially exposing them. If Bugsink runs in a container, the effect is confined to the container’s filesystem. In non-containerized setups, the overwrite may affect other parts of the system accessible to that user. This is fixed in versions 1.4.3, 1.5.5, 1.6.4 and 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54573 | CVAT vulnerable to email verification bypass by use of basic authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54573</link><description>CVAT is an open source interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions 1.1.0 through 2.41.0, email verification was not enforced when using Basic HTTP Authentication. As a result, users could create accounts using fake email addresses and use the product as verified users. Additionally, the missing email verification check leaves the system open to bot signups and further usage. CVAT 2.42.0 and later versions contain a fix for the issue. CVAT Enterprise customers have a workaround available; those customers may disable registration to prevent this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45515 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) through 10.1. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Zimbra webmail due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45515</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) through 10.1. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Zimbra webmail due to insufficient validation of the content type metadata when importing files into the briefcase. Attackers can exploit this issue by crafting a file with manipulated metadata, allowing them to bypass content type checks and execute arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46811 | SUSE Multi Linux Manager has unprotected websocket endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46811</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in SUSE Manager allows anyone with access to the websocket at /rhn/websocket/minion/remote-commands to execute arbitrary commands as root.




This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 0.3.7-150600.3.6.2; Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 5.0.14-150600.4.17.1; Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 5.0.14-150600.4.17.1; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-Azure: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-Azure: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-EC2: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-EC2: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-GCE: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-GCE: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 0.3.7-150400.3.39.4; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53111 | GLPI exposes data to non-allowed users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53111</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. In versions 0.80 through 10.0.18, a lack of permission checks can result in unauthorized access to some resources. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53112 | GLPI&amp;#x27;s incomprehensive permission checks can lead to data removal from allowed users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53112</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 9.1.0 through 10.0.18, a lack of permission checks can result in unauthorized removal of some specific resources. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53113 | GLPI technicians can access unauthorized information through external links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53113</link><description>GLPI, which stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique, is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.65 through 10.0.18, a technician can use the external links feature to fetch information on items they do not have the right to see. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53357 | GLPI permits reservation modification by unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53357</link><description>GLPI, which stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique, is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.78 through 10.0.18, a connected user can alter the reservations of another user. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52567 | GLPI has overly permissive URL verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52567</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.84 through 10.0.18, usage of RSS feeds or external calendars when planning is subject to SSRF exploit. The previous security patches provided since GLPI 10.0.4 were not robust enough for certain specific cases. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52897 | GLPI is vulnerable to XSS and open redirection attacks through planning feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52897</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. In versions 9.1.0 through 10.0.18, an unauthenticated user can send a malicious link to attempt a phishing attack from the planning feature. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53008 | GLPI&amp;#x27;s MailCollector Receiver is vulnerable to credential exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53008</link><description>GLPI stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 9.3.1 through 10.0.19, a connected user can use a malicious payload to steal mail receiver credentials. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54572 | Ruby SAML DOS vulnerability with large SAML response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54572</link><description>The Ruby SAML library is for implementing the client side of a SAML authorization. In versions 1.18.0 and below, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in ruby-saml even with the message_max_bytesize setting configured. The vulnerability occurs because the SAML response is validated for Base64 format prior to checking the message size, leading to potential resource exhaustion. This is fixed in version 1.18.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54425 | Umbraco&amp;#x27;s Delivery API allows for cached requests to be returned with an invalid API key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54425</link><description>Umbraco is an ASP.NET CMS. In versions 13.0.0 through 13.9.2, 15.0.0 through 15.4.1 and 16.0.0 through 16.1.0, the content delivery API can be restricted from public access where an API key must be provided in a header to authorize the request. It's also possible to configure output caching, such that the delivery API outputs will be cached for a period of time, improving performance. There's an issue when these two things are used together, where caching doesn't vary by the header that contains the API key. As such, it's possible for a user without a valid API key to retrieve a response for a given path and query if it has recently been requested and cached by request with a valid key. This is fixed in versions 13.9.3, 15.4.4 and 16.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54430 | dedupe is vulnerable to secret exfiltration via `issue_comment`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54430</link><description>dedupe is a python library that uses machine learning to perform fuzzy matching, deduplication and entity resolution quickly on structured data. Before commit 3f61e79, a critical severity vulnerability has been identified within the .github/workflows/benchmark-bot.yml workflow, where a issue_comment can be triggered using the @benchmark body. This workflow is susceptible to exploitation as it checkout the ${{ github.event.issue.number }}, which correspond to the branch of the PR manipulated by potentially malicious actors, and where untrusted code may be executed. Running untrusted code may lead to the exfiltration of GITHUB_TOKEN, which in this workflow has write permissions on most of the scopes - in particular the contents one - and could lead to potential repository takeover. This is fixed by commit 3f61e79.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54388 | Moby&amp;#x27;s Firewalld reload makes published container ports accessible from remote hosts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54388</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework developed by Docker Inc. that is distributed as Docker Engine, Mirantis Container Runtime, and various other downstream projects/products. In versions 28.2.0 through 28.3.2, when the firewalld service is reloaded it removes all iptables rules including those created by Docker. While Docker should automatically recreate these rules, versions before 28.3.3 fail to recreate the specific rules that block external access to containers. This means that after a firewalld reload, containers with ports published to localhost (like 127.0.0.1:8080) become accessible from remote machines that have network routing to the Docker bridge, even though they should only be accessible from the host itself. The vulnerability only affects explicitly published ports - unpublished ports remain protected. This issue is fixed in version 28.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54410 | Moby&amp;#x27;s Firewalld reload removes bridge network isolation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54410</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework developed by Docker Inc. that is distributed as Docker Engine, Mirantis Container Runtime, and various other downstream projects/products. A firewalld vulnerability affects Moby releases before 28.0.0. When firewalld reloads, Docker fails to re-create iptables rules that isolate bridge networks, allowing any container to access all ports on any other container across different bridge networks on the same host. This breaks network segmentation between containers that should be isolated, creating significant risk in multi-tenant environments. Only containers in --internal networks remain protected.
Workarounds include reloading firewalld and either restarting the docker daemon, re-creating bridge networks, or using rootless mode. Maintainers anticipate a fix for this issue in version 25.0.13.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47001 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47001</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.22 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8326 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s7.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8326</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_s7.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6348 | Smart Slider 3 &amp;lt;= 3.5.1.28 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via `sliderid` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6348</link><description>The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘sliderid’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1.28 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1221 | DoS in Zigbee device due to heavy traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1221</link><description>A Zigbee Radio Co-Processor (RCP), which is using SiLabs EmberZNet Zigbee stack, was unable to send messages to the host system (CPCd) due to heavy Zigbee traffic, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS) attack, Only hard reset will bring the device to normal operation</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1394 | Denial of Service (DoS) and memory leak vulnerabilities in Zigbee library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1394</link><description>Failure to handle the error status returned by the buffer management APIs in SiLabs EmberZNet Zigbee stack may result in data leaks or potential Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38498 | do_change_type(): refuse to operate on unmounted/not ours mounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38498</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

do_change_type(): refuse to operate on unmounted/not ours mounts

Ensure that propagation settings can only be changed for mounts located
in the caller's mount namespace. This change aligns permission checking
with the rest of mount(2).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8322 | Ventem｜e-School - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8322</link><description>The e-School from Ventem has a Missing Authorization vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to access administrator functions, including creating, modifying, and deleting accounts. They can even escalate any account to system administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8323 | Ventem｜e-School - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8323</link><description>The e-School from Ventem has a Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4422 | EfiSmiServices : EfiPcdProtocol, SMM memory corruption vulnerabilities in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4422</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4423 | SetupAutomationSmm:Vulnerability in the SMM module allow attacker to write arbitrary code and lead to memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4423</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4424 | SetupAutomationSmm : Arbitrary calls to SmmSetVariable with unsanitised arguments in SMI handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4424</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4425 | SetupAutomationSmm: Stack overflow vulnerability in SMI handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4425</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4426 | SetupAutomationSmm : SMRAM memory contents leak / information disclosure vulnerability in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4426</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8320 | Tesla Wall Connector Content-Length Header Improper Input Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8320</link><description>Tesla Wall Connector Content-Length Header Improper Input Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of the HTTP Content-Length header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in memory access past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26300.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8321 | Tesla Wall Connector Firmware Downgrade Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8321</link><description>Tesla Wall Connector Firmware Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware upgrade feature. The issue results from the lack of an anti-downgrade mechanism. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26299.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0712 | APM Server Uncontrolled Search Path Element can lead to Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) when using the Windows Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0712</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability can lead to local privilege Escalation (LPE) via Insecure Directory Permissions. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of directory permissions. An attacker with local access may exploit this flaw to move and delete arbitrary files, potentially gaining SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25011 | Beats Uncontrolled Search Path Element can lead to Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) when using the Windows Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25011</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability can lead to local privilege Escalation (LPE) via Insecure Directory Permissions. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of directory permissions. An attacker with local access may exploit this flaw to move and delete arbitrary files, potentially gaining SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4421 | EfiSmiServices: gEfiSmmCpuProtocol, SMM memory corruption vulnerabilities in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4421</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8217 | Inert Malicious script injected into Amazon Q Developer Visual Studio Code (VS Code) Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8217</link><description>The Amazon Q Developer Visual Studio Code (VS Code) extension v1.84.0 contains inert, injected code designed to call the Q Developer CLI. The code executes when the extension is launched within the VS Code environment; however the injected code contains a syntax error which prevents it from making a successful API call to the Q Developer CLI.



To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version v1.85.0. All installations of v1.84.0 should be removed from use.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43191 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43191</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43196 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43196</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43197 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43197</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43206 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43206</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43218 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43218</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43233 | This issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43233</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. A malicious app acting as a HTTPS proxy could get access to sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43237 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43237</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43265 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, visionOS 2.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43265</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, visionOS 2.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may disclose internal states of the app.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24119 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24119</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code out of its sandbox or with certain elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24188 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24188</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24224 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.5, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.5,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24224</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 18.5, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5, iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.5, watchOS 11.5, visionOS 2.5, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. A remote attacker may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31243 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31243</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31276 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Remote content m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31276</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Remote content may be loaded even when the 'Load Remote Images' setting is turned off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31278 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31278</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31280 | A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31280</link><description>A memory corruption issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43185 | A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43185</link><description>A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43186 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43186</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, visionOS 2.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. Parsing a file may lead to an unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43188 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A malicious app may be able to ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43188</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43194 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43194</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43195 | An issue existed in the handling of environment variables. This issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43195</link><description>An issue existed in the handling of environment variables. This issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43198 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43198</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43199 | A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ven...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43199</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43209 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43209</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, visionOS 2.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43211 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43211</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing web content may lead to a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43212 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43212</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43214 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43214</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43215 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafted image may result i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43215</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafted image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43216 | A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43216</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43217 | The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Privacy Indicators for m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43217</link><description>The issue was addressed by adding additional logic. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Privacy Indicators for microphone or camera access may not be correctly displayed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43224 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43224</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43226 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43226</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, visionOS 2.6. Processing a maliciously crafted image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43227 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43227</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6, watchOS 11.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may disclose sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43228 | The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43228</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved UI. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Visiting a malicious website may lead to address bar spoofing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43230 | The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43230</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, iPadOS 17.7.9, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43232 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43232</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43234 | Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43234</link><description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing a maliciously crafted texture may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43244 | A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43244</link><description>A race condition was addressed with improved state handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43245 | A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43245</link><description>A downgrade issue was addressed with additional code-signing restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43247 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43247</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. A malicious app with root privileges may be able to modify the contents of system files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43249 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43249</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43250 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43250</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43252 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A website may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43252</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A website may be able to access sensitive user data when resolving symlinks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43253 | This issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43253</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may be able to launch arbitrary binaries on a trusted device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43259 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43259</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An attacker with physical access to a locked device may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43260 | This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43260</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved data protection. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to hijack entitlements granted to other privileged apps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43266 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43266</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43270 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43270</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may gain unauthorized access to Local Network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43275 | A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43275</link><description>A race condition was addressed with additional validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43276 | A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. iCloud Private Relay may not activate w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43276</link><description>A logic error was addressed with improved error handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. iCloud Private Relay may not activate when more than one user is logged in at the same time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8319 | the BMA login interface allows arbitrary JavaScript or HTML to be written straight into the page’s Document Object Model via the error= URL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8319</link><description>the BMA login interface allows arbitrary JavaScript or HTML to be written straight into the page’s Document Object Model via the error= URL parameter</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31229 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Passcode may be read aloud by VoiceOver.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31229</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Passcode may be read aloud by VoiceOver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31273 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31273</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31275 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may be able t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31275</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may be able to launch any installed app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31277 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31277</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31279 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31279</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31281 | An input validation issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31281</link><description>An input validation issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43184 | This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43184</link><description>This issue was addressed by adding an additional prompt for user consent. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sequoia 15.4. A shortcut may be able to bypass sensitive Shortcuts app settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43189 | This issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43189</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may be able to read kernel memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43192 | A configuration issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. Account-dr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43192</link><description>A configuration issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. Account-driven User Enrollment may still be possible with Lockdown Mode turned on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43193 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43193</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43213 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43213</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected Safari crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43220 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43220</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43221 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43221</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.6, tvOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6. Processing a maliciously crafted media file may lead to unexpected app termination or corrupt process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43222 | A use-after-free issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43222</link><description>A use-after-free issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An attacker may be able to cause unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43223 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.7, iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43223</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.7.7, iPadOS 17.7.9, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, watchOS 11.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6, visionOS 2.6. A non-privileged user may be able to modify restricted network settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43225 | A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43225</link><description>A logging issue was addressed with improved data redaction. This issue is fixed in iPadOS 17.7.9, macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43229 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing maliciously crafted web co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43229</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to universal cross site scripting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43235 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43235</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43239 | An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43239</link><description>An out-of-bounds access issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43240 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A download's origin may be incorrectly associat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43240</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A download's origin may be incorrectly associated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43241 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43241</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to read files outside of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43243 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43243</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to modify protected parts of the file system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43246 | This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43246</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43248 | A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43248</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. A malicious app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43251 | An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A local attacker may gain ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43251</link><description>An authorization issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A local attacker may gain access to Keychain items.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43254 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43254</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43256 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43256</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43261 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43261</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to break out of its sandbox.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43267 | An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to access sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43267</link><description>An injection issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43273 | A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43273</link><description>A permissions issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43274 | A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may be able to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43274</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. A sandboxed process may be able to circumvent sandbox restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43277 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, watchOS 11.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43277</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, watchOS 11.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6, visionOS 2.6. Processing a maliciously crafted audio file may lead to memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54381 | BentoML is Vulnerable to an SSRF Attack Through File Upload Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54381</link><description>BentoML is a Python library for building online serving systems optimized for AI apps and model inference. In versions 1.4.0 until 1.4.19, the file upload processing system contains an SSRF vulnerability that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to force the server to make arbitrary HTTP requests. The vulnerability stems from the multipart form data and JSON request handlers, which automatically download files from user-provided URLs without validating whether those URLs point to internal network addresses, cloud metadata endpoints, or other restricted resources. The documentation explicitly promotes this URL-based file upload feature, making it an intended design that exposes all deployed services to SSRF attacks by default. Version 1.4.19 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54126 | WebAssembly Micro Runtime&amp;#x27;s `--addr-pool` option allows all IPv4 addresses when subnet mask is not specified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54126</link><description>The WebAssembly Micro Runtime's (WAMR) iwasm package is the executable binary built with WAMR VMcore which supports WebAssembly System Interface (WASI) and command line interface. In versions 2.4.0 and below, iwasm uses --addr-pool with an IPv4 address that lacks a subnet mask, allowing the system to accept all IP addresses. This can unintentionally expose the service to all incoming connections and bypass intended access restrictions. Services relying on --addr-pool for restricting access by IP may unintentionally become open to all external connections. This may lead to unauthorized access in production deployments, especially when users assume that specifying an IP without a subnet mask implies a default secure configuration. This is fixed in version 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 22:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7848 | Missing input check in lvpict.cpp used in NI LabVIEW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7848</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability due to improper input validation in lvpict.cpp exists in NI LabVIEW that may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7849 | Memory Corruption Issue in NI LabVIEW due to improper error handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7849</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability due to improper error handling when a VILinkObj is null exists in NI LabVIEW that may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40600 | Use of Externally-Controlled Format String vulnerability in the SonicOS SSL VPN interface allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40600</link><description>Use of Externally-Controlled Format String vulnerability in the SonicOS SSL VPN interface allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause service disruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4674 | Unexpected command execution in untrusted VCS repositories in cmd/go</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4674</link><description>The go command may execute unexpected commands when operating in untrusted VCS repositories. This occurs when possibly dangerous VCS configuration is present in repositories. This can happen when a repository was fetched via one VCS (e.g. Git), but contains metadata for another VCS (e.g. Mercurial). Modules which are retrieved using the go command line, i.e. via "go get", are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7361 | Code Injection Vulnerability in NI LabVIEW when using CIN nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7361</link><description>A code injection vulnerability due to an improper initialization check exists in NI LabVIEW that may result in arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI using a CIN node.  This vulnerability affects 32-bit NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.  LabVIEW 64-bit versions do not support CIN nodes and are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52490 | An issue was discovered in Couchbase Sync Gateway before 3.2.6. In sgcollect_info_options.log and sync_gateway.log, there are cleartext pass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52490</link><description>An issue was discovered in Couchbase Sync Gateway before 3.2.6. In sgcollect_info_options.log and sync_gateway.log, there are cleartext passwords in redacted and unredacted output.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 20:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45346 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Bacula-web before v.9.7.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP GET request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45346</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Bacula-web before v.9.7.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted HTTP GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5684 | MetForm &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `mf-template` DOM Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5684</link><description>The MetForm – Contact Form, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Custom Form Builder for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `mf-template` DOM Element in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:49:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53902 | Tuleap exposes artifacts to a mentioned user via email notifications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53902</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite created to facilitate management of software development and collaboration. In Tuleap Community Edition prior to version 16.9.99.1752585665 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition prior to 16.8-6 and 16.9-5, users may potentially access confidential information from artifacts that they are not authorized to view. This is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition prior to version 16.9.99.1752585665 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition prior to 16.8-6 and 16.9-5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43018 | Piwigo 13.8.0 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the parameters max_level and min_register. These parameters are used in ws_user_ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43018</link><description>Piwigo 13.8.0 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the parameters max_level and min_register. These parameters are used in ws_user_gerList function from file include\ws_functions\pwg.users.php and this same function is called by ws.php file at some point can be used for searching users in advanced way in /admin.php?page=user_list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52899 | Tuleap vulnerable to user enumeration via the lost password form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52899</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite created to facilitate management of software development and collaboration. In Tuleap Community Edition prior to version 16.9.99.1750843170 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition prior to 16.8-4 and 16.9-2, the forgot password form allows for user enumeration. This is fixed in Tuleap Community Edition version 16.9.99.1750843170 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.8-4 and 16.9-2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53102 | Discourse&amp;#x27;s WebAuthn challenge isn&amp;#x27;t cleared from user session after authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53102</link><description>Discourse is an open-source community discussion platform. Prior to version 3.4.7 on the `stable` branch and version 3.5.0.beta.8 on the `tests-passed` branch, upon issuing a physical security key for 2FA, the server generates a WebAuthn challenge, which the client signs. The challenge is not cleared from the user’s session after authentication, potentially allowing reuse and increasing security risk. This is fixed in versions 3.4.7 and 3.5.0.beta.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53541 | Tuleap is vulnerable to XSS attacks when displaying the children of a parent artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53541</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite created to facilitate management of software development and collaboration. In Tuleap Community Edition prior to version 16.9.99.1751892857 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition prior to 16.8-5 and 16.9-3, malicious users with some control over certain artifacts could insert malicious code when displaying the children of a parent artifact to force victims to execute the uncontrolled code. This is fixed in version Tuleap Community Edition prior to version 16.9.99.1751892857 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition prior to 16.8-5 and 16.9-3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49828 | IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49828</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5.0.0 through 10.5.0.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51473 | IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51473</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5.0.0 through 10.5.0.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 

is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52894 | IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52894</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5.0.0 through 10.5.0.11, 11.1.0 through 11.1.4.7, 11.5.0 through 11.5.9, and 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:24:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33092 | IBM Db2 for Linux code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33092</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux 12.1.0, 12.1.1, and 12.1.2 

is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow in db2fm, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33114 | IBM Db2 for Linux denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33114</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux 12.1.0, 12.1.1, and 12.1.2 



is vulnerable to denial of service with a specially crafted query under certain non-default conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36071 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36071</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes DB2 Connect Server) 11.5.0 through 11.5.9 and 12.1.0 through 12.1.2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query due to improper release of memory resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51044 | phpgurukul Nipah virus (NiV) Testing Management System 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /new-user-testing.php file, due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51044</link><description>phpgurukul Nipah virus (NiV) Testing Management System 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /new-user-testing.php file, due to insufficient validation of user input for the " govtissuedid" parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51045 | Phpgurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /admin/password-recovery.php file. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51045</link><description>Phpgurukul Pre-School Enrollment System 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /admin/password-recovery.php file. This vulnerability is attributed to the insufficient validation of user input for the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42651 | NanoMQ v0.17.9 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free vulnerability via the component sub_Ctx_handle. This vulnerability allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42651</link><description>NanoMQ v0.17.9 was discovered to contain a heap use-after-free vulnerability via the component sub_Ctx_handle. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SUBSCRIBE message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42655 | An access control issue in NanoMQ v0.21.10 allows attackers to bypass security restrictions and access sensitive system topic messages using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42655</link><description>An access control issue in NanoMQ v0.21.10 allows attackers to bypass security restrictions and access sensitive system topic messages using MQTT wildcard characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36010 | IBM Db2 for Linux denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36010</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux 12.1.0, 12.1.1, and 12.1.2 

could allow an unauthenticated user to cause a denial of service due to executable segments that are waiting for each other to release a necessary lock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53711 | TP-Link TL-WR841N WlanNetworkRpm.htm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53711</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TP-Link TL-WR841N V11. The vulnerability exists in the /userRpm/WlanNetworkRpm.htm file due to missing input parameter validation, which may lead to the buffer overflow to cause a crash of the web service and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53712 | TP-Link TL-WR841N WlanNetworkRpm_AP.htm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53712</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TP-Link TL-WR841N V11. The vulnerability exists in the /userRpm/WlanNetworkRpm_AP.htm file due to missing input parameter validation, which may lead to the buffer overflow to cause a crash of the web service and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition. The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53713 | TP-Link TL-WR841N WlanNetworkRpm_APC.htm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53713</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TP-Link TL-WR841N V11. The vulnerability exists in the /userRpm/WlanNetworkRpm_APC.htm file due to missing input parameter validation, which may lead to the buffer overflow to cause a crash of the web service and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.  The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53714 | TP-Link TL-WR841N WzdWlanSiteSurveyRpm_AP.htm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53714</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TP-Link TL-WR841N V11. The vulnerability exists in the /userRpm/WzdWlanSiteSurveyRpm_AP.htm file due to missing input parameter validation, which may lead to the buffer overflow to cause a crash of the web service and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.  The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53715 | TP-Link TL-WR841N Wan6to4TunnelCfgRpm.htm buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53715</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TP-Link TL-WR841N V11. The vulnerability exists in the /userRpm/Wan6to4TunnelCfgRpm.htm file due to missing input parameter validation, which may lead to the buffer overflow to cause a crash of the web service and result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.  The attack may be launched remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6637 | PRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6637</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7497 | PRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7497</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7675 | 3DM File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7675</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5038 | X_T File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5038</link><description>A maliciously crafted X_T file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5043 | 3DM File Parsing Heap-Based Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5043</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when linked or imported into certain Autodesk products, can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6631 | PRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6631</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write vulnerability. A malicious actor may leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, cause data corruption, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6635 | PRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6635</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when linked or imported into certain Autodesk products, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6636 | PRT File Parsing Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6636</link><description>A maliciously crafted PRT file, when parsed through certain Autodesk products, can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27514 | GLPI is susceptible to Stored XSS attack through project&amp;#x27;s kanban</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27514</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 9.5.0 through 10.0.18, a technician can use a malicious payload to trigger a stored XSS on the project's kanban. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2533 | IBM Db2 for Linux denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2533</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux 12.1.0, 12.1.1, and 12.1.2 is vulnerable to a denial of service as the server may crash under certain conditions with a specially crafted query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2928 | SQL Injection affecting the Archiver role.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2928</link><description>SQL Injection affecting the Archiver role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52284 | Totolink X6000R V9.4.0cu.1360_B20241207 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the sub_4184C0 function via the tz paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52284</link><description>Totolink X6000R V9.4.0cu.1360_B20241207 was found to contain a command injection vulnerability in the sub_4184C0 function via the tz parameter. This vulnerability allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2179 | GlobalProtect App: Non Admin User Can Disable the GlobalProtect App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2179</link><description>An incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect™ App on Linux devices enables a locally authenticated non administrative user to disable the app even if the GlobalProtect app configuration would not normally permit them to do so.

The GlobalProtect app on Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, Chrome OS and GlobalProtect UWP app are not affected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44137 | MapTiler Tileserver-php v2.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The renderTile function within tileserver.php is responsible for deliveri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44137</link><description>MapTiler Tileserver-php v2.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The renderTile function within tileserver.php is responsible for delivering tiles that are stored as files on the server via web request. Creating the path to a file allows the insertion of "../" and thus read any file on the web server. Affected GET parameters are "TileMatrix", "TileRow", "TileCol" and "Format"</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28170 | Grandstream Networks GXP1628 &lt;=1.0.4.130 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device is configured with directory listing enabled,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28170</link><description>Grandstream Networks GXP1628 &lt;=1.0.4.130 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device is configured with directory listing enabled, allowing unauthorized access to sensitive directories and files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31965 | HCL BigFix Remote Control is affected by an authorization bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31965</link><description>Improper access restrictions in HCL BigFix Remote Control Server WebUI (versions 10.1.0.0248 and lower) allow non-admin users to view unauthorized information on certain web pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44136 | MapTiler Tileserver-php v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The GET parameter "layer" is reflected in an error message without...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44136</link><description>MapTiler Tileserver-php v2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). The GET parameter "layer" is reflected in an error message without html encoding. This leads to XSS and allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or JavaScript code on a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5922 | Retrievable password hash protecting TSplus admin console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5922</link><description>Access to TSplus Remote Access Admin Tool is restricted to administrators (unless "Disable UAC" option is enabled) and requires a PIN code. In versions below v18.40.6.17 the PIN's hash is stored in a system registry accessible to regular users, making it possible to perform a brute-force attack using rainbow tables, since the hash is not salted.
LTS (Long-Term Support) versions also received patches in v17.2025.6.27 and v16.2025.6.27 releases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28171 | An issue in Grandstream UCM6510 v.1.0.20.52 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Login function at /c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28171</link><description>An issue in Grandstream UCM6510 v.1.0.20.52 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Login function at /cgi and /webrtccgi.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28172 | Grandstream Networks UCM6510 v1.0.20.52 and before is vulnerable to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts. An attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28172</link><description>Grandstream Networks UCM6510 v1.0.20.52 and before is vulnerable to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts. An attacker can perform an arbitrary number of authentication attempts using different passwords and eventually gain access to the targeted account using a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51970 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php endpoint of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper saniti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51970</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the action.php endpoint of PuneethReddyHC Online Shopping System Advanced 1.0 due to improper sanitization of user-supplied input in the keyword POST parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46059 | langchain-ai v0.3.51 was discovered to contain an indirect prompt injection vulnerability in the GmailToolkit component. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46059</link><description>langchain-ai v0.3.51 was discovered to contain an indirect prompt injection vulnerability in the GmailToolkit component. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and compromise the application via a crafted email message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50738 | The Memos application, up to version v0.24.3, allows for the embedding of markdown images with arbitrary URLs. When a user views a memo cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50738</link><description>The Memos application, up to version v0.24.3, allows for the embedding of markdown images with arbitrary URLs. When a user views a memo containing such an image, their browser automatically fetches the image URL without explicit user consent or interaction beyond viewing the memo. This can be exploited by an attacker to disclose the viewing user's IP address, browser User-Agent string, and potentially other request-specific information to the attacker-controlled server, leading to information disclosure and user tracking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42644 | FlashMQ v1.14.0 was discovered to contain an assertion failure in the function PublishCopyFactory::getNewPublish, which occurs when the QoS ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42644</link><description>FlashMQ v1.14.0 was discovered to contain an assertion failure in the function PublishCopyFactory::getNewPublish, which occurs when the QoS value of the publish object is greater than 0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:03:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42645 | An issue in FlashMQ v1.14.0 allows attackers to cause an assertion failure via sending a crafted retain message, leading to a Denial of Serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42645</link><description>An issue in FlashMQ v1.14.0 allows attackers to cause an assertion failure via sending a crafted retain message, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:03:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52358 | A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Vivaldi United Group iCONTROL+ Server including Firmware version 4.7.8.0.eden Logic version 5.32 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52358</link><description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Vivaldi United Group iCONTROL+ Server including Firmware version 4.7.8.0.eden Logic version 5.32 and below. This issue allows attackers to inject JavaScript payloads within the error or edit-menu-item parameters which are then executed in the victim's browser session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54422 | Sandboxie exposes encrypted sandbox key during password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54422</link><description>Sandboxie is a sandbox-based isolation software for 32-bit and 64-bit Windows NT-based operating systems. In versions 1.16.1 and below, a critical security vulnerability exists in password handling mechanisms. During encrypted sandbox creation, user passwords are transmitted via shared memory, exposing them to potential interception. The vulnerability is particularly severe during password modification operations, where both old and new passwords are passed as plaintext command-line arguments to the Imbox process without any encryption or obfuscation. This implementation flaw allows any process within the user session, including unprivileged processes, to retrieve these sensitive credentials by reading the command-line arguments, thereby bypassing standard privilege requirements and creating a significant security risk. This is fixed in version 1.16.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6504 | Possibilities of IP Spoofing via X-Forwarded-For (XFF) Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6504</link><description>In HDP Server versions below 4.6.2.2978 on Linux, unauthorized access could occur via IP spoofing using the X-Forwarded-For header. 

Since XFF is a client-controlled header, it could be spoofed, allowing unauthorized access if the spoofed IP matched a whitelisted range.


This vulnerability could be exploited to bypass IP restrictions, though valid user credentials would still be required for resource access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6505 | Unauthorized access and impersonation can occur in versions 4.6.2.3226 and below of Progress Software's Hybrid Data Pipeline Server on Linux...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6505</link><description>Unauthorized access and impersonation can occur in versions 4.6.2.3226 and below of Progress Software's Hybrid Data Pipeline Server on Linux. This vulnerability allows attackers to combine credentials from different sources, potentially leading to client impersonation and unauthorized access.
 When OAuth Clients perform an OAuth handshake with the Hybrid Data Pipeline Server, the server accepts client credentials from both HTTP headers and request parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7458 | SQLite integer overflow in key info allocation may lead to information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7458</link><description>An integer overflow in the sqlite3KeyInfoFromExprList function in SQLite versions 3.39.2 through 3.41.1 allows an attacker with the ability to execute arbitrary SQL statements to cause a denial of service or disclose sensitive information from process memory via a crafted SELECT statement with a large number of expressions in the ORDER BY clause.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41241 | Denial-of-service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41241</link><description>VMware vCenter contains a denial-of-service vulnerability. A malicious actor who is authenticated through vCenter and has permission to perform API calls for guest OS customisation may trigger this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6060 | XSS in DECE Software&amp;#x27;s Geodi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6060</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DECE Software Geodi allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Geodi: before GEODI Setup 9.0.146.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6175 | CRLF Injection in DECE Software&amp;#x27;s Geodi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6175</link><description>Improper Neutralization of CRLF Sequences ('CRLF Injection') vulnerability in DECE Software Geodi allows HTTP Request Splitting.This issue affects Geodi: before GEODI Setup 9.0.146.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40682 | SQL injection vulnerability in Human Resource Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40682</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Human Resource Management System version 1.0, which allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases via the “city” and “state” parameters in the /controller/ccity.php endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40683 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Human Resource Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40683</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Human Resource Management System version 1.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the 'searccity' parameter in /city.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40684 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Human Resource Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40684</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Human Resource Management System version 1.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the 'searccountry' parameter in/country.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40685 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Human Resource Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40685</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Human Resource Management System version 1.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the 'searcstate' parameter in/state.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40686 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Human Resource Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40686</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Human Resource Management System version 1.0. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending a malicious URL through the 'employeeid' parameter in/detailview.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5587 | Appzend &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via progressbarLayout Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5587</link><description>The Appzend theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘progressbarLayout’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:26:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6681 | Fan Page &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via width Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6681</link><description>The Fan Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘width’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6692 | YouTube Embed &amp;lt;= 10.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via instance Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6692</link><description>The YouTube Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘instance’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6730 | Bonanza – WooCommerce Free Gifts Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Opt In Success</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6730</link><description>The Bonanza – WooCommerce Free Gifts Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the xlo_optin_call() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to set the opt in status to success.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7689 | Hydra Booking 1.1.0 - 1.1.18 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via tfhb_reset_password_callback Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7689</link><description>The Hydra Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to a missing capability check on the tfhb_reset_password_callback() function in versions 1.1.0 to 1.1.18. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to reset the password of an Administrator user, achieving full privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8196 | Magical Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8196</link><description>The Magical Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Custom Attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8216 | Sky Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8216</link><description>The Sky Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26400 | SolarWinds Web Help Desk XML External Entity Injection (XXE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26400</link><description>SolarWinds Web Help Desk was reported to be affected by an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) vulnerability that could lead to information disclosure. A valid, low-privilege access is required unless the attacker had access to the local server to modify configuration files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53081 | An 'Arbitrary File Creation' in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to create arbitrary files in unintended locations on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53081</link><description>An 'Arbitrary File Creation' in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to create arbitrary files in unintended locations on the filesystem. Exploitation is restricted to specific, authorized private IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53082 | An 'Arbitrary File Deletion' in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to delete arbitrary files from unintended locations on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53082</link><description>An 'Arbitrary File Deletion' in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to delete arbitrary files from unintended locations on the filesystem. Exploitation is restricted to specific, authorized private IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53077 | An execution after redirect in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to execute limited functions without permissions. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53077</link><description>An execution after redirect in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to execute limited functions without permissions. An attacker could compromise the integrity of the platform by executing this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53078 | Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via write file to system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53078</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via write file to system</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53079 | Absolute Path Traversal in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows authenticated attacker (Administrator) to read sensitive files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53079</link><description>Absolute Path Traversal in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows authenticated attacker (Administrator) to read sensitive files</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53080 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53080</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') in Samsung DMS(Data Management Server) allows authenticated attackers to create arbitrary files in unintended locations on the filesystem</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8264 | Versions of the package z-push/z-push-dev before 2.7.6 are vulnerable to SQL Injection due to unparameterized queries in the IMAP backend. A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8264</link><description>Versions of the package z-push/z-push-dev before 2.7.6 are vulnerable to SQL Injection due to unparameterized queries in the IMAP backend. An attacker can inject malicious commands by manipulating the username field in basic authentication. This allows the attacker to access and potentially modify or delete sensitive data from a linked third-party database. &#13;&#13;**Note:** This vulnerability affects Z-Push installations that utilize the IMAP backend and have the IMAP_FROM_SQL_QUERY option configured. &#13;&#13; Mitigation&#13;Change configuration to use the default or LDAP in backend/imap/config.php&#13;&#13;php&#13;define('IMAP_DEFAULTFROM', '');&#13;&#13;or&#13;php&#13;define('IMAP_DEFAULTFROM', 'ldap');</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53649 | "SwitchBot" App for iOS/Android contains an insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability in versions V6.24 through V9.12. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53649</link><description>"SwitchBot" App for iOS/Android contains an insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability in versions V6.24 through V9.12. If this vulnerability is exploited, sensitive user information may be exposed to an attacker who has access to the application logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3075 | Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.29.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3075</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'elementor-element' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.29.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only impacts sites with 'Element Caching' enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4370 | Brizy &amp;lt;= 2.6.20 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4370</link><description>The Brizy – Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited file uploads due to missing authorization on process_external_asset_urls function as well as missing path validation in store_file function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.20. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload .TXT files on the affected site's server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4566 | Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.30.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Text Path Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4566</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More Than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-text DOM element attribute in Text Path widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.30.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This attack affects only Chrome/Edge browsers</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6495 | Bricks Builder &amp;lt;= 1.12.4 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via `p` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6495</link><description>The Bricks theme for WordPress is vulnerable to blind SQL Injection via the ‘p’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.4 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:04:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7809 | StreamWeasels Twitch Integration &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7809</link><description>The StreamWeasels Twitch Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'data-uuid' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 04:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7810 | StreamWeasels Kick Integration &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7810</link><description>The StreamWeasels Kick Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'data-uuid' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 04:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7811 | StreamWeasels YouTube Integration &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7811</link><description>The StreamWeasels YouTube Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'data-uuid' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 04:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>