<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-4637 | The WPvivid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the restore() and get_res...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4637</link><description>The WPvivid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the restore() and get_restore_progress() function in versions up to, and including, 0.9.94. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke these functions and obtain full file paths if they have access to a back-up ID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6526 | The Meta Box – WordPress Custom Fields Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom post meta valu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6526</link><description>The Meta Box – WordPress Custom Fields Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom post meta values displayed through the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6557 | The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.8.2 v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6557</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.8.2 via the route function hooked into wp_ajax_nopriv_tribe_dropdown. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract potentially sensitive data including post titles and IDs of pending, private and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6635 | The EditorsKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation on the 'import_styles' funct...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6635</link><description>The EditorsKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation on the 'import_styles' function in versions up to, and including, 1.40.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6700 | The Cookie Information | Free GDPR Consent Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary option updates due to a missing capabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6700</link><description>The Cookie Information | Free GDPR Consent Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary option updates due to a missing capability check on its AJAX request handler in versions up to, and including, 2.0.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access or higher, to edit arbitrary site options which can be used to create administrator accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6701 | The Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a custom text field in all versions u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6701</link><description>The Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a custom text field in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6808 | The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6808</link><description>The Booking for Appointments and Events Calendar – Amelia plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.93 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6884 | This plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6884</link><description>This plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'place_id' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6925 | The Unlimited Addons for WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6925</link><description>The Unlimited Addons for WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation on the 'importZipFile' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.42. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with a role that the administrator previously granted access to the plugin (the default is editor role, but access can also be granted to contributor role), to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6933 | The Better Search Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via deseria...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6933</link><description>The Better Search Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6953 | The PDF Generator For Fluent Forms – The Contact Form Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the heade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6953</link><description>The PDF Generator For Fluent Forms – The Contact Form Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the header, PDF body and footer content parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The exploitation level depends on who is granted the right to create forms by an administrator. This level can be as low as contributor, but by default is admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6959 | The Getwid – Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6959</link><description>The Getwid – Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the recaptcha_api_key_manage function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add, modify, or delete the 'Recaptcha Site Key' and 'Recaptcha Secret Key' settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6963 | The Getwid – Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CAPTCHA Bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6963</link><description>The Getwid – Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CAPTCHA Bypass in versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the Captcha Verification of the Contact Form block by omitting 'g-recaptcha-response' from the 'data' array.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6982 | The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6982</link><description>The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode and postmeta in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6983 | The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Refere...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6983</link><description>The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 via the vg_display_data shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to retrieve potentially sensitive post meta.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6985 | The 10Web AI Assistant – AI content writing assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6985</link><description>The 10Web AI Assistant – AI content writing assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the install_plugin AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.18. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins that can be used to gain further access to a compromised site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6989 | The Shield Security – Smart Bot Blocking &amp; Intrusion Prevention Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6989</link><description>The Shield Security – Smart Bot Blocking &amp; Intrusion Prevention Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 18.5.9 via the render_action_template parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attacker to include and execute PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6996 | The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Code Injection via the plugin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6996</link><description>The Display custom fields in the frontend – Post and User Profile Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Code Injection via the plugin's vg_display_data shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input validation and restriction on access to that shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to call arbitrary functions and execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7014 | The Author Box, Guest Author and Co-Authors for Your Posts – Molongui plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7014</link><description>The Author Box, Guest Author and Co-Authors for Your Posts – Molongui plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.4 via the 'ma_debu' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including post author emails and names if applicable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7029 | The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7029</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including 9.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 9.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0221 | The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0221</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.19 via the rename_item function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers to rename arbitrary files on the server. This can lead to site takeovers if the wp-config.php file of a site can be renamed. By default this can be exploited by administrators only. In the premium version of the plugin, administrators can give gallery management permissions to lower level users, which might make this exploitable by users as low as contributors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0254 | The (Simply) Guest Author Name plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's post meta in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0254</link><description>The (Simply) Guest Author Name plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's post meta in all versions up to, and including, 4.34 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0255 | The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wprm-recipe-text-share' shortcode in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0255</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wprm-recipe-text-share' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0324 | The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0324</link><description>The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wppb_two_factor_authentication_settings_update' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable or disable the 2FA functionality present in the Premium version of the plugin for arbitrary user roles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0366 | The Starbox – the Author Box for Humans plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0366</link><description>The Starbox – the Author Box for Humans plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.7 via the action function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for subscribers to view plugin preferences and potentially other user settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0370 | The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0370</link><description>The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_view' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to modify the titles of arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0371 | The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0371</link><description>The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'create_view' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to create form views.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0372 | The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0372</link><description>The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_form_fields' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access and above, to create form views.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0373 | The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forger...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0373</link><description>The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_view' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary post titles via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0374 | The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forger...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0374</link><description>The Views for WPForms – Display &amp; Edit WPForms Entries on your site frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'create_view' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create views via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0380 | The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0 via the 'icon' att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0380</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0 via the 'icon' attribute used in Shortcodes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include the contents of SVG files on the server, which can be leveraged for Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0382 | The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0382</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0 due to unrestricted use of the 'header_tag' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0384 | The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Recipe Notes in all versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0384</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Recipe Notes in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0428 | The Index Now plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3. This is due to m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0428</link><description>The Index Now plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'reset_form' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary site options via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0448 | The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget URL parameters in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0448</link><description>The Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widget URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0508 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Table Elementor Widget...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0508</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Pricing Table Elementor Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the user supplied link URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0509 | The WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘request’ parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0509</link><description>The WP 404 Auto Redirect to Similar Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘request’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0585 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0585</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Filterable Gallery widget in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the Image URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0586 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0586</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Login/Register Element in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the custom login URL. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0597 | The SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0597</link><description>The SEO Plugin by Squirrly SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to and including 12.3.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0612 | The Content Views – Post Grid, Slider, Accordion (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0612</link><description>The Content Views – Post Grid, Slider, Accordion (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0630 | The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the RSS feed source in all versions up to, and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0630</link><description>The WP RSS Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the RSS feed source in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0659 | The Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files (eCommerce Store &amp; Payments Made Easy) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Si...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0659</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – Sell Digital Files (eCommerce Store &amp; Payments Made Easy) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the variable pricing option title in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with shop manger-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0660 | The Formidable Forms – Contact Form, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cros...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0660</link><description>The Formidable Forms – Contact Form, Survey, Quiz, Payment, Calculator Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the update_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change form settings and add malicious JavaScript via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0668 | The Advanced Database Cleaner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3 via des...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0668</link><description>The Advanced Database Cleaner plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.3 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'process_bulk_action' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attacker, with administrator access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0678 | The Order Delivery Date for WP e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'available-days-tf' para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0678</link><description>The Order Delivery Date for WP e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'available-days-tf' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0691 | The FileBird plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imported folder titles in all versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0691</link><description>The FileBird plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imported folder titles in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. It may also be possible to socially engineer an administrator into uploading a malicious folder import.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0699 | The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0699</link><description>The AI Engine: Chatbots, Generators, Assistants, GPT 4 and more! plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'add_image_from_url' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0701 | The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Security Feature Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0701</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Security Feature Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the use of client-side restrictions to enforce the 'Disabled registration' Membership feature within the plugin's General settings. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an account even when account registration has been disabled by an administrator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0709 | The Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'coinslist' parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0709</link><description>The Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'coinslist' parameter in versions 2.0 to 2.6.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0761 | The File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1 due to ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0761</link><description>The File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1 due to insufficient randomness in the backup filenames, which use a timestamp plus 4 random digits. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers, to extract sensitive data including site backups in configurations where the .htaccess file in the directory does not block access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0790 | The WOLF – WordPress Posts Bulk Editor and Manager Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0790</link><description>The WOLF – WordPress Posts Bulk Editor and Manager Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpbe_create_new_term, wpbe_update_tax_term, and wpbe_delete_tax_term functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create, modify and delete taxonomy terms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Furthermore, the functions wpbe_save_options, wpbe_bulk_delete_posts_count, wpbe_bulk_delete_posts, and wpbe_save_meta are vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery allowing for plugin options update, post count deletion, post deletion and modification of post metadata via forged request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0791 | The WOLF – WordPress Posts Bulk Editor and Manager Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification or l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0791</link><description>The WOLF – WordPress Posts Bulk Editor and Manager Professional plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification or loss of data due to a missing capability check on the wpbe_create_new_term, wpbe_update_tax_term, and wpbe_delete_tax_term functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to create, delete or modify taxonomy terms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0796 | The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0796</link><description>The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions corresponding to AJAX actions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to invoke those functions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0797 | The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0797</link><description>The Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of functionality due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6.1. This makes it possible for subscribers and higher to execute functions intended for admin use.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0823 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Link To' url in carousels in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0823</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Link To' url in carousels in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0834 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the link_to parameter in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0834</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the link_to parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0835 | The Royal Elementor Kit theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary transient update due to a missing capability check on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0835</link><description>The Royal Elementor Kit theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary transient update due to a missing capability check on the dismissed_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.116. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber access or higher, to update arbitrary transients. Note, that these transients can only be updated to true and not arbitrary values.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0859 | The Affiliates Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.34. This i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0859</link><description>The Affiliates Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.34. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_bulk_action function in ListAffiliatesTable.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete affiliates via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0869 | The Instant Images – One Click Image Uploads from Unsplash, Openverse, Pixabay and Pexels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0869</link><description>The Instant Images – One Click Image Uploads from Unsplash, Openverse, Pixabay and Pexels plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized arbitrary options update due to an insufficient check that neglects to verify whether the updated option belongs to the plugin on the instant-images/license REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0. This makes it possible for authors and higher to update arbitrary options.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0954 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to St...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0954</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting through editing context via the 'data-eael-wrapper-link' wrapper in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied protocols. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0961 | The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the code editor in all versions up to, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0961</link><description>The SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the code editor in all versions up to, and including, 1.58.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0969 | The ARMember plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21 via the REST ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0969</link><description>The ARMember plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.21 via the REST API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass the plugin's "Default Restriction" feature and view restricted post content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1046 | The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1046</link><description>The Paid Membership Plugin, Ecommerce, User Registration Form, Login Form, User Profile &amp; Restrict Content – ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin 'reg-number-field' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.14.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1072 | The Website Builder by SeedProd — Theme Builder, Landing Page Builder, Coming Soon Page, Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1072</link><description>The Website Builder by SeedProd — Theme Builder, Landing Page Builder, Coming Soon Page, Maintenance Mode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the seedprod_lite_new_lpage function in all versions up to, and including, 6.15.21. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the contents of coming-soon, maintenance pages, login and 404 pages set up with the plugin. Version 6.15.22 addresses this issue but introduces a bug affecting admin pages. We suggest upgrading to 6.15.23.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1075 | The Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to maintenance mode bypass and information disclosure in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1075</link><description>The Minimal Coming Soon – Coming Soon Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to maintenance mode bypass and information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.37. This is due to the plugin improperly validating the request path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass maintenance mode and view pages that should be hidden.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1092 | The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1092</link><description>The RSS Aggregator by Feedzy – Feed to Post, Autoblogging, News &amp; YouTube Video Feeds Aggregator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized data modification due to a missing capability check on the feedzy dashboard in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to create, edit or delete feed categories created by them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1121 | The Advanced Forms for ACF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1121</link><description>The Advanced Forms for ACF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_json_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to export form settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1177 | The WP Club Manager – WordPress Sports Club Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1177</link><description>The WP Club Manager – WordPress Sports Club Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the settings_save() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the permalink structure for the clubs</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1208 | The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.2 via API....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1208</link><description>The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.2 via API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain access to quiz questions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1209 | The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.1 via dire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1209</link><description>The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.1 via direct file access due to insufficient protection of uploaded assignments. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain those uploads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1210 | The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.1 via API....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1210</link><description>The LearnDash LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.1 via API. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain access to quizzes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24595 | Allegro AI’s open-source version of ClearML stores passwords in plaintext within the MongoDB instance, resulting in a compromised server lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24595</link><description>Allegro AI’s open-source version of ClearML stores passwords in plaintext within the MongoDB instance, resulting in a compromised server leaking all user emails and passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:22:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24559 | Vyper SHA3 code generation bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24559</link><description>Vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the EVM. There is an error in the stack management when compiling the `IR` for `sha3_64`. Concretely, the `height` variable is miscalculated. The vulnerability can't be triggered without writing the `IR` by hand (that is, it cannot be triggered from regular vyper code). `sha3_64` is used for retrieval in mappings. No flow that would cache the `key` was found so the issue shouldn't be possible to trigger when compiling the compiler-generated `IR`. This issue isn't triggered during normal compilation of vyper code so the impact is low. At the time of publication there is no patch available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24574 | phpMyFAQ vulnerable to stored XSS on attachments filename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24574</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application for PHP 8.1+ and MySQL, PostgreSQL and other databases. Unsafe echo of filename in phpMyFAQ\phpmyfaq\admin\attachments.php leads to allowed execution of JavaScript code in client side (XSS). This vulnerability has been patched in version 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51951 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Stock Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter in the ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51951</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Stock Management System 1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id parameter in the manage_bo.php file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50782 | Python-cryptography: bleichenbacher timing oracle attack against rsa decryption - incomplete fix for cve-2020-25659</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50782</link><description>A flaw was found in the python-cryptography package. This issue may allow a remote attacker to decrypt captured messages in TLS servers that use RSA key exchanges, which may lead to exposure of confidential or sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:54:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50781 | M2crypto: bleichenbacher timing attacks in the rsa decryption api - incomplete fix for cve-2020-25657</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50781</link><description>A flaw was found in m2crypto. This issue may allow a remote attacker to decrypt captured messages in TLS servers that use RSA key exchanges, which may lead to exposure of confidential or sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0202 | Cryptlib: rsa key exchange ciphersuites in tls vulnerable to marvin attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0202</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in the cryptlib cryptographic library when cryptlib is compiled with the support for RSA key exchange ciphersuites in TLS (by setting the USE_RSA_SUITES define), it will be vulnerable to the timing variant of the Bleichenbacher attack. An attacker that is able to perform a large number of connections to the server will be able to decrypt RSA ciphertexts or forge signatures using server's certificate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1052 | Boundary Vulnerable to Session Hijacking Through TLS Certificate Tampering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1052</link><description>Boundary and Boundary Enterprise (“Boundary”) is vulnerable to session hijacking through TLS certificate tampering. An attacker with privileges to enumerate active or pending sessions, obtain a private key pertaining to a session, and obtain a valid trust on first use (TOFU) token may craft a TLS certificate to hijack an active session and gain access to the underlying service or application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22208 | phpMyFAQ sharing FAQ functionality can easily be abused for phishing purposes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22208</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an Open Source FAQ web application for PHP 8.1+ and MySQL, PostgreSQL and other databases. The 'sharing FAQ' functionality allows any unauthenticated actor to misuse the phpMyFAQ application to send arbitrary emails to a large range of targets. The phpMyFAQ application has a functionality where anyone can share a FAQ item to others. The front-end of this functionality allows any phpMyFAQ articles to be shared with 5 email addresses. Any unauthenticated actor can perform this action. There is a CAPTCHA in place, however the amount of people you email with a single request is not limited to 5 by the backend. An attacker can thus solve a single CAPTCHA and send thousands of emails at once. An attacker can utilize the target application's email server to send phishing messages. This can get the server on a blacklist, causing all emails to end up in spam. It can also lead to reputation damages. This issue has been patched in version 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27318 | Denial of Service Vulnerability in StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27318</link><description>StorageGRID (formerly StorageGRID Webscale) versions 11.6.0 through 
11.6.0.13 are susceptible to a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability. A 
successful exploit could lead to a crash of the Local Distribution 
Router (LDR) service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24543 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the function setSchedWifi in Tenda AC9 v.3.0, firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24543</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the function setSchedWifi in Tenda AC9 v.3.0, firmware version v.15.03.06.42_multi allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service or run arbitrary code via crafted overflow data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:46:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24807 | Sulu is vulnerable to HTML Injection via Autocomplete Suggestion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24807</link><description>Sulu is a highly extensible open-source PHP content management system based on the Symfony framework. There is an issue when inputting HTML into the Tag name. The HTML is executed when the tag name is listed in the auto complete form. Only admin users can create tags so they are the only ones affected. The problem is patched with version(s) 2.4.16 and 2.5.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22567 | File Upload vulnerability in MCMS 5.3.5 allows attackers to upload arbitrary files via crafted POST request to /ms/file/upload.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22567</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in MCMS 5.3.5 allows attackers to upload arbitrary files via crafted POST request to /ms/file/upload.do.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22202 | User Removal Page Allows Spoofing Of User Details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22202</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application for PHP 8.1+ and MySQL, PostgreSQL and other databases. phpMyFAQ's user removal page allows an attacker to spoof another user's detail, and in turn make a compelling phishing case for removing another user's account. The front-end of this page doesn't allow changing the form details, an attacker can utilize a proxy to intercept this request and submit other data. Upon submitting this form, an email is sent to the administrator informing them that this user wants to delete their account. An administrator has no way of telling the difference between the actual user wishing to delete their account or the attacker issuing this for an account they do not control. This issue has been patched in version 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24396 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24396</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the search bar component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6874 | Zigbee Unauthenticated DoS via NWK Sequence number manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6874</link><description>Prior to v7.4.0, Ember ZNet is vulnerable to a denial of service attack through manipulation of the NWK sequence number</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24258 | mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddSubMenu function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24258</link><description>mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddSubMenu function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24259 | mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddMenuEntry function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24259</link><description>mupdf v1.23.9 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the menuEntry variable in the glutAddMenuEntry function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24260 | media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_subscribe_remove function at /uac/sip-uac-sub...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24260</link><description>media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_subscribe_remove function at /uac/sip-uac-subscribe.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24262 | media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_uac_stop_timer function at /uac/sip-uac-trans...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24262</link><description>media-server v1.0.0 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the sip_uac_stop_timer function at /uac/sip-uac-transaction.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24263 | Lotos WebServer v0.1.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the response_append_status_line function at /lotos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24263</link><description>Lotos WebServer v0.1.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the response_append_status_line function at /lotos/src/response.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24265 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the dst_props variable in the gf_filter_pid_merge_properties_internal function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24265</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the dst_props variable in the gf_filter_pid_merge_properties_internal function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24266 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the dasher_configure_pid function at /src/filters/dasher.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24266</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability via the dasher_configure_pid function at /src/filters/dasher.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24267 | gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the gfio_blob variable in the gf_fileio_from_blob function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24267</link><description>gpac v2.2.1 was discovered to contain a memory leak via the gfio_blob variable in the gf_fileio_from_blob function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6028 | SDM Web interface vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6028</link><description>A reflected
cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SVG version of System
Diagnostics Manager of B&amp;R Automation Runtime versions &lt;= G4.93 that
enables a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the context
of the attacked user’s browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0953 | QR Code Scanner does not prompt before navigating user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0953</link><description>When a user scans a QR Code with the QR Code Scanner feature, the user is not prompted before being navigated to the page specified in the code.  This may surprise the user and potentially direct them to unwanted content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47355 | The com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot (aka Eyuep Can Yilmaz {ROOT] Quick Reboot) application 1.0.8 for Android has exposed broadcast receivers for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47355</link><description>The com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot (aka Eyuep Can Yilmaz {ROOT] Quick Reboot) application 1.0.8 for Android has exposed broadcast receivers for PowerOff, Reboot, and Recovery (e.g., com.eypcnnapps.quickreboot.widget.PowerOff) that are susceptible to unauthorized broadcasts because of missing input validation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0323 | FTP uses unsecure encryption mechanisms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0323</link><description>Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Runtime (SDM modules).



The FTP server used on the B&amp;R
Automation Runtime supports unsecure encryption mechanisms, such as SSLv3,
TLSv1.0 and TLS1.1. An network-based attacker can exploit the flaws to conduct
man-in-the-middle attacks or to decrypt communications between the affected product
clients.  

This issue affects Automation Runtime: from 14.0 before 14.93.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23054 | An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software that could allow for remote code execution due to a package liste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23054</link><description>An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software that could allow for remote code execution due to a package listed in ++plone++static/components not existing in the public package index (npm).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24397 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24397</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Stimulsoft GmbH Stimulsoft Dashboard.JS before v.2024.1.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the ReportName field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24469 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the delete_post .php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24469</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the delete_post .php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24468 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_customblock.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24468</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the add_customblock.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7216 | Cpio: extraction allows symlinks which enables remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7216</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in the CPIO utility. This issue could allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to trick a user into opening a specially crafted archive. During the extraction process, the archiver could follow symlinks outside of the intended directory, which could be utilized to run arbitrary commands on the target system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24768 | 1Panel set-cookie is missing the Secure keyword</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24768</link><description>1Panel is an open source Linux server operation and maintenance management panel. The HTTPS cookie that comes with the panel does not have the Secure keyword, which may cause the cookie to be sent in plain text if accessed using HTTP. This issue has been patched in version 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52138 | Path traversal via crafted cpio archives in Engrampa archivers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52138</link><description>Engrampa is an archive manager for the MATE environment. Engrampa is found to be vulnerable to a Path Traversal vulnerability that can be leveraged to achieve full Remote Command Execution (RCE) on the target. While handling CPIO archives, the Engrampa Archive manager follows symlink, cpio by default will follow stored symlinks while extracting and the Archiver will not check the symlink location, which leads to arbitrary file writes to unintended locations. When the victim extracts the archive, the attacker can craft a malicious cpio or ISO archive to achieve RCE on the target system. This vulnerability was fixed in commit 63d5dfa.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24762 | FastAPI vulnerable to content-type header Regular expression Denial of Service (ReDoS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24762</link><description>FastAPI is a web framework for building APIs with Python 3.8+ based on standard Python type hints. When using form data, `python-multipart` uses a Regular Expression to parse the HTTP `Content-Type` header, including options. An attacker could send a custom-made `Content-Type` option that is very difficult for the RegEx to process, consuming CPU resources and stalling indefinitely (minutes or more) while holding the main event loop. This means that process can't handle any more requests. It's a ReDoS(Regular expression Denial of Service), it only applies to those reading form data, using `python-multipart`. This vulnerability has been patched in version 0.109.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23108 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23108</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.2 and 6.7.0 through 6.7.8 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and 6.5.0 through 6.5.2 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23109 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23109</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 7.1.0 through 7.1.1 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.2 and 6.7.0 through 6.7.8 and 6.6.0 through 6.6.3 and 6.5.0 through 6.5.2 and 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1225 | QiboSoft QiboCMS X1 Pay.php rmb_pay deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1225</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in QiboSoft QiboCMS X1 up to 1.0.6. Affected by this vulnerability is the function rmb_pay of the file /application/index/controller/Pay.php. The manipulation of the argument callback_class leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252847. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5249 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5249</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper memory processing operations to exploit a software race condition. If the system’s memory is carefully prepared by the user, then this in turn cause a use-after-free.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r35p0 through r40p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r35p0 through r40p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5643 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5643</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user to make improper GPU memory processing operations. Depending on the configuration of the Mali GPU Kernel Driver, and if the system’s memory is carefully prepared by the user, then this in turn could write to memory outside of buffer bounds.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r41p0 through r45p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 09:56:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4436 | 3DPrint Lite &amp;lt; 1.9.1.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4436</link><description>The 3DPrint Lite WordPress plugin before 1.9.1.5 does not have any authorisation and does not check the uploaded file in its p3dlite_handle_upload AJAX action , allowing unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary file to the web server. However, there is a .htaccess, preventing the file to be accessed on Web servers such as Apache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22667 | Vim before 9.0.2142 has a stack-based buffer overflow because did_set_langmap in map.c calls sprintf to write to the error buffer that is pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22667</link><description>Vim before 9.0.2142 has a stack-based buffer overflow because did_set_langmap in map.c calls sprintf to write to the error buffer that is passed down to the option callback functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24864 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel media/dvb-core in dvbdmx_write()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24864</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's media/dvb-core in dvbdmx_write() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24857 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth in conn_info_{min,max}_age_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24857</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth device driver in conn_info_{min,max}_age_set() function. This can result in integrity overflow issue, possibly leading to bluetooth connection abnormality or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24858 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel net/bluetooth in {conn,adv}_{min,max}_interval_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24858</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth in {conn,adv}_{min,max}_interval_set() function. This can result in I2cap connection or broadcast abnormality issue, possibly leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24855 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel scsi device driver lpfc_unregister_fcf_rescan()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24855</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's scsi device driver in lpfc_unregister_fcf_rescan() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24859 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth sniff_{min,max}_interval_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24859</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's net/bluetooth in sniff_{min,max}_interval_set() function. This can result in a bluetooth sniffing exception issue, possibly leading denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24860 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel bluetooth driver in {min,max}_key_size_set()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24860</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's bluetooth device driver in {min,max}_key_size_set() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24861 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel media/xc4000 xc4000_get_frequency()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24861</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's media/xc4000 device driver in xc4000 xc4000_get_frequency() function. This can result in return value overflow issue, possibly leading to malfunction or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22386 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel drm/exynos exynos_drm_crtc_atomic_disable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22386</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's drm/exynos device driver in exynos_drm_crtc_atomic_disable() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23196 | Race condition vulnerability in Linux kernel sound/hda snd_hdac_regmap_sync</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23196</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux kernel's sound/hda  device driver in snd_hdac_regmap_sync() function. This can result in a null pointer dereference issue, possibly leading to a kernel panic or denial of service issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7077 | Sharp NEC Displays (P403, P463, P553, P703, P801, X554UN, X464UN, X554UNS, X464UNV, X474HB, X464UNS, X554UNV, X555UNS, X555UNV, X754HB, X554...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7077</link><description>Sharp NEC Displays (P403, P463, P553, P703, P801, X554UN, X464UN, X554UNS, X464UNV, X474HB, X464UNS, X554UNV, X555UNS, X555UNV, X754HB, X554HB, E705, E805, E905, UN551S, UN551VS, X551UHD, X651UHD, X841UHD, X981UHD, MD551C8) allows an attacker execute remote code by sending unintended parameters in http request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24838 | WordPress Five Star Restaurant Reviews Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24838</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Five Star Plugins Five Star Restaurant Reviews allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Five Star Restaurant Reviews: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24839 | WordPress Structured Content Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24839</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gordon Böhme, Antonio Leutsch Structured Content (JSON-LD) #wpsc allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Structured Content (JSON-LD) #wpsc: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24841 | WordPress Add Customer for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24841</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan's Art Add Customer for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Add Customer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24846 | WordPress Mighty Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24846</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MightyThemes Mighty Addons for Elementor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mighty Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.9.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24847 | WordPress CalculatorPro Calculators Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24847</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jgadbois CalculatorPro Calculators allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CalculatorPro Calculators: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24848 | WordPress PT Sign Ups Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24848</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MJS Software PT Sign Ups – Beautiful volunteer sign ups and management made easy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PT Sign Ups – Beautiful volunteer sign ups and management made easy: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24865 | WordPress Scroll Triggered Box Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24865</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Noah Kagan Scroll Triggered Box allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Scroll Triggered Box: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24866 | WordPress Biteship Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.24 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24866</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Biteship Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Biteship: Plugin Ongkos Kirim Kurir Instant, Reguler, Kargo: from n/a through 2.2.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20001 | In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20001</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961601; Issue ID: DTV03961601.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20002 | In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20002</link><description>In TVAPI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: DTV03961715; Issue ID: DTV03961715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20003 | In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20003</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01191612 (MSV-981).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20004 | In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20004</link><description>In Modem NL1, there is a possible system crash due to an improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service, if NW sent invalid NR RRC Connection Setup message, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01191612; Issue ID: MOLY01195812 (MSV-985).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20006 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20006</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08477148; Issue ID: ALPS08477148.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20007 | In mp3 decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20007</link><description>In mp3 decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a race condition. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441369; Issue ID: ALPS08441369.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20009 | In alac decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20009</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect error handling. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441150; Issue ID: ALPS08441150.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20010 | In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20010</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358560; Issue ID: ALPS08358560.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20011 | In alac decoder, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20011</link><description>In alac decoder, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441146; Issue ID: ALPS08441146.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20012 | In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20012</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08358566; Issue ID: ALPS08358566.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20013 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20013</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08471742; Issue ID: ALPS08308608.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20015 | In telephony, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20015</link><description>In telephony, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08441419; Issue ID: ALPS08441419.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20016 | In ged, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20016</link><description>In ged, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS07835901; Issue ID: ALPS07835901.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 06:09:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24870 | WordPress Advanced iFrame Plugin &amp;lt;= 2023.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24870</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Dempfle Advanced iFrame allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced iFrame: from n/a through 2023.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51504 | WordPress Dan&amp;#x27;s Embedder for Google Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51504</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dan Dulaney Dan's Embedder for Google Calendar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Dan's Embedder for Google Calendar: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5677 | Insufficient input validation in VAPIX API tcptext.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5677</link><description>Brandon
Rothel from QED Secure Solutions has found that the VAPIX API tcptest.cgi
did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code
execution. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an
operator- or administrator-privileged service account. The impact of exploiting
this vulnerability is lower with operator-privileges compared to
administrator-privileges service accounts. Axis has released patched AXIS OS
versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory
for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5800 | Insufficient input validation in VAPIX API create_overlay.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5800</link><description>Vintage,
member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that the VAPIX API create_overlay.cgi
did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code
execution. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an
operator- or administrator-privileged service account. Axis has released patched AXIS OS
versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory
for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 05:26:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25089 | Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.9.9.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via gRPC named pipes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25089</link><description>Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.9.9.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via gRPC named pipes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 21:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46902 | An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. Path...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46902</link><description>An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. Path validation is mishandled, and thus an admin can read or delete files in violation of expected access controls.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46903 | An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46903</link><description>An issue was discovered in LTOS-Web-Interface in Meinberg LANTIME-Firmware before 6.24.029 MBGID-9343 and 7 before 7.04.008 MBGID-6303. An admin can delete required user accounts (in violation of expected access control).</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 20:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52425 | libexpat through 2.5.0 allows a denial of service (resource consumption) because many full reparsings are required in the case of a large to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52425</link><description>libexpat through 2.5.0 allows a denial of service (resource consumption) because many full reparsings are required in the case of a large token for which multiple buffer fills are needed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52426 | libexpat through 2.5.0 allows recursive XML Entity Expansion if XML_DTD is undefined at compile time.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52426</link><description>libexpat through 2.5.0 allows recursive XML Entity Expansion if XML_DTD is undefined at compile time.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4435 | Yarn: untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4435</link><description>An untrusted search path vulnerability was found in Yarn. When a victim runs certain Yarn commands in a directory with attacker-controlled content, malicious commands could be executed in unexpected ways.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36773 | Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36773</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single character code in a PDF document can map to more than one Unicode code point (e.g., for a ligature).</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25098 | blockmason credit-protocol UCAC CreditProtocol.sol executeUcacTx denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25098</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in blockmason credit-protocol. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeUcacTx of the file contracts/CreditProtocol.sol of the component UCAC Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 082e01f18707ef995e80ebe97fcedb229a55efc5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252799. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25062 | An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XIncl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25062</link><description>An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XInclude expansion enabled, processing crafted XML documents can lead to an xmlValidatePopElement use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6240 | Kernel: marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage in the rsa decryption operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6240</link><description>A Marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage was found in the RSA decryption operation in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a network attacker to decrypt ciphertexts or forge signatures, limiting the services that use that private key.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25159 | mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso cargos.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25159</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso up to 4.50.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file config/cargos.php. The manipulation of the argument dni_profe leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 4.51.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 678190bee1dfd64b54a2b0e88abfd009e78adce8. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-252717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10129 | planet-freo auth.inc.php comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in planet-freo up to 20150116 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/inc/auth.inc.php. The manipulation of the argument auth leads to incorrect comparison. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 6ad38c58a45642eb8c7844e2f272ef199f59550d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252716.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 04:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33851 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33851</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW950.00 through FW950.90, FW1020.00 through FW1020.40, and FW1030.00 through FW1030.30 could reveal sensitive partition data to a system administrator.  IBM X-Force ID:  257135.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50947 | IBM Business Automation Workflow cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50947</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow 22.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  275665.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1215 | SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload fetch_data.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file fetch_data.php. The manipulation of the argument username/city leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252782 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0853 | OCSP verification bypass with TLS session reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0853</link><description>curl inadvertently kept the SSL session ID for connections in its cache even when the verify status (*OCSP stapling*) test failed. A subsequent transfer to
the same hostname could then succeed if the session ID cache was still fresh, which then skipped the verify status check.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 13:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1064 | Improper Neutralization of HTTP Headers for Scripting Syntax in Crafty Controller 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1064</link><description>A host header injection vulnerability in the HTTP handler component of Crafty Controller allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) condition via a modified host header</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 09:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49950 | The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a cust...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49950</link><description>The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a custom Jinja template in the Alert view. A remote attacker can craft a cross-site scripting (XSS) payload and send it to any system or device that sends logs to the SIEM. If an alert is created, the payload will execute upon the alert data being viewed with that template, which can lead to sensitive data disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43183 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43183</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change the password of an admin and hijack their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44031 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44031</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive files in insecure locations via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0895 | The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0895</link><description>The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied data. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0909 | The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0909</link><description>The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient restrictions through the REST API on the posts/pages that protections are being place on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access protected content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23550 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) may be vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23550</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) could disclose sensitive user information when installing the Windows agent.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attack to exploit an application parameter during execution of the Save Report.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1200 | Jspxcms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /template/1/default/. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31004 | IBM Security Access Manager Container gain access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31004</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote attacker to gain access to the underlying system using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  254765.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31006 | IBM Security Access Manager Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31006</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to a denial of service attacks on the DSC server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254776.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32327 | IBM Security Access Manager Container XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32327</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  254783.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32329 | IBM Security Access Manager Container improper file validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32329</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a user to download files from an incorrect repository due to improper file validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  254972.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43016 | IBM Security Access Manager Container unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43016</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote user to log into the server due to a user account with an empty password.  IBM X-Force ID:  266154.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30999 | IBM Security Access Manager denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30999</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  254651.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31005 | IBM Security Access Manager Container privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31005</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to an improper security configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  254767.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1199 | CodeAstro Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1199</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \employee-tasks-php\attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument aten_id leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>