<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:33:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-41390 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in the git functionality of Truffle Security Co. TruffleHog 3.90.2. A specially crafted rep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41390</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in the git functionality of Truffle Security Co. TruffleHog 3.90.2. A specially crafted repository can lead to a arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious respository to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11680 | Out-of-bounds Write in libwebsockets PNG parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11680</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write in unfilter_scanline in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_UPNG flag is enabled during compilation and the HTML display stack is used, to write past a heap allocated buffer possibly causing a crash, when the user visits an attacker controlled website that contains a crafted PNG file with a big width value that causes an integer overflow which value is used for determining the size of a heap allocation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11679 | Out-of-bounds Read in libwebsockets PNG parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11679</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in lws_upng_emit_next_line in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_UPNG flag is enabled during compilation and the HTML display stack is used, to read past a heap allocated buffer possibly causing a crash, when the user visits an attacker controlled website that contains a crafted PNG file with a big height dimension.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11678 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in libwebsockets DNS response parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11678</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow in lws_adns_parse_label in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_SYS_ASYNC_DNS flag is enabled during compilation, to overflow the label_stack, when the attacker is able to sniff a DNS request in order to craft a response with a matching id containing a label longer than the maximum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11677 | Use After Free in libwebsockets WebSocket server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11677</link><description>Use After Free in WebSocket server implementation in lws_handshake_server in warmcat libwebsockets may allow an attacker, in specific configurations where the user provides a callback function that handles LWS_CALLBACK_HTTP_CONFIRM_UPGRADE, to achieve denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61455 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the signup.inc.php endpoint. The application directl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61455</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the signup.inc.php endpoint. The application directly incorporates unsanitized user inputs into SQL queries, allowing unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and gain full access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56223 | A lack of rate limiting in the component /Home/UploadStreamDocument of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56223</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the component /Home/UploadStreamDocument of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via uploading an excessive number of files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61454 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the search endpoint. Unsanitized inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61454</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the search endpoint. Unsanitized input in the /search parameter is directly reflected back into the response HTML, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of a user who visits a malicious link or submits a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56219 | Incorrect access control in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to arbitrarily add user accounts without any rate limiting. This can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56219</link><description>Incorrect access control in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to arbitrarily add user accounts without any rate limiting. This can lead to a resource exhaustion and a Denial of Service (DoS) when an excessively large number of user accounts are created.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56224 | A lack of rate limiting in the One-Time Password (OTP) verification endpoint of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass verification vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56224</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the One-Time Password (OTP) verification endpoint of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass verification via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8349 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) stored in Tawk Live Chat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8349</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) stored vulnerability in Tawk Live Chat. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by uploading a malicious PDF with JavaScript payload through the chatbot. The PDF is stored by the application and subsequently displayed without proper sanitisation when other users access it. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41028 | SQL injection in Epsilon RH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41028</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability has been found in Epsilon RH by Grupo Castilla. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete database via sending a POST request using the parameter ‘sEstadoUsr’ in ‘/epsilonnetws/WSAvisos.asmx’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57837 | Tileservice module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57837</link><description>Tileservice module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57838 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57838</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57839 | Photo module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57839</link><description>Photo module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31342 | Galaxy Software Services Vitals ESP Forum Module - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31342</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in the upload file function of Galaxy Software Services Corporation Vitals ESP Forum Module through 1.3 version allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61932 | Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) (Client program (MR) and Detection agent (DA)) improperly verifies the origin of incoming requests, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61932</link><description>Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) (Client program (MR) and Detection agent (DA)) improperly verifies the origin of incoming requests, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code by sending specially crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 07:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62577 | ETERNUS SF provided by Fsas Technologies Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A low-privileged user with access to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62577</link><description>ETERNUS SF provided by Fsas Technologies Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A low-privileged user with access to the management server may obtain database credentials, potentially allowing execution of OS commands with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 05:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40004 | net/9p: Fix buffer overflow in USB transport layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40004</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/9p: Fix buffer overflow in USB transport layer

A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the USB 9pfs transport layer
where inconsistent size validation between packet header parsing and
actual data copying allows a malicious USB host to overflow heap buffers.

The issue occurs because:
- usb9pfs_rx_header() validates only the declared size in packet header
- usb9pfs_rx_complete() uses req-&gt;actual (actual received bytes) for
memcpy

This allows an attacker to craft packets with small declared size
(bypassing validation) but large actual payload (triggering overflow
in memcpy).

Add validation in usb9pfs_rx_complete() to ensure req-&gt;actual does not
exceed the buffer capacity before copying data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 05:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11948 | Excellent Infotek｜Document Management System - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11948</link><description>Document Management System developed by Excellent Infotek has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11947 | bftpd Configuration File options.c expand_groups heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11947</link><description>A weakness has been identified in bftpd up to 6.2. Impacted is the function expand_groups of the file options.c of the component Configuration File Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11946 | LogicalDOC Community Edition Add Contact frontend.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11946</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in LogicalDOC Community Edition up to 9.2.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /frontend.jsp of the component Add Contact Page. Performing manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name/Company/Address/Phone/Mobile results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11945 | toeverything AFFiNE Avatar Upload Image Endpoint cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11945</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in toeverything AFFiNE up to 0.24.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Avatar Upload Image Endpoint. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11944 | givanz Vvveb Raw SQL import.php import sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11944</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in givanz Vvveb up to 1.0.7.3. This affects the function Import of the file admin/controller/tools/import.php of the component Raw SQL Handler. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: 52204b4a106b2fb02d16eee06a88a1f2697f9b35. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11943 | 70mai X200 HTTP Web Server default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11943</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 70mai X200 up to 20251010. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HTTP Web Server. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 19:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11942 | 70mai X200 Pairing missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11942</link><description>A flaw has been found in 70mai X200 up to 20251010. Affected is an unknown function of the component Pairing. Executing manipulation can lead to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11941 | e107 CMS Avatar image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11941</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in e107 CMS up to 2.3.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /e107_admin/image.php?mode=main&amp;amp;action=avatar of the component Avatar Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument multiaction[] results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11940 | LibreWolf Installer setup.nsi uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11940</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LibreWolf up to 143.0.4-1 on Windows. This affects an unknown function of the file assets/setup.nsi of the component Installer. Such manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack must be carried out locally. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. Upgrading to version 144.0-1 mitigates this issue. The name of the patch is dd10e31dd873e9cb309fad8aed921d45bf905a55. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11939 | ChurchCRM Backup Restore RestoreJob.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11939</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/ChurchCRM/Backup/RestoreJob.php of the component Backup Restore Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument restoreFile can lead to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11938 | ChurchCRM setup.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11938</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setup/routes/setup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument DB_PASSWORD/ROOT_PATH/URL results in deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62672 | rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62672</link><description>rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This occurs in memcpy in the RPLAY_DATA case in rplay_unpack in librplay/rplay.c, potentially reachable via packet data with no authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47410 | Apache Geode: CSRF attacks through GET requests to the Management and Monitoring REST API that can execute gfsh commands on the target system</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47410</link><description>Apache Geode is vulnerable to CSRF attacks through GET requests to the Management and Monitoring REST API that could allow an attacker who has tricked a user into giving up their Geode session credentials to submit malicious commands on the target system on behalf of the authenticated user.


This issue affects Apache Geode: versions 1.10 through 1.15.1

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.15.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11926 | Related Posts Lite &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11926</link><description>The Related Posts Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9890 | Theme Editor &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9890</link><description>The Theme Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'theme_editor_theme' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40001 | scsi: mvsas: Fix use-after-free bugs in mvs_work_queue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40001</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: mvsas: Fix use-after-free bugs in mvs_work_queue

During the detaching of Marvell's SAS/SATA controller, the original code
calls cancel_delayed_work() in mvs_free() to cancel the delayed work
item mwq-&gt;work_q. However, if mwq-&gt;work_q is already running, the
cancel_delayed_work() may fail to cancel it. This can lead to
use-after-free scenarios where mvs_free() frees the mvs_info while
mvs_work_queue() is still executing and attempts to access the
already-freed mvs_info.

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0 (remove)            | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
mvs_pci_remove()          |
  mvs_free()              | mvs_work_queue()
    cancel_delayed_work() |
      kfree(mvi)          |
                          |   mvi-&gt; // UAF

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() to ensure
that the delayed work item is properly canceled and any executing
delayed work item completes before the mvs_info is deallocated.

This bug was found by static analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40002 | thunderbolt: Fix use-after-free in tb_dp_dprx_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40002</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

thunderbolt: Fix use-after-free in tb_dp_dprx_work

The original code relies on cancel_delayed_work() in tb_dp_dprx_stop(),
which does not ensure that the delayed work item tunnel-&gt;dprx_work has
fully completed if it was already running. This leads to use-after-free
scenarios where tb_tunnel is deallocated by tb_tunnel_put(), while
tunnel-&gt;dprx_work remains active and attempts to dereference tb_tunnel
in tb_dp_dprx_work().

A typical race condition is illustrated below:

CPU 0                            | CPU 1
tb_dp_tunnel_active()            |
  tb_deactivate_and_free_tunnel()| tb_dp_dprx_start()
    tb_tunnel_deactivate()       |   queue_delayed_work()
      tb_dp_activate()           |
        tb_dp_dprx_stop()        | tb_dp_dprx_work() //delayed worker
          cancel_delayed_work()  |
    tb_tunnel_put(tunnel);       |
                                 |   tunnel = container_of(...); //UAF
                                 |   tunnel-&gt; //UAF

Replacing cancel_delayed_work() with cancel_delayed_work_sync() is
not feasible as it would introduce a deadlock: both tb_dp_dprx_work()
and the cleanup path acquire tb-&gt;lock, and cancel_delayed_work_sync()
would wait indefinitely for the work item that cannot proceed.

Instead, implement proper reference counting:
- If cancel_delayed_work() returns true (work is pending), we release
  the reference in the stop function.
- If it returns false (work is executing or already completed), the
  reference is released in delayed work function itself.

This ensures the tb_tunnel remains valid during work item execution
while preventing memory leaks.

This bug was found by static analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40003 | net: mscc: ocelot: Fix use-after-free caused by cyclic delayed work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40003</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: mscc: ocelot: Fix use-after-free caused by cyclic delayed work

The origin code calls cancel_delayed_work() in ocelot_stats_deinit()
to cancel the cyclic delayed work item ocelot-&gt;stats_work. However,
cancel_delayed_work() may fail to cancel the work item if it is already
executing. While destroy_workqueue() does wait for all pending work items
in the work queue to complete before destroying the work queue, it cannot
prevent the delayed work item from being rescheduled within the
ocelot_check_stats_work() function. This limitation exists because the
delayed work item is only enqueued into the work queue after its timer
expires. Before the timer expiration, destroy_workqueue() has no visibility
of this pending work item. Once the work queue appears empty,
destroy_workqueue() proceeds with destruction. When the timer eventually
expires, the delayed work item gets queued again, leading to the following
warning:

workqueue: cannot queue ocelot_check_stats_work on wq ocelot-switch-stats
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 0 at kernel/workqueue.c:2255 __queue_work+0x875/0xaf0
...
RIP: 0010:__queue_work+0x875/0xaf0
...
RSP: 0018:ffff88806d108b10 EFLAGS: 00010086
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 0000000000000101 RCX: 0000000000000027
RDX: 0000000000000027 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffff88806d123e88
RBP: ffffffff813c3170 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: ffffed100da247d2
R10: ffffed100da247d1 R11: ffff88806d123e8b R12: ffff88800c00f000
R13: ffff88800d7285c0 R14: ffff88806d0a5580 R15: ffff88800d7285a0
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880e5725000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007fe18e45ea10 CR3: 0000000005e6c000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
Call Trace:
 
 ? kasan_report+0xc6/0xf0
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 call_timer_fn+0x25/0x1c0
 __run_timer_base.part.0+0x3be/0x8c0
 ? __pfx_delayed_work_timer_fn+0x10/0x10
 ? rcu_sched_clock_irq+0xb06/0x27d0
 ? __pfx___run_timer_base.part.0+0x10/0x10
 ? try_to_wake_up+0xb15/0x1960
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x603/0x7e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 ? sched_balance_trigger+0x1c0/0x9f0
 ? sched_tick+0x221/0x5a0
 ? _raw_spin_lock_irq+0x80/0xe0
 ? __pfx__raw_spin_lock_irq+0x10/0x10
 ? tick_nohz_handler+0x339/0x440
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote_up+0x10/0x10
 __walk_groups.isra.0+0x42/0x150
 tmigr_handle_remote+0x1f4/0x2e0
 ? __pfx_tmigr_handle_remote+0x10/0x10
 ? ktime_get+0x60/0x140
 ? lapic_next_event+0x11/0x20
 ? clockevents_program_event+0x1d4/0x2a0
 ? hrtimer_interrupt+0x322/0x780
 handle_softirqs+0x16a/0x550
 irq_exit_rcu+0xaf/0xe0
 sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x70/0x80
 
...

The following diagram reveals the cause of the above warning:

CPU 0 (remove)             | CPU 1 (delayed work callback)
mscc_ocelot_remove()       |
  ocelot_deinit()          | ocelot_check_stats_work()
    ocelot_stats_deinit()  |
      cancel_delayed_work()|   ...
                           |   queue_delayed_work()
      destroy_workqueue()  | (wait a time)
                           | __queue_work() //UAF

The above scenario actually constitutes a UAF vulnerability.

The ocelot_stats_deinit() is only invoked when initialization
failure or resource destruction, so we must ensure that any
delayed work items cannot be rescheduled.

Replace cancel_delayed_work() with disable_delayed_work_sync()
to guarantee proper cancellation of the delayed work item and
ensure completion of any currently executing work before the
workqueue is deallocated.

A deadlock concern was considered: ocelot_stats_deinit() is called
in a process context and is not holding any locks that the delayed
work item might also need. Therefore, the use of the _sync() variant
is safe here.

This bug was identified through static analysis. To reproduce the
issue and validate the fix, I simulated ocelot-swit
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5555 | Nixdorf Wincor PORT IO Driver IOCTL wnport.sys sub_11100 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5555</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Nixdorf Wincor PORT IO Driver up to 1.0.0.1. This affects the function sub_11100 in the library wnport.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. Such manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.0.0.1 is able to mitigate this issue. Upgrading the affected component is recommended. The vendor was contacted beforehand and was able to provide a patch very early.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10750 | PowerBI Embed Reports &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10750</link><description>The PowerBI Embed Reports plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This is due to missing capability checks and authentication verification on the 'testUser' endpoint accessible via the mo_epbr_admin_observer() function hooked on 'init'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive Azure AD user information including personal identifiable information (PII) such as displayName, mail, phones, department, or detailed OAuth error data including Azure AD Application/Client IDs, error codes, trace IDs, and correlation IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11256 | Kognetiks Chatbot &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Uploads and Conversation Erasing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11256</link><description>The Kognetiks Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload limited safe files and erase conversations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10006 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10006</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rev_slider_vc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when RevSlider is also installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10187 | GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.17.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10187</link><description>The GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'field' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.17.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11270 | Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp;amp; Patterns &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11270</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'titleTag' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11372 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Database Table Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11372</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to modification of data in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.9.2. This is due to missing capability checks on the Admin Tools REST endpoints which are registered with permission_callback set to __return_true. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform destructive database operations including dropping indexes on any table (including WordPress core tables like wp_options), creating duplicate configuration entries, and degrading site performance via the /wp-json/lp/v1/admin/tools/create-indexs endpoint granted they can provide table names.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11391 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11391</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the image cropper functionality in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. While the vulnerable code is in the free version, this only affected users with the paid version of the software installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11510 | FileBird &amp;lt;= 6.4.9 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11510</link><description>The FileBird – WordPress Media Library Folders &amp; File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /filebird/v1/fb-wipe-clear-all-data function in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to reset all of the plugin's configuration data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11517 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.26.5 - Unauthenticated Ticket Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11517</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.26.5. This is due to the /wp-json/tribe/tickets/v1/commerce/free/order endpoint not verifying that a ticket type should be free allowing the user to bypass the payment. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain access to paid tickets, without paying for them, causing a loss of revenue for the target.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11519 | Image optimization service by Optimole &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Media Offload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11519</link><description>The Optimole – Optimize Images | Convert WebP &amp; AVIF | CDN &amp; Lazy Load | Image Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 via the /wp-json/optml/v1/move_image REST API endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to offload media that doesn't belong to them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11691 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11691</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the PPOM_Meta::get_fields_by_id() function in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This is only exploitable when the Enable Legacy Price Calculations setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11703 | WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) &amp;lt;= 9.0.48 - Unauthenticated Cache Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11703</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cache Poisoning in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.48. This is due to the plugin not serving cached data from server-side responses and instead relying on user-input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to poison the cache location for location search results.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11741 | WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Private Product Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11741</link><description>The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5 via the 'woosq_quickview' AJAX endpoint due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft products that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9562 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via qs_date Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9562</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's qs_date shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11738 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.29 - Unauthenticated Limited File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11738</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited file reading in all versions up to, and including, 3.29 via the mla-stream-image.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary ai/eps/pdf/ps files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11742 | WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11742</link><description>The WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wishlist_quickview' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view other user's wishlist data and information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11857 | XX2WP Integration Tools &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11857</link><description>The XX2WP Integration Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mxp_fb2wp_display_embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of the 'post_id' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11937 | Stored XSS through a system message in SecurePoll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62666 | DoS vector through the cirrusbuilddoc query API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62666</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension allows HTTP DoS.This issue affects Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension: from master before 1.43.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62667 | Stored XSS through article extracts in GrowthExperiments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62668 | Insufficient permission checks in action=growthsetmentor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62668</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62669 | UserInfoCard: activeLocalBlocksAllWikis does not do permissions checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62669</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11361 | Essential Blocks &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11361</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 via the eb_save_ai_generated_image function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62670 | Stored XSS through a system message in FlexDiagrams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62671 | Stored XSS through wikitext in Cargo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62671</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Cargo Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Cargo Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62662 | Stored XSS through system messages in AdvancedSearch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62663 | Stored XSS through a system message in UploadWizard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62664 | Stored XSS through a system message in ImageRating</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62665 | Stored XSS through system messages in Skin:BlueSky</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20206 | Appointments &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20206</link><description>The Appointments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `wpmudev_appointments` cookie. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20207 | Flickr Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20207</link><description>The Flickr Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `pager ` parameter. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20208 | RegistrationMagic - Custom Registration Forms &amp;lt;= 3.7.9.2 - PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20208</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to 3.7.9.3 (exclusive) via deserialization of untrusted input from the is_expired_by_date() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to fetch a remote file and install it on the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36853 | 10WebMapBuilder &amp;lt;= 1.0.63 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36853</link><description>The 10WebMapBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change in versions up to, and including, 1.0.63 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and a lack of capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36854 | Async JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.19.07.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36854</link><description>The Async JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including,  2.19.07.14. This is due to missing authorization checks on the aj_steps AJAX aciton along with a lack on sanitization on the settings saved via the function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber level permissions and above to inject malicious web scripts into a page that execute whenever a user accesses that page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11378 | ShortPixel Image Optimizer &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Settings Import/Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11378</link><description>The ShortPixel Image Optimizer – Optimize Images, Convert WebP &amp; AVIF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'shortpixel_ajaxRequest' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to export and import site options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>