<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10558 | Form Maker by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.15.30 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10558</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.15.30 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13124 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.8.33 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13124</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1062 | Slider, Gallery, Carousel by MetaSlider &amp;lt; 3.95.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1062</link><description>The Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider  WordPress plugin before 3.95.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1203 | Slider, Gallery, Carousel by MetaSlider &amp;lt; 3.95.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1203</link><description>The Slider, Gallery, and Carousel by MetaSlider  WordPress plugin before 3.95.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2687 | PHPGurukul eLearning System Image index.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2687</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul eLearning System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/index.php of the component Image Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 06:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2686 | mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 Backend admin doFilter access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2686</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in mingyuefusu 明月复苏 tushuguanlixitong 图书管理系统 up to d4836f6b49cd0ac79a4021b15ce99ff7229d4694 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function doFilter of the file /admin/ of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument Request leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 05:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2684 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System search-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2684</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 05:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2683 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2683</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 04:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2682 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2682</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit-subadmin.php?said=3. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 04:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2681 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-locker.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit-locker.php?ltid=6. The manipulation of the argument lockersize leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2680 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System edit-assign-locker.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2680</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit-assign-locker.php?ltid=1. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2679 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System contact-us.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2679</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /contact-us.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 03:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2678 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System changeimage1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /changeimage1.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 02:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2677 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System changeidproof.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2677</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /changeidproof.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 02:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2676 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System add-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2676</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2675 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System add-lockertype.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2675</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /add-lockertype.php. The manipulation of the argument lockerprice leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2674 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2674</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:06:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2673 | code-projects Payroll Management System home_employee.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2673</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /home_employee.php. The manipulation of the argument division leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 23:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2672 | code-projects Payroll Management System add_deductions.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2672</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add_deductions.php. The manipulation of the argument bir leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 23:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25109 | Nintendo Animal Crossing Letter Trigram ac-exploit-gc memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25109</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Nintendo Animal Crossing, Doubutsu no Mori+ and Doubutsu no Mori e+ 1.00/1.01 on GameCube and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Letter Trigram Handler. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 22:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2671 | Yue Lao Blind Box 月老盲盒 Upload.php base64image unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2671</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yue Lao Blind Box 月老盲盒 up to 4.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function base64image of the file /app/controller/Upload.php. The manipulation of the argument data leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 22:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2665 | PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2665</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 21:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2664 | CodeZips Hospital Management System suadpeted.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2664</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeZips Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /suadpeted.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 21:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2663 | PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System search-locker-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2663</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /search-locker-details.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinput leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 20:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2662 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator studentdashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file student/studentdashboard.php. The manipulation of the argument course leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 20:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2661 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /staff/index.php. The manipulation of the argument e leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 19:37:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2660 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2660</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument e leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 19:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2659 | Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2659</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Project Worlds Online Time Table Generator 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /student/index.php. The manipulation of the argument e leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 18:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2658 | PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System search-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2658</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search-request.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 18:24:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2657 | projectworlds Apartment Visitors Management System front.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2657</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in projectworlds Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /front.php. The manipulation of the argument rid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 17:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2656 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2656</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 17:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2655 | SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System Users.php save_users sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function save_users of the file /classes/Users.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29795 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Update Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29795</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29806 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29806</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2654 | SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System manage_service.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2654</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester AC Repair and Services System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/services/manage_service.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2653 | FoxCMS improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FoxCMS 1.25 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0927 | HFS+ filesystem heap overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0927</link><description>Attila Szász discovered that the HFS+ file system implementation in the Linux Kernel contained a heap overflow vulnerability. An attacker could use a specially crafted file system image that, when mounted, could cause a denial of service (system crash) or possibly execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2652 | SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2652</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Employee and Visitor Gate Pass Logging System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. Multiple sub-directories are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2651 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop admin exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2651</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /oews/admin/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. Multiple sub-directories are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:35:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27553 | Apache Commons VFS: Possible path traversal issue when using NameScope.DESCENDENT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27553</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Apache Commons VFS before 2.10.0.

The FileObject API in Commons VFS has a 'resolveFile' method that
takes a 'scope' parameter. Specifying 'NameScope.DESCENDENT' promises that "an exception is thrown if the resolved file is not a descendent of
the base file". However, when the path contains encoded ".."
characters (for example, "%2E%2E/bar.txt"), it might return file objects that are not
a descendent of the base file, without throwing an exception.
This issue affects Apache Commons VFS: before 2.10.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2691 | Versions of the package nossrf before 1.0.4 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide a hostname th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2691</link><description>Versions of the package nossrf before 1.0.4 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide a hostname that resolves to a local or reserved IP address space and bypass the SSRF protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30474 | Apache Commons VFS: Failing to find an FTP file can reveal the URI&amp;#x27;s password in an error message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30474</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Apache Commons VFS.

The FtpFileObject class can throw an exception when a file is not found, revealing the original URI in its message, which may include a password. The fix is to mask the password in the exception message
This issue affects Apache Commons VFS: before 2.10.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2650 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System download-medical-cards.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2650</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /download-medical-cards.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:08:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2649 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System check-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2649</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /check-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 12:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2648 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System view-enquiry-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2648</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/view-enquiry-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 11:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2647 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2647</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 11:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2646 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2646</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 09:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2645 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System product.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2645</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /product.php. The manipulation of the argument artname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2644 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System add-art-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2644</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/add-art-product.php. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 08:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2643 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-art-type-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2643</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-art-type-detail.php?editid=1. The manipulation of the argument arttype leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 07:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2642 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-art-product-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2642</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-art-product-detail.php?editid=2. The manipulation of the argument editide/sprice/description leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 07:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0718 | Nested Pages &amp;lt; 3.2.13 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0718</link><description>The Nested Pages WordPress plugin before 3.2.13 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributors to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1446 | Pods &amp;lt; 3.2.8.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1446</link><description>The Pods  WordPress plugin before 3.2.8.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 06:14:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2641 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System edit-artist-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2641</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-artist-detail.php?editid=1. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 04:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2640 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doctor/appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2639 | JIZHICMS Article release.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2639</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/release.html of the component Article Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 03:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2638 | JIZHICMS Article release.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2638</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/release.html of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument ishot with the input 1 leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 02:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2637 | JIZHICMS Account Profile Page userinfo.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2637</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in JIZHICMS up to 1.7.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/userinfo.html of the component Account Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument jifen leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2628 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System art-enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2628</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /art-enquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2627 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2627</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2626 | SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System edit_case.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2626</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Kortex Lite Advocate Office Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file edit_case.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2625 | westboy CicadasCMS page sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2625</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /system/cms/content/page. The manipulation of the argument orderField/orderDirection leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2624 | westboy CicadasCMS save sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2624</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/content/save. The manipulation of the argument content/fujian/laiyuan leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 19:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2623 | westboy CicadasCMS save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2623</link><description>A vulnerability was found in westboy CicadasCMS 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/cms/content/save. The manipulation of the argument title/content/laiyuan leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 17:36:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2622 | aizuda snail-job Workflow-Task Management Module check-node-expression getRuntime deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in aizuda snail-job 1.4.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function getRuntime of the file /snail-job/workflow/check-node-expression of the component Workflow-Task Management Module. The manipulation of the argument nodeExpression leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 17:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2621 | D-Link DAP-1620 storage check_dws_cookie stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2621</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function check_dws_cookie of the file /storage. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 16:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2620 | D-Link DAP-1620 Authentication storage mod_graph_auth_uri_handler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2620</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function mod_graph_auth_uri_handler of the file /storage of the component Authentication Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2619 | D-Link DAP-1620 Cookie storage check_dws_cookie stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2619</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03. This affects the function check_dws_cookie of the file /storage of the component Cookie Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2618 | D-Link DAP-1620 Path api set_ws_action heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2618</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DAP-1620 1.03. Affected by this issue is the function set_ws_action of the file /dws/api/ of the component Path Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2186 | Recover WooCommerce Cart Abandonment, Newsletter, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation By FunnelKit &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;automationId&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2186</link><description>The Recover WooCommerce Cart Abandonment, Newsletter, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation By FunnelKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘automationId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2617 | yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 Department Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2617</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 1.0.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Department Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26796 | Apache Oozie: XSS in Oozie Web Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26796</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Oozie.

This issue affects Apache Oozie: all versions.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1970 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery via validate_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1970</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via the validate_file() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1971 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via form_data Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1971</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'form_data' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1972 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Deletion via admin_log_page Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1972</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the admin_log_page() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary log files on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1973 | Export and Import Users and Customers &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Directory Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Limited Arbitrary File Read via download_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1973</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 via the download_file() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary log files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2331 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 3.22.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2331</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.22.1 via a misconfigured capability check in the 'permissionsCheck' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including reports detailing donors and donation amounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2577 | Bitspecter Suite &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2577</link><description>The Bitspecter Suite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2616 | yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 Role Management Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2616</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in yangyouwang 杨有旺 crud 简约后台管理系统 1.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Role Management Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13666 | Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp;amp; Conversational Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.2.12 - IP-Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13666</link><description>The Fluent Forms – Customizable Contact Forms, Survey, Quiz, &amp; Conversational Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.12 due to insufficient IP address validation and use of user-supplied HTTP headers as a primary method for IP retrieval. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers spoof their IP address and submit forms that may have IP-based restrictions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13768 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Font Assignment Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13768</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cits_assign_fonts_tab() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete font assignments via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13856 | Make Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via make_builder_ajax_subscribe Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13856</link><description>The Your Friendly Drag and Drop Page Builder — Make Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.10 via the make_builder_ajax_subscribe() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0807 | CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts &amp;lt;= 4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0807</link><description>The CITS Support svg, webp Media and TTF,OTF File Upload, Use Custom Fonts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cits_settings_tab() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1311 | WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace – REST API &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1311</link><description>The WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace – REST API plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in the update_delivery_status() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2303 | Block Logic &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2303</link><description>The Block Logic – Full Gutenberg Block Display Control plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 via the block_logic_check_logic function. This is due to the unsafe evaluation of user-controlled input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2477 | CryoKey &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;ckemail&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2477</link><description>The CryoKey plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ckemail’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2478 | Code Clone &amp;lt;= 0.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via snippetId Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2478</link><description>The Code Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘snippetId’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2479 | Easy Custom Admin Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via msg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2479</link><description>The Easy Custom Admin Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘msg’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2482 | Gotcha | Gesture-based Captcha &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via menu Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2482</link><description>The Gotcha | Gesture-based Captcha plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'menu' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2484 | Multi Video Box &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via video_id and group_id Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2484</link><description>The Multi Video Box plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'video_id' and 'group_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13739 | Newsletters &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via To Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13739</link><description>The Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the "to" parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an admin user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0723 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0723</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to blind and time-based SQL Injections via the rid and search parameters in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0724 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0724</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.5 via deserialization of untrusted input in the get_user_meta_fields_html function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1408 | ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities &amp;lt;= 5.9.4.4 - Missing Authorinzation to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Join Group Requests Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1408</link><description>The ProfileGrid – User Profiles, Groups and Communities plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the pm_decline_join_group_request and pm_approve_join_group_request functions in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to approve or decline join group requests which is normally should be available to administrators only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13737 | Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp;amp; Listing &amp;lt;= 1.4.57 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion and Listing Template Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13737</link><description>The Motors – Car Dealer, Classifieds &amp; Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability checks on the motors_create_template and motors_delete_template functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.57. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts or create listing templates. This issue requires Elementor plugin to be installed, which is a required plugin for Motors Starter Theme.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 03:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30472 | Corosync through 3.1.9, if encryption is disabled or the attacker knows the encryption key, has a stack-based buffer overflow in orf_token_e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30472</link><description>Corosync through 3.1.9, if encryption is disabled or the attacker knows the encryption key, has a stack-based buffer overflow in orf_token_endian_convert in exec/totemsrp.c via a large UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>