<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-46082 | Scriptcase v.9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in nm_cor.php via the form and field parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46082</link><description>Scriptcase v.9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in nm_cor.php via the form and field parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47527 | LibreNMS has a Stored XSS (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in librenms/includes/html/pages/device-dependencies.inc.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47527</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the "Device Dependencies" feature allows authenticated users to inject arbitrary JavaScript through the device name ("hostname" parameter). This vulnerability can lead to the execution of malicious code in the context of other users' sessions, potentially compromising their accounts and allowing unauthorized actions. This vulnerability is fixed in 24.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47528 | LibreNMS Contains a Stored XSS via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47528</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) can be achieved by uploading a new Background for a Custom Map. Users with "admin" role can set background for a custom map, this allow the upload of SVG file that can contain XSS payload which will trigger on load. This led to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). The vulnerability is fixed in 24.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47609 | Remotely exploitable DoS in Tonic `&amp;lt;=v0.12.2`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47609</link><description>Tonic is a native gRPC client &amp; server implementation with async/await support. When using tonic::transport::Server there is a remote DoS attack that can cause the server to exit cleanly on accepting a TCP/TLS stream. This can be triggered by causing the accept call to error out with errors that were not covered correctly causing the accept loop to exit. Upgrading to tonic 0.12.3 and above contains the fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9407 | Buildah: podman: improper input validation in bind-propagation option of dockerfile run --mount instruction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9407</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the bind-propagation option of the Dockerfile RUN --mount instruction. The system does not properly validate the input passed to this option, allowing users to pass arbitrary parameters to the mount instruction. This issue can be exploited to mount sensitive directories from the host into a container during the build process and, in some cases, modify the contents of those mounted files. Even if SELinux is used, this vulnerability can bypass its protection by allowing the source directory to be relabeled to give the container access to host files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9411 | OFCMS add.json add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9411</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in OFCMS 1.1.2. This affects the function add of the file /admin/system/dict/add.json?sqlid=system.dict.save. The manipulation of the argument dict_value leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45999 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in Cloudlog 2.6.15, specifically within the get_station_info()function located in the file /app...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45999</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in Cloudlog 2.6.15, specifically within the get_station_info()function located in the file /application/models/Oqrs_model.php. The vulnerability is exploitable via the station_id parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46079 | Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in proj_new.php via the Descricao parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46079</link><description>Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in proj_new.php via the Descricao parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46081 | Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can craft malicious payloads in the To-Do...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46081</link><description>Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can craft malicious payloads in the To-Do List. The assigned user will trigger a stored XSS, which is particularly dangerous because tasks are assigned to various users on the platform.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46083 | Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can craft malicious payloads using the me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46083</link><description>Scriptcase v9.10.023 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can craft malicious payloads using the messages feature, which allows the injection of malicious code into any user's account on the platform. It is important to note that regular users can trigger actions for administrator users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 19:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42514 | A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.1.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42514</link><description>A vulnerability in the legacy chat component of Mitel MiContact Center Business through 10.1.0.4 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to conduct an unauthorized access attack due to inadequate access control checks. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to access sensitive information and send unauthorized messages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9341 | Podman: buildah: cri-o: fips crypto-policy directory mounting issue in containers/common go library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9341</link><description>A flaw was found in Go. When FIPS mode is enabled on a system, container runtimes may incorrectly handle certain file paths due to improper validation in the containers/common Go library. This flaw allows an attacker to exploit symbolic links and trick the system into mounting sensitive host directories inside a container. This issue also allows attackers to access critical host files, bypassing the intended isolation between containers and the host system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9355 | Golang-fips: golang fips zeroed buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Golang FIPS OpenSSL. This flaw allows a malicious user to randomly cause an uninitialized buffer length variable with a zeroed buffer to be returned in FIPS mode. It may also be possible to force a false positive match between non-equal hashes when comparing a trusted computed hmac sum to an untrusted input sum if an attacker can send a zeroed buffer in place of a pre-computed sum.  It is also possible to force a derived key to be all zeros instead of an unpredictable value.  This may have follow-on implications for the Go TLS stack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31835 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in flatpress CMS Flatpress v1.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31835</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in flatpress CMS Flatpress v1.3 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the file name parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47608 | Logicytics vulnerable to shell injections</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47608</link><description>Logicytics is designed to harvest and collect data for forensic analysis. Logicytics has a basic vuln affecting compromised devices from shell injections. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47071 | OSS Endpoint Manager allows unauthorized access to read system files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47071</link><description>OSS Endpoint Manager is an endpoint manager module for FreePBX. OSS Endpoint Manager module activation can allow authenticated web users unauthorized access to read system files with the permissions of the webserver process. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25660 | The WebDAV service in Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3 allows a low-privileged remote attacker to conduct unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25660</link><description>The WebDAV service in Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3 allows a low-privileged remote attacker to conduct unauthorized file operations, because of execution with unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47534 | Incorrect delegation lookups can make go-tuf download the wrong artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47534</link><description>go-tuf is a Go implementation of The Update Framework (TUF). The go-tuf client inconsistently traces the delegations. For example, if targets delegate to "A", and to "B", and "B" delegates to "C", then the client should trace the delegations in the order "A" then "B" then "C" but it may incorrectly trace the delegations "B"-&gt;"C"-&gt;"A". This vulnerability is fixed in 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47604 | XSS vulnerability in NuGetGallery HTML attributes handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47604</link><description>NuGet Gallery is a package repository that powers nuget.org. The NuGetGallery has a security vulnerability in its handling of HTML element attributes, which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or Javascript code in a victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25659 | In Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3, an insecure default configuration of the internal SFTP server on Linux serve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25659</link><description>In Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3, an insecure default configuration of the internal SFTP server on Linux servers allows remote attacker to access files and directories outside the SFTP user home directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9391 | A user who enables full-screen mode on a specially crafted web page could potentially be prevented from exiting full screen mode.  This may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9391</link><description>A user who enables full-screen mode on a specially crafted web page could potentially be prevented from exiting full screen mode.  This may allow spoofing of other sites as the address bar is no longer visible.
*This bug only affects Firefox Focus for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9392 | A compromised content process could have allowed for the arbitrary loading of cross-origin pages. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9392</link><description>A compromised content process could have allowed for the arbitrary loading of cross-origin pages. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9393 | An attacker could, via a specially crafted multipart response, execute arbitrary JavaScript under the `resource://pdf.js` origin.  This coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9393</link><description>An attacker could, via a specially crafted multipart response, execute arbitrary JavaScript under the `resource://pdf.js` origin.  This could allow them to access cross-origin PDF content. This access is limited to "same site" documents by the Site Isolation feature on desktop clients, but full cross-origin access is possible on Android versions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9394 | An attacker could, via a specially crafted multipart response, execute arbitrary JavaScript under the `resource://devtools` origin.  This co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9394</link><description>An attacker could, via a specially crafted multipart response, execute arbitrary JavaScript under the `resource://devtools` origin.  This could allow them to access cross-origin JSON content. This access is limited to "same site" documents by the Site Isolation feature on desktop clients, but full cross-origin access is possible on Android versions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9395 | A specially crafted filename containing a large number of spaces could obscure the file's extension when displayed in the download dialog.
*...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9395</link><description>A specially crafted filename containing a large number of spaces could obscure the file's extension when displayed in the download dialog.
*This bug only affects Firefox for Android. Other versions of Firefox are unaffected.* This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9396 | It is currently unknown if this issue is exploitable but a condition may arise where the structured clone of certain objects could lead to m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9396</link><description>It is currently unknown if this issue is exploitable but a condition may arise where the structured clone of certain objects could lead to memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9397 | A missing delay in directory upload UI could have made it possible for an attacker to trick a user into granting permission via clickjacking...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9397</link><description>A missing delay in directory upload UI could have made it possible for an attacker to trick a user into granting permission via clickjacking. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9398 | By checking the result of calls to `window.open` with specifically set protocol handlers, an attacker could determine if the application whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9398</link><description>By checking the result of calls to `window.open` with specifically set protocol handlers, an attacker could determine if the application which implements that protocol handler is installed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9399 | A website configured to initiate a specially crafted WebTransport session could crash the Firefox process leading to a denial of service con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9399</link><description>A website configured to initiate a specially crafted WebTransport session could crash the Firefox process leading to a denial of service condition. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9400 | A potential memory corruption vulnerability could be triggered if an attacker had the ability to trigger an OOM at a specific moment during ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9400</link><description>A potential memory corruption vulnerability could be triggered if an attacker had the ability to trigger an OOM at a specific moment during JIT compilation. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9401 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130, Firefox ESR 115.15, Firefox ESR 128.2, and Thunderbird 128.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9401</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130, Firefox ESR 115.15, Firefox ESR 128.2, and Thunderbird 128.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9402 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130, Firefox ESR 128.2, and Thunderbird 128.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9402</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130, Firefox ESR 128.2, and Thunderbird 128.2. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3, Thunderbird &lt; 128.3, and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9403 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort so...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9403</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 130. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131 and Thunderbird &lt; 131.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41673 | Decidim has a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the version control page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41673</link><description>Decidim is a participatory democracy framework. The version control feature used in resources is subject to potential XSS attack through a malformed URL. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.27.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25661 | In Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3, cleartext storage of sensitive information in memory of the desktop applicat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25661</link><description>In Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) 19.10.3, cleartext storage of sensitive information in memory of the desktop application TNMS Client allows guest OS administrators to obtain various users' passwords by reading memory dumps of the desktop application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45408 | eLabFTW contains a direct and indirect information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45408</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. An incorrect permission check has been found that could allow an authenticated user to access several kinds of otherwise restricted information. If anonymous access is allowed (something disabled by default), this extends to anyone. Users are advised to upgrade to at least version 5.1.0.  System administrators can disable anonymous access in the System configuration panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25632 | Unauthorised granting of administrator privileges over arbitrary teams under certain circumstances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25632</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. In the context of eLabFTW, an administrator is a user account with certain privileges to manage users and content in their assigned team/teams. A user may be an administrator in one team and a regular user in another. The vulnerability allows a regular user to become administrator of a team where they are a member, under a reasonable configuration. Additionally, in eLabFTW versions subsequent to v5.0.0, the vulnerability may allow an initially unauthenticated user to gain administrative privileges over an arbitrary team. The vulnerability does not affect system administrator status. Users should upgrade to version 5.1.0. System administrators are advised to turn off local user registration, saml_team_create and not allow administrators to import users into teams, unless strictly required.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25658 | Cleartext storage of passwords in Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) Server 19.10.3 allows attackers (with access to the da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25658</link><description>Cleartext storage of passwords in Infinera TNMS (Transcend Network Management System) Server 19.10.3 allows attackers (with access to the database or exported configuration files) to obtain SNMP users' usernames and passwords in cleartext.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-37577 | Bluetooth LE and BR/EDR Secure Connections pairing and Secure Simple Pairing using the Passkey entry protocol in Bluetooth Core Specificatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-37577</link><description>Bluetooth LE and BR/EDR Secure Connections pairing and Secure Simple Pairing using the Passkey entry protocol in Bluetooth Core Specifications 2.1 through 5.3 may permit an unauthenticated man-in-the-middle attacker to identify the Passkey used during pairing by reflection of a crafted public key with the same X coordinate as the offered public key and by reflection of the authentication evidence of the initiating device, potentially permitting this attacker to complete authenticated pairing with the responding device using the correct Passkey for the pairing session. This is a related issue to CVE-2020-26558.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44610 | PCAN-Ethernet Gateway FD before 1.3.0 and PCAN-Ethernet Gateway before 2.11.0 are vulnerable to Command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44610</link><description>PCAN-Ethernet Gateway FD before 1.3.0 and PCAN-Ethernet Gateway before 2.11.0 are vulnerable to Command injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45967 | Pagekit 1.0.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in index.php/admin/site/widget.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45967</link><description>Pagekit 1.0.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in index.php/admin/site/widget.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41276 | A vulnerability in Kaiten version 57.131.12 and earlier allows attackers to bypass the PIN code authentication mechanism. The application re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41276</link><description>A vulnerability in Kaiten version 57.131.12 and earlier allows attackers to bypass the PIN code authentication mechanism. The application requires users to input a 6-digit PIN code sent to their email for authorization after entering their login credentials. However, the request limiting mechanism can be easily bypassed, enabling attackers to perform a brute force attack to guess the correct PIN and gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46258 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_load_png_mem() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46258</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_load_png_mem() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46259 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_unfilter() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46259</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_unfilter() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46261 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_make32() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46261</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_make32() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46263 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the cp_dynamic() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46263</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the cp_dynamic() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46264 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_find() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46264</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_find() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46267 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_block() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46267</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_block() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46274 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_stored() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46274</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_stored() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46276 | cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_chunk() function at cute_png.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46276</link><description>cute_png v1.05 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow via the cp_chunk() function at cute_png.h.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44744 | An issue in Malwarebytes Premium Security v5.0.0.883 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via placing crafted binaries into unspecifie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44744</link><description>An issue in Malwarebytes Premium Security v5.0.0.883 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via placing crafted binaries into unspecified directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7273 | Cross Site Request Forgery in Kiteworks OwnCloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7273</link><description>Cross site request forgery in Kiteworks OwnCloud allows an unauthenticated attacker to forge requests.
If a request has no Authorization header, it is created with an empty string as value by a rewrite rule. The CSRF check is done by comparing the header value to null, meaning that the existing CSRF check is bypassed in this case. An attacker can, for example, create a new administrator account if the request is executed in the browser of an authenticated victim.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30132 | Missing default HTTP security headers affect HCL Nomad server on Domino</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30132</link><description>HCL Nomad server on Domino did not configure certain HTTP Security headers by default which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive information via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9405 | An incorrect limitation of a path to a restricted directory (path traversal) has been detected in Pluck CMS, affecting version 4.7.18. An un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9405</link><description>An incorrect limitation of a path to a restricted directory (path traversal) has been detected in Pluck CMS, affecting version 4.7.18. An unauthenticated attacker could extract sensitive information from the server via the absolute path of a file located in the same directory or subdirectory as the module, but not from recursive directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3441 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3441</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 8.0 before 16.4. The product did not sufficiently warn about security implications of granting merge rights to protected branches.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:53:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9060 | AVIF &amp;amp; SVG Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9060</link><description>The AVIF &amp; SVG Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in version 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9118 | QS Dark Mode Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9118</link><description>The QS Dark Mode Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:43:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8288 | Guten Post Layout – An Advanced Post Grid Collection for WordPress Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8288</link><description>The Guten Post Layout – An Advanced Post Grid Collection for WordPress Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ attribute within the 'wp:guten-post-layout/post-grid' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8324 | XO Slider &amp;lt;= 3.8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8324</link><description>The XO Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘get_slider’ function in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8430 | Spice Starter Sites &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Demo Content Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8430</link><description>The Spice Starter Sites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the spice_starter_sites_importer_creater function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import demo content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8786 | Auto Featured Image from Title &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8786</link><description>The Auto Featured Image from Title plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8793 | Store Exporter for WooCommerce – Export Products, Export Orders, Export Subscriptions, and More &amp;lt;= 2.7.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8793</link><description>The Store Exporter for WooCommerce – Export Products, Export Orders, Export Subscriptions, and More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8799 | Custom Banners &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8799</link><description>The Custom Banners plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9018 | WP Easy Gallery &amp;lt;= 4.8.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via key Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9018</link><description>The WP Easy Gallery – WordPress Gallery Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘key’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9209 | WP Search Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.4.10 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9209</link><description>The WP Search Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9220 | LH Copy Media File &amp;lt;= 1.08 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9220</link><description>The LH Copy Media File plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.08. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9224 | Hello World &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9224</link><description>The Hello World plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Reading in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 via the hello_world_lyric() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9228 | Loggedin – Limit Active Logins &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9228</link><description>The Loggedin – Limit Active Logins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This is only exploitable when the leave a review notice is present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9241 | PDF Image Generator &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9241</link><description>The PDF Image Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9265 | Echo RSS Feed Post Generator &amp;lt;= 5.4.6 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9265</link><description>The Echo RSS Feed Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.6. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting the roles that can set during registration through the echo_check_post_header_sent() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9289 | WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Affiliate Program &amp;lt;= 8.4.1 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9289</link><description>The WordPress &amp; WooCommerce Affiliate Program plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.1. This is due to the rtwwwap_login_request_callback() function not properly validating a user's identity prior to authenticating them to the site. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including administrators, granted they have access to the administrator's email.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7432 | Unseen Blog &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7432</link><description>The Unseen Blog theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7433 | Empowerment &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7433</link><description>The Empowerment theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7434 | UltraPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7434</link><description>The UltraPress theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7869 | 123.chat - Video Chat &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7869</link><description>The 123.chat - Video Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8548 | KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Multiple Administrator Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8548</link><description>The KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform multiple administrative actions, such as replying to arbitrary tickets, updating the status of any post, deleting any post, adding notes to tickets, flagging or unflagging tickets, and adding or removing ticket participants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8632 | KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Ticket Reply Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8632</link><description>The KB Support – WordPress Help Desk and Knowledge Base plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'kbs_ajax_load_front_end_replies' and 'kbs_ajax_mark_reply_as_read' functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read replies of any ticket, and mark any reply as read.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8675 | Soumettre.fr &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8675</link><description>The Soumettre.fr plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the soumettre_disconnect_gateway function in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to disconnect the gateway and delete the API key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8718 | Gravity Forms Toolbar &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8718</link><description>The Gravity Forms Toolbar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8720 | RumbleTalk Live Group Chat – HTML5 &amp;lt;= 6.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8720</link><description>The RumbleTalk Live Group Chat – HTML5 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rumbletalk-admin-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8727 | DK PDF &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8727</link><description>The DK PDF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8728 | Easy Load More &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8728</link><description>The Easy Load More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8989 | Stars Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via stars_testimonials Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8989</link><description>The Free Responsive Testimonials, Social Proof Reviews, and Customer Reviews – Stars Testimonials plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's stars_testimonials shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8990 | Geo Mashup &amp;lt;= 1.13.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via geo_mashup_visible_posts_list Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8990</link><description>The Geo Mashup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's geo_mashup_visible_posts_list shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9106 | Wechat Social login &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9106</link><description>The Wechat Social login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the social login. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id. This is only exploitable if the app secret is not set, so it has a default empty value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9108 | Wechat Social login &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9108</link><description>The Wechat Social login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'convert_remoteimage_to_local' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9119 | SVG Complete &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9119</link><description>The SVG Complete plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9267 | Easy WordPress Subscribe – Optin Hound &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via add_query_arg Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9267</link><description>The Easy WordPress Subscribe – Optin Hound plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9269 | Relogo &amp;lt;= 0.4.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9269</link><description>The Relogo plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9272 | R Animated Icon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9272</link><description>The R Animated Icon Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9274 | Elastik Page Builder &amp;lt;= 0.27.4 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9274</link><description>The Elastik Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.27.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9304 | LocateAndFilter &amp;lt;= 1.6.14 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9304</link><description>The LocateAndFilter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:44:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9145 | Local command injection in Wiz Code Visual Studio extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9145</link><description>Wiz Code Visual Studio extension in versions 1.0.0 up to 1.5.3 and Wiz (legacy) Visual Studio extension in versions 0.13.0 up to 0.17.8 are vulnerable to local command injection if the user opens a maliciously crafted Docker image file located in a path that has been marked as a "trusted folder" within Visual Studio Code, and initiates a manual scan of the file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 07:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8107 | Slider Revolution &amp;lt;= 6.7.18 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8107</link><description>The Slider Revolution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. By default, this can only be exploited by administrators, but the ability to use and configure Slider Revolution can be extended to authors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 06:49:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8421 | Golang.org/x/net/http2: multiple http/2 enabled web servers (rapid reset attack)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8421</link><description>This CVE has been rejected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21489 | Versions of the package uplot before 1.6.31 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the uplot.assign function due to missing check if the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21489</link><description>Versions of the package uplot before 1.6.31 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the uplot.assign function due to missing check if the attribute resolves to the object prototype.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21531 | All versions of the package git-shallow-clone are vulnerable to Command injection due to missing sanitization or mitigation flags in the pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21531</link><description>All versions of the package git-shallow-clone are vulnerable to Command injection due to missing sanitization or mitigation flags in the process variable of the gitShallowClone function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0116 | NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read issue by releasing a shared memory regi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0116</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server contains a vulnerability where a user may cause an out-of-bounds read issue by releasing a shared memory region while it is in use. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47295 | Insecure initial password configuration issue in SEIKO EPSON Web Config allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to set an arbitrary passwor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47295</link><description>Insecure initial password configuration issue in SEIKO EPSON Web Config allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to set an arbitrary password and operate the device with an administrative privilege. As for the details of the affected versions, see the information provided by the vendor under [References].</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 03:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9360 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System updatebal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9360</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /updatebal.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 03:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8981 | Broken Link Checker &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8981</link><description>The Broken Link Checker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg in /app/admin-notices/features/class-view.php without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 03:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47396 | WordPress Move Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47396</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in moveaddons Move Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Move Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9359 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System addcompany.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9359</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcompany.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47560 | RevoWorks Cloud Client 3.0.91 and earlier contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, unintended ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47560</link><description>RevoWorks Cloud Client 3.0.91 and earlier contains an incorrect authorization vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, unintended processes may be executed in the sandbox environment. Even if malware is executed in the sandbox environment, it does not compromise the client's local environment. However, information in the sandbox environment may be disclosed to outside or behaviors of the sandbox environment may be violated by tampering registry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9358 | ThingsBoard HTTP RPC API resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9358</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ThingsBoard up to 3.7.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HTTP RPC API. The manipulation leads to resource consumption. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.7.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was informed on 2024-07-24 about this vulnerability and announced the release of 3.7.1 for the second half of September 2024.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 02:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9194 | SQL Injection in the Octopus Server REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9194</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Linux and Microsoft Windows Octopus Server on Windows, Linux allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Octopus Server: from 2024.1.0 before 2024.1.13038, from 2024.2.0 before 2024.2.9482, from 2024.3.0 before 2024.3.12766.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 22:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45073 | IBM WebSphere Application Server cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45073</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 22:23:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46503 | An issue in the _readFileSync function of Simple-Spellchecker v1.0.2 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via a directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46503</link><description>An issue in the _readFileSync function of Simple-Spellchecker v1.0.2 allows attackers to read arbitrary files via a directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 21:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28807 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Cleartext storage of sensitive information in the memory of the @CT desktop management...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28807</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Cleartext storage of sensitive information in the memory of the @CT desktop management application allows guest OS administrators to obtain various users' passwords by accessing memory dumps of the desktop application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7670 | Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7670</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWFX file, when parsed in w3dtk.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7671 | Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7671</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWFX file, when parsed in dwfcore.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7672 | Out-of-Bounds Write Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7672</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWF file, when parsed in dwfcore.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force an Out-of-Bounds Write. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, write sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7673 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7673</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWFX file, when parsed in w3dtk.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force a Heap-based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7674 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7674</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWF file, when parsed in dwfcore.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force a Heap-based Buffer Overflow. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7675 | Use After Free Vulnerability in Autodesk Desktop Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7675</link><description>A maliciously crafted DWF file, when parsed in w3dtk.dll through Autodesk Navisworks, can force a Use-After-Free. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28808 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Hidden functionality in the web interface allows a remote authenticated attacker to ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28808</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Hidden functionality in the web interface allows a remote authenticated attacker to access reserved information by accessing undocumented web applications.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28810 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Sensitive information inside diagnostic files (exported by the @CT application) allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28810</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Sensitive information inside diagnostic files (exported by the @CT application) allows an attacker to achieve loss of confidentiality by analyzing these files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28813 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Undocumented privileged functions in the @CT management application allow an attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28813</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Undocumented privileged functions in the @CT management application allow an attacker to activate remote SSH access to the appliance via an unexpected network interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:38:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28811 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. A web application allows a remote privileged attacker to execute applications containe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28811</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. A web application allows a remote privileged attacker to execute applications contained in a specific OS directory via HTTP invocations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28812 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. A hidden SSH service (on the local management network interface) with hardcoded creden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28812</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. A hidden SSH service (on the local management network interface) with hardcoded credentials allows attackers to access the appliance operating system (with highest privileges) via an SSH connection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28809 | An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Cleartext storage of sensitive password in firmware update packages allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28809</link><description>An issue was discovered in Infinera hiT 7300 5.60.50. Cleartext storage of sensitive password in firmware update packages allows attackers to access various appliance services via hardcoded credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46511 | LoadZilla LLC LoadLogic v1.4.3 was discovered to contain insecure permissions vulnerability which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46511</link><description>LoadZilla LLC LoadLogic v1.4.3 was discovered to contain insecure permissions vulnerability which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the LogicLoadEc2DeployLambda and CredsGenFunction function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46635 | An issue in the API endpoint /AccountMaster/GetCurrentUserInfo of INROAD before v202402060 allows attackers to access sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46635</link><description>An issue in the API endpoint /AccountMaster/GetCurrentUserInfo of INROAD before v202402060 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a crafted payload to the UserNameOrPhoneNumber parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35495 | An Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Telemetry component in TP-Link Kasa KP125M V1.0.0 and Tapo P125M 1.0.0 Build 220930 Rel.14394...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35495</link><description>An Information Disclosure vulnerability in the Telemetry component in TP-Link Kasa KP125M V1.0.0 and Tapo P125M 1.0.0 Build 220930 Rel.143947 allows attackers to observe device state via observing network traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42017 | An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden iCare 2.7.1 through 2.7.11. The application exposes a web interface locally. In the worst-case scenar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42017</link><description>An issue was discovered in Atos Eviden iCare 2.7.1 through 2.7.11. The application exposes a web interface locally. In the worst-case scenario, if the application is remotely accessible, it allows an attacker to execute arbitrary commands with system privilege on the endpoint hosting the application, without any authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47536 | starcitizentools/citizen-skin vulnerable to stored, self-XSS in the &amp;quot;real name&amp;quot; field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47536</link><description>Citizen is a MediaWiki skin that makes extensions part of the cohesive experience. A user with the editmyprivateinfo right or who can otherwise change their name can XSS themselves by setting their "real name" to an XSS payload. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.31.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46540 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the component /admin/store.php of Emlog Pro before v2.3.15 allows attackers to use remote fil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46540</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the component /admin/store.php of Emlog Pro before v2.3.15 allows attackers to use remote file downloads and self-extract fucntions to upload webshells to the target server, thereby obtaining system privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45993 | Giflib Project v5.2.2 is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow via gif2rgb.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45993</link><description>Giflib Project v5.2.2 is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow via gif2rgb.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46548 | TP-Link Tapo P125M and Kasa KP125M v1.0.3 was discovered to improperly validate certificates, allowing attackers to eavesdrop on communicati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46548</link><description>TP-Link Tapo P125M and Kasa KP125M v1.0.3 was discovered to improperly validate certificates, allowing attackers to eavesdrop on communications and access sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9158 | XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9158</link><description>A stored cross site scripting vulnerability exists in Nessus Network Monitor where an authenticated, privileged local attacker could inject arbitrary code into the NNM UI via the local CLI.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46549 | An issue in the TP-Link MQTT Broker and API gateway of TP-Link Kasa KP125M v1.0.3 allows attackers to establish connections by impersonating...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46549</link><description>An issue in the TP-Link MQTT Broker and API gateway of TP-Link Kasa KP125M v1.0.3 allows attackers to establish connections by impersonating devices owned by other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46475 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the homepage of Metronic Admin Dashboard Template v2.0 allows attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46475</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on the homepage of Metronic Admin Dashboard Template v2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46869 | Bluetooth: btintel_pcie: Allocate memory for driver private data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46869</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: btintel_pcie: Allocate memory for driver private data

Fix driver not allocating memory for struct btintel_data which is used
to store internal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47067 | Alist Contains a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47067</link><description>AList is a file list program that supports multiple storages. AList contains a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in helper.go. The endpoint /i/:link_name takes in a user-provided value and reflects it back in the response. The endpoint returns an application/xml response, opening it up to HTML tags via XHTML and thus leading to a XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.29.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47531 | Scout contains insufficient output escaping of attachment names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47531</link><description>Scout is a web-based visualizer for VCF-files. Due to the lack of sanitization in the filename, it is possible bypass intended file extension and make users download malicious files with any extension. With malicious content injected inside the file data and users unknowingly downloading it and opening may lead to the compromise of users' devices or data. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.89.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47532 | RestrictedPython information leakage via `AttributeError.obj` and the `string` module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47532</link><description>RestrictedPython is a restricted execution environment for Python to run untrusted code. A user can gain access to protected (and potentially sensible) information indirectly via AttributeError.obj and the string module. The problem will be fixed in version 7.3. As a workaround, If the application does not require access to the module string, it can remove it from RestrictedPython.Utilities.utility_builtins or otherwise do not make it available in the restricted execution environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46510 | ESAFENET CDG v5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the NavigationAjax interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46510</link><description>ESAFENET CDG v5 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter in the NavigationAjax interface</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47178 | basic-auth-connect&amp;#x27;s callback uses time unsafe string comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47178</link><description>basic-auth-connect is Connect's Basic Auth middleware in its own module. basic-auth-connect &lt; 1.1.0 uses a timing-unsafe equality comparison that can leak timing information. This issue has been fixed in basic-auth-connect 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47530 | Scout contains an Open Redirect on Login via `next`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47530</link><description>Scout is a web-based visualizer for VCF-files. Open redirect vulnerability allows performing phishing attacks on users by redirecting them to malicious page. /login API endpoint is vulnerable to open redirect attack via next parameter due to absence of sanitization logic. Additionally, due to lack of scheme validation, HTTPS Downgrade Attack can be performed on the users. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.89.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47064 | Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) contains a reflected XSS via request endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47064</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. If an attacker can trick a logged-in CVAT user into visiting a maliciously-constructed URL, they can initiate any API calls on that user's behalf. This gives the attacker temporary access to all data that the victim user has access to. Upgrade to CVAT 2.19.0 or a later version to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47172 | Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) access control is broken in several PATCH endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47172</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. An attacker with a CVAT account may retrieve certain information about any project, task, job or membership resource on the CVAT instance. The information exposed in this way is the same as the information returned on a GET request to the resource. In addition, the attacker can also alter the default source and target storage associated with any project or task. Upgrade to CVAT 2.19.1 or any later version to fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46313 | TP-Link WR941ND V6 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in /userRpm/popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46313</link><description>TP-Link WR941ND V6 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the ssid parameter in /userRpm/popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47063 | Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) contains a stored XSS via the quality report data endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47063</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. If a malicious CVAT user with permissions to either create a task, or edit an existing task can trick another logged-in user into visiting a maliciously-constructed URL, they can initiate any API calls on that user's behalf. This gives the attacker temporary access to all data that the victim user has access to. Upgrade to CVAT 2.19.0 or a later version to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:58:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45792 | MantisBT vulnerable to information disclosure with user profiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45792</link><description>Mantis Bug Tracker (MantisBT) is an open source issue tracker. Using a crafted POST request, an unprivileged, registered user is able to retrieve information about other users' personal system profiles. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.26.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46293 | Sourcecodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a lack of authorization checks for ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46293</link><description>Sourcecodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. There is a lack of authorization checks for admin operations. Specifically, an attacker can perform admin-level actions without possessing a valid session token. The application does not verify whether the user is logged in as an admin or even check for a session token at all.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46280 | PIX-LINK LV-WR22 RE3002-P1-01_V117.0 is vulnerable to Improper Access Control. The TELNET service is enabled with weak credentials for a roo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46280</link><description>PIX-LINK LV-WR22 RE3002-P1-01_V117.0 is vulnerable to Improper Access Control. The TELNET service is enabled with weak credentials for a root-level account, without the possibility of changing them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45920 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Solvait 24.4.2 allows remote attackers to inject malicious scripts into the application...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45920</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Solvait 24.4.2 allows remote attackers to inject malicious scripts into the application. This issue arises due to insufficient input validation and sanitization in "Intrest" feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6051 | Cross Application Scripting in Redlink SDK</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6051</link><description>Cross Application Scripting vulnerability in Vercom S.A. Redlink SDK in specific situations allows local code injection and to manipulate the view of a vulnerable application.This issue affects Redlink SDK versions through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47641 | WordPress Confetti Fall Animation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloperr Confetti Fall Animation allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Confetti Fall Animation: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45772 | Apache Lucene Replicator: Security Vulnerability in Lucene Replicator - Deserialization Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45772</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Apache Lucene Replicator.

This issue affects Apache Lucene's replicator module: from 4.4.0 before 9.12.0.
The deprecated org.apache.lucene.replicator.http package is affected.
The org.apache.lucene.replicator.nrt package is not affected.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.12.0, which fixes the issue.

Java serialization filters (such as -Djdk.serialFilter='!*' on the commandline) can mitigate the issue on vulnerable versions without impacting functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6394 | Local File Inclusion in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6394</link><description>A Local File Inclusion vulnerability exists in parisneo/lollms-webui versions below v9.8. The vulnerability is due to unverified path concatenation in the `serve_js` function in `app.py`, which allows attackers to perform path traversal attacks. This can lead to unauthorized access to arbitrary files on the server, potentially exposing sensitive information such as private SSH keys, configuration files, and source code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 08:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8459 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Cleartext storage of SNMPv3 users&amp;#x27; passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8459</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology store SNMPv3 users' passwords in plaintext within the configuration files, allowing remote attackers with administrator privileges to read the file and obtain the credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 08:17:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41999 | Smart-tab Android app installed April 2023 or earlier contains an active debug code vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41999</link><description>Smart-tab Android app installed April 2023 or earlier contains an active debug code vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker with physical access to the device may exploit the debug function to gain access to the OS functions, escalate the privilege, change the device's settings, or spoof devices in other rooms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42496 | Smart-tab Android app installed April 2023 or earlier contains an issue with plaintext storage of a password. If this vulnerability is explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42496</link><description>Smart-tab Android app installed April 2023 or earlier contains an issue with plaintext storage of a password. If this vulnerability is exploited, an attacker with physical access to the device may retrieve the credential information and spoof the device to access the related external service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45200 | In Nintendo Mario Kart 8 Deluxe before 3.0.3, the LAN/LDN local multiplayer implementation allows a remote attacker to exploit a stack-based...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45200</link><description>In Nintendo Mario Kart 8 Deluxe before 3.0.3, the LAN/LDN local multiplayer implementation allows a remote attacker to exploit a stack-based buffer overflow upon deserialization of session information via a malformed browse-reply packet, aka KartLANPwn. The victim is not required to join a game session with an attacker. The victim must open the "Wireless Play" (or "LAN Play") menu from the game's title screen, and an attacker nearby (LDN) or on the same LAN network as the victim can send a crafted reply packet to the victim's console. This enables a remote attacker to obtain complete denial-of-service on the game's process, or potentially, remote code execution on the victim's console. The issue is caused by incorrect use of the Nintendo Pia library,</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8458 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Cross-site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8458</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have a web application that is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). An unauthenticated remote attacker can trick a user into visiting a malicious website, allowing the attacker to impersonate the user and perform actions on their behalf, such as creating accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8457 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in the User Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8457</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have a web application that does not properly validate specific parameters, allowing remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary JavaScript, leading to Stored XSS attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8456 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Missing Authentication for multiple HTTP routes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8456</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology lack proper access control in firmware upload and download functionality, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to download and upload firmware and system configurations, ultimately gaining full control of the devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8455 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Swctrl service exchanges weakly encoded passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8455</link><description>The swctrl service is used to detect and remotely manage PLANET Technology devices. For certain switch models, the authentication tokens used during communication with this service are encoded user passwords. Due to insufficient strength, unauthorized remote attackers who intercept the packets can directly crack them to obtain plaintext passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8453 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Weak hash for users&amp;#x27; passwords</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8453</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology use an insecure hashing function to hash user passwords without being salted. Remote attackers with administrator privileges can read configuration files to obtain the hash values, and potentially crack them to retrieve the plaintext passwords.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8454 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Swctrl service DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8454</link><description>The swctrl service is used to detect and remotely manage PLANET Technology devices. Certain switch models have a Denial-of-Service vulnerability in the swctrl service, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to send crafted packets that can crash the service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9329 | Glassfish redirect to untrusted site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9329</link><description>In Eclipse Glassfish versions before 7.0.17, The Host HTTP parameter could cause the web application to redirect to the specified URL, when the requested endpoint is '/management/domain'. By modifying the URL value to a malicious site, an attacker may successfully launch a phishing scam and steal user credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8452 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Insecure hash functions used for SNMPv3 credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8452</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology only support obsolete algorithms for authentication protocol and encryption protocol in the SNMPv3 service, allowing attackers to obtain plaintext SNMPv3 credentials potentially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 07:23:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8450 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Hard-coded SNMPv1 read-write community string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8450</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have a Hard-coded community string in the SNMPv1 service, allowing unauthorized remote attackers to use this community string to access the SNMPv1 service with read-write privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8451 | PLANET Technology switch devices - SSH server DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8451</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have an SSH service that improperly handles insufficiently authenticated connection requests, allowing unauthorized remote attackers to exploit this weakness to occupy connection slots and prevent legitimate users from accessing the SSH service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8449 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Local users&amp;#x27; passwords recovery through hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8449</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have a Hard-coded Credential in the password recovering functionality, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to connect to the device via the serial console and use this credential to reset any user's password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8448 | PLANET Technology switch devices - Remote privilege escalation using hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8448</link><description>Certain switch models from PLANET Technology have a hard-coded credential in the specific command-line interface, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to log in with this credential and obtain a Linux root shell.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3635 | The Post Grid &amp;lt; 7.5.0 - Editor+ Stored XSS via Grid Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3635</link><description>The Post Grid  WordPress plugin before 7.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Grid settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Editor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8239 | Starbox &amp;lt; 3.5.3  - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8239</link><description>The Starbox  WordPress plugin before 3.5.3 does not properly render social media profiles URLs in certain contexts, like the malicious user's profile or pages where the starbox shortcode is used, which may be abused by users with at least the contributor role to conduct Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8283 | Slider by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.2.59 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8283</link><description>The Slider by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.2.59 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8379 | Cost Calculator Builder &amp;lt; 3.2.29 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8379</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder WordPress plugin before 3.2.29 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by users with a role as low as Admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8536 | Ultimate Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.2 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8536</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.2.2 does not validate and escape some of its block attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9328 | SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System edit_client.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9328</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Advocate Office Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /control/edit_client.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 22:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9327 | code-projects Blood Bank System forgot.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9327</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forgot.php. The manipulation of the argument useremail leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 11:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9326 | PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal Admin Panel index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9326</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /shopping/admin/index.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 08:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9325 | Intelbras InControl incontrol-service-watchdog.exe unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9325</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.56. This affects an unknown part of the file C:\Program Files (x86)\Intelbras\Incontrol Cliente\incontrol_webcam\incontrol-service-watchdog.exe. The manipulation leads to unquoted search path. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The vendor was informed early on 2024-08-05 about this issue. The release of a fixed version 2.21.58 was announced for the end of August 2024 but then was postponed until 2024-09-20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9324 | Intelbras InControl Relatório de Operadores Page operador code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9324</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras InControl up to 2.21.57. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /v1/operador/ of the component Relatório de Operadores Page. The manipulation of the argument fields leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was informed early on 2024-07-19 about this issue. The release of a fixed version 2.21.58 was announced for the end of August 2024 but then was postponed until 2024-09-20.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9323 | SourceCodester Inventory Management System add_staff.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9323</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/action/add_staff.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 06:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9322 | code-projects Supply Chain Management edit_manufacturer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9322</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Supply Chain Management 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_manufacturer.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 03:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9321 | SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System view_details.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9321</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Railway Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/inquiries/view_details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9320 | SourceCodester Online Timesheet App Add Timesheet Form add-timesheet.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9320</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Timesheet App 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/add-timesheet.php of the component Add Timesheet Form. The manipulation of the argument day/task leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>