<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:37:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-13505 | Survey Maker &amp;lt;= 5.1.3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Survey Question</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13505</link><description>The Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ays_sections[5][questions][8][title]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11641 | VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp;amp; PMS &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11641</link><description>The VikBooking Hotel Booking Engine &amp; PMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change plugin access privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Successful exploitation allows attackers with subscriber-level privileges and above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11936 | Zox News &amp;lt;= 3.16.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11936</link><description>The Zox News theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'backup_options' and 'restore_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12334 | WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12334</link><description>The WC Affiliate – A Complete WooCommerce Affiliate Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via any parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 11:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10705 | Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG &amp;lt;= 4.0.5 - Authenticated (Editor+) Server-Side Request Forgery via fileUrl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10705</link><description>The Multiple Page Generator Plugin – MPG plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.5 via the 'mpg_download_file_by_link' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with editor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11090 | Membership Plugin – Restrict Content &amp;lt;= 3.2.13 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11090</link><description>The Membership Plugin – Restrict Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.13 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46881 | Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.1.8 has Incorrect Access Control. Project-level access control configuration was introdu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46881</link><description>Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.1.8 has Incorrect Access Control. Project-level access control configuration was introduced in Enterprise Config schema version 8. Migration functionality from schema version 8 to versions 9 and 10 (in affected vulnerable versions) does not include the projects section of the configuration. This leads to all of the project settings being reset to their defaults when the old schema is loaded. In the case of projects.enabled, the default is false. Thus, using an enterprise config v8 results in Project level access control being disabled, even if it was previously enabled, and previously restricted project information disclosed. Most commonly, this occurs when a Develocity instance is upgraded from an earlier version. Specifically, this occurs if: Develocity 2023.3.X is upgraded to 2023.4.X; Develocity 2023.3.X is upgraded to 2024.1.X up to and including 2024.1.7; or Develocity 2023.4.X is upgraded to 2024.1.X up to and including 2024.1.7. The flaw does not occur when upgrading to a fixed version. An upgrade can only be triggered via administrator access, and cannot be forced by an external attacker.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:32:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24858 | Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.3.1 allows an attacker who has network access to a Develocity server to obtain the hashe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24858</link><description>Develocity (formerly Gradle Enterprise) before 2024.3.1 allows an attacker who has network access to a Develocity server to obtain the hashed password of the system user. The hash algorithm used by Develocity was chosen according to best practices for password storage and provides some protection against brute-force attempts. The applicable severity of this vulnerability depends on whether a Develocity server is accessible by external or unauthorized users, and the complexity of the System User password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49043 | xmlXIncludeAddNode in xinclude.c in libxml2 before 2.11.0 has a use-after-free.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49043</link><description>xmlXIncludeAddNode in xinclude.c in libxml2 before 2.11.0 has a use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10574 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Missing Authorization to Google Sheets Integration Credentials Modification and Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10574</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ays_save_google_credentials' function in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the Google Sheets integration credentials within the plugin's settings. Because the 'client_id' parameter is not sanitized or escaped when used in output, this vulnerability could also be leveraged to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10628 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via id</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10628</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency) due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10633 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions) - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10633</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency). This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10636 | Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency &amp;lt;= (Multiple Versions)  - Reflected DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10636</link><description>The Quiz Maker Business, Developer, and Agency plugins for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.0 (Business), up to, and including, 21.8.0 (Developer), and up to, and including, 31.8.0 (Agency) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 05:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0542 | G DATA Management Server Local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0542</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to incorrect assignment of privileges of temporary files in the update mechanism of G DATA Management Server. This vulnerability allows a local, unprivileged attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations by placing a crafted ZIP archive in a globally writable directory, which gets unpacked in the context of SYSTEM and results in arbitrary file write.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0543 | G DATA Security Client Local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0543</link><description>Local privilege escalation in G DATA Security Client due to incorrect assignment of privileges to directories. This vulnerability allows a local, unprivileged attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations by placing an arbitrary executable in a globally writable directory resulting in execution by the SetupSVC.exe service in the context of SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 16:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35144 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35144</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10, 8.11, and 9.0 - Monitor Component stores source code on the web server that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35148 | IBM Maximo Application Suite SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35148</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10.10, 8.11.7, and 9.0 - Monitor Component is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35150 | IBM Maximo Application Suite log manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35150</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 8.10.12, 8.11.0, 9.0.1, and 9.1.0 - Monitor Component does not neutralize output that is written to logs, which could allow an attacker to inject false log entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35145 | IBM Maximo Application Suite cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35145</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 9.0.0 - Monitor Component is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35134 | IBM Analytics Content Hub information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35134</link><description>IBM Analytics Content Hub 2.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39750 | IBM Analytics Content Hub buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39750</link><description>IBM Analytics Content Hub 2.0 is vulnerable to a buffer overflow due to improper return length checking. A remote authenticated attacker could overflow a buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system or cause the server to crash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38013 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38013</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.0, 2.3.3.3, 2.3.3.3 iFix1, 2.3.3.4, 2.3.3.5, 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.6 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, and 2.3.3.7 iFix1 could disclose sensitive information in HTTP responses that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38271 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38271</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.0, 2.3.3.3, 2.3.3.3 iFix1, 2.3.3.4, 2.3.3.5, 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.6 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, and 2.3.3.7 iFix1 could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information from log files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38713 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38713</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.0, 2.3.3.3, 2.3.3.3 iFix1, 2.3.3.4, 2.3.3.5, 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.6 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, and 2.3.3.7 iFix1 could disclose sensitive information about the system that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38714 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38714</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.0, 2.3.3.3, 2.3.3.3 iFix1, 2.3.3.4, 2.3.3.5, 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.6 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, and 2.3.3.7 iFix1 could disclose sensitive information about the system that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38012 | IBM Cloud Pak System directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38012</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.6, 2.3.3.6 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, 2.3.3.7 iFix1, and 2.3.4.0 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38716 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38716</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.3.6, 2.3.36 iFix1, 2.3.3.6 iFix2, 2.3.3.7, 2.3.3.7 iFix1, and 2.3.4.0 could disclose sensitive information about the system that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35111 | IBM Control Center information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35111</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 and 6.3.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35112 | IBM Control Center cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35112</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 and 6.3.1 

could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35113 | IBM Control Center information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35113</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 and 6.3.1 



could allow an authenticated user to obtain sensitive information exposed through a directory listing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35114 | IBM Control Center information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35114</link><description>IBM Control Center 6.2.1 and 6.3.1 





could allow a remote attacker to enumerate usernames due to an observable discrepancy between login attempts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13562 | Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.14.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13562</link><description>The Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.5 via the uploads directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data  stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/ directory which can contain information like imported or local user data and files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 11:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0350 | Divi Carousel Lite &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Carousel and Logo Carousel Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0350</link><description>The Divi Carousel Maker – Image, Logo, Testimonial, Post Carousel &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Carousel and Logo Carousel in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 09:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13449 | Boom Fest &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13449</link><description>The Boom Fest plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'bf_admin_action' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin settings that change the appearance of the website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 08:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13450 | Contact Form by Bit Form &amp;lt;= 2.17.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13450</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.17.4 via the Webhooks integration. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. The vulnerability can also be exploited in Multisite environments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 08:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11825 | Broadstreet &amp;lt;= 1.50.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via zone Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11825</link><description>The Broadstreet plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘zone’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.50.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12076 | Target Video Easy Publish &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12076</link><description>The Target Video Easy Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the resync_carousel(), seek_snapshot(), uploaded_cc(), and remove_cc() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12113 | Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp;amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress By KaineLabs &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Review Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12113</link><description>The Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_user_review() and delete_review() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete other user's reviews.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12512 | Ask Me Anything (Anonymously) &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12512</link><description>The Ask Me Anything (Anonymously) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'askmeanythingpeople' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12529 | brodos.net Onlineshop Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12529</link><description>The brodos.net Onlineshop Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'BrodosCategory' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12816 | NOTICE BOARD BY TOWKIR &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12816</link><description>The NOTICE BOARD BY TOWKIR plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'notice-board' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12817 | Etsy Importer &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12817</link><description>The Etsy Importer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'product_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12826 | GoHero Store Customizer for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unuthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12826</link><description>The GoHero Store Customizer for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wooh_action_settings_save_frontend() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update limited plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12885 | Connections Business Directory &amp;lt;= 10.4.66 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary Directory Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12885</link><description>The Connections Business Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary directory deletion due to insufficient file path validation when deleting a connections image directory in all versions up to, and including, 10.4.66. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary folders on the server and all their content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13368 | Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp;amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13368</link><description>The Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the youzify_offer_banner() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary site options to a value of one.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13370 | Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp;amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update (save_addon_key_license)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13370</link><description>The Youzify – BuddyPress Community, User Profile, Social Network &amp; Membership Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the save_addon_key_license() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options to a value of a valid license key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13441 | Bilingual Linker &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13441</link><description>The Bilingual Linker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the bl_otherlang_link_1 parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13458 | WordPress SEO Friendly Accordion FAQ with AI assisted content generation &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13458</link><description>The WordPress SEO Friendly Accordion FAQ with AI assisted content generation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'noticefaq' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13467 | WP Contact Form7 Email Spam Blocker &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13467</link><description>The WP Contact Form7 Email Spam Blocker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'post' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13548 | Power Ups for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13548</link><description>The Power Ups for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'magic-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13550 | ABC Notation &amp;lt;= 6.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13550</link><description>The ABC Notation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.3 via the 'file' attribute of the 'abcjs' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13551 | ABC Notation &amp;lt;= 6.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13551</link><description>The ABC Notation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'abcjs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13586 | Masy Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13586</link><description>The Masy Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'justified-gallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13599 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7.5 - Authenticated (LP Instructor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Lesson Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13599</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of a lesson name. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with LP Instructor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 07:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10552 | Flexmls® IDX Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via API parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10552</link><description>The Flexmls® IDX Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘api_key’ and 'api_secret' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.14.25.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12600 | Custom Product Tabs Lite for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12600</link><description>The Custom Product Tabs Lite for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'frs_woo_product_tabs' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13721 | Plethora Plugins Tabs + Accordions &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via anchor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13721</link><description>The Plethora Plugins Tabs + Accordions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the anchor parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0682 | ThemeREX Addons &amp;lt;= 2.33.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0682</link><description>The ThemeREX Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.33.0 via the 'trx_sc_reviews' shortcode 'type' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 05:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0411 | 7-Zip Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0411</link><description>7-Zip Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-of-the-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of 7-Zip. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of archived files. When extracting files from a crafted archive that bears the Mark-of-the-Web, 7-Zip does not propagate the Mark-of-the-Web to the extracted files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-25456.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13709 | Linear &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cache Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13709</link><description>The Linear plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'linear-debug'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin's cache via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 03:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0357 | WPBookit &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0357</link><description>The WPBookit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'WPB_Profile_controller::handle_image_upload' function in versions up to, and including, 1.6.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 02:07:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24360 | Opening a malicious website while running a Nuxt dev server could allow read-only access to code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24360</link><description>Nuxt is an open-source web development framework for Vue.js. Starting in version 3.8.1 and prior to version 3.15.3, Nuxt allows any websites to send any requests to the development server and read the response due to default CORS settings. Users with the default server.cors option using Vite builder may get the source code stolen by malicious websites. Version 3.15.3 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24361 | Opening a malicious website while running a Nuxt dev server could allow read-only access to code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24361</link><description>Nuxt is an open-source web development framework for Vue.js. Source code may be stolen during dev when using version 3.0.0 through 3.15.12 of the webpack builder or version 3.12.2 through 3.152 of the rspack builder and a victim opens a malicious web site. Because the request for classic script by a script tag is not subject to same origin policy, an attacker can inject a malicious script in their site and run the script. By using `Function::toString` against the values in `window.webpackChunknuxt_app`, the attacker can get the source code. Version 3.15.13 of Nuxt patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:57:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50698 | SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow due to bounds checks of the MQTT message co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50698</link><description>SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow due to bounds checks of the MQTT message content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50690 | SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions contains a hardcoded password that can be used to decrypt all firmware updates.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50690</link><description>SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions contains a hardcoded password that can be used to decrypt all firmware updates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50692 | SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions contains hardcoded MQTT credentials that allow an attacker to send arbitrary commands t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50692</link><description>SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions contains hardcoded MQTT credentials that allow an attacker to send arbitrary commands to an arbitrary inverter. It is also possible to impersonate the broker, because TLS is not used to identify the real MQTT broker. This means that MQTT communications are vulnerable to MitM attacks at the TCP/IP level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50694 | In SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions, when copying the timestamp read from an MQTT message, the underlying code does not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50694</link><description>In SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions, when copying the timestamp read from an MQTT message, the underlying code does not check the bounds of the buffer that is used to store the message. This may lead to a stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50695 | SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow when parsing MQTT messages, due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50695</link><description>SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions is vulnerable to stack-based buffer overflow when parsing MQTT messages, due to missing MQTT topic bounds checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50697 | In SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions, when decrypting MQTT messages, the code that parses specific TLV fields does not ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50697</link><description>In SunGrow WiNet-SV200.001.00.P027 and earlier versions, when decrypting MQTT messages, the code that parses specific TLV fields does not have sufficient bounds checks. This may result in a stack-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:19:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21262 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21262</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0710 | CampCodes School Management Software Notice Board Page notice-list cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0710</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /notice-list of the component Notice Board Page. The manipulation of the argument Notice leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0709 | Dcat-Admin Roles Page roles cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0709</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dcat-Admin 2.2.1-beta. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/auth/roles of the component Roles Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0707 | Rise Group Rise Mode Temp CPU Startup CRYPTBASE.dll untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Rise Group Rise Mode Temp CPU 2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part in the library CRYPTBASE.dll of the component Startup. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. The attack needs to be approached locally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0708 | fumiao opencms Add Model Management Page addOrUpdate cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in fumiao opencms 2.2. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/model/addOrUpdate of the component Add Model Management Page. The manipulation of the argument 模板前缀 leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57095 | SQL injection vulnerability in Go-CMS v.1.1.10 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57095</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Go-CMS v.1.1.10 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57277 | InnoShop V.0.3.8 and below is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via SVG file upload.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57277</link><description>InnoShop V.0.3.8 and below is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via SVG file upload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0706 | JoeyBling bootplus admin.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/sys/admin.html. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57041 | A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in NodeBB v3.11.0 allows remote attackers to store arbitrary code in the 'about me' se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57041</link><description>A persistent cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in NodeBB v3.11.0 allows remote attackers to store arbitrary code in the 'about me' section of their profile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0705 | JoeyBling bootplus QrCodeController.java qrCode redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0705</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function qrCode of the file src/main/java/io/github/controller/QrCodeController.java. The manipulation of the argument text leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24363 | Potential GitHub repo user and credential information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24363</link><description>The HL7 FHIR IG publisher is a tool to take a set of inputs and create a standard FHIR IG. Prior to version 1.8.9, in CI contexts, the IG Publisher CLI uses git commands to determine the URL of the originating repo. If the repo was cloned, or otherwise set to use a repo that uses a username and credential based URL, the entire URL will be included in the built Implementation Guide, exposing username and credential. This does not impact users that clone public repos without credentials, such as those using the auto-ig-build continuous integration infrastructure. This problem has been patched in release 1.8.9. Some workarounds are available. Users should ensure the IG repo they are publishing does not have username or credentials included in the `origin` URL. Running the command `git remote origin url` should return a URL that contains no username, password, or token; or users should run the IG Publisher CLI with the `-repo` parameter and specify a URL that contains no username, password, or token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52807 | XXE vulnerability in XSLT parsing in `org.hl7.fhir.publisher`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52807</link><description>The HL7 FHIR IG publisher is a tool to take a set of inputs and create a standard FHIR IG. Prior to version 1.7.4, XSLT transforms performed by various components are vulnerable to XML external entity injections. A processed XML file with a malicious DTD tag `( ]&gt;` could produce XML containing data from the host system. This impacts use cases where org.hl7.fhir.publisher is being used to within a host where external clients can submit XML. A previous release provided an incomplete solution revealed by new testing. This issue has been patched as of version 1.7.4. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0703 | JoeyBling bootplus SysFileController.java path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0703</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/main/java/io/github/controller/SysFileController.java. The manipulation of the argument name leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0704 | JoeyBling bootplus QrCodeController.java qrCode resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0704</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. Affected is the function qrCode of the file src/main/java/io/github/controller/QrCodeController.java. The manipulation of the argument w/h leads to resource consumption. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24362 | CodeQL GitHub Action failed workflow writes GitHub PAT to debug artifacts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24362</link><description>In some circumstances, debug artifacts uploaded by the CodeQL Action after a failed code scanning workflow run may contain the environment variables from the workflow run, including any secrets that were exposed as environment variables to the workflow. Users with read access to the repository would be able to access this artifact, containing any secrets from the environment. This vulnerability is patched in CodeQL Action version 3.28.3 or later, or CodeQL CLI version 2.20.3 or later.

For some affected workflow runs, the exposed environment variables in the debug artifacts included a valid `GITHUB_TOKEN` for the workflow run, which has access to the repository in which the workflow ran, and all the permissions specified in the workflow or job. The `GITHUB_TOKEN` is valid until the job completes or 24 hours has elapsed, whichever comes first.

Environment variables are exposed only from workflow runs that satisfy all of the following conditions:
- Code scanning workflow configured to scan the Java/Kotlin languages.
- Running in a repository containing Kotlin source code.
- Running with debug artifacts enabled.
- Using CodeQL Action versions &lt;= 3.28.2, and CodeQL CLI versions &gt;= 2.9.2 (May 2022) and &lt;= 2.20.2.
- The workflow run fails before the CodeQL database is finalized within the `github/codeql-action/analyze` step.
- Running in any GitHub environment: GitHub.com, GitHub Enterprise Cloud, and GitHub Enterprise Server. Note: artifacts are only accessible to users within the same GitHub environment with access to the scanned repo.

The `GITHUB_TOKEN` exposed in this way would only have been valid for workflow runs that satisfy all of the following conditions, in addition to the conditions above:
- Using CodeQL Action versions &gt;= 3.26.11 (October 2024) and &lt;= 3.28.2, or &gt;= 2.26.11 and &lt; 3.
- Running in GitHub.com or GitHub Enterprise Cloud only (not valid on GitHub Enterprise Server).

In rare cases during advanced setup, logging of environment variables may also occur during database creation of Java, Swift, and C/C++. Please read the corresponding CodeQL CLI advisory GHSA-gqh3-9prg-j95m for more details.

In CodeQL CLI versions &gt;= 2.9.2 and &lt;= 2.20.2, the CodeQL Kotlin extractor logs all environment variables by default into an intermediate file during the process of creating a CodeQL database for Kotlin code. This is a part of the CodeQL CLI and is invoked by the CodeQL Action for analyzing Kotlin repositories. 

On Actions, the environment variables logged include GITHUB_TOKEN, which grants permissions to the repository being scanned.
The intermediate file containing environment variables is deleted when finalizing the database, so it is not included in a successfully created database. It is, however, included in the debug artifact that is uploaded on a failed analysis run if the CodeQL Action was invoked in debug mode.

Therefore, under these specific circumstances (incomplete database creation using the CodeQL Action in debug mode) an attacker with access to the debug artifact would gain unauthorized access to repository secrets from the environment, including both the `GITHUB_TOKEN` and any user-configured secrets made available via environment variables.

The impact of the `GITHUB_TOKEN` leaked in this environment is limited:
- For workflows on GitHub.com and GitHub Enterprise Cloud using CodeQL Action versions &gt;= 3.26.11 and &lt;= 3.28.2, or &gt;= 2.26.11 and &lt; 3, which in turn use the `actions/artifacts v4` library, the debug artifact is uploaded before the workflow job completes. During this time the `GITHUB_TOKEN` is still valid, providing an opportunity for attackers to gain access to the repository.
- For all other workflows, the debug artifact is uploaded after the workflow job completes, at which point the leaked `GITHUB_TOKEN` has been revoked and cannot be used to access the repository.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0702 | JoeyBling bootplus SysFileController.java unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0702</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file src/main/java/io/github/controller/SysFileController.java. The manipulation of the argument portraitFile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-15690 | LibVNCServer 0.9.12 release and earlier contains heap buffer overflow vulnerability within the HandleCursorShape() function in libvncclient/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-15690</link><description>LibVNCServer 0.9.12 release and earlier contains heap buffer overflow vulnerability within the HandleCursorShape() function in libvncclient/cursor.c. An attacker sends cursor shapes with specially crafted dimensions, which can result in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35122 | IBM i denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35122</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 is vulnerable to a file level local denial of service caused by an insufficient authority requirement. A local non-privileged user can configure a referential constraint with the privileges of a user socially engineered to access the target file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24587 | WordPress Email Subscription Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.23 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24587</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in I Thirteen Web Solution Email Subscription Popup allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Email Subscription Popup: from n/a through 1.2.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24542 | WordPress Icegram Engage plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24542</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in icegram Icegram allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Icegram: from n/a through 3.1.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24543 | WordPress Ultimate Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;=  1.0.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24543</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RSTheme Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24546 | WordPress Ultimate Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;=  1.0.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24546</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RSTheme Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Ultimate Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24547 | WordPress Caching Compatible Cookie Opt-In plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.10 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matthias Wagner - FALKEmedia Caching Compatible Cookie Opt-In and JavaScript allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Caching Compatible Cookie Opt-In and JavaScript: from n/a through 0.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24552 | WordPress Paytium plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.11 - Full Path Disclosure (FPD)  vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24552</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in David de Boer Paytium allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Paytium: from n/a through 4.4.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24555 | WordPress Subscription DNA plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24555</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SubscriptionDNA.com Subscription DNA allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Subscription DNA: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24561 | WordPress ReviewsTap plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24561</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ReviewsTap ReviewsTap allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ReviewsTap: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24562 | WordPress KBucket plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.6 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24562</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Optimal Access Inc. KBucket allows Stored XSS. This issue affects KBucket: from n/a through 4.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24568 | WordPress Starter Templates plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24568</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Brainstorm Force Starter Templates allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Starter Templates: from n/a through 4.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24570 | WordPress Atarim plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Atarim Atarim allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Atarim: from n/a through 4.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24571 | WordPress WP Fast Total Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.78.258 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24571</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Epsiloncool WP Fast Total Search allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Fast Total Search: from n/a through 1.78.258.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24572 | WordPress WP Fast Total Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.78.258 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24572</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Epsiloncool WP Fast Total Search allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Fast Total Search: from n/a through 1.78.258.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24573 | WordPress Pagelayer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pagelayer Team PageLayer allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects PageLayer: from n/a through 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24575 | WordPress HelloAsso plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24575</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HelloAsso HelloAsso allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HelloAsso: from n/a through 1.1.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24578 | WordPress ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24578</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ElementInvader ElementInvader Addons for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects ElementInvader Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24579 | WordPress Nested pages plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24579</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kyle Phillips Nested Pages allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Nested Pages: from n/a through 3.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24580 | WordPress 12 Step Meeting List plugin &amp;lt;= 3.16.5 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24580</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Code for Recovery 12 Step Meeting List allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 12 Step Meeting List: from n/a through 3.16.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24582 | WordPress 12 Step Meeting List plugin &amp;lt;= 3.16.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24582</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Code for Recovery 12 Step Meeting List allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects 12 Step Meeting List: from n/a through 3.16.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24585 | WordPress Event post plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.7 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24585</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in N.O.U.S. Open Useful and Simple Event post allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Event post: from n/a through 5.9.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24588 | WordPress Patreon WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24588</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Patreon Patreon WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Patreon WordPress: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24589 | WordPress JSM Show Post Metadata plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24589</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Morisset JSM Show Post Metadata allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects JSM Show Post Metadata: from n/a through 4.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24591 | WordPress GDPR CCPA Compliance &amp;amp; Cookie Consent Banner plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24591</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NinjaTeam GDPR CCPA Compliance Support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects GDPR CCPA Compliance Support: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24594 | WordPress Linet ERP-Woocommerce Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - CSRF to Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24594</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Speedcomp Linet ERP-Woocommerce Integration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Linet ERP-Woocommerce Integration: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24595 | WordPress All Embed – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24595</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins All Embed – Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects All Embed – Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24596 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Table Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24596</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WC Product Table WooCommerce Product Table Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooCommerce Product Table Lite: from n/a through 3.8.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24604 | WordPress Lifetime free Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress VForm plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24604</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Vikas Ratudi VForm allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects VForm: from n/a through 3.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24610 | WordPress Restrict Anonymous Access Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Christian Leuenberg, L.net Web Solutions Restrict Anonymous Access allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Restrict Anonymous Access: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24611 | WordPress Export All Posts, Products, Orders, Refunds &amp;amp; Users Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24611</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Smackcoders WP Ultimate Exporter allows Absolute Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Ultimate Exporter: from n/a through 2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24613 | WordPress FV Thoughtful Comments plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24613</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Foliovision FV Thoughtful Comments allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects FV Thoughtful Comments: from n/a through 0.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24618 | WordPress ElementInvader Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24618</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ElementInvader ElementInvader Addons for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ElementInvader Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24622 | WordPress Job Board Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.59 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24622</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.59.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24623 | WordPress Really Simple Security plugin &amp;lt;= 9.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24623</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Really Simple Security Really Simple SSL allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Really Simple SSL: from n/a through 9.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24625 | WordPress Taxonomy/Term and Role based Discounts for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24625</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Marco Almeida | Webdados Taxonomy/Term and Role based Discounts for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Taxonomy/Term and Role based Discounts for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24627 | WordPress Blur Text Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24627</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Linnea Huxford, LinSoftware Blur Text allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Blur Text: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24633 | WordPress Build Private Store For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24633</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in silverplugins217 Build Private Store For Woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Build Private Store For Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24634 | WordPress Orbisius Simple Notice plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Svetoslav Marinov (Slavi) Orbisius Simple Notice allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Orbisius Simple Notice: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24636 | WordPress MachForm Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24636</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Laymance Technologies LLC MachForm Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MachForm Shortcode: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24638 | WordPress Create with Code plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24638</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pete Dring Create with Code allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Create with Code: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24644 | WordPress WooCommerce PDF Invoices plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24644</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebToffee WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Invoices, Packing Slips, Delivery Notes and Shipping Labels: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24647 | WordPress WooCommerce Cloak Affiliate Links plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.35 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24647</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in datafeedr.com WooCommerce Cloak Affiliate Links allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WooCommerce Cloak Affiliate Links: from n/a through 1.0.35.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24649 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24649</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpase.com Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE): from n/a through 7.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24650 | WordPress Tourfic plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24650</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Themefic Tourfic allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Tourfic: from n/a through 2.15.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24652 | WordPress WP Duplicate plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24652</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Revmakx WP Duplicate – WordPress Migration Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Duplicate – WordPress Migration Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24657 | WordPress Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;=2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebToffee Wishlist for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Wishlist for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24658 | WordPress Auction Nudge – Your eBay on Your Site plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24658</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Joe Hawes Auction Nudge – Your eBay on Your Site allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Auction Nudge – Your eBay on Your Site: from n/a through 7.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24659 | WordPress Premium Packages – Sell Digital Products Securely plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24659</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WordPress Download Manager Premium Packages allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Premium Packages: from n/a through 5.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24663 | WordPress Simple Download Monitor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.25 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Tips and Tricks HQ, Ruhul Amin, Josh Lobe Simple Download Monitor allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Simple Download Monitor: from n/a through 3.9.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24666 | WordPress Hyve Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24666</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeIsle AI Chatbot for WordPress – Hyve Lite allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AI Chatbot for WordPress – Hyve Lite: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24668 | WordPress PPOM for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 33.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24668</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeisle PPOM for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PPOM for WooCommerce: from n/a through 33.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24669 | WordPress SERPed.net Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24669</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SERPed SERPed.net allows SQL Injection. This issue affects SERPed.net: from n/a through 4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24672 | WordPress Form Builder CP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.41 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24672</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in CodePeople Form Builder CP allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Form Builder CP: from n/a through 1.2.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24673 | WordPress Ketchup Shortcodes Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in AyeCode Ltd Ketchup Shortcodes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ketchup Shortcodes: from n/a through 0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24674 | WordPress ShMapper by Teplitsa Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Teplitsa. Technologies for Social Good ShMapper by Teplitsa allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ShMapper by Teplitsa: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24675 | WordPress WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic) plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24675</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in osamaesh WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic) allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Visitor Statistics (Real Time Traffic): from n/a through 7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24678 | WordPress Listamester Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Listamester Listamester allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Listamester: from n/a through 2.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24679 | WordPress Internal Links Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24679</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in webraketen Internal Links Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Internal Links Manager: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24681 | WordPress Product Carousel Slider &amp;amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce  Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24681</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpWax Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24682 | WordPress Super Block Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24682</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in mikemmx Super Block Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Super Block Slider: from n/a through 2.7.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24683 | WordPress RSVP and Event Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.14 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24683</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPChill RSVP and Event Management Plugin allows SQL Injection. This issue affects RSVP and Event Management Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24687 | WordPress Show/Hide Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24687</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lars Wallenborn Show/Hide Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Show/Hide Shortcode: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24691 | WordPress People Lists plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24691</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gagan Sandhu , Enej Bajgoric , CTLT DEV, UBC People Lists allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects People Lists: from n/a through 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24693 | WordPress Advanced Notifications plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24693</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Yehi Advanced Notifications allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Advanced Notifications: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24695 | WordPress Extensions For CF7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24695</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in HasThemes Extensions For CF7 allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Extensions For CF7: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24696 | WordPress Gutenberg Blocks and Page Layouts Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24696</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Attire Attire Blocks allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Attire Blocks: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24698 | WordPress Essential Real Estate plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24698</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in G5Theme Essential Real Estate allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Essential Real Estate: from n/a through 5.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24701 | WordPress Chained Quiz Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2.9 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24701</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Kiboko Labs Chained Quiz allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Chained Quiz: from n/a through 1.3.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24702 | WordPress Xagio SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.0.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xagio Xagio SEO allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Xagio SEO: from n/a through 7.0.0.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24703 | WordPress Comment Edit Core – Simple Comment Editing Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.33 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24703</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in DLX Plugins Comment Edit Core – Simple Comment Editing allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Comment Edit Core – Simple Comment Editing: from n/a through 3.0.33.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24704 | WordPress Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24704</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sebastian Zaha Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Magic the Gathering Card Tooltips: from n/a through 3.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24705 | WordPress WooCommerce Quick View plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24705</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Arshid WooCommerce Quick View allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooCommerce Quick View: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24706 | WordPress MultiVendorX plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24706</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MultiVendorX WC Marketplace allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WC Marketplace: from n/a through 4.2.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24709 | WordPress Plethora Plugins Tabs + Accordions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24709</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Plethora Plugins Plethora Plugins Tabs + Accordions allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Plethora Plugins Tabs + Accordions: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24711 | WordPress Popup Box Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24711</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Popup Box allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Popup Box: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24712 | WordPress Radius Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24712</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RadiusTheme Radius Blocks allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Radius Blocks: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24713 | WordPress Button Generator – easily Button Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24713</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Button Generator – easily Button Builder allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Button Generator – easily Button Builder: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24714 | WordPress Bubble Menu  Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24714</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Bubble Menu – circle floating menu allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Bubble Menu – circle floating menu: from n/a through 4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24715 | WordPress Counter Box Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24715</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Counter Box allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Counter Box: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24716 | WordPress Herd Effects Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24716</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Herd Effects allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Herd Effects: from n/a through 6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24717 | WordPress Modal Window Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24717</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Modal Window allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Modal Window: from n/a through 6.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24719 | WordPress Widget Countdown plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24719</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdevart Widget Countdown allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Widget Countdown: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24720 | WordPress Sticky Buttons Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24720</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Sticky Buttons allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sticky Buttons: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24721 | WordPress Easy YouTube Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24721</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aleksandar Urošević Easy YouTube Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Easy YouTube Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24722 | WordPress FAQ Builder AYS Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24722</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in F.A.Q Builder Team FAQ Builder AYS allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FAQ Builder AYS: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24723 | WordPress Booking Calendar Contact Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.55 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24723</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodePeople Booking Calendar Contact Form allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Booking Calendar Contact Form: from n/a through 1.2.55.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24724 | WordPress Side Menu Lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24724</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company Side Menu Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Side Menu Lite: from n/a through 5.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24725 | WordPress Thim Elementor Kit Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24725</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ThimPress Thim Elementor Kit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Thim Elementor Kit: from n/a through 1.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24726 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24726</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HT Plugins HT Conctact Form 7 allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HT Conctact Form 7: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24727 | WordPress Contact Form to Email Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.52 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24727</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodePeople Contact Form Email allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form Email: from n/a through 1.3.52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24728 | WordPress Bug Library plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24728</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Bug Library allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Bug Library: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24729 | WordPress ElementInvader Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24729</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ElementInvader ElementInvader Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ElementInvader Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24730 | WordPress WP VR plugin &amp;lt;= 8.5.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24730</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rextheme WP VR allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP VR: from n/a through 8.5.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24731 | WordPress IP2Location Country Blocker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.38.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24731</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in IP2Location Download IP2Location Country Blocker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Download IP2Location Country Blocker: from n/a through 2.38.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24732 | WordPress BookingPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24732</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Booking &amp; Appointment - Repute Infosystems BookingPress allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects BookingPress: from n/a through 1.1.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24733 | WordPress Post Grid Master plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.12 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24733</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AddonMaster Post Grid Master allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24736 | WordPress Post Duplicator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.35 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24736</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Metaphor Creations Post Duplicator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Post Duplicator: from n/a through 2.35.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24738 | WordPress Call Now Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.13 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24738</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in NowButtons.com Call Now Button allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Call Now Button: from n/a through 1.4.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24739 | WordPress FluentSMTP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.80 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24739</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FluentSMTP &amp; WPManageNinja Team FluentSMTP allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects FluentSMTP: from n/a through 2.2.80.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24746 | WordPress Popup Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.20.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24746</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Popup Maker Popup Maker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Popup Maker: from n/a through 1.20.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24750 | WordPress ExactMetrics plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24750</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ExactMetrics ExactMetrics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects ExactMetrics: from n/a through 8.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24751 | WordPress CoBlocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24751</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GoDaddy CoBlocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CoBlocks: from n/a through 3.1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24753 | WordPress Kadence Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24753</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kadence WP Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24755 | WordPress PDF Invoices for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in add-ons.org PDF Invoices for WooCommerce + Drag and Drop Template Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PDF Invoices for WooCommerce + Drag and Drop Template Builder: from n/a through 4.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24756 | WordPress Roi Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24756</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in mgplugin Roi Calculator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Roi Calculator: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56404 | In One Identity Identity Manager 9.x before 9.3, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows privilege escalation. Only ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56404</link><description>In One Identity Identity Manager 9.x before 9.3, an insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability allows privilege escalation. Only On-Premise installations are affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0700 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0700</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/sys/log/list. The manipulation of the argument logId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0701 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0701</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/sys/user/list. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23222 | An issue was discovered in Deepin dde-api-proxy through 1.0.19 in which unprivileged users can access D-Bus services as root. Specifically, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23222</link><description>An issue was discovered in Deepin dde-api-proxy through 1.0.19 in which unprivileged users can access D-Bus services as root. Specifically, dde-api-proxy runs as root and forwards messages from arbitrary local users to legacy D-Bus methods in the actual D-Bus services, and the actual D-Bus services don't know about the proxy situation (they believe that root is asking them to do things). Consequently several proxied methods, that shouldn't be accessible to non-root users, are accessible to non-root users. In situations where Polkit is involved, the caller would be treated as admin, resulting in a similar escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:07:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24355 | Updatecli may expose Maven credentials in console output</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24355</link><description>Updatecli is a tool used to apply file update strategies. Prior to version 0.93.0, private maven repository credentials may be leaked in application logs in case of unsuccessful retrieval operation. During the execution of an updatecli pipeline which contains a `maven` source configured with basic auth credentials, the credentials are being leaked in the application execution logs in case of failure. Credentials are properly sanitized when the operation is successful but not when for whatever reason there is a failure in the maven repository, e.g. wrong coordinates provided, not existing artifact or version. Version 0.93.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24359 | ASTEVAL Vulnerable to Maliciously Crafted Format Strings Leading to Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24359</link><description>ASTEVAL is an evaluator of Python expressions and statements. Prior to version 1.0.6, if an attacker can control the input to the `asteval` library, they can bypass asteval's restrictions and execute arbitrary Python code in the context of the application using the library. The vulnerability is rooted in how `asteval` performs handling of `FormattedValue` AST nodes. In particular, the `on_formattedvalue` value uses the dangerous format method of the str class. The code allows an attacker to manipulate the value of the string used in the dangerous call `fmt.format(__fstring__=val)`. This vulnerability can be exploited to access protected attributes by intentionally triggering an `AttributeError` exception. The attacker can then catch the exception and use its `obj` attribute to gain arbitrary access to sensitive or protected object properties. Version 1.0.6 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22612 | Coolify Vulnerable to Private Key Enumeration on Onboarding resulting in Remote Command Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22612</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.374, the missing authorization allows an authenticated user to retrieve any existing private keys on a coolify instance in plain text. If the server configuration of IP / domain, port (most likely 22) and user (root) matches with the victim's server configuration, then the attacker can execute arbitrary commands on the remote server. Version 4.0.0-beta.374 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24025 | Coolify Vulnerable to Reflected XSS on Tag Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24025</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.380, the tags page allows users to search for tags. If the search does not return any results, the query gets reflected on the error modal, which leads to cross-site scripting. Version 4.0.0-beta.380 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22610 | Coolify Vulnerable to OAuth Secrets Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22610</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.361, the missing authorization allows any authenticated user to fetch the global coolify instance OAuth configuration. This exposes the "client id" and "client secret" for every custom OAuth provider. The attacker can also modify the global OAuth configuration. Version 4.0.0-beta.361 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22611 | Coolify vulnerable to Privilege Escalation resulting in Remote Command Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22611</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.361, the missing authorization allows any authenticated user to escalate his or any other team members privileges to any role, including the owner role. He's also able to kick every other member out of the team, including admins and owners. This allows the attacker to access the `Terminal` feature and execute remote commands. Version 4.0.0-beta.361 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22608 | Coolify Vulnerable to Revocation of Arbitrary Team Invitations (DOS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22608</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.361, the missing authorization allows any authenticated user to revoke any team invitations on a Coolify instance by only providing a predictable and incrementing ID, resulting in a Denial-of-Service attack (DOS). Version 4.0.0-beta.361 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22609 | Coolify Vulnerable to Private Key Hijacking / Remote Command Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22609</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.361, the missing authorization allows any authenticated user to attach any existing private key on a coolify instance to his own server. If the server configuration of IP / domain, port (most likely 22) and user (root) matches with the victim's server configuration, then the attacker can use the `Terminal` feature and execute arbitrary commands on the victim's server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22607 | Coolify Vulnerable to GitHub / GitLab OAuth Secrets Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22607</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Prior to version 4.0.0-beta.361, the missing authorization allows any authenticated user to fetch the details page for any GitHub / GitLab configuration on a Coolify instance by only knowing the UUID of the model. This exposes the "client id", "client secret" and "webhook secret." Version 4.0.0-beta.361 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45077 | IBM Maximo Asset Management file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45077</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 MXAPIASSET API is vulnerable to unrestricted file upload which allows authenticated low privileged user to upload restricted file types with a simple method of adding a dot to the end of the file name if Maximo is installed on Windows operating system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22606 | Coolify Command Injection Vulnerability in Project Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22606</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. In version 4.0.0-beta.358 and possibly earlier versions, when creating or updating a "project," it is possible to inject arbitrary shell commands by altering the project name. If a name includes unescaped characters, such as single quotes (`'`), it breaks out of the intended command structure, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host system. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host server, which could result in full system compromise; create, modify, or delete sensitive system files; and escalate privileges depending on the permissions of the executed process. Attackers with access to project management features could exploit this flaw to gain unauthorized control over the host environment. Version 4.0.0-beta.359 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0698 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/sys/menu/list. The manipulation of the argument sort/order leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0699 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0699</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/sys/role/list. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23991 | WordPress Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23991</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theDotstore Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce.This issue affects Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13698 | Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery, Arbitrary Image Upload, and Image Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13698</link><description>The Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'download_image_via_ai' and 'generate_image_via_ai' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application to upload files in an image format, and to generate AI images using the site's OpenAI key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25034 | IBM Planning Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25034</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 and 2.1 could be vulnerable to malicious file upload by not validating the type of file in the File Manager T1 process. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system that can be sent to victims for performing further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40693 | IBM Planning Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40693</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 and 2.1 could be vulnerable to malicious file upload by not validating the content of the file uploaded to the web interface. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system, and it can be sent to victim for performing further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40706 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40706</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote user to obtain sensitive version information that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41757 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41757</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 and 1.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0697 | Telstra Smart Modem Gen 2 HTTP Header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0697</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Telstra Smart Modem Gen 2 up to 20250115. This affects an unknown part of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content-Disposition leads to injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22605 | Coolify OS Command Injection Vulnerability in SSH Command Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22605</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Starting in version 4.0.0-beta.18 and prior to 4.0.0-beta.253, a vulnerability in the execution of commands on remote servers allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the local Coolify container, gaining access to data and private keys or tokens of other users/teams. The ability to inject malicious commands into the Coolify container gives authenticated attackers the ability to fully retrieve and control the data and availability of the software. Centrally hosted Coolify instances (open registration and/or multiple teams with potentially untrustworthy users) are especially at risk, as sensitive data of all users and connected servers can be leaked by any user. Additionally, attackers are able to modify the running software, potentially deploying malicious images to remote nodes or generally changing its behavior. Version 4.0.0-beta.253 patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9494 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in CP210 VCP Win 2k installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9494</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the 



CP210 VCP Win 2k



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9495 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in CP210x VCP Windows installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9495</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the CP210x VCP Windows 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9496 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress Dev Kit installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9496</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress Dev Kit

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9497 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress 4 SDK installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9497</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress 4 SDK

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9498 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress SDK installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9498</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress SDK

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9499 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress Win 98SE Dev Kit installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9499</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress Win 98SE Dev Kit installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9492 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Flash Programming Utility installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9492</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Flash Programming Utility installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9493 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in ToolStick installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9493</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the 

ToolStick

 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9490 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Silicon Labs IDE installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9490</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Silicon Labs (8-bit) IDE installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9491 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Configuration Wizard 2 installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9491</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Configuration Wizard 2 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57184 | An issue was discovered in GPAC v0.8.0, as demonstrated by MP4Box. It contains a heap-based buffer overflow in gf_m2ts_process_pmt in media_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57184</link><description>An issue was discovered in GPAC v0.8.0, as demonstrated by MP4Box. It contains a heap-based buffer overflow in gf_m2ts_process_pmt in media_tools/mpegts.c:2163 that can cause a denial of service (DOS) via a crafted MP4 file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47090 | GPAC MP4box 2.1-DEV-rev574-g9d5bb184b contains a buffer overflow in gf_vvc_read_pps_bs_internal function of media_tools/av_parsers.c, check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47090</link><description>GPAC MP4box 2.1-DEV-rev574-g9d5bb184b contains a buffer overflow in gf_vvc_read_pps_bs_internal function of media_tools/av_parsers.c, check needed for num_exp_tile_columns</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10324 | RomethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10324</link><description>The RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the register_controls function in widgets/offcanvas-rometheme.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11913 | Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11913</link><description>The Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 via the 'ajax_preview_link' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41739 | IBM Cognos Dashboards on Cloud Pak for Data privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41739</link><description>IBM Cognos Dashboards 4.0.7 and 5.0.0 on Cloud Pak for Data could allow a remote attacker to perform unauthorized actions due to dependency confusion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13335 | Sastra Essential Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons, Widgets and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Spexo Theme Install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13335</link><description>The Spexo Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons, Widgets and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the tmpcoder_theme_install_func() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install a theme.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13354 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13354</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML tags in several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13408 | Post Grid, Slider &amp;amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor Widget &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13408</link><description>The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.10 via the 'theme' attribute of the `pgcu` shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php files can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13409 | Post Grid, Slider &amp;amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor Widget &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via post_type_ajax_handler()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13409</link><description>The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.10 via the 'theme' parameter of the post_type_ajax_handler() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13542 | WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp;amp; Google maps + Local SEO &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13542</link><description>The WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp; Google maps + Local SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpgsv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13572 | Precious Metals Charts and Widgets for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13572</link><description>The Precious Metals Charts and Widgets for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'nfusion-widget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13594 | Simple Downloads List &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13594</link><description>The Simple Downloads List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'category' attribute of the 'neofix_sdl' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22714 | WordPress MDJM Event Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22714</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MDJM MDJM Event Management allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MDJM Event Management: from n/a through 1.7.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23422 | WordPress Store Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.98.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23422</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound Store Locator allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Store Locator: from n/a through 3.98.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23427 | WordPress Redux Converter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23427</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dovy Paukstys Redux Converter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Redux Converter: from n/a through 1.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23522 | WordPress HM Portfolio plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23522</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in humanmade limited, Joe Hoyle, Tom Wilmott, Matthew Haines-Young HM Portfolio allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects HM Portfolio: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23621 | WordPress Causes – Donation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.01 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23621</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Causes – Donation Plugin allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Causes – Donation Plugin: from n/a through 1.0.01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23622 | WordPress CBX Accounting &amp;amp; Bookkeeping plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23622</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound CBX Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CBX Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping: from n/a through 1.3.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23711 | WordPress Quote me plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23711</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Quote me allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Quote me: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23734 | WordPress Gigaom Sphinx plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23734</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Gigaom Sphinx allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Gigaom Sphinx: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23737 | WordPress Network-Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Network-Favorites allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Network-Favorites: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23837 | WordPress One Backend Language Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23837</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound One Backend Language allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects One Backend Language: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23838 | WordPress Bauernregeln Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23838</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Bauernregeln allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bauernregeln: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23839 | WordPress Sticky Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23839</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Sticky Button allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sticky Button: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23885 | WordPress MJ Contact us Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MJ Contact us allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MJ Contact us: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23888 | WordPress Custom Page Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23888</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Custom Page Extensions allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Page Extensions: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23889 | WordPress FooGallery Captions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FooGallery Captions allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FooGallery Captions: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12494 | BMLT Meeting Map &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12494</link><description>The BMLT Meeting Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bmlt_meeting_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13583 | Simple Gallery with Filter &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13583</link><description>The Simple Gallery with Filter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'c2tw_sgwf' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13545 | Bootstrap Ultimate &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Unauthenticated Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13545</link><description>The Bootstrap Ultimate theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9 via the path parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included. If php://filter is enabled on the server, this issue may directly lead to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13680 | Form Builder CP &amp;lt;= 1.2.41 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13680</link><description>The Form Builder CP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'CP_EASY_FORM_WILL_APPEAR_HERE' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.41 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13683 | Automate Hub Free by Sperse.IO &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Activation Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13683</link><description>The Automate Hub Free by Sperse.IO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'automate_hub' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update an activation status via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13659 | Listamester &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13659</link><description>The Listamester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'listamester' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11931 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11931</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.6.4, from 17.7 prior to 17.7.3, and from 17.8 prior to 17.8.1. Under certain conditions, it may have been possible for users with developer role to exfiltrate protected CI variables via CI lint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0314 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0314</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.2 before 17.6.4, 17.7 before 17.7.3, and 17.8 before 17.8.1. Improper rendering of certain file types lead to cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 02:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>