<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-36448 | Apache IoTDB Workbench: SSRF Vulnerability (EOL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36448</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Apache IoTDB Workbench.

This issue affects Apache IoTDB Workbench: from 0.13.0.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38856 | Apache OFBiz: Unauthenticated endpoint could allow execution of screen rendering code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38856</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache OFBiz.

This issue affects Apache OFBiz: through 18.12.14.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.15, which fixes the issue.

Unauthenticated endpoints could allow execution of screen rendering code of screens if some preconditions are met (such as when the screen definitions don't explicitly check user's permissions because they rely on the configuration of their endpoints).</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42447 | Apache Airflow Providers FAB: FAB provider 1.2.1 and 1.2.0 did not let user to logout for Airflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42447</link><description>Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability in Apache Airflow Providers FAB.

This issue affects Apache Airflow Providers FAB: 1.2.1 (when used with Apache Airflow 2.9.3) and FAB 1.2.0 for all Airflow versions. The FAB provider prevented the user from logging out.  

* FAB provider 1.2.1 only affected Airflow 2.9.3 (earlier and later versions of Airflow are not affected)

* FAB provider 1.2.0 affected all versions of Airflow.

Users who run Apache Airflow 2.9.3 are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow Providers FAB version 1.2.2 which fixes the issue.

Users who run Any Apache Airflow version and have FAB provider 1.2.0 are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow Providers FAB version 1.2.2 which fixes the issue.

Also upgrading Apache Airflow to latest version available is recommended.

Note: Early version of Airflow reference container images of Airflow 2.9.3 and constraint files contained FAB provider 1.2.1 version, but this is fixed in updated versions of the images. 

Users are advised to pull the latest Airflow images or reinstall FAB provider according to the current constraints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 08:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2232 | Himer - Social Questions and Answers &amp;lt; 2.1.3 - CSRF While Sending the Invites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2232</link><description>The  lacks CSRF checks allowing a user to invite any user to any group (including private groups)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3636 | Pinpoint Booking System &amp;lt; 2.9.9.4.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3636</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System  WordPress plugin before 2.9.9.4.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5081 | WP eMember &amp;lt;= v10.7.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5081</link><description>The wp-eMember WordPress plugin before v10.7.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6270 | Community Events &amp;lt; 1.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6270</link><description>The Community Events WordPress plugin before 1.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6498 | CollectChat &amp;lt; 2.4.4 - Admin+ XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6498</link><description>The Chatbot for WordPress by Collect.chat ⚡️ WordPress plugin before 2.4.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6710 | Ditty &amp;lt; 3.1.45 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6710</link><description>The Ditty  WordPress plugin before 3.1.45 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39838 | ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a network-adjacent attacker with an admin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39838</link><description>ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to alter the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41720 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15, which may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41720</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in ZWX-2000CSW2-HN firmware versions prior to Ver.0.3.15, which may allow a network-adjacent authenticated attacker to alter the configuration of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41889 | Multiple Pimax products accept WebSocket connections from unintended endpoints. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41889</link><description>Multiple Pimax products accept WebSocket connections from unintended endpoints. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39713 | A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) affects Rocket.Chat's Twilio webhook endpoint before version 6.10.1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39713</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) affects Rocket.Chat's Twilio webhook endpoint before version 6.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6117 | Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6117</link><description>A Unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in meeting management function in Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings 2021 allows remote authenticated users to perform arbitrary system commands via a crafted ASP file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6118 | Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings - Plaintext Storage of a Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6118</link><description>A Plaintext Storage of a Password vulnerability in ebooknote function in Hamastar MeetingHub Paperless Meetings 2021 allows remote attackers to obtain the other users’ credentials and gain access to the product via an XML file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7470 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface vpn_template_style.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/vpn_template_style.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273563. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7469 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_vpn_web_custom.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_vpn_web_custom.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7468 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_service_manage.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7468</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_service_manage.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273561 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7467 | Raisecom MSG1200/MSG2100E/MSG2200/MSG2300 Web Interface list_ip_network.php sslvpn_config_mod os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7467</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Raisecom MSG1200, MSG2100E, MSG2200 and MSG2300 3.90 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sslvpn_config_mod of the file /vpn/list_ip_network.php of the component Web Interface. The manipulation of the argument template/stylenum leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273560. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7466 | PMWeb Web Application Firewall cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7466</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PMWeb 7.2.00 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Web Application Firewall. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273559. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7465 | TOTOLINK CP450 cstecgi.cgi loginauth buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7465</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK CP450 4.1.0cu.747_B20191224. Affected is the function loginauth of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument http_host leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273558 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7464 | TOTOLINK CP900 Telnet Service setTelnetCfg command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7464</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This issue affects the function setTelnetCfg of the component Telnet Service. The manipulation of the argument telnet_enabled leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273557 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7463 | TOTOLINK CP900 cstecgi.cgi UploadCustomModule buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7463</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK CP900 6.3c.566. This vulnerability affects the function UploadCustomModule of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument File leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273556. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7462 | TOTOLINK N350RT cstecgi.cgi setWizardCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7462</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. This affects the function setWizardCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ssid leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273555. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:08:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7461 | ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX monitcallcenter authMonitCallcenter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7461</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ForIP Tecnologia Administração PABX 1.x. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /authMonitCallcenter of the component monitcallcenter. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273554 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7460 | OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System change_password.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7460</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System 1.0/2.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /change_password.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273553 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7459 | OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System edit_account.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7459</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OSWAPP Warehouse Inventory System 1.0/2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit_account.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273552.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7458 | elunez eladmin Database Management/Deployment Management upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7458</link><description>A vulnerability was found in elunez eladmin up to 2.7 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/deploy/upload /api/database/upload of the component Database Management/Deployment Management. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: 'dir/../../filename'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273551.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7458 | elunez eladmin Database Management/Deployment Management upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7458</link><description>A vulnerability was found in elunez eladmin up to 2.7 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/deploy/upload /api/database/upload of the component Database Management/Deployment Management. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: 'dir/../../filename'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273551.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35143 | IBM Planning Analytics Local missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35143</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 connects to a MongoDB server. MongoDB, a document-oriented database system, is listening on the remote port, and it is configured to allow connections without password authentication. A remote attacker can gain unauthorized access to the database.  IBM X-Force ID:  292420.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7455 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System partedit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7455</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file partedit.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273549 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7454 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System patients.php patient_name sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7454</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function patient_name of the file patients.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273548.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7453 | FastAdmin Attachment Management Section 4 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7453</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FastAdmin 1.5.0.20240328. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /[admins_url].php/general/attachment/edit/ids/4?dialog=1 of the component Attachment Management Section. The manipulation of the argument row[url]/row[imagewidth]/row[imageheight] leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273544.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7452 | itsourcecode Placement Management System view_company.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7452</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file view_company.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273543.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7451 | itsourcecode Placement Management System apply_now.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7451</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file apply_now.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273542 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7450 | itsourcecode Placement Management System Image resume_upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7450</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /resume_upload.php of the component Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument fileToUpload leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273541 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7449 | itsourcecode Placement Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7449</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273540.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 02:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6331 | Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6331</link><description>stitionai/devika main branch as of commit cdfb782b0e634b773b10963c8034dc9207ba1f9f is vulnerable to Local File Read (LFI) by Prompt Injection. The integration of Google Gimini 1.0 Pro with `HarmBlockThreshold.BLOCK_NONE` for `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HATE_SPEECH` and `HarmCategory.HARM_CATEGORY_HARASSMENT` in `safety_settings` disables content protection. This allows malicious commands to be executed, such as reading sensitive file contents like `/etc/passwd`.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7446 | itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System list_tickets.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7446</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file list_tickets.php. The manipulation of the argument prefSeat_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273531.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 21:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7445 | itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System checkout_ticket_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7445</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file checkout_ticket_save.php. The manipulation of the argument data leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273530 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7444 | itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System Login Page login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7444</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Ticket Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php of the component Login Page. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273529 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7443 | Vivotek IB8367A upload_file.cgi getenv command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7443</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Vivotek IB8367A VVTK-0100b. Affected is the function getenv of the file upload_file.cgi. The manipulation of the argument QUERY_STRING leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273528. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7442 | Vivotek SD9364 upload_file.cgi getenv command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7442</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek SD9364 VVTK-0103f. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function getenv of the file upload_file.cgi. The manipulation of the argument QUERY_STRING leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273527. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7441 | Vivotek SD9364 httpd read stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7441</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek SD9364 VVTK-0103f. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function read of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273526 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7440 | Vivotek CC8160 upload_file.cgi getenv command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7440</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function getenv of the file upload_file.cgi. The manipulation of the argument QUERY_STRING leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-273525 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7439 | Vivotek CC8160 httpd read stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7439</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Vivotek CC8160 VVTK-0100d and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function read of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273524. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: Vendor was contacted early and confirmed that the affected release tree is end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7438 | SimpleMachines SMF User Alert Read Status index.php resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7438</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=read of the component User Alert Read Status Handler. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-273523. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37286 | APM Server Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37286</link><description>APM server logs contain document body from a partially failed bulk index request. For example, in case of unavailable_shards_exception for a specific document, since the ES response line contains the document body, and that APM server logs the ES response line on error, the document is effectively logged.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7437 | SimpleMachines SMF Delete User index.php resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7437</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SimpleMachines SMF 2.1.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php?action=profile;u=2;area=showalerts;do=remove of the component Delete User Handler. The manipulation of the argument aid leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-273522 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7436 | D-Link DI-8100 msp_info.htm msp_info_htm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7436</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07. This issue affects the function msp_info_htm of the file msp_info.htm. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-273521 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38321 | IBM Business Automation Workflow information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38321</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow 22.0.2, 23.0.1, 23.0.2, and 24.0.0 stores potentially sensitive information in log files under certain situations that could be read by an authenticated user.  IBM X-Force ID:  284868.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6709 | Sync Post With Other Site &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Creation and Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6709</link><description>The Sync Post With Other Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'sps_add_update_post' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create new draft posts and update existing posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6872 | Build Your Dream Website Fast with 400+ Starter Templates and Landing Pages, No Coding Needed, One-Click Import for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg Blocks! – TemplateSpare &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6872</link><description>The Build Your Dream Website Fast with 400+ Starter Templates and Landing Pages, No Coding Needed, One-Click Import for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg Blocks! – TemplateSpare plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'templatespare_activate_required_theme' and 'templatespare_get_theme_status' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to activate any installed theme and read any theme status. If the attacker attempts to activate a theme that is not installed, a non-existent theme with the slug chosen by the attacker will be considered the active theme, leaving the site with no theme functionality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7356 | Zephyr Project Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.100 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via filename Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7356</link><description>The Zephyr Project Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘filename’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.100 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7257 | YayExtra – WooCommerce Extra Product Options &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via handle_upload_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7257</link><description>The YayExtra – WooCommerce Extra Product Options plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the handle_upload_file function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7031 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Authenticated Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7031</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'njt_fs_saveSettingRestrictions' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with a role that has been granted permissions by an Administrator, to update the plugin settings for user role restrictions, including allowing file types such as .php to be uploaded.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7291 | JetFormBuilder &amp;lt;= 3.3.4.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7291</link><description>The JetFormBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4.1. This is due to improper restriction on user meta fields. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level and above permissions, to register as super-admins on the sites configured as multi-sites.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6390 | Quiz and Survey Master (QSM) &amp;lt; 9.1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6390</link><description>The Quiz and Survey Master (QSM)  WordPress plugin before 9.1.0 does not properly sanitise and escape some of its Quizz settings, which could allow high privilege users such as contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6477 | UsersWP &amp;lt; 1.2.12 - Users Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6477</link><description>The UsersWP  WordPress plugin before 1.2.12 uses predictable filenames when an admin generates an export, which could allow unauthenticated attackers to download them and retrieve sensitive information such as IP, username, and email address</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>