<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:27:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-47003 | An issue in RedisGraph v.2.12.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted string in DataBloc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47003</link><description>An issue in RedisGraph v.2.12.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service via a crafted string in DataBlock_ItemIsDeleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43275 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 in 110 backend management interface via /catalog_add.php, allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43275</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DedeCMS v5.7 in 110 backend management interface via /catalog_add.php, allows attackers to create crafted web pages due to a lack of verification of the token value of the submitted form.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35437 | SQL injection vulnerability in LMXCMS v.1.4 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the TagsAction.class.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35437</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in LMXCMS v.1.4 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the TagsAction.class.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47471 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in strukturag libde265 v1.10.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the slice_segment_hea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47471</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in strukturag libde265 v1.10.12 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the slice_segment_header function in the slice.cc component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47470 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg before github commit 4565747056a11356210ed8edcecb920105e40b60 allows a remote attacker to achieve an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47470</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg before github commit 4565747056a11356210ed8edcecb920105e40b60 allows a remote attacker to achieve an out-of-array write, execute arbitrary code, and cause a denial of service (DoS) via the ref_pic_list_struct function in libavcodec/evc_ps.c</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47263 | Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service (DoS) in the antivirus engine when scanning a fuzzed PE32 file. This affects WithSecur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47263</link><description>Certain WithSecure products allow a Denial of Service (DoS) in the antivirus engine when scanning a fuzzed PE32 file. This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 15 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47264 | Certain WithSecure products have a buffer over-read whereby processing certain fuzz file types may cause a denial of service (DoS). This aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47264</link><description>Certain WithSecure products have a buffer over-read whereby processing certain fuzz file types may cause a denial of service (DoS). This affects WithSecure Client Security 15, WithSecure Server Security 15, WithSecure Email and Server Security 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection 17 and later, WithSecure Client Security for Mac 15, WithSecure Elements Endpoint Protection for Mac 17 and later, WithSecure Linux Security 64 12.0, WithSecure Linux Protection 12.0, and WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 15 and later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48204 | An issue in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the appToken and Parameters parameter of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48204</link><description>An issue in PublicCMS v.4.0.202302.e allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the appToken and Parameters parameter of the api/method/getHtml component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48199 | An issue in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code funciton in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48199</link><description>An issue in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code funciton in the manageapikeys component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:59:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48198 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48198</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the product description component in the api/stock/products endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48197 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48197</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the QR code function in the manageapikeys component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4689 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4689</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the eae_save_elements function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable/disable elementor addon elements via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4690 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4690</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the eae_save_config function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change configuration settings for the plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4723 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4723</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 via the ajax_eae_post_data function. This can allow unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including post/page ids and titles including  those of with pending/draft/future/private status.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5381 | The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and inc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5381</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in versions up to, and including, 1.12.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48200 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48200</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Grocy v.4.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the equipment description component within /equipment/ component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47347 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP messages whose Sequence Number...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47347</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP messages whose Sequence Number is mutated to overflow bytes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47444 | An issue discovered in OpenCart 4.0.0.0 to 4.0.2.3 allows authenticated backend users having common/security write privilege can write arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47444</link><description>An issue discovered in OpenCart 4.0.0.0 to 4.0.2.3 allows authenticated backend users having common/security write privilege can write arbitrary untrusted data inside config.php and admin/config.php, resulting in remote code execution on the underlying server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47345 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP message with malformed PFCP He...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47345</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in free5gc 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted PFCP message with malformed PFCP Heartbeat message whose Recovery Time Stamp IE length is mutated to zero.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41442 | An issue in Kloudq Technologies Limited Tor Equip 1.0, Tor Loco Mini 1.0 through 3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41442</link><description>An issue in Kloudq Technologies Limited Tor Equip 1.0, Tor Loco Mini 1.0 through 3.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the MQTT component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48365 | Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows before August 2023 Patch 2 allows unauthenticated remote code execution, aka QB-21683. Due to improper val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48365</link><description>Qlik Sense Enterprise for Windows before August 2023 Patch 2 allows unauthenticated remote code execution, aka QB-21683. Due to improper validation of HTTP headers, a remote attacker is able to elevate their privilege by tunneling HTTP requests, allowing them to execute HTTP requests on the backend server that hosts the repository application. The fixed versions are August 2023 Patch 2, May 2023 Patch 6, February 2023 Patch 10, November 2022 Patch 12, August 2022 Patch 14, May 2022 Patch 16, February 2022 Patch 15, and November 2021 Patch 17. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-41265.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48224 | Cryptographically Weak Generation of One-Time Codes for Identity Verification in ethyca-fides</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48224</link><description>Fides is an open-source privacy engineering platform for managing the fulfillment of data privacy requests in a runtime environment, and the enforcement of privacy regulations in code. The Fides Privacy Center allows data subject users to submit privacy and consent requests to data controller users of the Fides web application. Privacy requests allow data subjects to submit a request to access all person data held by the data controller, or delete/erase it.  Consent request allows data subject users to modify their privacy preferences for how the data controller uses their personal data e.g. data sales and sharing consent opt-in/opt-out. If `subject_identity_verification_required` in the `[execution]` section of `fides.toml` or the env var `FIDES__EXECUTION__SUBJECT_IDENTITY_VERIFICATION_REQUIRED` is set to `True` on the fides webserver backend, data subjects are sent a one-time code to their email address or phone number, depending on messaging configuration, and the one-time code must be entered in the Privacy Center UI by the data subject before the privacy or consent request is submitted. It was identified that the one-time code values for these requests were generated by the python `random` module, a cryptographically weak pseduo-random number generator (PNRG). If an attacker generates several hundred consecutive one-time codes, this vulnerability allows the attacker to predict all future one-time code values during the lifetime of the backend python process. There is no security impact on data access requests as the personal data download package is not shared in the Privacy Center itself. However, this vulnerability allows an attacker to (i) submit a verified data erasure request, resulting in deletion of data for the targeted user and (ii) submit a verified consent request, modifying a user's privacy preferences. The vulnerability has been patched in Fides version `2.24.0`. Users are advised to upgrade to this version or later to secure their systems against this threat. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6105 | ManageEngine Information Disclosure in Multiple Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6105</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability exists in multiple ManageEngine products that can result in encryption keys being exposed. A low-privileged OS user with access to the host where an affected ManageEngine product is installed can view and use the exposed key to decrypt product database passwords. This allows the user to access the ManageEngine product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 21:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22818 | Multiple DLL Search Order hijacking Vulnerabilities in SanDisk Security Installer for Windows </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22818</link><description>Multiple DLL Search Order Hijack vulnerabilities were addressed in the SanDisk Security Installer for
Windows that could allow attackers with local access to execute arbitrary code by executing the installer
in the same folder as the malicious DLL. This can lead to the execution of arbitrary
code with the privileges of the vulnerable application or obtain a certain level of persistence
on the compromised host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 20:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41699 | Payara Platform: URL Redirection to untrusted site using FORM authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41699</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server, Micro and Embedded (Servlet Implementation modules) allows Redirect Access to Libraries.This issue affects Payara Server, Micro and Embedded: from 5.0.0 before 5.57.0, from 4.1.2.191 before 4.1.2.191.46, from 6.0.0 before 6.8.0, from 6.2023.1 before 6.2023.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30954 | Gotham Video Broken Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30954</link><description>The Gotham video-application-server service contained a race condition which would cause it to not apply certain acls new videos if the source system had not yet initialized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47636 | Full Path Disclosure via re-export document in pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47636</link><description>The Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. Full Path Disclosure (FPD) vulnerabilities enable the attacker to see the path to the webroot/file. e.g.: /home/omg/htdocs/file/. Certain vulnerabilities, such as using the load_file() (within a SQL Injection) query to view the page source, require the attacker to have the full path to the file they wish to view. In the case of pimcore, the fopen() function here doesn't have an error handle when the file doesn't exist on the server so the server response raises the full path "fopen(/var/www/html/var/tmp/export-{ uniqe id}.csv)". This issue has been patched in commit `10d178ef771` which has been included in release version 1.2.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47637 | SQL Injection in Admin Grid Filter API in Pimcore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47637</link><description>Pimcore is an Open Source Data &amp; Experience Management Platform. In affected versions the `/admin/object/grid-proxy` endpoint calls `getFilterCondition()` on fields of classes to be filtered for, passing input from the request, and later executes the returned SQL.  One implementation of `getFilterCondition()` is in `Multiselect`, which does not normalize/escape/validate the passed value. Any backend user with very basic permissions can execute arbitrary SQL statements and thus alter any data or escalate their privileges to at least admin level. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 11.1.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48011 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the flush_ref_samples function at /gpac/src/isome...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48011</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a heap-use-after-free via the flush_ref_samples function at /gpac/src/isomedia/movie_fragments.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48013 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a double free via the gf_filterpacket_del function at /gpac/src/filter_core...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48013</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a double free via the gf_filterpacket_del function at /gpac/src/filter_core/filter.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48014 | GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the hevc_parse_vps_extension function at /media_tools/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48014</link><description>GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev566-g50c2ab06f-master was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the hevc_parse_vps_extension function at /media_tools/av_parsers.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48219 | Special characters in unescaped text nodes can trigger mXSS in TinyMCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48219</link><description>TinyMCE is an open source rich text editor. A mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS) vulnerability was discovered in TinyMCE’s core undo/redo functionality and other APIs and plugins. Text nodes within specific parents are not escaped upon serialization according to the HTML standard. If such text nodes contain a special character reserved as an internal marker, they can be combined with other HTML patterns to form malicious snippets. These snippets pass the initial sanitisation layer when the content is parsed into the editor body, but can trigger XSS when the special internal marker is removed from the content and re-parsed. his vulnerability has been patched in TinyMCE versions 6.7.3 and 5.10.9. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5997 | Use after free in Garbage Collection in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrupti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5997</link><description>Use after free in Garbage Collection in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:28:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6112 | Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6112</link><description>Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 119.0.6045.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34982 | AVEVA Operations Control Logger External Control of File Name or Path </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34982</link><description>This external control vulnerability, if exploited, could allow a local OS-authenticated user with standard privileges to delete files with System privilege on the machine where these products are installed, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33873 | AVEVA Operations Control Logger Execution with Unnecessary Privileges </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33873</link><description>This privilege escalation vulnerability, if exploited, cloud allow a local OS-authenticated user with standard privileges to escalate to System privilege on the machine where these products are installed, resulting in complete compromise of the target machine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48087 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/clearLog and /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailCat.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48087</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/clearLog and /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailCat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48088 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailPage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48088</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /xxl-job-admin/joblog/logDetailPage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48089 | xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via /xxl-job-admin/jobcode/save.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48089</link><description>xxl-job-admin 2.4.0 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via /xxl-job-admin/jobcode/save.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:03:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5676 | Eclipse OpenJ9 possible infinite busy hang</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5676</link><description>In Eclipse OpenJ9 before version 0.41.0, the JVM can be forced into an infinite busy hang on a spinlock or a segmentation fault if a shutdown signal (SIGTERM, SIGINT or SIGHUP) is received before the JVM has finished initializing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5720 | Quarkus: build env information disclosure via gradle plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5720</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus, where it does not properly sanitize artifacts created using the Gradle plugin, allowing certain build system information to remain. This flaw allows an attacker to access potentially sensitive information from the build system within the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4602 | The Namaste! LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'course_id'  parameter in versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4602</link><description>The Namaste! LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'course_id'  parameter in versions up to, and including, 2.6.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5245 | Using MLeap for loading a saved model (zip archive) can lead to path traversal/arbitrary file creation and possibly remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5245</link><description>FileUtil.extract() enumerates all zip file entries and extracts each file without validating whether file paths in the archive are outside the intended directory.

When creating an instance of TensorflowModel using the saved_model format and an exported tensorflow model, the apply() function invokes the vulnerable implementation of FileUtil.extract().

Arbitrary file creation can directly lead to code execution</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:56:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23549 | DoS via long hostnames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23549</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Checkmk &lt;2.2.0p15, &lt;2.1.0p37, &lt;=2.0.0p39 allows priviledged attackers to cause partial denial of service of the UI via too long hostnames.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34062 | In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, a malicious user can send a request using a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34062</link><description>In Reactor Netty HTTP Server, versions 1.1.x prior to 1.1.13 and versions 1.0.x prior to 1.0.39, a malicious user can send a request using a specially crafted URL that can lead to a directory traversal attack.

Specifically, an application is vulnerable if Reactor Netty HTTP Server is configured to serve static resources.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 09:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46672 | Logstash Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46672</link><description>An issue was identified by Elastic whereby sensitive information is recorded in Logstash logs under specific circumstances.

The prerequisites for the manifestation of this issue are:

  *  Logstash  is configured to log in JSON format https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/logstash/current/running-logstash-command-line.html , which is not the default logging format.


  *  Sensitive data is stored in the Logstash keystore and referenced as a variable in Logstash configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4889 | The Shareaholic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shareaholic' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4889</link><description>The Shareaholic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'shareaholic' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 9.7.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6133 | The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient blacklisting on the 'forminator_allowed_mime...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6133</link><description>The Forminator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient blacklisting on the 'forminator_allowed_mime_types' function in versions up to, and including, 1.27.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server, but due to the htaccess configuration, remote code cannot be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47584 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47584</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47585 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47585</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47586 | Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47586</link><description>Multiple heap-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities exist in V-Server V4.0.18.0 and earlier and V-Server Lite V4.0.18.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted VPR file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41597 | EyouCms v1.6.2 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/twitter.php?active_t.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41597</link><description>EyouCms v1.6.2 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin/twitter.php?active_t.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47446 | Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the profile.php page via fullname parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47446</link><description>Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) on the profile.php page via fullname parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47580 | Multiple improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer issues exist in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47580</link><description>Multiple improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer issues exist in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47581 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47581</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47582 | Access of uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47582</link><description>Access of uninitialized pointer vulnerability exists in TELLUS V4.0.17.0 and earlier and TELLUS Lite V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1, V8, or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47583 | Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in TELLUS Simulator V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1 or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47583</link><description>Multiple out-of-bounds read vulnerabilities exist in TELLUS Simulator V4.0.17.0 and earlier. If a user opens a specially crafted file (X1 or V9 file), information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47445 | Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the username parameter in preschool/admin/ page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47445</link><description>Pre-School Enrollment version 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the username parameter in preschool/admin/ page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40923 | MyPrestaModules ordersexport before v5.0 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at send.php via the key and save_s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40923</link><description>MyPrestaModules ordersexport before v5.0 was discovered to contain multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities at send.php via the key and save_setting parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6032 | A CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal')
vulnerability exists that could cause a file system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6032</link><description>A CWE-22: Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal')
vulnerability exists that could cause a file system enumeration and file download when an
attacker navigates to the Network Management Card via HTTPS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5987 | A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (Cross-site Scripting)
vulnerability that could cause a vulnerability l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5987</link><description>A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (Cross-site Scripting)
vulnerability that could cause a vulnerability leading to a cross site scripting condition where
attackers can have a victim’s browser run arbitrary JavaScript when they visit a page containing
the injected payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5986 | A CWE-601 URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerability exists that could cause an openredirect vulnerability leading to a cross site scri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5986</link><description>A CWE-601 URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerability exists that could cause an openredirect vulnerability leading to a cross site scripting attack. By providing a URL-encoded input
attackers can cause the software’s web application to redirect to the chosen domain after a
successful login is performed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5984 | A CWE-494 Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could allow
modified firmware to be uploaded when an authorized...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5984</link><description>A CWE-494 Download of Code Without Integrity Check vulnerability exists that could allow
modified firmware to be uploaded when an authorized admin user begins a firmware update
procedure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5985 | A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability
exists that could cause compromise of a user’s browser wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5985</link><description>A CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability
exists that could cause compromise of a user’s browser when an attacker with admin privileges
has modified system values.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47678 | An improper access control vulnerability exists in RT-AC87U all versions. An attacker may read or write files that are not intended to be ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47678</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in RT-AC87U all versions. An attacker may read or write files that are not intended to be accessed by connecting to a target device via tftp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47308 | In the module "Newsletter Popup PRO with Voucher/Coupon code" (newsletterpop) before version 2.6.1 from Active Design for PrestaShop, a gues...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47308</link><description>In the module "Newsletter Popup PRO with Voucher/Coupon code" (newsletterpop) before version 2.6.1 from Active Design for PrestaShop, a guest can perform SQL injection in affected versions. The method `NewsletterpopsendVerificationModuleFrontController::checkEmailSubscription()` has sensitive SQL calls that can be executed with a trivial http call and exploited to forge a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47309 | Nukium nkmgls before version 3.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via NkmGlsCheckoutModuleFrontController::displayAjaxSavePhone...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47309</link><description>Nukium nkmgls before version 3.0.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via NkmGlsCheckoutModuleFrontController::displayAjaxSavePhoneMobile.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43979 | ETS Soft ybc_blog before v4.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Ybc_blogBlogModuleFrontController:...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43979</link><description>ETS Soft ybc_blog before v4.4.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Ybc_blogBlogModuleFrontController::getPosts().</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46121 | Generic Extractor MITM Vulnerability in yt-dlp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46121</link><description>yt-dlp is a youtube-dl fork with additional features and fixes. The Generic Extractor in yt-dlp is vulnerable to an attacker setting an arbitrary proxy for a request to an arbitrary url, allowing the attacker to MITM the request made from yt-dlp's HTTP session. This could lead to cookie exfiltration in some cases. Version 2023.11.14 removed the ability to smuggle `http_headers` to the Generic extractor, as well as other extractors that use the same pattern. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable the Ggneric extractor (or only pass trusted sites with trusted content) and ake caution when using `--no-check-certificate`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31100 | Improper Access Control in SMI handler vulnerability in Phoenix SecureCore™ Technology™ 4 allows SPI flash modification.
This issue affects ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31100</link><description>Improper Access Control in SMI handler vulnerability in Phoenix SecureCore™ Technology™ 4 allows SPI flash modification.
This issue affects SecureCore™ Technology™ 4:


  *  from 4.3.0.0 before 4.3.0.203
  *  

from 

4.3.1.0 before 4.3.1.163
  *  

from 

4.4.0.0 before 4.4.0.217
  *  

from 

4.5.0.0 before 4.5.0.138</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35080 | A vulnerability has been identified in the Ivanti Secure Access Windows client, which could allow a locally authenticated attacker to exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35080</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Ivanti Secure Access Windows client, which could allow a locally authenticated attacker to exploit a vulnerable configuration, potentially leading to various security risks, including the escalation of privileges, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38043 | When a specific component is loaded a local attacker and is able to send a specially crafted request to this component, the attacker could g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38043</link><description>When a specific component is loaded a local attacker and is able to send a specially crafted request to this component, the attacker could gain elevated privileges on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38543 | When a specific component is loaded a local attacker and is able to send a specially crafted request to this component, the attacker could g...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38543</link><description>When a specific component is loaded a local attacker and is able to send a specially crafted request to this component, the attacker could gain elevated privileges on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38544 | A logged in user can modify specific files that may lead to unauthorized changes in system-wide configuration settings. This vulnerability c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38544</link><description>A logged in user can modify specific files that may lead to unauthorized changes in system-wide configuration settings. This vulnerability could be exploited to compromise the integrity and security of the network on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39335 | A security vulnerability has been identified in EPMM Versions 11.10, 11.9 and 11.8 and older allowing an unauthenticated threat actor to imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39335</link><description>A security vulnerability has been identified in EPMM Versions 11.10, 11.9 and 11.8 and older allowing an unauthenticated threat actor to impersonate any existing user during the device enrollment process. This issue poses a significant security risk, as it enables unauthorized access and potential misuse of user accounts and resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39337 | A security vulnerability in EPMM Versions 11.10, 11.9 and 11.8 older allows a threat actor with knowledge of an enrolled device identifier t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39337</link><description>A security vulnerability in EPMM Versions 11.10, 11.9 and 11.8 older allows a threat actor with knowledge of an enrolled device identifier to access and extract sensitive information, including device and environment configuration details, as well as secrets. This vulnerability poses a serious security risk, potentially exposing confidential data and system integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41718 | When a particular process flow is initiated, an attacker may be able to gain unauthorized elevated privileges on the affected system when ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41718</link><description>When a particular process flow is initiated, an attacker may be able to gain unauthorized elevated privileges on the affected system when having control over a specific file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43582 | Improper authorization in some Zoom clients may allow an authorized user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43582</link><description>Improper authorization in some Zoom clients may allow an authorized user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43588 | Insufficient control flow management in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct an information disclosure via network a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43588</link><description>Insufficient control flow management in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43590 | Link following  in Zoom Rooms for macOS before version 5.16.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43590</link><description>Link following  in Zoom Rooms for macOS before version 5.16.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43591 | Improper privilege management  in Zoom Rooms for macOS before version 5.16.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43591</link><description>Improper privilege management  in Zoom Rooms for macOS before version 5.16.0 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39199 | Cryptographic issues with In-Meeting Chat for some Zoom clients may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39199</link><description>Cryptographic issues with In-Meeting Chat for some Zoom clients may allow a privileged user to conduct an information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39206 | Buffer overflow in some Zoom clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39206</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45623 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the Wi-Fi Uplink service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45623</link><description>Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the Wi-Fi Uplink service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45624 | An unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the soft ap daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45624</link><description>An unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the soft ap daemon accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45625 | Multiple authenticated command injection vulnerabilities exist in the command line interface. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabiliti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45625</link><description>Multiple authenticated command injection vulnerabilities exist in the command line interface. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45626 | An authenticated vulnerability has been identified allowing an attacker to effectively establish highly privileged persistent arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45626</link><description>An authenticated vulnerability has been identified allowing an attacker to effectively establish highly privileged persistent arbitrary code execution across boot cycles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45627 | An authenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the CLI service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45627</link><description>An authenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability exists in the CLI service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to interrupt the normal

operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5189 | Ansible automation hub: insecure galaxy-importer tarfile extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5189</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in Ansible when extracting tarballs. An attacker could craft a malicious tarball so that when using the galaxy importer of Ansible Automation Hub, a symlink could be dropped on the disk, resulting in files being overwritten.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45618 | There are arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities in the AirWave client service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol)....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45618</link><description>There are arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities in the AirWave client service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to delete arbitrary files on the underlying operating system, which could lead to the ability to interrupt normal operation and impact the integrity of the access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45619 | There is an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the RSSI service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol). Successfu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45619</link><description>There is an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the RSSI service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol). Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to delete arbitrary files on the underlying operating system, which could lead to the ability to interrupt normal operation and impact the integrity of the access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45620 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the CLI service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45620</link><description>Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the CLI service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45621 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the CLI service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45621</link><description>Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the CLI service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45622 | Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the BLE daemon service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45622</link><description>Unauthenticated Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerabilities exist in the BLE daemon service accessed via the PAPI protocol. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to interrupt the normal operation of the affected access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45615 | There are buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45615</link><description>There are buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45616 | There is a buffer overflow vulnerability in the underlying AirWave client service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45616</link><description>There is a buffer overflow vulnerability in the underlying AirWave client service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45617 | There are arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities in the CLI service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol). Successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45617</link><description>There are arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities in the CLI service accessed by PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to delete arbitrary files on the underlying operating system, which could lead to the ability to interrupt normal operation and impact the integrity of the access point.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45614 | There are buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45614</link><description>There are buffer overflow vulnerabilities in the underlying CLI service that could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution by sending specially crafted packets destined to the PAPI (Aruba's access point management protocol) UDP port (8211). Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities result in the ability to execute arbitrary code as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:49:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39204 | Buffer overflow in some Zoom clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39204</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Zoom clients may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39205 | Improper conditions check in Zoom Team Chat for Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39205</link><description>Improper conditions check in Zoom Team Chat for Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39203 | Uncontrolled resource consumption in Zoom Team Chat for Zoom Desktop Client for Windows and Zoom VDI Client may allow an unauthenticated use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39203</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in Zoom Team Chat for Zoom Desktop Client for Windows and Zoom VDI Client may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39202 | Untrusted search path in Zoom Rooms Client for Windows and Zoom VDI Client may allow a privileged user to conduct a denial of service via lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39202</link><description>Untrusted search path in Zoom Rooms Client for Windows and Zoom VDI Client may allow a privileged user to conduct a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41570 | MikroTik RouterOS v7.1 to 7.11 was discovered to contain incorrect access control mechanisms in place for the Rest API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41570</link><description>MikroTik RouterOS v7.1 to 7.11 was discovered to contain incorrect access control mechanisms in place for the Rest API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47517 | WordPress SendPress Newsletters Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.23.11.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47517</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SendPress Newsletters plugin &lt;= 1.23.11.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47518 | WordPress Restrict Categories Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47518</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Matthew Muro Restrict Categories plugin &lt;= 2.6.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46581 | SQL injection vulnerability in Inventory Management v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the name, uname and email pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46581</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Inventory Management v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the name, uname and email parameters in the registration.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46582 | SQL injection vulnerability in Inventory Management v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id paramter in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46582</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Inventory Management v.1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id paramter in the deleteProduct.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46580 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Inventory Management V1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the pname parameter of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46580</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Inventory Management V1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the pname parameter of the editProduct.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46025 | SQL Injection vulnerability in teacher-info.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to obtain se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46025</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in teacher-info.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the 'editid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46026 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in profile.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46026</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in profile.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the 'adminname' and 'email' parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47520 | WordPress Responsive Column Widgets Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47520</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Michael Uno (miunosoft) Responsive Column Widgets plugin &lt;= 1.2.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36038 | ASP.NET Core Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36038</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36558 | ASP.NET Core - Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36558</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46024 | SQL Injection vulnerability in index.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46024</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in index.php in phpgurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands and obtain sensitive information via the 'searchdata' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47522 | WordPress Photo Feed Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47522</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Photo Feed plugin &lt;= 2.2.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48217 | Remote code execution via form uploads in statamic/cms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48217</link><description>Statamic is a flat-first, Laravel + Git powered CMS designed for building websites. In affected versions certain additional PHP files crafted to look like images may be uploaded regardless of mime type validation rules. This affects front-end forms using the "Forms" feature, and asset upload fields in the control panel. Malicious users could leverage this vulnerability to upload and execute code. This issue has been patched in versions 3.4.14 and 4.34.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46023 | SQL injection vulnerability in addTask.php in Code-Projects Simple Task List 1.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the 's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46023</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in addTask.php in Code-Projects Simple Task List 1.0 allows attackers to obtain sensitive information via the 'status' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47524 | WordPress CodeBard&amp;#x27;s Patron Button and Widgets for Patreon Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47524</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability (requires PHP 8.x) in CodeBard CodeBard's Patron Button and Widgets for Patreon plugin &lt;= 2.1.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39535 | Improper input validation in BIOS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39535</link><description>AMI AptioV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an Attacker may use an improper input validation via the local network. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39536 | Improper input validation in BIOS OFBD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39536</link><description>AMI AptioV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an Attacker may use an improper input validation via the local network. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39537 | Improper input validation in BIOS TCG2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39537</link><description>AMI AptioV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an Attacker may use an improper input validation via the local network. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46022 | SQL Injection vulnerability in delete.php in Code-Projects Blood Bank 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the 'bid' param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46022</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in delete.php in Code-Projects Blood Bank 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the 'bid' parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47528 | WordPress WP Edit Username Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47528</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sajjad Hossain Sagor WP Edit Username plugin &lt;= 1.0.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45781 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1_2994 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45781</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1_2994 and earlier allows attackers to run arbitrary code via /goform/SetOnlineDevName.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47532 | WordPress WP Crowdfunding Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47532</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Themeum WP Crowdfunding plugin &lt;= 2.1.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47533 | WordPress Countdown and CountUp, WooCommerce Sales Timer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47533</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in wpdevart Countdown and CountUp, WooCommerce Sales Timer plugin &lt;= 1.8.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47631 | vantage6 Node accepts non-whitelisted algorithms from malicious server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47631</link><description>vantage6 is a framework to manage and deploy privacy enhancing technologies like Federated Learning (FL) and Multi-Party Computation (MPC). In affected versions a node does not check if an image is allowed to run if a `parent_id` is set. A malicious party that breaches the server may modify it to set a fake `parent_id` and send a task of a non-whitelisted algorithm. The node will then execute it because the `parent_id` that is set prevents checks from being run. This impacts all servers that are breached by an expert user. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.1.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47544 | WordPress Atarim Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47544</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Atarim Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp; Project Management – Atarim plugin &lt;= 3.12 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47630 | Attacker can cause Kyverno user to unintentionally consume insecure image</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47630</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for Kubernetes. An issue was found in Kyverno that allowed an attacker to control the digest of images used by Kyverno users. The issue would require the attacker to compromise the registry that the Kyverno users fetch their images from. The attacker could then return an vulnerable image to the the user and leverage that to further escalate their position. As such, the attacker would need to know which images the Kyverno user consumes and know of one of multiple exploitable vulnerabilities in previous digests of the images. Alternatively, if the attacker has compromised the registry, they could craft a malicious image with a different digest with intentionally placed vulnerabilities and deliver the image to the user.  Users pulling their images by digests and from trusted registries are not impacted by this vulnerability. There is no evidence of this being exploited in the wild. The issue has been patched in 1.10.5. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47545 | WordPress Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47545</link><description>Auth. (editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Fatcat Apps Forms for Mailchimp by Optin Cat – Grow Your MailChimp List plugin &lt;= 2.5.4 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47640 | Insecure Use of HMAC-SHA1 For Session Signing in datahub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47640</link><description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. The HMAC signature for DataHub Frontend sessions was being signed using a SHA-1 HMAC with the frontend secret key. SHA1 with a 10 byte key can be brute forced using sufficient resources (i.e. state level actors with large computational capabilities). DataHub Frontend was utilizing the Play LegacyCookiesModule with default settings which utilizes a SHA1 HMAC for signing. This is compounded by using a shorter key length than recommended by default for the signing key for the randomized secret value. An authenticated attacker (or attacker who has otherwise obtained a session token) could crack the signing key for DataHub and obtain escalated privileges by generating a privileged session cookie. Due to key length being a part of the risk, deployments should update to the latest helm chart and rotate their session signing secret. All deployments using the default helm chart configurations for generating the Play secret key used for signing are affected by this vulnerability. Version 0.11.1 resolves this vulnerability. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 21:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47546 | WordPress OneClick Chat to Order Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47546</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Walter Pinem OneClick Chat to Order plugin &lt;= 1.0.4.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47547 | WordPress Products, Order &amp;amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47547</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WPFactory Products, Order &amp; Customers Export for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 2.0.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47627 | Request smuggling in aiohttp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47627</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. The HTTP parser in AIOHTTP has numerous problems with header parsing, which could lead to request smuggling. This parser is only used when AIOHTTP_NO_EXTENSIONS is enabled (or not using a prebuilt wheel). These bugs have been addressed in commit `d5c12ba89` which has been included in release version 3.8.6. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for these issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47549 | WordPress EazyDocs Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47549</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability on 302 response page in spider-themes EazyDocs plugin &lt;= 2.3.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47641 | Inconsistent interpretation of `Content-Length` vs. `Transfer-Encoding` in aiohttp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47641</link><description>aiohttp is an asynchronous HTTP client/server framework for asyncio and Python. Affected versions of aiohttp have a security vulnerability regarding the inconsistent interpretation of the http protocol. HTTP/1.1 is a persistent protocol, if both Content-Length(CL) and Transfer-Encoding(TE) header values are present it can lead to incorrect interpretation of two entities that parse the HTTP and we can poison other sockets with this incorrect interpretation. A possible Proof-of-Concept (POC) would be a configuration with a reverse proxy(frontend) that accepts both CL and TE headers and aiohttp as backend. As aiohttp parses anything with chunked, we can pass a chunked123 as TE, the frontend entity will ignore this header and will parse Content-Length. The impact of this vulnerability is that it is possible to bypass any proxy rule, poisoning sockets to other users like passing Authentication Headers, also if it is present an Open Redirect an attacker could combine it to redirect random users to another website and log the request. This vulnerability has been addressed in release 3.8.0 of aiohttp. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47130 | Unsafe deserialization of user data in yiisoft/yii</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47130</link><description>Yii is an open source PHP web framework. yiisoft/yii before version 1.1.29 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) if the application calls `unserialize()` on arbitrary user input. An attacker may leverage this vulnerability to compromise the host system. A fix has been developed for the 1.1.29 release. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5528 | Kubernetes - Windows nodes - Insufficient input sanitization in in-tree storage plugin leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5528</link><description>A security issue was discovered in Kubernetes where a user that can create pods and persistent volumes on Windows nodes may be able to escalate to admin privileges on those nodes. Kubernetes clusters are only affected if they are using an in-tree storage plugin for Windows nodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46132 | Crosslinking transaction attack in hyperledger/fabric</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46132</link><description>Hyperledger Fabric is an open source permissioned distributed ledger framework. Combining two molecules to one another, called "cross-linking" results in a molecule with a chemical formula that is composed of all atoms of the original two molecules. In Fabric, one can take a block of transactions and cross-link the transactions in a way that alters the way the peers parse the transactions. If a first peer receives a block B and a second peer receives a block identical to B but with the transactions being cross-linked, the second peer will parse transactions in a different way and thus its world state will deviate from the first peer. Orderers or peers cannot detect that a block has its transactions cross-linked, because there is a vulnerability in the way Fabric hashes the transactions of blocks. It simply and naively concatenates them, which is insecure and lets an adversary craft a "cross-linked block" (block with cross-linked transactions) which alters the way peers process transactions. For example, it is possible to select a transaction and manipulate a peer to completely avoid processing it, without changing the computed hash of the block. Additional validations have been added in v2.2.14 and v2.5.5 to detect potential cross-linking issues before processing blocks. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34060 | VMware Cloud Director Appliance contains an authentication bypass vulnerability in case VMware Cloud Director Appliance was upgraded to 10.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34060</link><description>VMware Cloud Director Appliance contains an authentication bypass vulnerability in case VMware Cloud Director Appliance was upgraded to 10.5 from
an older version. On an upgraded version of VMware Cloud Director Appliance 10.5, a malicious actor with network access to the appliance can bypass login
restrictions when authenticating on port 22 (ssh) or port 5480 (appliance management console) . This bypass is not present on port 443 (VCD provider
and tenant login). On a new installation of VMware Cloud Director Appliance 10.5, the bypass is not present.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36007 | Microsoft Send Customer Voice survey from Dynamics 365 Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36007</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36049 | .NET, .NET Framework, and Visual Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36049</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36437 | Azure DevOps Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36437</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47125 | By-passing Cross-Site Scripting Protection in HTML Sanitizer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47125</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In affected versions DOM processing instructions are not handled correctly. This allows bypassing the cross-site scripting mechanism of typo3/html-sanitizer. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 1.5.3 and 2.1.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47126 | Information Disclosure in Install Tool in typo3/cms-install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47126</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In affected versions the login screen of the standalone install tool discloses the full path of the transient data directory (e.g. /var/www/html/var/transient/). This applies to composer-based scenarios only - “classic” non-composer installations are not affected. This issue has been addressed in version 12.4.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47550 | WordPress Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47550</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RedNao Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations: from n/a through 4.0.12.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47554 | WordPress Actueel Financieel Nieuws – Denk Internet Solutions Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47554</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in DenK BV Actueel Financieel Nieuws – Denk Internet Solutions plugin &lt;= 5.1.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47384 | MP4Box GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master was discovered to contain a memory leak in the function gf_isom_add_chapter at /isomedia/isom_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47384</link><description>MP4Box GPAC v2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master was discovered to contain a memory leak in the function gf_isom_add_chapter at /isomedia/isom_write.c. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted MP4 file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47646 | WordPress Recently viewed and most viewed products Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47646</link><description>Auth. (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CedCommerce Recently viewed and most viewed products plugin &lt;= 1.1.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26222 | TIBCO EBX Cross-site Scripting (XXS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26222</link><description>The Web Application component of TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX contains an easily exploitable vulnerability that allows a low privileged attacker with network access to execute a stored XSS on the affected system. Affected releases are TIBCO Software Inc.'s TIBCO EBX: versions 5.9.22 and below, versions 6.0.13 and below and TIBCO Product and Service Catalog powered by TIBCO EBX: versions 5.0.0 and below.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47127 | Weak Authentication in Session Handling in typo3/cms-core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47127</link><description>TYPO3 is an open source PHP based web content management system released under the GNU GPL. In typo3 installations there are always at least two different sites. Eg. first.example.org and second.example.com. In affected versions a session cookie generated for the first site can be reused on the second site without requiring additional authentication. This vulnerability has been addressed in versions 8.7.55, 9.5.44, 10.4.41, 11.5.33, and 12.4.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28741 | Buffer overflow in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 1.0 before version 1.10 may allow an authenticated user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28741</link><description>Buffer overflow in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 1.0 before version 1.10 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-24379 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server System M70KLP Family BIOS firmware before version 01.04.0029 may allow a privileged user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-24379</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server System M70KLP Family BIOS firmware before version 01.04.0029 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-27229 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7i3DN, NUC7i5DN, NUC7i7DN HDMI firmware update tool software before version 1.79.1.1 may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-27229</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7i3DN, NUC7i5DN, NUC7i7DN HDMI firmware update tool software before version 1.79.1.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-29262 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Server Board BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29262</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Server Board BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-29510 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Server Board M10JNP2SB BIOS firmware before version 7.219 may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29510</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Server Board M10JNP2SB BIOS firmware before version 7.219 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33898 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) NUC Watchdog Timer installation software before version 2.0.21.0 may allow an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33898</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) NUC Watchdog Timer installation software before version 2.0.21.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33945 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server board and Intel(R) Server System BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33945</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server board and Intel(R) Server System BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36374 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools before version iDmi Windows 5.27.03.0003 may allow a privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36374</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools before version iDmi Windows 5.27.03.0003 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36396 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools before version iDmiEdit-Linux-5.27.06.0017 may allow a priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36396</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools before version iDmiEdit-Linux-5.27.06.0017 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38786 | Improper access control in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38786</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41659 | Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41659</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41689 | Improper access control in some Intel In-Band Manageability software before version 3.0.14 may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41689</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel In-Band Manageability software before version 3.0.14 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41700 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) NUC Pro Software Suite installation software before version 2.0.0.9 may allow an authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41700</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) NUC Pro Software Suite installation software before version 2.0.0.9 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42879 | NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42879</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43477 | Incomplete cleanup for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43477</link><description>Incomplete cleanup for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43666 | Exposure of sensitive system information due to uncleared debug information for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43666</link><description>Exposure of sensitive system information due to uncleared debug information for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45109 | Improper initialization for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45109</link><description>Improper initialization for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45469 | Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45469</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46298 | Incomplete cleanup for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46298</link><description>Incomplete cleanup for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46299 | Insufficient control flow management for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46299</link><description>Insufficient control flow management for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46301 | Improper Initialization for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46301</link><description>Improper Initialization for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46646 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46646</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46647 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46647</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22285 | Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22285</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22290 | Uncaught exception for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22290</link><description>Uncaught exception for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22292 | Uncaught exception for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22292</link><description>Uncaught exception for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22305 | Integer overflow in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22305</link><description>Integer overflow in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22310 | Race condition in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22310</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22313 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) QAT Library software before version 22.07.1 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22313</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) QAT Library software before version 22.07.1 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22327 | Out-of-bounds write in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 2.8.1 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22327</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in firmware for some Intel(R) FPGA products before version 2.8.1 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22329 | Improper input validation in the BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22329</link><description>Improper input validation in the BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22337 | Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via netwo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22337</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22448 | Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22448</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22663 | Improper authentication for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via net...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22663</link><description>Improper authentication for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23583 | Sequence of processor instructions leads to unexpected behavior for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23583</link><description>Sequence of processor instructions leads to unexpected behavior for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege and/or information disclosure and/or denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24587 | Insufficient control flow management in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24587</link><description>Insufficient control flow management in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24588 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an unauthenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24588</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via physical access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24592 | Path traversal in the some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkits and Component software before version 2023.1 may allow authenticated user to potentially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24592</link><description>Path traversal in the some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkits and Component software before version 2023.1 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25071 | NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows Drviers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25071</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows Drviers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25075 | Unquoted search path in the installer for some Intel Server Configuration Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25075</link><description>Unquoted search path in the installer for some Intel Server Configuration Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25080 | Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) Distribution of OpenVINO toolkit software before version 2023.0.0 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25080</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) Distribution of OpenVINO toolkit software before version 2023.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25756 | Out-of-bounds read in the BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25756</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the BIOS firmware for some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25949 | Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25949</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25952 | Out-of-bounds write in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25952</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26589 | Use after free in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allowed an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26589</link><description>Use after free in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allowed an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27305 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27305</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27306 | Improper Initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27306</link><description>Improper Initialization in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27383 | Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) oneAPI HPC Toolkit 2023.1 and Intel(R)MPI Library software before version 2021.9 may allow a p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27383</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) oneAPI HPC Toolkit 2023.1 and Intel(R)MPI Library software before version 2021.9 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27513 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Server Information Retrieval Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27513</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Server Information Retrieval Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27519 | Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27519</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27879 | Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable inform...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27879</link><description>Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Optane(TM) SSD products may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via physical access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28376 | Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some Intel(R) E810 Ethernet Controllers and Adapters before version 1.7.1 may allow an unauthenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28376</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some Intel(R) E810 Ethernet Controllers and Adapters before version 1.7.1 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28377 | Improper authentication in some Intel(R) NUC Kit NUC11PH USB firmware installation software before version 1.1 for Windows may allow an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28377</link><description>Improper authentication in some Intel(R) NUC Kit NUC11PH USB firmware installation software before version 1.1 for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28378 | Improper authorization in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 2.0 before version 2.0.4 may allow an authenticated user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28378</link><description>Improper authorization in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 2.0 before version 2.0.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28388 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Chipset Device Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28388</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Chipset Device Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28397 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated to potentially enable escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28397</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated to potentially enable escalation of privileges via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28401 | Out-of-bounds write in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28401</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28404 | Out-of-bounds read in the Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28404</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28723 | Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28723</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28737 | Improper initialization in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28737</link><description>Improper initialization in some Intel(R) Aptio* V UEFI Firmware Integrator Tools may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28740 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 2.0 before version 2.0.4 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28740</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) QAT drivers for Windows - HW Version 2.0 before version 2.0.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29157 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29157</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29161 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29161</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29165 | Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29165</link><description>Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Arc(TM) &amp; Iris(R) Xe Graphics - WHQL - Windows drivers before version 31.0.101.4255 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29504 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) RealSense(TM) Dynamic Calibration software before version 2.13.1.0 may allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29504</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) RealSense(TM) Dynamic Calibration software before version 2.13.1.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31203 | Improper input validation in some OpenVINO Model Server software before version 2022.3 for Intel Distribution of OpenVINO toolkit may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31203</link><description>Improper input validation in some OpenVINO Model Server software before version 2022.3 for Intel Distribution of OpenVINO toolkit may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31273 | Protection mechanism failure in some Intel DCM software before version 5.2 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31273</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some Intel DCM software before version 5.2 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32204 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32204</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32278 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Uniwill Service Driver for Intel(R) NUC M15 Laptop Kits - LAPRC510 &amp; LAPRC710 Uniwill Service Driver i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32278</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Uniwill Service Driver for Intel(R) NUC M15 Laptop Kits - LAPRC510 &amp; LAPRC710 Uniwill Service Driver installation software before version 1.0.1.7 for Intel(R) NUC Software Studio may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32279 | Improper access control in user mode driver for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite before version 2.1123.214.2 may allow unauthent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32279</link><description>Improper access control in user mode driver for some Intel(R) Connectivity Performance Suite before version 2.1123.214.2 may allow unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32283 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file in some Intel(R) On Demand software before versions 1.16.2, 2.1.1, 3.1.0 may allow an authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32283</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file in some Intel(R) On Demand software before versions 1.16.2, 2.1.1, 3.1.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32638 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Arc RGB Controller software before version 1.06 may allow an authenticated user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32638</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel Arc RGB Controller software before version 1.06 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32641 | Improper input validation in firmware for Intel(R) QAT before version QAT20.L.1.0.40-00004 may allow escalation of privilege and denial of s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32641</link><description>Improper input validation in firmware for Intel(R) QAT before version QAT20.L.1.0.40-00004 may allow escalation of privilege and denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32655 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Kits &amp; Mini PCs - NUC8i7HVK &amp; NUC8HNK USB Type C power delivery controller installatio software before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32655</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC Kits &amp; Mini PCs - NUC8i7HVK &amp; NUC8HNK USB Type C power delivery controller installatio software before version 1.0.10.3 for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32658 | Unquoted search path in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7i3DN, NUC7i5DN, NUC7i7DN HDMI firmware update tool software before version 1.79.1.1 may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32658</link><description>Unquoted search path in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7i3DN, NUC7i5DN, NUC7i7DN HDMI firmware update tool software before version 1.79.1.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32660 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) NUC Kit NUC6i7KYK Thunderbolt(TM) 3 Firmware Update Tool installation software before version 46 m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32660</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) NUC Kit NUC6i7KYK Thunderbolt(TM) 3 Firmware Update Tool installation software before version 46 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32661 | Improper authentication in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7PJYH and NUC7CJYH Realtek* SD Card Reader Driver installation software before version ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32661</link><description>Improper authentication in some Intel(R) NUC Kits NUC7PJYH and NUC7CJYH Realtek* SD Card Reader Driver installation software before version 10.0.19041.29098 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32662 | Improper authorization in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool installation software before version 2.2.1 may allow a privilaged user to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32662</link><description>Improper authorization in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool installation software before version 2.2.1 may allow a privilaged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33872 | Improper access control in the Intel Support android application all verions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33872</link><description>Improper access control in the Intel Support android application all verions may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33874 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) NUC 12 Pro Kits &amp; Mini PCs - NUC12WS Intel(R) HID Event Filter Driver installation software before...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33874</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) NUC 12 Pro Kits &amp; Mini PCs - NUC12WS Intel(R) HID Event Filter Driver installation software before version 2.2.2.1 for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33878 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC P14E Laptop Element Audio Install Package software before version 156 for Windows may allow an authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33878</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) NUC P14E Laptop Element Audio Install Package software before version 156 for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34314 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Simics Simulator software before version 1.7.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentiall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34314</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Simics Simulator software before version 1.7.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34350 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.15 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34350</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.15 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34430 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34430</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.2.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34431 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server Board BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34431</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Server Board BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34997 | Insecure inherited permissions in the installer for some Intel Server Configuration Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an auth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34997</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in the installer for some Intel Server Configuration Utility software before version 16.0.9 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36860 | Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36860</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38131 | Improper input validationation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38131</link><description>Improper input validationation for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38411 | Improper access control in the Intel Smart Campus android application before version 9.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38411</link><description>Improper access control in the Intel Smart Campus android application before version 9.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38570 | Access of memory location after end of buffer for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38570</link><description>Access of memory location after end of buffer for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39221 | Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via net...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39221</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39228 | Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39228</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel Unison software may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39230 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel Rapid Storage Technology software before version 16.8.5.1014.9 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39230</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel Rapid Storage Technology software before version 16.8.5.1014.9 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39411 | Improper input validationation for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39411</link><description>Improper input validationation for some Intel Unison software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39412 | Cross-site request forgery in some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39412</link><description>Cross-site request forgery in some Intel Unison software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40220 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40220</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40540 | Non-Transparent Sharing of Microarchitectural Resources in some Intel(R) NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40540</link><description>Non-Transparent Sharing of Microarchitectural Resources in some Intel(R) NUC BIOS firmware may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-26345 | Failure to validate the value in APCB may allow a privileged attacker to tamper with the APCB token to force an out-of-bounds memory read po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-26345</link><description>Failure to validate the value in APCB may allow a privileged attacker to tamper with the APCB token to force an out-of-bounds memory read potentially resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46758 | Insufficient validation of SPI flash addresses in the ASP (AMD Secure Processor) bootloader may allow an attacker to read data in memory map...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46758</link><description>Insufficient validation of SPI flash addresses in the ASP (AMD Secure Processor) bootloader may allow an attacker to read data in memory mapped beyond SPI flash resulting in a potential loss of availability and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23821 | Improper access control in System Management Mode (SMM) may allow an attacker to write to SPI ROM potentially leading to arbitrary code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23821</link><description>Improper access control in System Management Mode (SMM) may allow an attacker to write to SPI ROM potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23830 | SMM configuration may not be immutable, as intended, when SNP is enabled resulting in a potential limited loss of guest memory integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23830</link><description>SMM configuration may not be immutable, as intended, when SNP is enabled resulting in a potential limited loss of guest memory integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20519 | A Use-After-Free vulnerability in the management of an SNP guest context page may allow a malicious hypervisor to masquerade as the guest's ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20519</link><description>A Use-After-Free vulnerability in the management of an SNP guest context page may allow a malicious hypervisor to masquerade as the guest's migration agent resulting in a potential loss of guest integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20563 | Insufficient protections in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20563</link><description>Insufficient protections in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20565 | Insufficient protections in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20565</link><description>Insufficient protections in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20566 | Improper address validation in ASP with SNP enabled may potentially allow an attacker to compromise guest memory integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20566</link><description>Improper address validation in ASP with SNP enabled may potentially allow an attacker to compromise guest memory integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20571 | A race condition in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker using a compromised user space to leverage CVE-2018-8897 potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20571</link><description>A race condition in System Management Mode (SMM) code may allow an attacker using a compromised user space to leverage CVE-2018-8897 potentially resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20592 | Improper or unexpected behavior of the INVD instruction in some AMD CPUs may allow an attacker with a malicious hypervisor to affect cache l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20592</link><description>Improper or unexpected behavior of the INVD instruction in some AMD CPUs may allow an attacker with a malicious hypervisor to affect cache line write-back behavior of the CPU leading to a potential loss of guest virtual machine (VM) memory integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20596 | Improper input validation in the SMM Supervisor may allow an attacker with a compromised SMI handler to gain Ring0 access potentially leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20596</link><description>Improper input validation in the SMM Supervisor may allow an attacker with a compromised SMI handler to gain Ring0 access potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47653 | WordPress TWB Woocommerce Reviews Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47653</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Abu Bakar TWB Woocommerce Reviews plugin &lt;= 1.7.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46748 | Insufficient bounds checking in the ASP (AMD Secure Processor) may allow an attacker to access memory outside the bounds of what is permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46748</link><description>Insufficient bounds checking in the ASP (AMD Secure Processor) may allow an attacker to access memory outside the bounds of what is permissible to a TA (Trusted Application) resulting in a potential denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46766 | Improper clearing of sensitive data in the ASP Bootloader may expose secret keys to a privileged attacker accessing ASP SRAM, potentially le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46766</link><description>Improper clearing of sensitive data in the ASP Bootloader may expose secret keys to a privileged attacker accessing ASP SRAM, potentially leading to a loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46774 | Insufficient DRAM address validation in System
Management Unit (SMU) may allow an attacker to read/write from/to an invalid
DRAM address, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46774</link><description>Insufficient DRAM address validation in System
Management Unit (SMU) may allow an attacker to read/write from/to an invalid
DRAM address, potentially resulting in denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23820 | Failure to validate the AMD SMM communication buffer
may allow an attacker to corrupt the SMRAM potentially leading to arbitrary
code execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23820</link><description>Failure to validate the AMD SMM communication buffer
may allow an attacker to corrupt the SMRAM potentially leading to arbitrary
code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20521 | TOCTOU in the ASP Bootloader may allow an attacker with physical access to tamper with SPI ROM records after memory content verification, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20521</link><description>TOCTOU in the ASP Bootloader may allow an attacker with physical access to tamper with SPI ROM records after memory content verification, potentially leading to loss of confidentiality or a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20526 | Insufficient input validation in the ASP Bootloader may enable a privileged attacker with physical access to expose the contents of ASP memo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20526</link><description>Insufficient input validation in the ASP Bootloader may enable a privileged attacker with physical access to expose the contents of ASP memory potentially leading to a loss of confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20533 | Insufficient DRAM address validation in System
Management Unit (SMU) may allow an attacker to read/write from/to an invalid
DRAM address, po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20533</link><description>Insufficient DRAM address validation in System
Management Unit (SMU) may allow an attacker to read/write from/to an invalid
DRAM address, potentially resulting in denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20567 | Improper signature verification of RadeonTM RX Vega M Graphics driver for Windows may allow an attacker with admin privileges to launch AMDS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20567</link><description>Improper signature verification of RadeonTM RX Vega M Graphics driver for Windows may allow an attacker with admin privileges to launch AMDSoftwareInstaller.exe without validating the file signature potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20568 | Improper signature verification of RadeonTM RX Vega M Graphics driver for Windows may allow an attacker with admin privileges to launch Rade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20568</link><description>Improper signature verification of RadeonTM RX Vega M Graphics driver for Windows may allow an attacker with admin privileges to launch RadeonInstaller.exe without validating the file signature potentially leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31320 | Improper input validation in the AMD RadeonTM Graphics display driver may allow an attacker to corrupt the display potentially resulting in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31320</link><description>Improper input validation in the AMD RadeonTM Graphics display driver may allow an attacker to corrupt the display potentially resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47654 | WordPress BZScore – Live Score Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.03 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47654</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in livescore.Bz BZScore – Live Score plugin &lt;= 1.03 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47656 | WordPress ANAC XML Bandi di Gara Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47656</link><description>Auth. (editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Marco Milesi ANAC XML Bandi di Gara plugin &lt;= 7.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47658 | WordPress Extra Product Options for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47658</link><description>Auth. (ShopManager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in actpro Extra Product Options for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 3.0.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32701 | Vulnerability in Networking Stack Impacts QNX Software Development Platform (SDP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32701</link><description>Improper Input Validation in the Networking Stack of QNX SDP version(s) 6.6, 7.0, and 7.1 could allow an attacker to potentially cause Information Disclosure or a Denial-of-Service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40681 | A incorrect authorization in Fortinet FortiClient (Windows) 7.0.0 - 7.0.7, 6.4.0 - 6.4.9, 6.2.0 - 6.2.9 and 6.0.0 - 6.0.10 allows an attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40681</link><description>A incorrect authorization in Fortinet FortiClient (Windows) 7.0.0 - 7.0.7, 6.4.0 - 6.4.9, 6.2.0 - 6.2.9 and 6.0.0 - 6.0.10 allows an attacker to cause denial of service via sending a crafted request to a specific named pipe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25603 | A permissive cross-domain policy with untrusted domains vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 7.1.0 - 7.1.1, FortiDDoS-F 6.3.0 - 6.3.4 and 6.4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25603</link><description>A permissive cross-domain policy with untrusted domains vulnerability in Fortinet FortiADC 7.1.0 - 7.1.1, FortiDDoS-F 6.3.0 - 6.3.4 and 6.4.0 - 6.4.1 allow an unauthorized attacker to carry out privileged actions and retrieve sensitive information via crafted web requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29177 | Multiple buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') vulnerabilities [CWE-120] in FortiADC version 7.2.0 and befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29177</link><description>Multiple buffer copy without checking size of input ('classic buffer overflow') vulnerabilities [CWE-120] in FortiADC version 7.2.0 and before 7.1.2 &amp; FortiDDoS-F version 6.5.0 and before 6.4.1 allows a privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via specifically crafted CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40719 | A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer and FortiManager 7.0.0 - 7.0.8, 7.2.0 - 7.2.3 and 7.4.0 allows an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40719</link><description>A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer and FortiManager 7.0.0 - 7.0.8, 7.2.0 - 7.2.3 and 7.4.0 allows an attacker to access Fortinet private testing data via the use of static credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26205 | An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiADC automation feature 7.1.0 through 7.1.2, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26205</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiADC automation feature 7.1.0 through 7.1.2, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.1 all versions may allow an authenticated low-privileged attacker to escalate their privileges to super_admin via a specific crafted configuration of fabric automation CLI script.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28002 | An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.12, 6.4 all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28002</link><description>An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.12, 6.4 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.0 all versions and FortiProxy 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 2.0 all versions VMs may allow a local attacker with admin privileges to boot a malicious image on the device and bypass the filesystem integrity check in place.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33304 | A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClient Windows 7.0.0 - 7.0.9 and 7.2.0 - 7.2.1 allows an attacker to bypass s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33304</link><description>A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClient Windows 7.0.0 - 7.0.9 and 7.2.0 - 7.2.1 allows an attacker to bypass system protections via the use of static credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34991 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34991</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in an sql command ('sql injection') in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and 8.5.0 through 8.5.4 and 8.4.0 through 8.4.2 and 8.3.0 through 8.3.2 and 8.2.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via a crafted http request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36553 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 5.4.0 and 5.3.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36553</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in an os command ('os command injection') in Fortinet FortiSIEM version 5.4.0 and 5.3.0 through 5.3.3 and 5.2.5 through 5.2.8 and 5.2.1 through 5.2.2 and 5.1.0 through 5.1.3 and 5.0.0 through 5.0.1 and 4.10.0 and 4.9.0 and 4.7.2 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via crafted API requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36633 | An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiMail webmail version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7.0.5 allows an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36633</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiMail webmail version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7.0.5 allows an authenticated attacker to see and modify the title of address book folders of other users via crafted HTTP or HTTPs requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36641 | A numeric truncation error in Fortinet FortiProxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, FortiProxy version 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, FortiProxy 2.0 all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36641</link><description>A numeric truncation error in Fortinet FortiProxy version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, FortiProxy version 7.0.0 through 7.0.10, FortiProxy 2.0 all versions, FortiProxy 1.2 all versions, FortiProxy 1.1, all  versions, FortiProxy 1.0 all versions, FortiOS version 7.4.0, FortiOS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, FortiOS version 7.0.0 through 7.0.12, FortiOS 6.4 all versions, FortiOS 6.2 all versions, FortiOS 6.0 all versions allows attacker to denial of service via specifically crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41676 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor [CWE-200] in FortiSIEM version  7.0.0 and before 6.7.5 may allow an attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41676</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor [CWE-200] in FortiSIEM version  7.0.0 and before 6.7.5 may allow an attacker with access to windows agent logs to obtain the windows agent password via searching through the logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41840 | A untrusted search path vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.0.9 allows an attacker to perform a DLL Hijack attack via a malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41840</link><description>A untrusted search path vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.0.9 allows an attacker to perform a DLL Hijack attack via a malicious OpenSSL engine library in the search path.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42783 | A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and 8.5.0 through 8.5.4 and 8.4.2 through 8.4.0 and 8.3.2 through...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42783</link><description>A relative path traversal in Fortinet FortiWLM version 8.6.0 through 8.6.5 and 8.5.0 through 8.5.4 and 8.4.2 through 8.4.0 and 8.3.2 through 8.3.0 and 8.2.2 allows attacker to read arbitrary files via crafted http requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44248 | An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiEDRCollectorWindows version 5.2.0.4549 and below, 5.0.3.1007 and below, 4.0 all m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44248</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiEDRCollectorWindows version 5.2.0.4549 and below, 5.0.3.1007 and below, 4.0 all may allow a local attacker to prevent the collector service to start in the next system reboot by tampering with some registry keys of the service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45582 | An improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts vulnerability [CWE-307] in FortiMail webmail version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45582</link><description>An improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts vulnerability [CWE-307] in FortiMail webmail version 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6 and before 6.4.8 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to  perform a brute force attack on the affected endpoints via repeated login attempts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45585 | An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability [CWE-532] in FortiSIEM version 7.0.0, version 6.7.6 and below, version  6....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45585</link><description>An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerability [CWE-532] in FortiSIEM version 7.0.0, version 6.7.6 and below, version  6.6.3 and below, version 6.5.1 and below, version 6.4.2 and below, version 6.3.3 and below, version 6.2.1 and below, version 6.1.2 and below, version 5.4.0, version 5.3.3 and below may allow an authenticated user to view an encrypted ElasticSearch password via debug log files generated when FortiSIEM is configured with ElasticSearch Event Storage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36016 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36016</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36017 | Windows Scripting Engine Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36017</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36018 | Visual Studio Code Jupyter Extension Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36018</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36021 | Microsoft On-Prem Data Gateway Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36021</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36025 | Windows SmartScreen Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36025</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36028 | Microsoft Protected Extensible Authentication Protocol (PEAP) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36028</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36030 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Sales Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36030</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36031 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36031</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36033 | Windows DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36033</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36035 | Microsoft Exchange Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36035</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36036 | Windows Cloud Files Mini Filter Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36036</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36037 | Microsoft Excel Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36037</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36039 | Microsoft Exchange Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36039</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36041 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36041</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36042 | Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36042</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36043 | Open Management Infrastructure Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36043</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36045 | Microsoft Office Graphics Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36045</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36046 | Windows Authentication Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36046</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36047 | Windows Authentication Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36047</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36050 | Microsoft Exchange Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36050</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36052 | Azure CLI REST Command Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36052</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36392 | DHCP Server Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36392</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36393 | Windows User Interface Application Core Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36393</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36394 | Windows Search Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36394</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36395 | Windows Deployment Services Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36395</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36396 | Windows Compressed Folder Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36396</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36397 | Windows Pragmatic General Multicast (PGM) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36397</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36398 | Windows NTFS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36398</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36399 | Windows Storage Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36399</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36400 | Windows HMAC Key Derivation Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36400</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36401 | Microsoft Remote Registry Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36401</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36402 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36402</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36403 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36403</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36404 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36404</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36405 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36405</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36406 | Windows Hyper-V Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36406</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36407 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36407</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36408 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36408</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36410 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36410</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36413 | Microsoft Office Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36413</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36422 | Microsoft Windows Defender Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36422</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36423 | Microsoft Remote Registry Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36423</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36424 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36424</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36425 | Windows Distributed File System (DFS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36425</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36427 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36427</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36428 | Microsoft Local Security Authority Subsystem Service Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36428</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36439 | Microsoft Exchange Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36439</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36560 | ASP.NET Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36560</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36705 | Windows Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36705</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36719 | Microsoft Speech Application Programming Interface (SAPI) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36719</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38151 | Microsoft Host Integration Server 2020 Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38151</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38177 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38177</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47659 | WordPress Lava Directory Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.34 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47659</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Lavacode Lava Directory Manager plugin &lt;= 1.1.34 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47660 | WordPress Product Visibility by Country for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47660</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WP Wham Product Visibility by Country for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 1.4.9 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48094 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CesiumJS v1.111 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's brow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48094</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CesiumJS v1.111 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of the victim's browser via sending a crafted payload to /container_files/public_html/doc/index.html.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6131 | Code Injection in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6131</link><description>Code Injection in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6130 | Path Traversal: &amp;#x27;\..\filename&amp;#x27; in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6130</link><description>Path Traversal: '\..\filename' in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6128 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6128</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Reflected in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6127 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6127</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47262 | In Abbott ID NOW before 7.1, settings can be modified via physical access to an internal serial port.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47262</link><description>In Abbott ID NOW before 7.1, settings can be modified via physical access to an internal serial port.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6126 | Code Injection in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6126</link><description>Code Injection in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6125 | Code Injection in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6125</link><description>Code Injection in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 7.12.14, 8.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6124 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in salesagility/suitecrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6124</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in GitHub repository salesagility/suitecrm prior to 7.14.2, 8.4.2, 7.12.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45684 | Northern.tech CFEngine Enterprise before 3.21.3 allows SQL Injection. The fixed versions are 3.18.6 and 3.21.3. The earliest affected versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45684</link><description>Northern.tech CFEngine Enterprise before 3.21.3 allows SQL Injection. The fixed versions are 3.18.6 and 3.21.3. The earliest affected version is 3.6.0. The issue is in the Mission Portal login page in the CFEngine hub.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48020 | Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/task/changeStatus.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48020</link><description>Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/task/changeStatus.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48021 | Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/task/update.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48021</link><description>Dreamer CMS v4.1.3 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /admin/task/update.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6111 | Use-after-free in Linux kernel&amp;#x27;s netfilter: nf_tables component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6111</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability in the Linux kernel's netfilter: nf_tables component can be exploited to achieve local privilege escalation.

The function nft_trans_gc_catchall did not remove the catchall set element from the catchall_list when the argument sync is true, making it possible to free a catchall set element many times.

We recommend upgrading past commit 93995bf4af2c5a99e2a87f0cd5ce547d31eb7630.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44319 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44319</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices use a weak checksum algorithm to protect the configuration backup that an administrator can export from the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privileges or an attacker that tricks a legitimate administrator to upload a modified configuration file to change the configuration of an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44320 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44320</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices do not properly validate the authentication when performing certain modifications in the web interface allowing an authenticated attacker to influence the user interface configured by an administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44321 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44321</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices do not properly validate the length of inputs when performing certain configuration changes in the web interface allowing an authenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition. The device needs to be restarted for the web interface to become available again.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44322 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44322</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices can be configured to send emails when certain events occur on the device. When presented with an invalid response from the SMTP server, the device triggers an error that disrupts email sending. An attacker with access to the network can use this to do disable notification of users when certain events occur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44373 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44373</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices do not properly sanitize an input field.  This could allow an authenticated remote attacker with administrative privileges to inject code or spawn a system root shell. Follow-up of CVE-2022-36323.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44374 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44374</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices allow to change the password, but insufficiently check which password is to be changed. With this  an authenticated attacker could, under certain conditions, be able to change the password of another, potential admin user allowing her to escalate her privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45794 | A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix Applications using Mendix 10 (All versions &lt; V10.4.0), Mendix Applications using Mendix 7 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45794</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix Applications using Mendix 10 (All versions &lt; V10.4.0), Mendix Applications using Mendix 7 (All versions &lt; V7.23.37), Mendix Applications using Mendix 8 (All versions &lt; V8.18.27), Mendix Applications using Mendix 9 (All versions &lt; V9.24.10). A capture-replay flaw in the platform could have an impact to apps built with the platform, if certain preconditions are met that depend on the app's model and access control design.&#13;
&#13;
This could allow authenticated attackers to access or modify objects without proper authorization, or escalate privileges in the context of the vulnerable app.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46096 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). The PUD Manager of affected products does not properly authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46096</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). The PUD Manager of affected products does not properly authenticate users in the PUD Manager web service. This could allow an unauthenticated adjacent attacker to generate a privileged token and upload additional documents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46097 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). The PUD Manager of affected products does not properly neutral...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46097</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). The PUD Manager of affected products does not properly neutralize user provided inputs. This could allow an authenticated adjacent attacker to execute SQL statements in the underlying database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46098 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). When accessing the Information Server from affected products, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46098</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). When accessing the Information Server from affected products, the products use an overly permissive CORS policy. This could allow an attacker to trick a legitimate user to trigger unwanted behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46099 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). There is a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46099</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC PCS neo (All versions &lt; V4.1). There is a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Administration Console of the affected product, that could allow an attacker with high privileges to inject Javascript code into the application that is later executed by another legitimate user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46590 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens OPC UA Modelling Editor (SiOME) (All versions &lt; V2.8). Affected products suffer from a XML ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46590</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens OPC UA Modelling Editor (SiOME) (All versions &lt; V2.8). Affected products suffer from a XML external entity (XXE) injection vulnerability. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to interfere with an application's processing of XML data and read arbitrary files in the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46601 | A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions). The affected application lacks proper access controls in making the SQLServer c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46601</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions). The affected application lacks proper access controls in making the SQLServer connection. This could allow an attacker to query the database directly to access information that the user should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43503 | A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions &lt; V10.4.4). Caching system in the affected application leaks sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43503</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions &lt; V10.4.4). Caching system in the affected application leaks sensitive information such as user and project information in cleartext via UDP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43504 | A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions &lt; V10.4.4). Ptmcast executable used for testing cache validation service in affec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43504</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions &lt; V10.4.4). Ptmcast executable used for testing cache validation service in affected application is vulnerable to Structured Exception Handler (SEH) based buffer overflow. This could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the target system or cause denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43505 | A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions). The affected application lacks proper access controls in SMB shares. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43505</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in COMOS (All versions). The affected application lacks proper access controls in SMB shares. This could allow an attacker to access files that the user should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44317 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44317</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected products do not properly validate the content of uploaded X509 certificates which could allow an attacker with administrative privileges to execute arbitrary code on the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44318 | A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44318</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SCALANCE XB205-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB205-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB208 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3 (ST, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB213-3LD (SC, PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (E/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XB216 (PN) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (SC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2 (ST/BFOC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2G PoE EEC (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G (EIP DEF.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC206-2SFP G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G (EIP def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC208G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-3G PoE (54 V DC) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G (EIP Def.) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XC224-4C G EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204 DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XF204-2BA DNA (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP208PoE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216 (Ethernet/IP) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XP216POE EEC (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 x FE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR324WG (24 X FE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR326-2C PoE WG (without UL) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24XFE, 4XGE, 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE, 4xGE,DC24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (24xFE,4xGE,AC230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, AC 230V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SCALANCE XR328-4C WG (28xGE, DC 24V) (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC206-2SFP (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC208 (All versions &lt; V4.5), SIPLUS NET SCALANCE XC216-4C (All versions &lt; V4.5). Affected devices use a hardcoded key to obfuscate the configuration backup that an administrator can export from the device. This could allow an authenticated attacker with administrative privileges or an attacker that obtains a configuration backup to extract configuration information from the exported file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24585 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted networ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24585</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can send a network request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25181 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25181</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted set of network packets can lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27882 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server form boundary functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27882</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server form boundary functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28379 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server form boundary functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28379</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server form boundary functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28391 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server header parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. Specially craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28391</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server header parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. Specially crafted network packets can lead to code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31247 | A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server Host header parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31247</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the HTTP Server Host header parsing functionality of Weston Embedded uC-HTTP v3.01.01. A specially crafted network packet can lead to code execution. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6109 | The YOP Poll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to a race condition in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.26. This is due to improper re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6109</link><description>The YOP Poll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to a race condition in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.26. This is due to improper restrictions on the add() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to place multiple votes on a single poll even when the poll is set to one vote per person.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 06:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45880 | GibbonEdu Gibbon through version 25.0.0 allows Directory Traversal via the report template builder. An attacker can create a new Asset Compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45880</link><description>GibbonEdu Gibbon through version 25.0.0 allows Directory Traversal via the report template builder. An attacker can create a new Asset Component. The templateFileDestination parameter can be set to an arbitrary pathname (and extension). This allows creation of PHP files outside of the uploads directory, directly in the webroot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45881 | GibbonEdu Gibbon through version 25.0.0 allows /modules/Planner/resources_addQuick_ajaxProcess.php file upload with resultant XSS. The image...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45881</link><description>GibbonEdu Gibbon through version 25.0.0 allows /modules/Planner/resources_addQuick_ajaxProcess.php file upload with resultant XSS. The imageAsLinks parameter must be set to Y to return HTML code. The filename attribute of the bodyfile1 parameter is reflected in the response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45879 | GibbonEdu Gibbon version 25.0.0 allows HTML Injection via an IFRAME element to the Messager component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45879</link><description>GibbonEdu Gibbon version 25.0.0 allows HTML Injection via an IFRAME element to the Messager component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45878 | GibbonEdu Gibbon version 25.0.1 and before allows Arbitrary File Write because rubrics_visualise_saveAjax.phps does not require authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45878</link><description>GibbonEdu Gibbon version 25.0.1 and before allows Arbitrary File Write because rubrics_visualise_saveAjax.phps does not require authentication. The endpoint accepts the img, path, and gibbonPersonID parameters. The img parameter is expected to be a base64 encoded image. If the path parameter is set, the defined path is used as the destination folder, concatenated with the absolute path of the installation directory. The content of the img parameter is base64 decoded and written to the defined file path. This allows creation of PHP files that permit Remote Code Execution (unauthenticated).</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47609 | SQL injection vulnerability in OSS Calendar versions prior to v.2.0.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or ob...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47609</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in OSS Calendar versions prior to v.2.0.3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or obtain and/or alter the information stored in the database by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43902 | Incorrect access control in the Forgot Your Password function of EMSigner v2.8.7 allows unauthenticated attackers to access accounts of all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43902</link><description>Incorrect access control in the Forgot Your Password function of EMSigner v2.8.7 allows unauthenticated attackers to access accounts of all registered users, including those with administrator privileges via a crafted password reset token.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43901 | Incorrect access control in the AdHoc User creation form of EMSigner v2.8.7 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily modify usernames...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43901</link><description>Incorrect access control in the AdHoc User creation form of EMSigner v2.8.7 allows unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily modify usernames and privileges by using the email address of a registered user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43900 | Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in EMSigner v2.8.7 allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to application content and view sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43900</link><description>Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) in EMSigner v2.8.7 allow attackers to gain unauthorized access to application content and view sensitive data of other users via manipulation of the documentID and EncryptedDocumentId parameters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42326 | An issue in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the interfaces_gif_edit.php ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42326</link><description>An issue in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request to the interfaces_gif_edit.php and interfaces_gre_edit.php components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6006 | Local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6006</link><description>This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of PaperCut NG. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.
The specific flaw exists within the pc-pdl-to-image process. The process loads an executable from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42325 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via a crafted url to the sta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42325</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via a crafted url to the status_logs_filter_dynamic.php page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42327 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via a crafted URL to the get...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42327</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Netgate pfSense v.2.7.0 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via a crafted URL to the getserviceproviders.php page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 03:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31754 | Optimizely CMS UI before v12.16.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Admin panel.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31754</link><description>Optimizely CMS UI before v12.16.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Admin panel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 03:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46445 | An issue in AsyncSSH v2.14.0 and earlier allows attackers to control the extension info message (RFC 8308) via a man-in-the-middle attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46445</link><description>An issue in AsyncSSH v2.14.0 and earlier allows attackers to control the extension info message (RFC 8308) via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46446 | An issue in AsyncSSH v2.14.0 and earlier allows attackers to control the remote end of an SSH client session via packet injection/removal an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46446</link><description>An issue in AsyncSSH v2.14.0 and earlier allows attackers to control the remote end of an SSH client session via packet injection/removal and shell emulation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45560 | An issue in Yasukawa memberscard v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45560</link><description>An issue in Yasukawa memberscard v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45558 | An issue in Golden v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45558</link><description>An issue in Golden v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31403 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in SAP Business One product installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31403</link><description>SAP Business One installation - version 10.0, does not perform proper authentication and authorization checks for SMB shared folder. As a result, any malicious user can read and write to the SMB shared folder. Additionally, the files in the folder can be executed or be used by the installation process leading to considerable impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:07:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41366 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41366</link><description>Under certain condition SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP - versions KERNEL 722, KERNEL 7.53, KERNEL 7.77, KERNEL 7.85, KERNEL 7.89, KERNEL 7.54, KERNEL 7.91, KERNEL 7.92, KERNEL 7.93, KERNEL 7.94, KERNEL64UC 7.22, KERNEL64UC 7.22EXT, KERNEL64UC 7.53, KERNEL64NUC 7.22, KERNEL64NUC 7.22EXT, allows an unauthenticated attacker to access the unintended data due to the lack of restrictions applied which may lead to low impact in confidentiality and no impact on the integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42480 | Information Disclosure in NetWeaver AS Java Logon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42480</link><description>The unauthenticated attacker in NetWeaver AS Java Logon application - version 7.50, can brute force the login functionality to identify the legitimate user ids. This will have an impact on confidentiality but there is no other impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:07:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47628 | Session Expiration Misconfiguration in datahub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47628</link><description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. DataHub Frontend's sessions are configured using Play Framework's default settings for stateless session which do not set an expiration time for a cookie. Due to this, if a session cookie were ever leaked, it would be valid forever. DataHub uses a stateless session cookie that is not invalidated on logout, it is just removed from the browser forcing the user to login again. However, if an attacker extracted a cookie from an authenticated user it would continue to be valid as there is no validation on a time window the session token is valid for due to a combination of the usage of LegacyCookiesModule from Play Framework and using default settings which do not set an expiration time. All DataHub instances prior to the patch that have removed the datahub user, but not the default policies applying to that user are affected. Users are advised to update to version 0.12.1 which addresses the issue. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47629 | Privilege escalation through email sign-up in datahub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47629</link><description>DataHub is an open-source metadata platform. In affected versions sign-up through an invite link does not properly restrict users from signing up as privileged accounts. If a user is given an email sign-up link they can potentially create an admin account given certain preconditions. If the default datahub user has been removed, then the user can sign up for an account that leverages the default policies giving admin privileges to the datahub user. All DataHub instances prior to the patch that have removed the datahub user, but not the default policies applying to that user are affected. Users are advised to update to version 0.12.1 which addresses the issue. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>