<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-56156 | Halo Vulnerable to Stored XSS and RCE via File Upload Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56156</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. Prior to version 2.20.13, a vulnerability in Halo allows attackers to bypass file type validation controls. This bypass enables the upload of malicious files including executables and HTML files, which can lead to stored cross-site scripting attacks and potential remote code execution under certain circumstances. This issue has been patched in version 2.20.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32432 | Craft CMS Allows Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32432</link><description>Craft is a flexible, user-friendly CMS for creating custom digital experiences on the web and beyond. Starting from version 3.0.0-RC1 to before 3.9.15, 4.0.0-RC1 to before 4.14.15, and 5.0.0-RC1 to before 5.6.17, Craft is vulnerable to remote code execution. This is a high-impact, low-complexity attack vector. This issue has been patched in versions 3.9.15, 4.14.15, and 5.6.17, and is an additional fix for CVE-2023-41892.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43862 | Dify Allows Unauthorized Access and Modification of APP Orchestration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43862</link><description>Dify is an open-source LLM app development platform. Prior to version 0.6.12, a normal user is able to access and modify APP orchestration, even though the web UI of APP orchestration is not presented for a normal user. This access control flaw allows non-admin users to make unauthorized access and changes on the APPSs. This issue has been patched in version 0.6.12. A workaround for this vulnerability involves updating the the access control mechanisms to enforce stricter user role permissions and implementing role-based access controls (RBAC) to ensure that only users with admin privileges can access Orchestration of the APPs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28076 | Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in EasyVirt DCScope &lt;= 8.6.4 and CO2Scope &lt;= 1.3.4 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28076</link><description>Multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities in EasyVirt DCScope &lt;= 8.6.4 and CO2Scope &lt;= 1.3.4 allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the (1) timeago, (2) user, (3) filter, (4) target, (5) p1, (6) p2, (7) p3, (8) p4, (9) p5, (10) p6, (11) p7, (12) p8, (13) p9, (14) p10, (15) p11, (16) p12, (17) p13, (18) p14, (19) p15, (20) p16, (21) p17, (22) p18, (23) p19, or (24) p20 parameter to /api/management/updateihmsettings; the (25) ID, (26) NAME, (27) CPUTHREADNB, (28) RAMCAP, or (29) DISKCAP parameter to /api/capaplan/savetemplates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32044 | Moodle: unauthenticated rest api user data exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32044</link><description>A flaw has been identified in Moodle where, on certain sites, unauthenticated users could retrieve sensitive user data—including names, contact information, and hashed passwords—via stack traces returned by specific API calls. Sites with PHP configured with zend.exception_ignore_args = 1 in the php.ini file are not affected by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32045 | Moodle: hidden grades shown to users without permission on some grade reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32045</link><description>A flaw has been identified in Moodle where insufficient capability checks in certain grade reports allowed users without the necessary permissions to access hidden grades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3625 | Moodle: user dos and name disclosure via idor in moodle mfa email factor revoke action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3625</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that can allow hackers to gain access to sensitive information about students and prevent them from logging into their accounts, even after they had completed two-factor authentication (2FA).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3627 | Moodle: partial data exposure in moodle before completing multi-factor authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3627</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows some users to access sensitive information about other students before they finish verifying their identities using two-factor authentication (2FA).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3628 | Moodle: moodle assignment submission search leaks anonymous student identities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3628</link><description>A flaw has was found in Moodle where anonymous assignment submissions can be de-anonymized via search, revealing student identities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3635 | Moodle: csrf risk in moodle user tours manager allows tour duplication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3635</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows anyone to duplicate existing tours without needing to log in due to a lack of protection against cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3636 | Moodle: idor in moodle rss block allows unauthorized access to rss feeds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3636</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to access and view RSS feeds due to insufficient capability checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3637 | Moodle: csrf token exposure via url in moodle mod_data module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3637</link><description>A security vulnerability was found in Moodle where confidential information that prevents cross-site request forgery (CSRF) attacks was shared publicly through the site's URL. This vulnerability occurred specifically on two types of pages within the mod_data module: edit and delete pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3638 | Moodle: csrf risk in brickfield tool&amp;#x27;s analysis request action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3638</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. The analysis request action in the Brickfield tool did not include the necessary token to prevent a Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3640 | Moodle: idor in web service allows users enrolled in a course to access some details of other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3640</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Insufficient capability checks made it possible for a user enrolled in a course to access some details, such as the full name and profile image URL, of other users they did not have permission to access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3641 | Moodle: authenticated remote code execution risk in the moodle lms dropbox repository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3641</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. A remote code execution risk was identified in the Moodle LMS Dropbox repository. By default, this was only available to teachers and managers on sites with the Dropbox repository enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3642 | Moodle: authenticated remote code execution risk in the moodle lms equella repository</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3642</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. A remote code execution risk was identified in the Moodle LMS EQUELLA repository. By default, this was only available to teachers and managers on sites with the EQUELLA repository enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3643 | Moodle: reflected xss risk in policy tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3643</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. The return URL in the policy tool required additional sanitizing to prevent a reflected Cross-site scripting (XSS) risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3644 | Moodle: ajax section delete does not respect course_can_delete_section()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3644</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Additional checks were required to prevent users from deleting course sections they did not have permission to modify.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3645 | Moodle: idor in messaging web service allows access to some user details</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3645</link><description>A flaw was found in Moodle. Insufficient capability checks in a messaging web service allowed users to view other users' names and online statuses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3647 | Moodle: idor when accessing the cohorts report</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3647</link><description>A flaw was discovered in Moodle. Additional checks were required to ensure that users can only access cohort data they are authorized to retrieve.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43016 | In JetBrains Rider before 2025.1.2 custom archive unpacker allowed arbitrary file overwrite during remote debug session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43016</link><description>In JetBrains Rider before 2025.1.2 custom archive unpacker allowed arbitrary file overwrite during remote debug session</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46432 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 base64-encoded credentials could be exposed in build logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46432</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 base64-encoded credentials could be exposed in build logs</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46433 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 improper path validation in loggingPreset parameter was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46433</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 improper path validation in loggingPreset parameter was possible</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46618 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 stored XSS was possible on Data Directory tab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46618</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.03.1 stored XSS was possible on Data Directory tab</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57375 | Andamiro Pump It Up 20th Anniversary (aka Double X or XX/2019) 1.00.0-2.08.3 allows a physically proximate attacker to cause a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57375</link><description>Andamiro Pump It Up 20th Anniversary (aka Double X or XX/2019) 1.00.0-2.08.3 allows a physically proximate attacker to cause a denial of service (application crash) via certain deselect actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3634 | Moodle: moodle allows course self-enrolment before completing mfa</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3634</link><description>A security vulnerability was discovered in Moodle that allows students to enroll themselves in courses without completing all the necessary safety checks. Specifically, users can sign up for courses prematurely, even if they haven't finished two-step verification processes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28354 | An issue in the Printer Manager Systm of Entrust Corp Printer Manager D3.18.4-3 and below allows attackers to execute a directory traversal ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28354</link><description>An issue in the Printer Manager Systm of Entrust Corp Printer Manager D3.18.4-3 and below allows attackers to execute a directory traversal via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 14:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6198 | SNORE Interface Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6198</link><description>The device exposes a web interface on ports TCP/3030 and TCP/9882. This web service runs lighttpd, which implements the “SNORE” interface. This interface is affected by a stack buffer overflow vulnerability due to insecure path parsing. An attacker
with access to the LAN network interface could use a specially crafted HTTP request to exploit a buffer overflow on the modem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6199 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6199</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker on the WAN interface, with the ability to intercept Dynamic DNS (DDNS) traffic between DDNS services and the modem, could manipulate specific responses to include code that forces a buffer overflow on the modem.

Customers that have not enabled Dynamic DNS on their modem are not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11917 | JobSearch WP Job Board &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Authentication Bypass via Social Logins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11917</link><description>The JobSearch WP Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8. This is due to improper configurations in the 'jobsearch_xing_response_data_callback', 'set_access_tokes', and 'google_callback' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as the first connected Xing user, or any connected Xing user if the Xing id is known. It is also possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as the first connected Google user if the user has logged in, without subsequently logging out, in thirty days. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2470 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 5.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via &amp;#x27;nsl_registration_store_extra_input&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2470</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress, used by the Service Finder - Directory and Job Board WordPress Theme, is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 5.1. This is due to a lack of restriction on user role in the 'nsl_registration_store_extra_input' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an account on the site with an arbitrary role, including Administrator, when registering via a social login. The Nextend Social Login plugin must be installed and configured to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2986 | IBM Maximo Asset Management cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2986</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3912 | WS Form LITE – Drag &amp;amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.10.35 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3912</link><description>The WS Form LITE – Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_config' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.10.35. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the value of the plugin's settings, including API keys for integrated services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1565 | Mayosis Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1565</link><description>The Mayosis Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.1 via the library/wave-audio/peaks/remote_dl.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 09:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1279 | BM Content Builder &amp;lt;= 3.16.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1279</link><description>The BM Content Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the ux_cb_tools_import_item_ajax AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3870 | 1 Decembrie 1918 &amp;lt;= 1.dec.2012 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3870</link><description>The 1 Decembrie 1918 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.dec.2012. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 1-decembrie-1918/1-decembrie-1918.php page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46535 | WordPress Custom Login and Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46535</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AlphaEfficiencyTeam Custom Login and Registration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Custom Login and Registration: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 08:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46482 | WordPress WP Quiz plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46482</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MyThemeShop WP Quiz allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Quiz: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 07:58:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2238 | Vikinger &amp;lt;= 1.9.30 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via &amp;#x27;vikinger_user_meta_update_ajax&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2238</link><description>The Vikinger theme for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.30. This is due to insufficient user_meta restrictions in the 'vikinger_user_meta_update_ajax' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to escalate their privileges to Administrator-level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3743 | Upsell Funnel Builder for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Unauthenticated Order Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3743</link><description>The Upsell Funnel Builder for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to order manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0. This is due to the plugin allowing the additional product ID and discount field to be manipulated prior to processing via the 'add_offer_in_cart' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to arbitrarily update the product associated with any order bump, and arbitrarily update the discount applied to any order bump item, when adding it to the cart.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3866 | Add Google +1 (Plus one) social share Button &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3866</link><description>The Add Google +1 (Plus one) social share Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the google-plus-one-share-button page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3867 | Ajax Comment Form CST &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3867</link><description>The Ajax Comment Form CST plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation via the 'acform_cst_settings' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3868 | Custom Admin-Bar Favorites &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3868</link><description>The Custom Admin-Bar Favorites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'menuObject' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46616 | Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 allows potential Arbitrary Remote Code Execution (RCE) via upload of a file. This affects StorNext...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46616</link><description>Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 allows potential Arbitrary Remote Code Execution (RCE) via upload of a file. This affects StorNext RYO before 7.2.4, StorNext Xcellis Workflow Director before 7.2.4, and ActiveScale Cold Storage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46617 | Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 grants access to internal StorNext configuration and unauthorized modification of some software co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46617</link><description>Quantum StorNext Web GUI API before 7.2.4 grants access to internal StorNext configuration and unauthorized modification of some software configuration parameters via undocumented user credentials. This affects StorNext RYO before 7.2.4, StorNext Xcellis Workflow Director before 7.2.4, and ActiveScale Cold Storage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0671 | Email Subscribers &amp;lt; 5.7.50 - Admin+ Stored XSS in Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0671</link><description>The Icegram Express  WordPress plugin before 5.7.50 does not sanitise and escape some of its Template settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46613 | OpenPLC 3 through 64f9c11 has server.cpp Memory Corruption because a thread may access handleConnections arguments after the parent stack fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46613</link><description>OpenPLC 3 through 64f9c11 has server.cpp Memory Corruption because a thread may access handleConnections arguments after the parent stack frame becomes unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2580 | Contact Form by Bit Form &amp;lt;= 2.18.3 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2580</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.18.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3511 | Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3511</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation CC-Link IE TSN Remote I/O module, CC-Link IE TSN Analog-Digital Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN Digital-Analog Converter module, CC-Link IE TSN FPGA module and CC-Link IE TSN Remote Station Communication LSI CP620 with GbE-PHY allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service condition in the products by sending specially crafted UDP packets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3861 | Prevent Direct Access 2.8.6 - 2.8.8.2 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Multiple Media Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3861</link><description>The Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data| due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'pda_lite_custom_permission_check' function in versions 2.8.6 to 2.8.8.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to access and change the protection status of media.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3923 | Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3923</link><description>The Prevent Direct Access – Protect WordPress Files plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'generate_unique_string' due to insufficient randomness of the generated file name. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including files protected by the plugin if the attacker can determine the file name.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 05:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3752 | Able Player, accessible HTML5 media player &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via preload Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3752</link><description>The Able Player, accessible HTML5 media player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘preload’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3775 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery via URL Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3775</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 via the woolentor_template_proxy function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application, and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46599 | CNCF K3s 1.32 before 1.32.4-rc1+k3s1 has a Kubernetes kubelet configuration change with the unintended consequence that, in some situations,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46599</link><description>CNCF K3s 1.32 before 1.32.4-rc1+k3s1 has a Kubernetes kubelet configuration change with the unintended consequence that, in some situations, ReadOnlyPort is set to 10255. For example, the default behavior of a K3s online installation might allow unauthenticated access to this port, exposing credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 04:37:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46595 | An XSS issue was discovered in the Flag module before 1.x-3.6.2 for Backdrop CMS. Flag is a module that allows flags to be added to nodes, c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46595</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in the Flag module before 1.x-3.6.2 for Backdrop CMS. Flag is a module that allows flags to be added to nodes, comments, users, and any other type of entity. It doesn't verify flag links before performing the flag action, or verify that the response returned was provided by the flag module. This can allow crafted HTML to result in Cross Site Scripting. This is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have a role with permission to create links on the website, for example: create or edit comments or content with a filtered text format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46544 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, a low-privileged user can elevate their privileges by creating new users and roles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46544</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, a low-privileged user can elevate their privileges by creating new users and roles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46545 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the functionality for adding or updating licenses allows for stored XSS attacks by an administrator through t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46545</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the functionality for adding or updating licenses allows for stored XSS attacks by an administrator through the name parameter. The XSS payload can execute when the license expires.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46546 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, multiple time-based blind SQL injections can be performed by an authenticated user. This affects api/gui/asse...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46546</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, multiple time-based blind SQL injections can be performed by an authenticated user. This affects api/gui/asset/list, /api/gui/files/export/csv/, /api/gui/files/list, /api/gui/process/export/csv, /api/gui/process/export/xlsx, /api/gui/process/listAll, /api/gui/processVersion/export/csv/, /api/gui/processVersion/export/xlsx/, /api/gui/processVersion/list/, /api/gui/robot/list/, /api/gui/task/export/csv/, /api/gui/task/export/xlsx/, and /api/gui/task/list/.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46547 | In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the web application lacks protection against CSRF attacks, with resultant effects of an attacker conducting X...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46547</link><description>In Sherpa Orchestrator 141851, the web application lacks protection against CSRF attacks, with resultant effects of an attacker conducting XSS attacks, adding a new user or role, or exploiting a SQL injection issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43864 | React Router allows a DoS via cache poisoning by forcing SPA mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43864</link><description>React Router is a router for React. Starting in version 7.2.0 and prior to version 7.5.2, it is possible to force an application to switch to SPA mode by adding a header to the request. If the application uses SSR and is forced to switch to SPA, this causes an error that completely corrupts the page. If a cache system is in place, this allows the response containing the error to be cached, resulting in a cache poisoning that strongly impacts the availability of the application. This issue has been patched in version 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43865 | React Router allows pre-render data spoofing on React-Router framework mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43865</link><description>React Router is a router for React. In versions on the 7.0 branch prior to version 7.5.2, it's possible to modify pre-rendered data by adding a header to the request. This allows to completely spoof its contents and modify all the values ​​of the data object passed to the HTML. This issue has been patched in version 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2185 | ALBEDO Telecom Net.Time - PTP/NTP Clock Insufficient Session Expiration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2185</link><description>ALBEDO Telecom Net.Time - PTP/NTP clock (Serial No. NBC0081P) software release 1.4.4 is vulnerable to an insufficient session expiration vulnerability, which
 could permit an attacker to transmit passwords over unencrypted 
connections, resulting in the product becoming vulnerable to 
interception.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3606 | Vestel AC Charger Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3606</link><description>Vestel AC Charger 
version 

3.75.0 contains a vulnerability that 
could enable an attacker to access files containing sensitive 
information, such as credentials which could be used to further 
compromise the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46272 | Planet Technology Network Products OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46272</link><description>WGS-80HPT-V2 and WGS-4215-8T2S are vulnerable to a command injection 
attack that could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute OS 
commands on the host system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46273 | Planet Technology Network Products Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46273</link><description>UNI-NMS-Lite uses hard-coded credentials that could allow an 
unauthenticated attacker to gain administrative privileges to all 
UNI-NMS managed devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46274 | Planet Technology Network Products Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46274</link><description>UNI-NMS-Lite uses hard-coded credentials that could allow an 
unauthenticated attacker to read, manipulate and create entries in the 
managed database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:19:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46275 | Planet Technology Network Products Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46275</link><description>WGS-80HPT-V2 and WGS-4215-8T2S are missing authentication that could 
allow an attacker to create an administrator account without knowing any
 existing credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:19:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46271 | Planet Technology Network Products OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46271</link><description>UNI-NMS-Lite is vulnerable to a command injection attack that could 
allow an unauthenticated attacker to read or manipulate device data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1294 | eForm &amp;lt;= 4.18.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1294</link><description>The eForm - WordPress Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 4.18.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 22:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3749 | Breeze Display &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via cal_size Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3749</link><description>The Breeze Display plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cal_size’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 22:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25777 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Codeastro Bus Ticket Booking System v1.0 allows unauthorized access to user profiles. By manipula...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25777</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Codeastro Bus Ticket Booking System v1.0 allows unauthorized access to user profiles. By manipulating the user ID in the URL, an attacker can access another user's profile without proper authentication or authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29529 | ITC Systems Multiplan/Matrix OneCard platform v3.7.4.1002 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Forgotpa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29529</link><description>ITC Systems Multiplan/Matrix OneCard platform v3.7.4.1002 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the component Forgotpassword.aspx.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43861 | ManageWiki Vulnerable to Self-XSS in review dialog via unsanitized field reflection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43861</link><description>ManageWiki is a MediaWiki extension allowing users to manage wikis. Prior to commit 2f177dc, ManageWiki is vulnerable to reflected or stored XSS in the review dialog. A logged-in attacker must change a form field to include a malicious payload. If that same user then opens the "Review Changes" dialog, the payload will be rendered and executed in the context of their own session. This issue has been patched in commit 2f177dc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44759 | HCL Leap is affected by Cross-site scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44759</link><description>Improper sanitization of SVG files in HCL Leap
allows client-side script injection in deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44760 | HCL Leap is affected by an unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44760</link><description>Unsafe default file type filter policy in HCL
Leap allows execution of unsafe JavaScript in deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:45:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37516 | HCL Leap is affected by missing &amp;quot;no cache&amp;quot; headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37516</link><description>Missing "no cache" headers in HCL Leap permits user directory information to be cached.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30127 | HCL Leap is affected by missing &amp;quot;no cache&amp;quot; headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30127</link><description>Missing "no cache" headers in HCL Leap permits sensitive data to be cached.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26382 | iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) Tool - Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26382</link><description>Under certain circumstances the iSTAR Configuration Utility (ICU) tool could have a buffer overflow issue</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43859 | h11 accepts some malformed Chunked-Encoding bodies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43859</link><description>h11 is a Python implementation of HTTP/1.1. Prior to version 0.16.0, a leniency in h11's parsing of line terminators in chunked-coding message bodies can lead to request smuggling vulnerabilities under certain conditions. This issue has been patched in version 0.16.0. Since exploitation requires the combination of buggy h11 with a buggy (reverse) proxy, fixing either component is sufficient to mitigate this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43858 | YoutubeDLSharp allows command injection on windows system due to non sanitized arguments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43858</link><description>YoutubeDLSharp is a wrapper for the command-line video downloaders youtube-dl and yt-dlp. In versions starting from 1.0.0-beta4 and prior to 1.1.2, an unsafe conversion of arguments allows the injection of a malicious commands when starting `yt-dlp` from a commands prompt running on Windows OS with the `UseWindowsEncodingWorkaround` value defined to true (default behavior). If a user is using built-in methods from the YoutubeDL.cs file, the value is true by default and a user cannot disable it from these methods. This issue has been patched in version 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31324 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver (Visual Composer development server)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31324</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer Metadata Uploader is not protected with a proper authorization, allowing unauthenticated agent to upload potentially malicious executable binaries that could severely harm the host system. This could significantly affect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37534 | HCL Leap is affected by a Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37534</link><description>Insufficient URI protocol whitelist in HCL Leap
allows script injection through query parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45720 | HCL Leap is affected by a disclosure of private personal information vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45720</link><description>Insufficient default configuration in HCL Leap
allows anonymous access to directory information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30113 | HCL Leap is affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30113</link><description>Insufficient sanitization policy in HCL Leap
allows client-side script injection in the deployed application through the
HTML widget.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30114 | HCL Leap is affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30114</link><description>Insufficient sanitization in HCL Leap allows
client-side script injection in the authoring environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30147 | HCL Leap is affected by a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30147</link><description>Multiple vectors in HCL Leap allow client-side
script injection in the authoring environment and deployed applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30148 | HCL Leap is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30148</link><description>Improper access control of endpoint in HCL Leap
allows certain admin users to import applications from the
server's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32921 | WordPress Arrival theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32921</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPoperation Arrival allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Arrival: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39359 | WordPress CWW Portfolio theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39359</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Code Work Web CWW Portfolio allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects CWW Portfolio: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39360 | WordPress Grace Mag theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39360</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in everestthemes Grace Mag allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Grace Mag: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39377 | WordPress Appsero Helper plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39377</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in weDevs Appsero Helper allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Appsero Helper: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39378 | WordPress Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.37 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39378</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Holest Engineering Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Spreadsheet Price Changer for WooCommerce and WP E-commerce – Light: from n/a through 2.4.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39379 | WordPress Capturly plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39379</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Capturly Capturly allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Capturly: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39381 | WordPress KiotViet Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39381</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kiotviet KiotViet Sync allows Stored XSS. This issue affects KiotViet Sync: from n/a through 1.8.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39382 | WordPress ACF: Google Font Selector plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39382</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in danielpataki ACF: Google Font Selector allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ACF: Google Font Selector: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39383 | WordPress Xews Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39383</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Code Work Web Xews Lite allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Xews Lite: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39384 | WordPress Product Lister for eBay plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39384</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in cedcommerce Product Lister for eBay allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Product Lister for eBay: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39385 | WordPress Sirat theme &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39385</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VW Themes Sirat allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Sirat: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39387 | WordPress Opstore theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39387</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WPoperation Opstore allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Opstore: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39390 | WordPress Booking and Rental Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39390</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in magepeopleteam Booking and Rental Manager allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Booking and Rental Manager: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39391 | WordPress Checkout Field Visibility for WooCommerce plugin  &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39391</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in zamartz Checkout Field Visibility for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Checkout Field Visibility for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39397 | WordPress Anything Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39397</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gopiplus@hotmail.com Anything Popup allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Anything Popup: from n/a through 7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39399 | WordPress License For Envato plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39399</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Ashraful Sarkar Naiem License For Envato allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects License For Envato: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39400 | WordPress User Registration plugin &amp;lt; 4.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39400</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpeverest User Registration allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects User Registration: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39404 | WordPress Sassy Social Share plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.73 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39404</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Heateor Support Sassy Social Share allows Phishing. This issue affects Sassy Social Share: from n/a through 3.3.73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39408 | WordPress BruteGuard – Brute Force Login Protection plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39408</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EverPress BruteGuard – Brute Force Login Protection allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BruteGuard – Brute Force Login Protection: from n/a through 0.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46230 | WordPress Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 1.1.35 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46230</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in GhozyLab Popup Builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Popup Builder: from n/a through 1.1.35.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46234 | WordPress Control Listings plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Habibur Rahman Razib Control Listings allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Control Listings: from n/a through 1.0.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46248 | WordPress Frontend Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46248</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in M A Vinoth Kumar Frontend Dashboard allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Frontend Dashboard: from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46260 | WordPress Sky Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wowDevs Sky Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sky Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46261 | WordPress Seriously Simple Podcasting plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Craig Hewitt Seriously Simple Podcasting allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Seriously Simple Podcasting: from n/a through 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46264 | WordPress PowerPress Podcasting &amp;lt;= 11.12.5 - Arbitrary File Upload Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46264</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Angelo Mandato PowerPress Podcasting allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects PowerPress Podcasting: from n/a through 11.12.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46435 | WordPress Time Based Greeting plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46435</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yash Binani Time Based Greeting allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Time Based Greeting: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46436 | WordPress SCSS-Library &amp;lt;= 0.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46436</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sebastian Echeverry SCSS-Library allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SCSS-Library: from n/a through 0.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46438 | WordPress GTDB Guitar Tuners &amp;lt;= 4.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46438</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in warmwhisky GTDB Guitar Tuners allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GTDB Guitar Tuners: from n/a through 4.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46439 | WordPress Plugin Central plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46439</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Vladimir Prelovac Plugin Central allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Plugin Central: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46442 | WordPress Loan Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46442</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Casey Johnson Loan Calculator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Loan Calculator: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46443 | WordPress Animate &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46443</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Adam Pery Animate allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Animate: from n/a through 0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46445 | WordPress External Markdown &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46445</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pReya External Markdown allows Stored XSS. This issue affects External Markdown: from n/a through 0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46447 | WordPress Fable Extra &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46447</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFable Fable Extra allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Fable Extra: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46449 | WordPress WoWHead Tooltips &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46449</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Novium WoWHead Tooltips allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WoWHead Tooltips: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46450 | WordPress occupancyplan plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46450</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in x000x occupancyplan allows Stored XSS. This issue affects occupancyplan: from n/a through 1.0.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46451 | WordPress Floating Social Bar &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46451</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Syed Balkhi Floating Social Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Floating Social Bar: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46452 | WordPress Google News plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46452</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Olav Kolbu Google News allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Google News: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46453 | WordPress Zoho Creator Forms &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46453</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CreatorTeam Zoho Creator Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Zoho Creator Forms: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46457 | WordPress Wp Custom CMS Block plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46457</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in digontoahsan Wp Custom CMS Block allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Wp Custom CMS Block: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46459 | WordPress Confirm User Registration &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46459</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ralf Hortt Confirm User Registration allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Confirm User Registration: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46461 | WordPress RRSSB &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46461</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Relentless Apps RRSSB allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects RRSSB: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46462 | WordPress WPVN &amp;lt;= 0.7.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46462</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Trân Minh-Quân WPVN allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WPVN: from n/a through 0.7.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46465 | WordPress Print Science Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.155 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46465</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in John Weissberg Print Science Designer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Print Science Designer: from n/a through 1.3.155.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46466 | WordPress Modern Polls plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46466</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in felixtz Modern Polls allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Modern Polls: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46467 | WordPress RAphicon &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46467</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rahendra Putra K™ RAphicon allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects RAphicon: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46469 | WordPress Send From &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46469</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Benjamin Buddle Send From allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Send From: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46470 | WordPress Smart Hashtags [#hashtagger] &amp;lt;= 7.2.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46470</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Peter Raschendorfer Smart Hashtags [#hashtagger] allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Smart Hashtags [#hashtagger]: from n/a through 7.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46471 | WordPress WP Custom Post Popup &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46471</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in gnanavelshenll WP Custom Post Popup allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects WP Custom Post Popup: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46472 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46472</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46473 | WordPress Social Counter &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46473</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in djjmz Social Counter allows Object Injection. This issue affects Social Counter: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46475 | WordPress Able Player &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46475</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in terrillthompson Able Player allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Able Player: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46476 | WordPress Awesome Wp Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46476</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nayon46 Awesome Wp Image Gallery allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Awesome Wp Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46477 | WordPress WP Customize Login Page &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46477</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Carlo La Pera WP Customize Login Page allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Customize Login Page: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46478 | WordPress Dropdown Content &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46478</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in metaloha Dropdown Content allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dropdown Content: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46479 | WordPress BBCode Deluxe &amp;lt;= 2020.08.01.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46479</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DevynCJohnson BBCode Deluxe allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects BBCode Deluxe: from n/a through 2020.08.01.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46480 | WordPress Nepali Post Date &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46480</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Padam Shankhadev Nepali Post Date allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Nepali Post Date: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46481 | WordPress Flickr Shortcode Importer &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - PHP Object Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46481</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Michael Cannon Flickr Shortcode Importer allows Object Injection. This issue affects Flickr Shortcode Importer: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46483 | WordPress Peadig’s Google +1 Button &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46483</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alex Moss Peadig’s Google +1 Button allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Peadig’s Google +1 Button: from n/a through 0.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46484 | WordPress Image Hover Effects For WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46484</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nasir179125 Image Hover Effects For WPBakery Page Builder allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Image Hover Effects For WPBakery Page Builder: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46485 | WordPress WP Customize Login Page &amp;lt;= 1.6.5 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46485</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Carlo La Pera WP Customize Login Page allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WP Customize Login Page: from n/a through 1.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46489 | WordPress Bulk Assign Linked Products For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46489</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in vinodvaswani9 Bulk Assign Linked Products For WooCommerce allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Bulk Assign Linked Products For WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46491 | WordPress Multi-Column Taxonomy List &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46491</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matthew Muro Multi-Column Taxonomy List allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Multi-Column Taxonomy List: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46492 | WordPress Call Now PHT Blog plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46492</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Pham Thanh Call Now PHT Blog allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Call Now PHT Blog: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46495 | WordPress Drop Caps plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46495</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in tomontoast Drop Caps allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Drop Caps: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46496 | WordPress Mini twitter feed &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46496</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in oniswap Mini twitter feed allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mini twitter feed: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46497 | WordPress Navegg Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46497</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Navegg Navegg Analytics allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Navegg Analytics: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46498 | WordPress Zalo Official Live Chat &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46498</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in nghialuu Zalo Official Live Chat allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Zalo Official Live Chat: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46499 | WordPress PayPal Express Checkout plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46499</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hccoder PayPal Express Checkout allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PayPal Express Checkout: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46501 | WordPress Mixcloud Embed &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46501</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in biancardi Mixcloud Embed allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Mixcloud Embed: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46502 | WordPress LSD Custom taxonomy and category meta plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46502</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bas Matthee LSD Custom taxonomy and category meta allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects LSD Custom taxonomy and category meta: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46503 | WordPress Simple Google Photos Grid &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46503</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in josheli Simple Google Photos Grid allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple Google Photos Grid: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46504 | WordPress Vasaio QR Code plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46504</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Olar Marius Vasaio QR Code allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Vasaio QR Code: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46505 | WordPress Peekaboo &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46505</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in farinspace Peekaboo allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Peekaboo: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46506 | WordPress WpZon – Amazon Affiliate Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46506</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Lora77 WpZon – Amazon Affiliate Plugin allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WpZon – Amazon Affiliate Plugin: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46507 | WordPress Unsafe Mimetypes plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46507</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ldrumm Unsafe Mimetypes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Unsafe Mimetypes: from n/a through 0.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46508 | WordPress Advanced lazy load plugin &amp;lt;=  1.6.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46508</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in kasonzhao Advanced lazy load allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advanced lazy load: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46509 | WordPress 360 View &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46509</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Andrey Mikhalchuk 360 View allows Stored XSS. This issue affects 360 View: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46510 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46510</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in harrysudana Contact Form 7 Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Calendar: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46511 | WordPress BeerXML Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.71 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46511</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Derek Springer BeerXML Shortcode allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects BeerXML Shortcode: from n/a through 0.71.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46512 | WordPress Custom Functions Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46512</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shamim Hasan Custom Functions Plugin allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Functions Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46513 | WordPress All in One Time Clock Lite &amp;lt;= 1.3.324 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46513</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Codebangers All in One Time Clock Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects All in One Time Clock Lite: from n/a through 1.3.324.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46514 | WordPress Milat jQuery Automatic Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46514</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in milat Milat jQuery Automatic Popup allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Milat jQuery Automatic Popup: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46516 | WordPress Twitter Card Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46516</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in silencecm Twitter Card Generator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Twitter Card Generator: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46517 | WordPress Blog Manager WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46517</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdiscover Blog Manager WP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Blog Manager WP: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46519 | WordPress Media Library Downloader &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46519</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Michael Revellin-Clerc Media Library Downloader allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Media Library Downloader: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46520 | WordPress Related Posts via Taxonomies plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46520</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in alphasis Related Posts via Taxonomies allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Related Posts via Taxonomies: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46521 | WordPress WS Force Login Page &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46521</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Silver Muru WS Force Login Page allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WS Force Login Page: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46522 | WordPress Tabs plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46522</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Billy Bryant Tabs allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tabs: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46523 | WordPress COVID-19 (Coronavirus) Update Your Customers &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46523</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in devignstudiosltd COVID-19 (Coronavirus) Update Your Customers allows Stored XSS. This issue affects COVID-19 (Coronavirus) Update Your Customers: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46524 | WordPress WP Filter Post Category plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46524</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in stesvis WP Filter Post Category allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Filter Post Category: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46525 | WordPress WP Cookie Consent &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in msmitley WP Cookie Consent allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP Cookie Consent: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46528 | WordPress Availability Calendar &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46528</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Steve Availability Calendar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Availability Calendar: from n/a through 0.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46529 | WordPress Business Contact Widget &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46529</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in StressFree Sites Business Contact Widget allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Business Contact Widget: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46530 | WordPress Hacklog Remote Attachment &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46530</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in HuangYe WuDeng Hacklog Remote Attachment allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Hacklog Remote Attachment: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46531 | WordPress WP AVCL Automation Helper (formerly WPFlyLeads) &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46531</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Ankur Vishwakarma WP AVCL Automation Helper (formerly WPFlyLeads) allows Server Side Request Forgery. This issue affects WP AVCL Automation Helper (formerly WPFlyLeads): from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46532 | WordPress Tooltip &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46532</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Haris Zulfiqar Tooltip allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Tooltip: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46533 | WordPress Landing pages and Domain aliases for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46533</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpdrift.no Landing pages and Domain aliases for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Landing pages and Domain aliases for WordPress: from n/a through 0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46534 | WordPress Image Style Hover &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46534</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DanielRiera Image Style Hover allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Image Style Hover: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46536 | WordPress Carousel-of-post-images &amp;lt;= 1.07 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RichardHarrison Carousel-of-post-images allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Carousel-of-post-images: from n/a through 1.07.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46538 | WordPress Inline Text Popup &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46538</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webplanetsoft Inline Text Popup allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Inline Text Popup: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46540 | WordPress GNA Search Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46540</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chris Mok GNA Search Shortcode allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GNA Search Shortcode: from n/a through 0.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46541 | WordPress WP-reCAPTCHA-bp &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in elrata_ WP-reCAPTCHA-bp allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP-reCAPTCHA-bp: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46542 | WordPress Xpert Tab &amp;lt;=  1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46542</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeXpert Xpert Tab allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Xpert Tab: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29568 | A vulnerability has been discovered in the code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0. The issue affects some unknown feature...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29568</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in the code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0. The issue affects some unknown features in the file /Scheduling/pages/class_sched.php. Manipulating the class parameter can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44134 | A vulnerability was found in Code-Projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 in the file /Scheduling/pages/class_save.php. Manipul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44134</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Code-Projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 in the file /Scheduling/pages/class_save.php. Manipulation of parameter class will lead to SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44135 | A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 in /Scheduling/pages/profile_update.php. Manipulating...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44135</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Class and Exam Scheduling System 1.0 in /Scheduling/pages/profile_update.php. Manipulating the parameter username will cause SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43855 | tRPC 11 WebSocket DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43855</link><description>tRPC allows users to build &amp; consume fully typesafe APIs without schemas or code generation. In versions starting from 11.0.0 to before 11.1.1, an unhandled error is thrown when validating invalid connectionParams which crashes a tRPC WebSocket server. This allows any unauthenticated user to crash a tRPC 11 WebSocket server. Any tRPC 11 server with WebSocket enabled with a createContext method set is vulnerable. This issue has been patched in version 11.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30408 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30408</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 39904.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30409 | Denial of service due to allocation of resources without limits. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Win...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30409</link><description>Denial of service due to allocation of resources without limits. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 39904.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46420 | Libsoup: memory leak on soup_header_parse_quality_list() via soup-headers.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46420</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. It is vulnerable to memory leaks in the soup_header_parse_quality_list() function when parsing a quality list that contains elements with all zeroes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46421 | Libsoup: information disclosure may leads libsoup client sends authorization header to a different host when being redirected by a server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46421</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. When libsoup clients encounter an HTTP redirect, they mistakenly send the HTTP Authorization header to the new host that the redirection points to. This allows the new host to impersonate the user to the original host that issued the redirect.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27820 | Apache HttpComponents: PSL (Public Suffix List) validation bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27820</link><description>A bug in PSL validation logic in Apache HttpClient 5.4.x disables domain checks, affecting cookie management and host name verification. Discovered by the Apache HttpClient team. Fixed in the 5.4.3 release</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 11:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47662 | Unauthenticated remote shutdown of the cobot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47662</link><description>Due to missing authorization an unauthenticated remote attacker can cause a DoS attack by connecting via HTTPS and triggering the shutdown button.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47663 | Improper session handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47663</link><description>Due to improper JSON Web Tokens implementation an unauthenticated remote attacker can guess a valid session ID and therefore impersonate a user to gain full access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47664 | Enumeration of valid user names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47664</link><description>Due to improper authentication mechanism an unauthenticated remote attacker can enumerate valid usernames.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3872 | Privilege escalation by altering payload in contact form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3872</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Centreon centreon-web (User configuration form modules) allows SQL Injection.


A user with high privileges is able to become administrator by intercepting the contact form request and altering its payload.



This issue affects Centreon: from 22.10.0 before 22.10.28, from 23.04.0 before 23.04.25, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.20, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.10, from 24.10.0 before 24.10.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13307 | Reales WP - Real Estate WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Attachment Deletion and Favorite Property Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13307</link><description>The Reales WP - Real Estate WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'reales_delete_file', 'reales_delete_file_plans', 'reales_add_to_favourites', and 'reales_remove_from_favourites' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary attachments, and add or remove favorite property listings for any user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1284 | Woocommerce Automatic Order Printing | ( Formerly WooCommerce Google Cloud Print) &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Order Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1284</link><description>The Woocommerce Automatic Order Printing | ( Formerly WooCommerce Google Cloud Print) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 via the xc_woo_printer_preview AJAX action due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view other user's invoices and orders which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2543 | Advanced Accordion Gutenberg Block &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2543</link><description>The Advanced Accordion Gutenberg Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2579 | Lottie Player &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2579</link><description>The Lottie Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the uploaded file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3058 | Xelion Webchat &amp;lt;=  9.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3058</link><description>The Xelion Webchat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the xwc_save_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3065 | Database Toolset &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3065</link><description>The Database Toolset plugin is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in a function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3101 | Configurator Theme Core &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3101</link><description>The Configurator Theme Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating user meta fields prior to updating them in the database. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change escalate their privileges to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3280 | ELEX WooCommerce Advanced Bulk Edit Products, Prices &amp;amp; Attributes &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3280</link><description>The ELEX WooCommerce Advanced Bulk Edit Products, Prices &amp; Attributes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'attribute_value_filter' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3300 | WPMasterToolKit (WPMTK) – All in one plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) to Arbitrary File Read and Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3300</link><description>The WPMasterToolKit (WPMTK) – All in one plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read and modify the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3603 | Flynax Bridge &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3603</link><description>The Flynax Bridge plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3604 | Flynax Bridge &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3604</link><description>The Flynax Bridge plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3607 | Frontend Login and Registration Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3607</link><description>The Frontend Login and Registration Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating a password. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3776 | Verification SMS with TargetSMS &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Unauthenticated Limited Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3776</link><description>The Verification SMS with TargetSMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 via the 'targetvr_ajax_handler' function. This is due to a lack of validation on the type of function that can be called. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute any callable function on the site, such as phpinfo().</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3793 | Buddypress Force Password Change &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Account Takeover via Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3793</link><description>The Buddypress Force Password Change plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authenticated account takeover due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the 'bp_force_password_ajax' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above and under certain prerequisites, to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3832 | FuseDesk &amp;lt;= 6.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via successredirect Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3832</link><description>The FuseDesk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘successredirect’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 08:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12244 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12244</link><description>An issue has been discovered in access controls could allow users to view certain restricted project information even when related features are disabled in GitLab EE, affecting all versions from 17.7 prior to 17.9.7, 17.10 prior to 17.10.5, and 17.11 prior to 17.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0639 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0639</link><description>An issue has been discovered affecting service availability via issue preview in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.7 before 17.9.7, 17.10 before 17.10.5, and 17.11 before 17.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1908 | Business Logic Errors in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1908</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE that could allow an attacker to track users' browsing activities, potentially leading to full account take-over, affecting all versions from 16.6 before 17.9.7, 17.10 before 17.10.5, and 17.11 before 17.11.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3761 | My Tickets – Accessible Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 2.0.16 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3761</link><description>The My Tickets – Accessible Event Ticketing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.16. This is due to the mt_save_profile() function not appropriately restricting access to unauthorized users to update roles. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update their role to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41423 | Unauthorized Playbooks Post Deletion in Mattermost Playbooks Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41423</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.10 fail to properly validate permissions for the API endpoint /plugins/playbooks/api/v0/signal/keywords/ignore-thread, allowing any user or attacker to delete posts containing actions created by the Playbooks bot, even without channel access or appropriate permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 07:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35965 | DoS in Mattermost Playbooks via Excessive Task Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35965</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.10 fail to validate the uniqueness and quantity of task actions within the UpdateRunTaskActions GraphQL operation, which allows an attacker to create task items containing an excessive number of actions triggered by specific posts, overloading the server and leading to a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41395 | Webapp DoS via malicious retrospective post in Playbooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41395</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.4.x &lt;= 10.4.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.0, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.10 fail to properly validate the props used by the RetrospectivePost custom post type in the Playbooks plugin, which allows an attacker to create a specially crafted post with maliciously crafted props and cause a denial of service (DoS) of the web app for all users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:57:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32730 | Use of hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability in i-PRO Configuration Tool affects the network system for i-PRO Co., Ltd. surveillance ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32730</link><description>Use of hard-coded cryptographic key vulnerability in i-PRO Configuration Tool affects the network system for i-PRO Co., Ltd. surveillance cameras and recorders. This vulnerability allows a local authenticated attacker to use the authentication information from the last connected surveillance cameras and recorders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1453 | Category Posts Widget &amp;lt; 4.9.20 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1453</link><description>The Category Posts Widget WordPress plugin before 4.9.20 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2558 | The Wound &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2558</link><description>The-wound WordPress theme through 0.0.1 does not validate some parameters before using them to generate paths passed to include function/s, allowing unauthenticated users to perform LFI attacks and download arbitrary file from the server</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 06:27:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3435 | MangBoard WP &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Board Header And Footer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3435</link><description>The Mang Board WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the board_header and board_footer parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 03:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1976 | Code injection exposure in Fabric OS 9.1.0 through 9.1.1d6</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1976</link><description>Brocade Fabric OS versions starting with 9.1.0 have root access removed, however, a local user with admin privilege can potentially execute arbitrary code with full root privileges on Fabric OS versions 9.1.0 through 9.1.1d6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46419 | Westermo WeOS 5 through 5.23.0 allows a reboot via a malformed ESP packet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46419</link><description>Westermo WeOS 5 through 5.23.0 allows a reboot via a malformed ESP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 02:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46417 | The unsafe globals in Picklescan before 0.0.25 do not include ssl. Consequently, ssl.get_server_certificate can exfiltrate data via DNS afte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46417</link><description>The unsafe globals in Picklescan before 0.0.25 do not include ssl. Consequently, ssl.get_server_certificate can exfiltrate data via DNS after deserialization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:53:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27581 | NIH BRICS (aka Biomedical Research Informatics Computing System) through 14.0.0-67 allows users who lack the InET role to access the InET mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27581</link><description>NIH BRICS (aka Biomedical Research Informatics Computing System) through 14.0.0-67 allows users who lack the InET role to access the InET module via direct requests to known endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 23:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27580 | NIH BRICS (aka Biomedical Research Informatics Computing System) through 14.0.0-67 generates predictable tokens (that depend on username, ti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27580</link><description>NIH BRICS (aka Biomedical Research Informatics Computing System) through 14.0.0-67 generates predictable tokens (that depend on username, time, and the fixed 7Dl9#dj- string) and thus allows unauthenticated users with a Common Access Card (CAC) to escalate privileges and compromise any account, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 23:18:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25045 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25045</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information 11.7 Server authenticated user to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in a request.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 22:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25046 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25046</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 DataStage Flow Designer 

transmits sensitive information via URL or query parameters that could be exposed to an unauthorized actor using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 22:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22351 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22351</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information 11.7 Server does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 22:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46397 | fig2dev stack-overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46397</link><description>Stack-overflow in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker possible code execution via local input manipulation via bezier_spline function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46398 | fig2dev stack-overflow via read_objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46398</link><description>Stack-overflow in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker possible code execution via local input manipulation via read_objects function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46399 | fig2dev segmentation fault in genge_itp_spline</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46399</link><description>Segmentation fault in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker to availability via local input manipulation via genge_itp_spline function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46400 | fig2dev segmentation fault in read_arcobject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46400</link><description>Segmentation fault in fig2dev in version 3.2.9a allows an attacker to availability via local input manipulation via read_arcobject function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28169 | BYD QIN PLUS DM-i Dilink OS v3.0_13.1.7.2204050.1 to v3.0_13.1.7.2312290.1_0 was discovered to cend broadcasts to the manufacturer's cloud s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28169</link><description>BYD QIN PLUS DM-i Dilink OS v3.0_13.1.7.2204050.1 to v3.0_13.1.7.2312290.1_0 was discovered to cend broadcasts to the manufacturer's cloud server unencrypted, allowing attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32818 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN Virtual office interface allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to crash t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32818</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN Virtual office interface allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to crash the firewall, potentially leading to a Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 19:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58251 | In netstat in BusyBox through 1.37.0, local users can launch of network application with an argv[0] containing an ANSI terminal escape seque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58251</link><description>In netstat in BusyBox through 1.37.0, local users can launch of network application with an argv[0] containing an ANSI terminal escape sequence, leading to a denial of service (terminal locked up) when netstat is used by a victim.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28025 | TOTOLINK A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 wer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28025</link><description>TOTOLINK A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 were found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v14 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3900 | Colorbox - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-041</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3900</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Colorbox allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Colorbox: from 0.0.0 before 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3901 | Bootstrap Site Alert - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-042</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Bootstrap Site Alert allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Bootstrap Site Alert: from 0.0.0 before 1.13.0, from 3.0.0 before 3.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3902 | Block Class - Moderately critical - Cross Site Scripting - SA-CONTRIB-2025-043</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3902</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Drupal Block Class allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Block Class: from 4.0.0 before 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3903 | UEditor - 百度编辑器 - Critical - Unsupported - SA-CONTRIB-2025-044</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3903</link><description>Vulnerability in Drupal UEditor - 百度编辑器.This issue affects UEditor - 百度编辑器: *.*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3904 | Sportsleague - Critical - Unsupported - SA-CONTRIB-2025-045</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3904</link><description>Vulnerability in Drupal Sportsleague.This issue affects Sportsleague: *.*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3907 | Search API Solr - Moderately critical - Cross Site Request Forgery - SA-CONTRIB-2025-046</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3907</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Drupal Search API Solr allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Search API Solr: from 0.0.0 before 4.3.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28021 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi through the v14 and v3 p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28021</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi through the v14 and v3 parameters</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28028 | TOTOLINK A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 wer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28028</link><description>TOTOLINK A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 were found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v5 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2760 | GIMP XWD File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2760</link><description>GIMP XWD File Parsing Integer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XWD files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in an integer overflow before allocating a buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25082.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2761 | GIMP FLI File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2761</link><description>GIMP FLI File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of GIMP. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FLI files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25100.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2762 | CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Missing Root of Trust Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2762</link><description>CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Missing Root of Trust Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA devices. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the application system-on-chip (SoC). The issue results from the lack of a properly configured hardware root of trust. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the boot process. Was ZDI-CAN-25948.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2763 | CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2763</link><description>CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of update packages on USB drives. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24356.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2764 | CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA update.cgi Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2764</link><description>CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA update.cgi Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA devices. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of update packages provided to update.cgi. The issue results from the lack of proper verification of a cryptographic signature. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24355.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2765 | CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Wireless Hotspot Hard-Coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2765</link><description>CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA Wireless Hotspot Hard-Coded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of CarlinKit CPC200-CCPA devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of the wireless hotspot. The issue results from the use of hard-coded credentials. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-24349.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2767 | Arista NG Firewall User-Agent Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2767</link><description>Arista NG Firewall User-Agent Cross-Site Scripting Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Minimal user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of the User-Agent HTTP header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can lead to the injection of an arbitrary script. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24407.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2768 | Bdrive NetDrive Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2768</link><description>Bdrive NetDrive Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Bdrive NetDrive. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL. The product loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25041.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2769 | Bdrive NetDrive Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2769</link><description>Bdrive NetDrive Uncontrolled Search Path Element Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Bdrive NetDrive. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the configuration of OpenSSL. The product loads an OpenSSL configuration file from an unsecured location. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25295.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2770 | BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Cleartext Password Storage Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2770</link><description>BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Cleartext Password Storage Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BEC Technologies routers. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web-based user interface. The issue results from storing credentials in a recoverable format. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-25986.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2771 | BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2771</link><description>BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of BEC Technologies routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the web-based user interface. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25894.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2772 | BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Insufficiently Protected Credentials Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2772</link><description>BEC Technologies Multiple Routers Insufficiently Protected Credentials Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BEC Technologies routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within /cgi-bin/tools_usermanage.asp. The issue results from transmitting a list of users and their credentials to be handled on the client side. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose transported credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-25895.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2773 | BEC Technologies Multiple Routers sys ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2773</link><description>BEC Technologies Multiple Routers sys ping Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of BEC Technologies Multiple Routers. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the management interface, which listens on TCP port 22 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-25903.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1045 | Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1045</link><description>Luxion KeyShot Viewer KSP File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot Viewer. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of KSP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24586.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1046 | Luxion KeyShot SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1046</link><description>Luxion KeyShot SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23646.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1047 | Luxion KeyShot PVS File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1047</link><description>Luxion KeyShot PVS File Parsing Access of Uninitialized Pointer Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Luxion KeyShot. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of pvs files. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23694.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1048 | Sonos Era 300 Speaker libsmb2 Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1048</link><description>Sonos Era 300 Speaker libsmb2 Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sonos Era 300 speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of SMB data. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the anacapa user. Was ZDI-CAN-25535.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1049 | Sonos Era 300 Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1049</link><description>Sonos Era 300 Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Sonos Era 300 speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the processing of ID3 data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the anacapa user. Was ZDI-CAN-25601.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1050 | Sonos Era 300 Out-of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1050</link><description>Sonos Era 300 Out-of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Sonos Era 300 speakers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HLS playlist data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the anacapa user. Was ZDI-CAN-25606.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1520 | PostHog ClickHouse Table Functions SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1520</link><description>PostHog ClickHouse Table Functions SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PostHog. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the SQL parser. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the database account. Was ZDI-CAN-25350.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1521 | PostHog slack_incoming_webhook Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1521</link><description>PostHog slack_incoming_webhook Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PostHog. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of the slack_incoming_webhook parameter. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a URI prior to accessing resources. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25352.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1522 | PostHog database_schema Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1522</link><description>PostHog database_schema Server-Side Request Forgery Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PostHog. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the database_schema method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a URI prior to accessing resources. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose information in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-25358.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28020 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v25 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28020</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v25 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28022 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v25 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28022</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v25 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:58:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28018 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v14 parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28018</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in downloadFile.cgi through the v14 parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28019 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28019</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the downloadFile.cgi component</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29526 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function of Q4 Inc Investor Relations Platform v5.147.1.2 allows attackers to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29526</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function of Q4 Inc Investor Relations Platform v5.147.1.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Javascript via injecting a crafted payload into the SearchTerm parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28017 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5032_B20200408 is vulnerable to Command Injection in downloadFile.cgi via the QUERY_STRING parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28017</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5032_B20200408 is vulnerable to Command Injection in downloadFile.cgi via the QUERY_STRING parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47829 | pnpm uses the md5 path shortening function causes packet paths to coincide, which causes indirect packet overwriting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47829</link><description>pnpm is a package manager. Prior to version 10.0.0, the path shortening function uses the md5 function as a path shortening compression function, and if a collision occurs, it will result in the same storage path for two different libraries. Although the real names are under the package name /node_modoules/, there are no version numbers for the libraries they refer to. This issue has been patched in version 10.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21605 | Redis DoS Vulnerability due to unlimited growth of output buffers abused by unauthenticated client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21605</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. In versions starting at 2.6 and prior to 7.4.3, An unauthenticated client can cause unlimited growth of output buffers, until the server runs out of memory or is killed. By default, the Redis configuration does not limit the output buffer of normal clients (see client-output-buffer-limit). Therefore, the output buffer can grow unlimitedly over time. As a result, the service is exhausted and the memory is unavailable. When password authentication is enabled on the Redis server, but no password is provided, the client can still cause the output buffer to grow from "NOAUTH" responses until the system will run out of memory. This issue has been patched in version 7.4.3. An additional workaround to mitigate this problem without patching the redis-server executable is to block access to prevent unauthenticated users from connecting to Redis. This can be done in different ways. Either using network access control tools like firewalls, iptables, security groups, etc, or enabling TLS and requiring users to authenticate using client side certificates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32969 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-rest-server allows SQL injection in query endpoint of REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32969</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 1.8 and prior to 15.10.16, 16.4.6, and 16.10.1, it is possible for a remote unauthenticated user to escape from the HQL execution context and perform a blind SQL injection to execute arbitrary SQL statements on the database backend, including when "Prevent unregistered users from viewing pages, regardless of the page rights" and "Prevent unregistered users from editing pages, regardless of the page rights" options are enabled. Depending on the used database backend, the attacker may be able to not only obtain confidential information such as password hashes from the database, but also execute UPDATE/INSERT/DELETE queries. This issue has been patched in versions 16.10.1, 16.4.6 and 15.10.16. There is no known workaround, other than upgrading XWiki.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32966 | Dataease H2 JDBC Connection Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32966</link><description>DataEase is an open-source BI tool alternative to Tableau. Prior to version 2.10.8, authenticated users can complete RCE through the backend JDBC link. This issue has been patched in version 2.10.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32968 | org.xwiki.platform:xwiki-platform-oldcore allows SQL injection in short form select requests through the script query API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32968</link><description>XWiki is a generic wiki platform. In versions starting from 1.6-milestone-1 to before 15.10.16, 16.4.6, and 16.10.1, it is possible for a user with SCRIPT right to escape from the HQL execution context and perform a blind SQL injection to execute arbitrary SQL statements on the database backend. Depending on the used database backend, the attacker may be able to not only obtain confidential information such as password hashes from the database, but also execute UPDATE/INSERT/DELETE queries. This issue has been patched in versions 16.10.1, 16.4.6 and 15.10.16. There is no known workaround, other than upgrading XWiki. The protection added to this REST API is the same as the one used to validate complete select queries, making it more consistent. However, while the script API always had this protection for complete queries, it's important to note that it's a very strict protection and some valid, but complex, queries might suddenly require the author to have programming right.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46394 | In tar in BusyBox through 1.37.0, a TAR archive can have filenames hidden from a listing through the use of terminal escape sequences.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46394</link><description>In tar in BusyBox through 1.37.0, a TAR archive can have filenames hidden from a listing through the use of terminal escape sequences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45429 | In the Tenda ac9 v1.0 router with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, there is a stack overflow vulnerability in /goform/WifiWpsStart, which may le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45429</link><description>In the Tenda ac9 v1.0 router with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, there is a stack overflow vulnerability in /goform/WifiWpsStart, which may lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45427 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, the security parameter of /goform/WifiBasicSet has a stack overflow vulnerability, which...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45427</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, the security parameter of /goform/WifiBasicSet has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45428 | In Tenda ac9 v1.0 with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg has a stack overflow vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45428</link><description>In Tenda ac9 v1.0 with firmware V15.03.05.14_multi, the rebootTime parameter of /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46393 | In multispectral MIFF image processing in ImageMagick before 7.1.1-44, packet_size is mishandled (related to the rendering of all channels i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46393</link><description>In multispectral MIFF image processing in ImageMagick before 7.1.1-44, packet_size is mishandled (related to the rendering of all channels in an arbitrary order).</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43965 | In MIFF image processing in ImageMagick before 7.1.1-44, image depth is mishandled after SetQuantumFormat is used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43965</link><description>In MIFF image processing in ImageMagick before 7.1.1-44, image depth is mishandled after SetQuantumFormat is used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 14:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43716 | A directory traversal vulnerability exists in Ivanti LANDesk Management Gateway through 4.2-1.9. By appending %3F.php to the URI of the /cli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43716</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in Ivanti LANDesk Management Gateway through 4.2-1.9. By appending %3F.php to the URI of the /client/index.php endpoint, an attacker can bypass access controls and gain unauthorized access to various endpoints such as /client/index.php%3F.php/gsb/firewall.php within the management web panel, potentially exposing sensitive device information. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2703 | The built-in XY Chart plugin is vulnerable to a DOM XSS vulnerability. 

A user with Editor permissions is able to modify such a panel in or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2703</link><description>The built-in XY Chart plugin is vulnerable to a DOM XSS vulnerability. 

A user with Editor permissions is able to modify such a panel in order to make it execute arbitrary JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42604 | Detailed Error Response Vulnerability in Meon KYC solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42604</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Meon KYC solutions due to debug mode is enabled in certain API endpoints. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing certain unauthorized API endpoints leading to detailed error messages as response leading to disclosure of system related information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42605 | Improper Access Control Vulnerability in Meon Bidding Solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42605</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Meon Bidding Solutions due to improper authorization controls on certain API endpoints for the initiation, modification, or cancellation operations. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameter in the API request body to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attacker to perform authorized manipulation of data associated with other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42602 | Improper Authentication Vulnerability in Meon KYC solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42602</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Meon KYC solutions due to improper handling of access and refresh tokens in certain API endpoints of authentication process. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting and manipulating the responses through API request body leading to unauthorized access of other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42603 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in Meon KYC solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42603</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the Meon KYC solutions due to transmission of sensitive data in plain text within the response payloads of certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting API response that contains unencrypted sensitive information belonging to other users.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attacker to impersonate the target user and gain unauthorized access to the user account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42600 | Brute Force Attack Vulnerability in Meon KYC solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42600</link><description>This vulnerability exists in KYC solutions due to missing restrictions on the number of incorrect One-Time Password (OTP) attempts through certain API endpoints of login process. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a brute force attack on OTP, which could lead to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42601 | Captcha Bypass Vulnerability in Meon KYC solutions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42601</link><description>This vulnerability exists in KYC solutions due to insufficient server-side validation of the Captcha in certain API endpoints. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by intercepting the request and removing the Captcha parameter leading to bypassing the Captcha verification mechanism.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:41:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10306 | Mod_proxy_cluster: mod_proxy_cluster unauthorized mcmp requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10306</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mod_proxy_cluster. The issue is that the  directive should be replaced by the  directive as the former does not restrict IP/host access as `Require ip IP_ADDRESS` would suggest. This means that anyone with access to the host might send MCMP requests that may result in adding/removing/updating nodes for the balancing. However, this host should not be accessible to the public network as it does not serve the general traffic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 10:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1054 | UiCore Elements – Free Elementor widgets and templates &amp;lt;= 1.0.16 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1054</link><description>The UiCore Elements – Free Elementor widgets and templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the UI Counter, UI Icon Box, UI Testimonial Slider, UI Testimonial Grid, and UI Testimonial Carousel widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 09:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2595 | Forced Browsing Vulnerability in CODESYS Visualization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2595</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can bypass the user management in CODESYS Visualization and read visualization template files or static elements by means of forced browsing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3529 | WordPress Simple PayPal Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via file_url Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3529</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2 via the 'file_url' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information and download a digital product without paying for it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3530 | WordPress Simple PayPal Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Unauthenticated Product Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3530</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to product price manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2. This is due to a logic flaw involving the inconsistent use of parameters during the cart addition process. The plugin uses the parameter 'product_tmp_two' for computing a security hash against price tampering while using 'wspsc_product' to display the product, allowing an unauthenticated attacker to substitute details from a cheaper product and bypass payment for a more expensive item.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 07:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0618 | A malicious third party could invoke a persistent denial of service vulnerability in FireEye EDR agent by sending a specially-crafted tamper...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0618</link><description>A malicious third party could invoke a persistent denial of service vulnerability in FireEye EDR agent by sending a specially-crafted tamper protection event to the HX service to trigger an exception. This exception will prevent any further tamper protection events from being processed, even after a reboot of HX.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 06:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0926 | Gee-netics, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to remove system files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0926</link><description>Gee-netics, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to remove system files causing a boot loop by redirecting a file deletion when recording video.
Axis has released a patched version for the highlighted flaw. Please 
refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 05:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1056 | Gee-netics, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has identified an issue with a specific file that the server is using. A n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1056</link><description>Gee-netics, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has identified an issue with a specific file that the server is using. A non-admin user can modify this file to either create files or change the content of files in an admin-protected location.
Axis has released a patched version for the highlighted flaw. Please 
refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 05:37:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1021 | Missing authorization vulnerability in synocopy in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.1.1-42962-8, 7.2.1-69057-7 and 7.2.2-72806-3 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1021</link><description>Missing authorization vulnerability in synocopy in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.1.1-42962-8, 7.2.1-69057-7 and 7.2.2-72806-3 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 03:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>