<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 04:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-10131 | Remote Code Execution in infiniflow/ragflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10131</link><description>The `add_llm` function in `llm_app.py` in infiniflow/ragflow version 0.11.0 contains a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability. The function uses user-supplied input `req['llm_factory']` and `req['llm_name']` to dynamically instantiate classes from various model dictionaries. This approach allows an attacker to potentially execute arbitrary code due to the lack of comprehensive input validation or sanitization. An attacker could provide a malicious value for 'llm_factory' that, when used as an index to these model dictionaries, results in the execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 04:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25218 | Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp;amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25218</link><description>The Photo Gallery Slideshow &amp; Masonry Tiled Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 03:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9219 | WordPress Social Share Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.19 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9219</link><description>The WordPress Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29213 | Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29213</link><description>Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via unspecified attack vector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29821 | Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via uns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29821</link><description>Ivanti DSM &lt; version 2024.2 allows authenticated users on the local machine to run code with elevated privileges due to insecure ACL via unspecified attack vector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37404 | Improper Input Validation in the admin portal of Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.1 and 9.1R18.9, or Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37404</link><description>Improper Input Validation in the admin portal of Ivanti Connect Secure before 22.7R2.1 and 9.1R18.9, or Ivanti Policy Secure before 22.7R1.1 allows a remote authenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 23:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43577 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43577</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 22:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10129 | HFO4 shudong-share Share create_share.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10129</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in HFO4 shudong-share up to 2.4.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /includes/create_share.php of the component Share Handler. The manipulation of the argument fkey leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10130 | Tenda AC8 SetSysAutoRebbotCfg formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10130</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. This vulnerability affects the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10128 | Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer td.js.gz risky encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10128</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer 2.01. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file td.js.gz. The manipulation leads to risky cryptographic algorithm. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 21:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10123 | Tenda AC8 saveParentControlInfo compare_parentcontrol_time stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10123</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC8 16.03.34.06. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function compare_parentcontrol_time of the file /goform/saveParentControlInfo. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This is not the same issue like CVE-2023-33671. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10122 | Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer Operator Details Form InnerRepPlus.html missing password field masking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Topdata Inner Rep Plus WebServer 2.01. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /InnerRepPlus.html of the component Operator Details Form. The manipulation leads to missing password field masking. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49361 | Potential Vulnerability in ACON Library: Improper Input Validation Leading to Malicious Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49361</link><description>ACON is a widely-used library of tools for machine learning that focuses on adaptive correlation optimization. A potential vulnerability has been identified in the input validation process, which could lead to arbitrary code execution if exploited. This issue could allow an attacker to submit malicious input data, bypassing input validation, resulting in remote code execution in certain machine learning applications using the ACON library. All users utilizing ACON’s input-handling functions are potentially at risk. Specifically, machine learning models or applications that ingest user-generated data without proper sanitization are the most vulnerable. Users running ACON on production servers are at heightened risk, as the vulnerability could be exploited remotely. As of time of publication, it is unclear whether a fix is available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 19:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10121 | wfh45678 Radar Interface authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10121</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wfh45678 Radar up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Interface Handler. The manipulation with the input /../ leads to authorization bypass. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This appears not to be a path traversal weakness. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45944 | In J2eeFAST &lt;=2.7, the backend function has unsafe filtering, which allows an attacker to trigger certain sensitive functions resulting in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45944</link><description>In J2eeFAST &lt;=2.7, the backend function has unsafe filtering, which allows an attacker to trigger certain sensitive functions resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 18:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9593 | Time Clock &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 &amp;amp; Time Clock Pro &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated (Limited) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9593</link><description>The Time Clock plugin and Time Clock Pro plugin for WordPress are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 (for Time Clock) and 1.1.4 (for Time Clock Pro) via the 'etimeclockwp_load_function_callback' function. This allows unauthenticated attackers to execute code on the server. The invoked function's parameters cannot be specified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 17:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10120 | wfh45678 Radar upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10120</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wfh45678 Radar up to 1.0.8 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /services/v1/common/upload. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48016 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48016</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure. The attacker may be able to use exposed credentials to access the system with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47241 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47241</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.0 Appliance - SRS, version(s) 5.24, contains an Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to unauthorized access and modification of transmitted data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6080 | Privilege Escalation to SYSTEM in Lakeside Software Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6080</link><description>Lakeside Software’s SysTrack LsiAgent Installer version 10.7.8 for Windows contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability which allows attackers SYSTEM level access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42508 | This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42508</link><description>This vulnerability could be exploited, leading to unauthorized disclosure of information to authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9537 | ScienceLogic SL1 unspecified vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9537</link><description>ScienceLogic SL1 (formerly EM7) is affected by an unspecified vulnerability involving an unspecified third-party component packaged with SL1. The vulnerability is addressed in SL1 versions 12.1.3+, 12.2.3+, and 12.3+.  Remediations have been made available for all SL1 versions back to version lines 10.1.x, 10.2.x, 11.1.x, 11.2.x, and 11.3.x.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47240 | Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47240</link><description>Dell Secure Connect Gateway (SCG) 5.24 contains an Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability. A local attacker with low privileges can access the file system and could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain write access to unauthorized data and cause a version update failure condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9674 | Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9674</link><description>The Debrandify · Remove or Replace WordPress Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43300 | WordPress Movie Database plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43300</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bert Kößler Movie Database allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Movie Database: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:36:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49224 | WordPress Mitm Bug Tracker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mahesh Patel Mitm Bug Tracker allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Mitm Bug Tracker: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49225 | WordPress wpPricing Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Swebdeveloper wpPricing Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects wpPricing Builder: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49228 | WordPress bVerse Convert plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CrossedCode bVerse Convert allows Stored XSS.This issue affects bVerse Convert: from n/a through 1.3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49230 | WordPress  Ajax Custom CSS/JS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49230</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Harpreet Singh Ajax Custom CSS/JS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ajax Custom CSS/JS: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49231 | WordPress WordPress Video plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Peter CyClop WordPress Video allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Video: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49232 | WordPress El mejor Cluster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49232</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Javier Loureiro El mejor Cluster allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects El mejor Cluster: from n/a through 1.1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49233 | WordPress MAS Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MadrasThemes MAS Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects MAS Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49234 | WordPress Plexx Elementor Extension plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in themeworm Plexx Elementor Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Plexx Elementor Extension: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49236 | WordPress Crazy Call To Action Box plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hafiz Uddin Ahmed Crazy Call To Action Box allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Crazy Call To Action Box: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49238 | WordPress ADIF Log Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0f - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M. Konieczny, DH9SB ADIF Log Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ADIF Log Search Widget: from n/a through 1.0f.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49239 | WordPress Add Categories Post Footer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nikhil Vaghela Add Categories Post Footer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Add Categories Post Footer: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49240 | WordPress AB Categories Search Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Agustin Berasategui AB Categories Search Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AB Categories Search Widget: from n/a through 0.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49241 | WordPress Tito plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tady Walsh Tito allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Tito: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49243 | WordPress Dynamic Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49243</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jon Vincent Mendoza Dynamic Elementor Addons allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dynamic Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10057 | RSS Feed Widget &amp;lt;= 2.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via rfw-youtube-videos Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10057</link><description>The RSS Feed Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rfw-youtube-videos shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9425 | Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ad_tax_image Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9425</link><description>The Advanced Category and Custom Taxonomy Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ad_tax_image shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47486 | There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47486</link><description>There is an XSS vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could inject scripts into certain pages by building malicious data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47485 | There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to gene...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47485</link><description>There is a CSV injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Master Lite versions. If exploited, an attacker could build malicious data to generate executable commands in the CSV file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47487 | There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47487</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in some HikCentral Professional versions. This could allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4740 | MXsecurity Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4740</link><description>MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior are vulnerable because of the use of hard-coded credentials. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to tamper with sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49570 | Insecure Trust of Basic Constraints certificate in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11210)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49570</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software trusts a certificate issued by an entity that isn't authorized to issue certificates. This occurs when the "Basic Constraints" extension in the certificate indicates that it is meant to be an "End Entity”. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4739 | MXsecurity License Generation Function Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4739</link><description>The lack of access restriction to a resource from unauthorized users makes MXsecurity software versions v1.1.0 and prior vulnerable. By acquiring a valid authenticator, an attacker can pose as an authorized user and successfully access the resource.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49567 | Insecure Trust of certificates using collision hash functions in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11239)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49567</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the product incorrectly checks the site's certificate, which allows an attacker to make MITM SSL connections to an arbitrary site. The product trusts certificates that are issued using the MD5 and SHA1 collision hash functions which allow attackers to create rogue certificates that appear legitimate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6058 | HTTPS Certificate Validation Issue in Bitdefender Safepay (VA-11167)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6058</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Safepay's handling of HTTPS connections. The issue arises when the product blocks a connection due to an untrusted server certificate but allows the user to add the site to exceptions, resulting in the product trusting the certificate for subsequent HTTPS scans. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack by using a self-signed certificate, which the product will trust after the site has been added to exceptions. This can lead to the interception and potential alteration of secure communications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6057 | Insecure Trust of DSA-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11166)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6057</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of certificates issued using the DSA signature algorithm. The product does not properly check the certificate chain, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites using a DSA-signed certificate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10055 | Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpsaio_snapchat Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10055</link><description>The Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpsaio_snapchat shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10078 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10078</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to add, modify, or delete plugin options and posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10079 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10079</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'text' parameter in the 'ajax_import_content' function. This allows authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10080 | WP Easy Post Types &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Meta</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10080</link><description>The WP Easy Post Types plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via post meta in versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:49:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6056 | Insecure Trust of Self-Signed Certificates in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11164)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6056</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality that results in the improper trust of self-signed certificates. The product is found to trust certificates signed with the RIPEMD-160 hashing algorithm without proper validation, allowing an attacker to establish MITM SSL connections to arbitrary sites.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6055 | Improper Certificate Validation in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS Scanning (VA-11158)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6055</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Bitdefender Total Security HTTPS scanning functionality where the software fails to properly validate website certificates. Specifically, if a site certificate lacks the "Server Authentication" specification in the Extended Key Usage extension, the product does not verify the certificate's compliance with the site, deeming such certificates as valid. This flaw could allow an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack, intercepting and potentially altering communications between the user and the website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9206 | MAS Companies For WP Job Manager &amp;lt;= 1.0.13 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9206</link><description>The MAS Companies For WP Job Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9703 | Arconix Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9703</link><description>The Arconix Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 07:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46897 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46897</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource issue exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. A logged-in user with the permission of table management may obtain and/or alter the information of the unauthorized table.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47793 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47793</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Exment v6.1.4 and earlier and Exment v5.0.11 and earlier. When accessing the edit screen containing custom columns (column type: images or files), an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38820 | CVE-2024-38820: Spring Framework DataBinder Case Sensitive Match Exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38820</link><description>The fix for CVE-2022-22968 made disallowedFields patterns in DataBinder case insensitive. However, String.toLowerCase() has some Locale dependent exceptions that could potentially result in fields not protected as expected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10014 | Flat UI Button &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via flatbtn Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10014</link><description>The Flat UI Button plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's flatbtn shortcode in version 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10040 | Infinite-Scroll &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10040</link><description>The Infinite-Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_ajax_edit and process_ajax_delete function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make changes to plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10049 | Edit WooCommerce Templates &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10049</link><description>The Edit WooCommerce Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8740 | GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8740</link><description>The GetResponse Forms by Optin Cat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8790 | Social Share With Floating Bar &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8790</link><description>The Social Share With Floating Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8916 | Suki Sites Import &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8916</link><description>The Suki Sites Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9350 | DPD Baltic Shipping &amp;lt;= 1.2.83 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9350</link><description>The DPD Baltic Shipping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_value' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.83 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9361 | Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename ... &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9361</link><description>The Bulk images optimizer: Resize, optimize, convert to webp, rename … plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_configuration' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9364 | SendGrid for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9364</link><description>The SendGrid for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wp_mailplus_clear_logs' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's log files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9366 | Easy Menu Manager | WPZest &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9366</link><description>The Easy Menu Manager | WPZest plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9373 | Elemenda &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9373</link><description>The Elemenda plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9382 | Gantry 4 Framework &amp;lt;= 4.1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9382</link><description>The Gantry 4 Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'override_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9383 | Parcel Pro &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9383</link><description>The Parcel Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'action' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9452 | Branding &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9452</link><description>The Branding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9848 | Product Customizer Light &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9848</link><description>The Product Customizer Light plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9892 | Add Widget After Content &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9892</link><description>The Add Widget After Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10119 | SECOM WRTM326 - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10119</link><description>The wireless router WRTM326 from SECOM does not properly validate a specific parameter. An unauthenticated remote attacker could execute arbitrary system commands by sending crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10118 | SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10118</link><description>SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC does not properly filter user input in the specific functionality. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject and execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 04:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9264 | Grafana SQL Expressions allow for remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9264</link><description>The SQL Expressions experimental feature of Grafana allows for the evaluation of `duckdb` queries containing user input. These queries are insufficiently sanitized before being passed to `duckdb`, leading to a command injection and local file inclusion vulnerability. Any user with the VIEWER or higher permission is capable of executing this attack.  The `duckdb` binary must be present in Grafana's $PATH for this attack to function; by default, this binary is not installed in Grafana distributions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 03:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49023 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49023</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 23:24:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43566 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43566</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43578 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43578</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43579 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43579</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43580 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43580</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43587 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43587</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43595 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43595</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43596 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43596</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10093 | VSO ConvertXtoDvd ConvertXtoDvd.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10093</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in VSO ConvertXtoDvd 7.0.0.83. Affected is an unknown function in the library avcodec.dll of the file ConvertXtoDvd.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7316 | Denial of Service (DoS) Vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7316</link><description>Improper Validation of Specified Quantity in Input vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric CNC Series allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) condition on the product by sending specially crafted packets to TCP port 683, causing an emergency stop.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26785 | MariaDB v10.5 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26785</link><description>MariaDB v10.5 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39593 | Insecure permissions in the sys_exec function of Oracle MYSQL MariaDB v10.5 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39593</link><description>Insecure permissions in the sys_exec function of Oracle MYSQL MariaDB v10.5 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27766 | An issue in MYSQL MariaDB v.11.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lib_mysqludf_sys.so function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27766</link><description>An issue in MYSQL MariaDB v.11.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lib_mysqludf_sys.so function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30875 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in JavaScript Library jquery-ui v.1.13.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30875</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in JavaScript Library jquery-ui v.1.13.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the window.addEventListener component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33453 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the externalId component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33453</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in esp-idf v.5.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the externalId component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48924 | MessagePack allows untrusted data to lead to DoS attack due to hash collisions and stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48924</link><description>### Impact

When this library is used to deserialize messagepack data from an untrusted source, there is a risk of a denial of service attack by an attacker that sends data contrived to produce hash collisions, leading to large CPU consumption disproportionate to the size of the data being deserialized.

This is similar to [a prior advisory](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/security/advisories/GHSA-7q36-4xx7-xcxf), which provided an inadequate fix for the hash collision part of the vulnerability.

### Patches

The following steps are required to mitigate this risk.

1. Upgrade to a version of the library where a fix is available.
1. Review the steps in [this previous advisory](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/security/advisories/GHSA-7q36-4xx7-xcxf) to ensure you have your application configured for untrusted data.

### Workarounds

If upgrading MessagePack to a patched version is not an option for you, you may apply a manual workaround as follows:

1. Declare a class that derives from `MessagePackSecurity`.
2. Override the `GetHashCollisionResistantEqualityComparer` method to provide a collision-resistant hash function of your own and avoid calling `base.GetHashCollisionResistantEqualityComparer()`.
3. Configure a `MessagePackSerializerOptions` with an instance of your derived type by calling `WithSecurity` on an existing options object.
4. Use your custom options object for all deserialization operations. This may be by setting the `MessagePackSerializer.DefaultOptions` static property, if you call methods that rely on this default property, and/or by passing in the options object explicitly to any `Deserialize` method.

### References

- Learn more about best security practices when reading untrusted data with [MessagePack 1.x](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/tree/v1.x#security) or [MessagePack 2.x](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp#security).
- The .NET team's [discussion on hash collision vulnerabilities of their `HashCode` struct](https://github.com/GrabYourPitchforks/runtime/blob/threat_models/docs/design/security/System.HashCode.md).

### For more information

If you have any questions or comments about this advisory:

* [Start a public discussion](https://github.com/MessagePack-CSharp/MessagePack-CSharp/discussions)
* [Email us privately](mailto:andrewarnott@live.com)</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 20:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49248 | WordPress Ad Inserter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.37 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49248</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Igor Funa Ad Inserter allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ad Inserter: from n/a through 2.7.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49255 | WordPress Da Reactions plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49255</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Daniele Alessandra Da Reactions allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Da Reactions: from n/a through 5.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49259 | WordPress Primary Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49259</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Primary Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Primary Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49261 | WordPress Arkhe Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.23.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LOOS,Inc. Arkhe Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arkhe Blocks: from n/a through 2.23.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49262 | WordPress Country Flags for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wepic Country Flags for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Country Flags for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49263 | WordPress My Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Takashi Matsuyama My Favorites allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My Favorites: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49264 | WordPress Events Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49264</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Events Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Events Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49276 | WordPress Clio Grow plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49276</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themis Solutions, Inc. Clio Grow allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Clio Grow: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49277 | WordPress UltraAddons – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49277</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeAstrology Team UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49278 | WordPress Omnipress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49278</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in omnipressteam Omnipress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Omnipress: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49279 | WordPress Hyperlink Group Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49279</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TipTopPress Hyperlink Group Block allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Hyperlink Group Block: from n/a through 1.17.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49280 | WordPress Lightbox slider -- Responsive Lightbox Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49280</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Weblizar Lightbox slider – Responsive Lightbox Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Lightbox slider – Responsive Lightbox Gallery: from n/a through 1.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49281 | WordPress Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NinjaTeam Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Click to Chat – WP Support All-in-One Floating Widget: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49282 | WordPress Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49282</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in dFactory Responsive Lightbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Responsive Lightbox: from n/a through 2.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49283 | WordPress CURCY plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49283</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VillaTheme CURCY allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CURCY: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49288 | WordPress Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49288</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VillaTheme Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Email Template Customizer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49289 | WordPress Cooked Pro plugin &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49289</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gora Tech LLC Cooked Pro allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cooked Pro: from n/a before 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49292 | WordPress Exclusive Addons for Elementor  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Exclusive Addons Exclusive Addons Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Exclusive Addons Elementor: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49295 | WordPress Simple Testimonials Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49295</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Testimonials Showcase.This issue affects Simple Testimonials Showcase: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49296 | WordPress Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49296</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coder426 Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Add to Cart Button Label and Link: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49298 | WordPress PeproDev Ultimate Invoice plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49298</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev Ultimate Invoice allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PeproDev Ultimate Invoice: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 19:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49301 | WordPress G Meta Keywords plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sinan Yorulmaz G Meta Keywords allows Stored XSS.This issue affects G Meta Keywords: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49302 | WordPress WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49302</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Portfoliohub WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49307 | WordPress Admin Management Xtended plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49307</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Oliver Schlöbe Admin Management Xtended allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Admin Management Xtended: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49308 | WordPress Animator – Scroll Triggered Animations plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Toast Plugins Animator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Animator: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49309 | WordPress Digitally theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49309</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digitally allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Digitally: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49310 | WordPress Themesflat Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49310</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themesflat Themesflat Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themesflat Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49311 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49311</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49316 | WordPress Akismet htaccess writer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49316</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in zodiac Akismet htaccess writer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Akismet htaccess writer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10099 | Stored XSS in comfyanonymous/comfyui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10099</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in comfyanonymous/comfyui version 0.2.2 and possibly earlier. The vulnerability occurs when an attacker uploads an HTML file containing a malicious XSS payload via the `/api/upload/image` endpoint. The payload is executed when the file is viewed through the `/view` API endpoint, leading to potential execution of arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10100 | Path Traversal in binary-husky/gpt_academic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10100</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in binary-husky/gpt_academic version 3.83. The vulnerability is due to improper handling of the file parameter, which is open to path traversal through URL encoding. This allows attackers to view any file on the host system, including sensitive files such as critical application files, SSH keys, API keys, and configuration values.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10101 | Stored XSS in binary-husky/gpt_academic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10101</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in binary-husky/gpt_academic version 3.83. The vulnerability occurs at the /file endpoint, which renders HTML files. Malicious HTML files containing XSS payloads can be uploaded and stored in the backend, leading to the execution of the payload in the victim's browser when the file is accessed. This can result in the theft of session cookies or other sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49319 | WordPress Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49319</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in B.M. Rafiul Alam Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Awesome Contact Form7 for Elementor: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7755 | HMS Networks EWON FLEXY 202 Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7755</link><description>The EWON FLEXY 202 transmits credentials using a weak encoding method base64. An attacker who is present in the network can sniff the traffic and decode the credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43997 | WordPress easy.jobs- Best Recruitment Plugin for Job Board Listing, Manager, Career Page for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43997</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in easy.Jobs EasyJobs allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects EasyJobs: from n/a through 2.4.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49220 | WordPress Cookie Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49220</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cookie Scanner – Nikel Schubert Cookie Scanner allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cookie Scanner: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49221 | WordPress cSlider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49221</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Julian Weinert // cs&amp;amp;m cSlider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects cSlider: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49223 | WordPress CJ Change Howdy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS  vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49223</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shibu Lijack a.K.A CyberJack CJ Change Howdy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CJ Change Howdy: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49229 | WordPress Better Author Bio plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.10.11 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49229</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Arif Nezami Better Author Bio allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Better Author Bio: from n/a through 2.7.10.11.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49237 | WordPress Ahmeti Wp Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49237</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ahmet Imamoglu Ahmeti Wp Timeline allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ahmeti Wp Timeline: from n/a through 5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49304 | WordPress  Pinpoint Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49304</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PINPOINT.WORLD Pinpoint Booking System allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pinpoint Booking System: from n/a through 2.9.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49313 | WordPress VKontakte Wall Post plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49313</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in RudeStan VKontakte Wall Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects VKontakte Wall Post: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49217 | WordPress Adding drop down roles in registration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49217</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Madiri Salman Aashish Adding drop down roles in registration allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Adding drop down roles in registration: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49219 | WordPress RS-Members plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49219</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in themexpo RS-Members allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects RS-Members: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49322 | WordPress Job Board Manager for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49322</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in CodePassenger Job Board Manager for WordPress allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Job Board Manager for WordPress: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:51:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47304 | WordPress Fluent Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Fluent Support allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Fluent Support: from n/a through 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47312 | WordPress Classic Editor and Classic Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPGrim Classic Editor and Classic Widgets allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Classic Editor and Classic Widgets: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49244 | WordPress SV Product Import Export for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in cmssoft CSV Product Import Export for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection.This issue affects CSV Product Import Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49246 | WordPress Ajax Rating with Custom Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in anand23 Ajax Rating with Custom Login allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Ajax Rating with Custom Login: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49297 | WordPress Zoho CRM Lead Magnet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.9.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49297</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Zoho CRM Zoho CRM Lead Magnet allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Zoho CRM Lead Magnet: from n/a through 1.7.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49299 | WordPress Surfer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0.502 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49299</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Surfer allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Surfer: from n/a through 1.5.0.502.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48629 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the IPAddress paramete...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48629</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the IPAddress parameter in the SetGuestZoneRouterSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48630 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the MacAddress paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48630</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the MacAddress parameter in the SetMACFilters2 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48631 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SSID parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48631</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SSID parameter in the SetWLanRadioSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48632 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the LocalIPAd...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48632</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the LocalIPAddress, TCPPorts, and UDPPorts parameters in the SetPortForwardingSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48633 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the ExternalP...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48633</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain multiple command injection vulnerabilities via the ExternalPort, InternalPort, ProtocolNumber, and LocalIPAddress parameters in the SetVirtualServerSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48634 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the key parameter in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48634</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the key parameter in the SetWLanRadioSecurity function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48635 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:2/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48635</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:2/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48636 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:0/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48636</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:0/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48637 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:1/VID param...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48637</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the VLANID:1/VID parameter in the SetVLANSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48638 | D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SubnetMask paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48638</link><description>D-Link DIR_882_FW130B06 and DIR_878 DIR_878_FW130B08 were discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the SubnetMask parameter in the SetGuestZoneRouterSettings function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49235 | WordPress Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49235</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in VideoWhisper.Com Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Contact Forms, Live Support, CRM, Video Messages: from n/a through 1.10.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49284 | WordPress WP SendFox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49284</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in BogdanFix WP SendFox allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects WP SendFox: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49285 | WordPress SSV MailChimp plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49285</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Moridrin SSV MailChimp allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SSV MailChimp: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49291 | WordPress Cooked Pro plugin &amp;lt; 1.8.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49291</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Gora Tech LLC Cooked Pro.This issue affects Cooked Pro: from n/a before 1.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49305 | WordPress Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.10 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPFactory Email Verification for WooCommerce allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Email Verification for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49314 | WordPress JiangQie Free Mini Program plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49314</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in 酱茄 JiangQie Free Mini Program allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects JiangQie Free Mini Program: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49287 | WordPress PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49287</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Marco Heine PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects PDF-Rechnungsverwaltung: from n/a through 0.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49312 | WordPress Edwiser Bridge plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49312</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in WisdmLabs Edwiser Bridge.This issue affects Edwiser Bridge: from n/a through 3.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49317 | WordPress Point Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49317</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in ZIPANG Point Maker allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Point Maker: from n/a through 0.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49318 | WordPress My Reading Library plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49318</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Scott Olson My Reading Library allows Object Injection.This issue affects My Reading Library: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49400 | Tacquito prior to commit 07b49d1358e6ec0b5aa482fcd284f509191119e2 was not properly performing regex matches on authorized commands and argum...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49400</link><description>Tacquito prior to commit 07b49d1358e6ec0b5aa482fcd284f509191119e2 was not properly performing regex matches on authorized commands and arguments. Configured allowed commands/arguments were intended to require a match on the entire string, but instead only enforced a match on a sub-string. That would have potentially allowed unauthorized commands to be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10072 | ESAFENET CDG EncryptPolicyService.java actionAddEncryptPolicyGroup sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10072</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This issue affects the function actionAddEncryptPolicyGroup of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/EncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument checklist leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10073 | flairNLP flair Mode File Loader clustering.py ClusteringModel code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10073</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in flairNLP flair 0.14.0. Affected is the function ClusteringModel of the file flair\models\clustering.py of the component Mode File Loader. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48192 | Tenda G3 v15.01.0.5(2848_755)_EN was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc_ro/shadow, which allows attackers to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48192</link><description>Tenda G3 v15.01.0.5(2848_755)_EN was discovered to contain a hardcoded password vulnerability in /etc_ro/shadow, which allows attackers to log in as root</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49396 | Insufficiently Protected Credentials in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49396</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable due to insufficiently protected credentials, which may allow an attacker to impersonate Elvaco and send false information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49397 | Cross-site Scripting in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49397</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack which may allow an attacker to bypass authentication and takeover admin accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49398 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49398</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to unrestricted file uploads, which may allow an attacker to remotely execute code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49399 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in Elvaco M-Bus Metering Gateway CMe3100</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49399</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to an attacker being able to use commands without providing a password which may allow an attacker to leak information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:42:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10071 | ESAFENET CDG EncryptPolicyService.java actionUpdateEncryptPolicyEdit sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10071</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This vulnerability affects the function actionUpdateEncryptPolicyEdit of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/EncryptPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument encryptPolicyId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9414 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in LCDS LAquis SCADA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9414</link><description>In LAquis SCADA version 4.7.1.511, a cross-site scripting vulnerability could allow an attacker to inject arbitrary code into a web page. This could allow an attacker to steal cookies, redirect users, or perform unauthorized actions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25104 | CoinGate Plugin Payment callback.php postProcess logic error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25104</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CoinGate Plugin up to 1.2.7 on PrestaShop. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function postProcess of the file modules/coingate/controllers/front/callback.php of the component Payment Handler. The manipulation leads to business logic errors. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.2.8 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 0a3097db0aec7c5d66686c142c6abaa1e126ca16. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10069 | ESAFENET CDG MailDecryptApplicationService.java actionPassMainApplication sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10069</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function actionPassMainApplication of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/MailDecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10070 | ESAFENET CDG PolicyPushControlAction.java actionPolicyPush sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10070</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. This affects the function actionPolicyPush of the file /com/esafenet/policy/action/PolicyPushControlAction.java. The manipulation of the argument policyId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47459 | Substance3D - Sampler | NULL Pointer Dereference (CWE-476)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47459</link><description>Substance3D - Sampler versions 4.5 and earlier are affected by a NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service (DoS) condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to crash the application, resulting in a DoS. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48920 | PutongOJ: unprivileged users can escalate privileges by constructing requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48920</link><description>PutongOJ is online judging software. Prior to version 2.1.0-beta.1, unprivileged users can escalate privileges by constructing requests. This can lead to unauthorized access, enabling users to perform admin-level operations, potentially compromising sensitive data and system integrity. This problem has been fixed in v2.1.0.beta.1. As a workaround, one may apply the patch from commit `211dfe9` manually.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9683 | Quay: quay allows successful authentication with trucated version of the password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9683</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quay, which allows successful authentication even when a truncated password version is provided. This flaw affects the authentication mechanism, reducing the overall security of password enforcement.  While the risk is relatively low due to the typical length of the passwords used (73 characters), this vulnerability can still be exploited to reduce the complexity of brute-force or password-guessing attacks. The truncation of passwords weakens the overall authentication process, thereby reducing the effectiveness of password policies and potentially increasing the risk of unauthorized access in the future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2005-10003 | mikexstudios Xcomic os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2005-10003</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in mikexstudios Xcomic up to 0.8.2. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation of the argument cmd leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 0.8.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 6ed8e3cc336e29f09c7e791863d0559939da98bf. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:14:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6333 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution in Altalink, Versalink &amp;amp; WorkCentre Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6333</link><description>Authenticated Remote Code Execution in Altalink, Versalink &amp; WorkCentre Products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49315 | WordPress FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49315</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in CodeFlock FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER allows Path Traversal.This issue affects FREE DOWNLOAD MANAGER: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49579 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47197 insecure plugin iframe allowed arbitrary JavaScript execution and unauthorized API requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49579</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.3.47197 insecure plugin iframe allowed arbitrary JavaScript execution and unauthorized API requests</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49580 | In JetBrains Ktor before 3.0.0 improper caching in HttpCache Plugin could lead to response information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49580</link><description>In JetBrains Ktor before 3.0.0 improper caching in HttpCache Plugin could lead to response information disclosure</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48021 | WordPress Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp;amp; Stripe Add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48021</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Scott Paterson Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Contact Form 7 – PayPal &amp; Stripe Add-on: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:08:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6728 | Nokia SR OS: BOF File Encryption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6728</link><description>Nokia SR OS bof.cfg file encryption is vulnerable to a brute force attack. This weakness allows an attacker in possession of the encrypted file to decrypt the bof.cfg file and obtain the BOF configuration content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6729 | Nokia SR OS: File Access Security Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6729</link><description>Nokia SR OS routers allow read-write access to the entire file system via SFTP or SCP for users configured with "access console." Consequently, a low privilege authenticated user with "access console" can read or replace the router configuration file as well as other files stored in the Compact Flash or SD card without using CLI commands. This type of attack can lead to a compromise or denial of service of the router after the system is rebooted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48022 | WordPress Shortcode For Elementor Templates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48022</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SysBasics Shortcode For Elementor Templates allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Shortcode For Elementor Templates: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48023 | WordPress Restaurant Reservations Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48023</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RestaurantConnect, Inc Restaurant Reservations Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Reservations Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48025 | WordPress Simple Baseball Scoreboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48025</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DOGROW.NET Simple Baseball Scoreboard allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simple Baseball Scoreboard: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48031 | WordPress Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48031</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Sumit Surai Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG): from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48032 | WordPress Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48032</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sumit Surai Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG) allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Featured Posts with Multiple Custom Groups (FPMCG): from n/a through 4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48036 | WordPress SKT Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48036</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48037 | WordPress Contact Form Widget – Contact Query, Contact Page, Form Maker, Query Table plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48037</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in A WP Life Contact Form Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contact Form Widget: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48046 | WordPress Contact Form by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.28 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48046</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Supsystic Contact Form by Supsystic allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contact Form by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.7.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48048 | WordPress Wsify Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48048</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WSIFY – Sales can fly Wsify Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Wsify Widget: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48024 | WordPress Keep Backup Daily plugin &amp;lt;=2.0.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48024</link><description>: Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Keep Backup Daily allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Keep Backup Daily: from n/a through 2.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48038 | WordPress wp-Monalisa plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48038</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hans Matzen wp-Monalisa allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects wp-Monalisa: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48043 | WordPress ShortPixel Image Optimizer plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48043</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ShortPixel ShortPixel Image Optimizer allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects ShortPixel Image Optimizer: from n/a through 5.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48047 | WordPress Linked Variation for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48047</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Razon Komar Pal Linked Variation for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Linked Variation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49320 | WordPress Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.60 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dennis Hoppe Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Encyclopedia / Glossary / Wiki: from n/a through 1.7.60.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10068 | OpenSight Software FlashFXP FlashFXP.exe uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10068</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenSight Software FlashFXP 5.4.0.3970. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function in the library libcrypto-1_1.dll of the file FlashFXP.exe. The manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45713 | SolarWinds Kiwi CatTools Sensitive Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45713</link><description>SolarWinds Kiwi CatTools is susceptible to a sensitive data disclosure vulnerability when a non-default setting has been enabled for troubleshooting purposes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9898 | Parallax Image &amp;lt;= 1.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via dd-parallax Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9898</link><description>The Parallax Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's dd-parallax shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10025 | Vulnerability in SICK CLV6xx, SICK Lector6xx and SICK RFx6xx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10025</link><description>A vulnerability in the .sdd file allows an attacker to read default passwords stored in plain text within the code. By exploiting these plaintext credentials, an attacker can log into affected SICK products as an “Authorized Client” if the customer has not changed the default password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49386 | Sensitive information disclosure due to spell-jacking. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49386</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to spell-jacking. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49389 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49389</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49390 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49390</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49391 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49391</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49392 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on enrollment invitation page. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Win...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49392</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability on enrollment invitation page. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Files (Windows) before build 9.0.0x24.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8920 | Fonto – Custom Web Fonts Manager &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8920</link><description>The Fonto – Custom Web Fonts Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9184 | SendPulse Free Web Push &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9184</link><description>The SendPulse Free Web Push plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to incorrect use of the wp_kses_allowed_html function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 09:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3184 | Multiple CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerabilities were found in GoAhead Web Server up to version 6.0.0 when compiled with the ME_GOA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3184</link><description>Multiple CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerabilities were found in GoAhead Web Server up to version 6.0.0 when compiled with the ME_GOAHEAD_REPLACE_MALLOC flag. Without a memory notifier for allocation failures, remote attackers can exploit these vulnerabilities by sending malicious requests, leading to a crash and Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3186 | CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the evalExpr() function of GoAhead Web Server (version &lt;= 6.0.0) when compiled with the ME...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3186</link><description>CWE-476 NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in the evalExpr() function of GoAhead Web Server (version &lt;= 6.0.0) when compiled with the ME_GOAHEAD_JAVASCRIPT flag. This vulnerability allows a remote attacker with the privileges to modify JavaScript template (JST) files to trigger a crash and cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by providing malicious templates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3187 | This issue tracks two CWE-416 Use After Free (UAF) and one CWE-415 Double Free vulnerabilities in Goahead versions &lt;= 6.0.0. These are cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3187</link><description>This issue tracks two CWE-416 Use After Free (UAF) and one CWE-415 Double Free vulnerabilities in Goahead versions &lt;= 6.0.0. These are caused by JST values not being nulled when freed during parsing of JST templates. If the ME_GOAHEAD_JAVASCRIPT flag is enabled, a remote attacker with the privileges to modify JavaScript template (JST) files could exploit this by providing malicious templates. This may lead to memory corruption, potentially causing a Denial of Service (DoS) or, in rare cases, code execution, though the latter is highly context-dependent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9951 | Wordpress Photo Album Plus &amp;lt;= 8.8.05.003 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9951</link><description>The WP Photo Album Plus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wppa-tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.05.003 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9213 | Persian WooCommerce SMS &amp;lt;= 7.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9213</link><description>The افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5429 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5429</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.1.0 does not validate and escape some of its Slider Settings before outputting them back in attributes, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9351 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.35.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Draft Quiz Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9351</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.35.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the quiz 'create_module' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create draft quizzes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9352 | Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp;amp; Custom Form Builder &amp;lt;= 1.35.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Draft Custom Form Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9352</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.35.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the custom form 'create_module' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create draft forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 05:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49593 | In Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) before 6.3.9 and Secure Custom Fields before 6.3.6.3 (plugins for WordPress), using the Field Group editor t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49593</link><description>In Advanced Custom Fields (ACF) before 6.3.9 and Secure Custom Fields before 6.3.6.3 (plugins for WordPress), using the Field Group editor to edit one of the plugin's fields can result in execution of a stored XSS payload. NOTE: if you wish to use the WP Engine alternative update mechanism for the free version of ACF, then you can follow the process shown at the advancedcustomfields.com blog URL within the References section below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 04:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7417 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.986 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Private Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7417</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.986 via the data_fetch. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8719 | Flexmls® IDX Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.14.22 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8719</link><description>The Flexmls® IDX Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters like 'MaxBeds' and 'MinBeds' in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9263 | WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.25 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password/Email Reset/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9263</link><description>The WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Account Takeover/Privilege Escalation via Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.25 via the save() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the emails and passwords of arbitrary user accounts, including administrators, which makes account takeover and privilege escalation possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9347 | The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9347</link><description>The The Ultimate WordPress Toolkit – WP Extended plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpext-export' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45766 | Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45766</link><description>Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45767 | Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45767</link><description>Dell OpenManage Enterprise, version(s) OME 4.1 and prior, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9215 | Co-Authors, Multiple Authors and Guest Authors in an Author Box with PublishPress Authors &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary User Email Update and Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9215</link><description>The Co-Authors, Multiple Authors and Guest Authors in an Author Box with PublishPress Authors plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference to Privilege Escalation/Account Takeover in all versions up to, and including, 4.7.1 via the action_edited_author() due to missing validation on the 'authors-user_id' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to update arbitrary user accounts email addresses, including administrators, which can then be leveraged to reset that user's account password and gain access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9240 | ReDi Restaurant Reservation &amp;lt;= 24.0902 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9240</link><description>The ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 24.0902. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9861 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9861</link><description>The Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This is due to missing validation on the token being supplied during the otp login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they know the phone number associated with that user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9862 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9862</link><description>The Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources, and the user current password check is missing. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9863 | Miniorange OTP Verification with Firebase &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Privilege Escalation via Registration due to Administrator Default User Role Value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9863</link><description>The UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions up to, and including, 3.6.0 due to the insecure 'administrator' default value for the 'default_user_role' option. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an administrator user even if the registration form is disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9940 | Calculated Fields Form &amp;lt;= 5.2.45 - HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9940</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to HTML Injection in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.45. This is due to the plugin not properly neutralizing HTML elements from submitted forms. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary HTML that will render when the administrator views form submissions in their email.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 02:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>