<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:59:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-2178 | Path Traversal Vulnerability in parisneo/lollms-webui</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2178</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the parisneo/lollms-webui, specifically within the 'copy_to_custom_personas' endpoint in the 'lollms_personalities_infos.py' file. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files by manipulating the 'category' and 'name' parameters during the 'Copy to custom personas folder for editing' process. By inserting '../' sequences in these parameters, attackers can traverse the directory structure and access files outside of the intended directory. Successful exploitation results in unauthorized access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5587 | Casdoor Configuration File app.conf file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Casdoor up to 1.335.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /conf/app.conf of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-266838 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4344 | Shield Security – Smart Bot Blocking &amp;amp; Intrusion Prevention Security &amp;lt;= 19.1.13 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4344</link><description>The Shield Security – Smart Bot Blocking &amp; Intrusion Prevention Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 19.1.13. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the exec function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable pin protection for the admin interface of the plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 04:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35645 | WordPress Random Banner plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vinoth06 Random Banner allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Random Banner: from n/a through 4.2.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35646 | WordPress Smartarget Message Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Smartarget Smartarget Message Bar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Smartarget Message Bar: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35647 | WordPress Global Notification Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Global Notification Bar allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Global Notification Bar: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4148 | Redos (Regular Expression Denial of Service) in lunary-ai/lunary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4148</link><description>A Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the lunary-ai/lunary application, version 1.2.10. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by maliciously manipulating regular expressions, which can significantly impact the response time of the application and potentially render it completely non-functional. Specifically, the vulnerability can be triggered by sending a specially crafted request to the application, leading to a denial of service where the application crashes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35636 | WordPress Uploadcare File Uploader and Adaptive Delivery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35636</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Uploadcare Uploadcare File Uploader and Adaptive Delivery (beta) uploadcare.This issue affects Uploadcare File Uploader and Adaptive Delivery (beta): from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 09:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3200 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3200</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'slug' attribute of the 'wpforo' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3820 | wpDataTables - Tables &amp;amp; Table Charts (Premium) &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3820</link><description>The wpDataTables – WordPress Data Table, Dynamic Tables &amp; Table Charts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id_key' parameter of the wdt_delete_table_row AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. Please note this only affects the premium version of the plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3821 | wpDataTables - Tables &amp;amp; Table Charts (Premium) &amp;lt;= 6.3.2 - Missing Authorization to DataTable Access &amp;amp; Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3821</link><description>The wpDataTables – WordPress Data Table, Dynamic Tables &amp; Table Charts Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several functions in the wdt_ajax_actions.php file in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate data tables. Please note this only affects the premium version of the plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 08:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5348 | Elements For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Multiple Widget Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5348</link><description>The Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 via the 'beforeafter_layout' attribute of the beforeafter widget, the 'eventsgrid_layout' attribute of the eventsgrid and list widgets, the 'marquee_layout' attribute of the marquee widget, the 'postgrid_layout' attribute of the postgrid widget, the 'woocart_layout'  attribute of the woocart widget, and the 'woogrid_layout' attribute of the woogrid widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 08:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2295 | Contact Form Manager &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2295</link><description>The Contact Form Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [xyz-cfm-form] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:48:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4958 | User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4958</link><description>The User Registration – Custom Registration Form, Login Form, and User Profile WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'import_form_action' function in versions up to, and including, 3.2.0.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to import a registration form with a default user role of administrator. If an administrator approves or publishes a post or page with the shortcode to the imported form, any user can register as an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:48:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1324 | QQWorld Auto Save Images &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary Post Content Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1324</link><description>The QQWorld Auto Save Images plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the save_remote_images_get_auto_saved_results() function hooked via a norpriv AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the contents of arbitrary posts that may not be public.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2506 | Popup Builder &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Authenticated(Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom JS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2506</link><description>The Popup Builder – Create highly converting, mobile friendly marketing popups. plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JS functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4087 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.975 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Back to Top Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4087</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Back to Top widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.975 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4342 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.975 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4342</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's image hotspot, image accordion, off canvas, woogrid, and product mini cart widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.975  due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5501 | Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder &amp;lt;= 2.5.51 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5501</link><description>The Supreme Modules Lite – Divi Theme, Extra Theme and Divi Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘button_one_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.51 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6382 | Master Slider - Responsive Touch Slider &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6382</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ms_slide' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'css_class' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 04:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3564 | Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3564</link><description>The Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0 via the plugin's 'content_block' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:42:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3565 | Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via content_block Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3565</link><description>The Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'content_block' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4711 | WordPress Infinite Scroll – Ajax Load More &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4711</link><description>The WordPress Infinite Scroll – Ajax Load More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ajax_load_more shortcode in versions up to, and including, 7.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 02:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2933 | Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks – CoBlocks &amp;lt;= 3.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social Profiles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2933</link><description>The Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks – CoBlocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Social Profiles widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 02:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5138 | The snapctl component within snapd allows a confined snap to interact with the snapd daemon to take certain privileged actions on behalf of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5138</link><description>The snapctl component within snapd allows a confined snap to interact with the snapd daemon to take certain privileged actions on behalf of the snap. It was found that snapctl did not properly parse command-line arguments, allowing an unprivileged user to trigger an authorised action on behalf of the snap that would normally require administrator privileges to perform. This could possibly allow an unprivileged user to perform a denial of service or similar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34009 | moodle: ReCAPTCHA can be bypassed on the login page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34009</link><description>Insufficient checks whether ReCAPTCHA was enabled made it possible to bypass the checks on the login page. This did not affect other pages where ReCAPTCHA is utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:57:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34008 | moodle: CSRF risk in analytics management of models</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34008</link><description>Actions in the admin management of analytics models did not include the necessary token to prevent a CSRF risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34006 | moodle: unsanitized HTML in site log for config_log_created</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34006</link><description>The site log report required additional encoding of event descriptions to ensure any HTML in the content is displayed in plaintext instead of being rendered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34007 | moodle: logout CSRF in admin/tool/mfa/auth.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34007</link><description>The logout option within MFA did not include the necessary token to avoid the risk of users inadvertently being logged out via CSRF.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34004 | moodle: authenticated LFI risk in some misconfigured shared hosting environments via modified mod_wiki backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34004</link><description>In a shared hosting environment that has been misconfigured to allow access to other users' content, a Moodle user with both access to restore wiki modules and direct access to the web server outside of the Moodle webroot could execute a local file include.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34005 | moodle: authenticated LFI risk in some misconfigured shared hosting environments via modified mod_data backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34005</link><description>In a shared hosting environment that has been misconfigured to allow access to other users' content, a Moodle user with both access to restore database activity modules and direct access to the web server outside of the Moodle webroot could execute a local file include.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34002 | moodle: authenticated LFI risk in some misconfigured shared hosting environments via modified mod_feedback backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34002</link><description>In a shared hosting environment that has been misconfigured to allow access to other users' content, a Moodle user with both access to restore feedback modules and direct access to the web server outside of the Moodle webroot could execute a local file include.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34003 | moodle: authenticated LFI risk in some misconfigured shared hosting environments via modified mod_workshop backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34003</link><description>In a shared hosting environment that has been misconfigured to allow access to other users' content, a Moodle user with both access to restore workshop modules and direct access to the web server outside of the Moodle webroot could execute a local file include.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34001 | moodle: CSRF risk in admin preset tool management of presets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34001</link><description>Actions in the admin preset tool did not include the necessary token to prevent a CSRF risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34000 | moodle: stored XSS in lesson overview report via user ID number</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34000</link><description>ID numbers displayed in the lesson overview report required additional sanitizing to prevent a stored XSS risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33999 | moodle: unsafe direct use of $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;HTTP_REFERER&amp;#x27;] in admin/tool/mfa/index.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33999</link><description>The referrer URL used by MFA required additional sanitizing, rather than being used directly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33998 | moodle: stored XSS via user&amp;#x27;s name on participants page when opening some options</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33998</link><description>Insufficient escaping of participants' names in the participants page table resulted in a stored XSS risk when interacting with some features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33997 | moodle: stored XSS risk when editing another user&amp;#x27;s equation in equation editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33997</link><description>Additional sanitizing was required when opening the equation editor to prevent a stored XSS risk when editing another user's equation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33996 | moodle: broken access control when setting calendar event type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33996</link><description>Incorrect validation of allowed event types in a calendar web service made it possible for some users to create events with types/audiences they did not have permission to publish to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36843 | libmodbus v3.1.6 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the modbus_mapping_free() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36843</link><description>libmodbus v3.1.6 was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the modbus_mapping_free() function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36844 | libmodbus v3.1.6 was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the ctx-&gt;backend pointer. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36844</link><description>libmodbus v3.1.6 was discovered to contain a use-after-free via the ctx-&gt;backend pointer. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message sent to the unit-test-server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36845 | An invalid pointer in the modbus_receive() function of libmodbus v3.1.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted me...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36845</link><description>An invalid pointer in the modbus_receive() function of libmodbus v3.1.6 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message sent to the unit-test-server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23316 | PingAccess HTTP Request Desynchronization Weakness</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23316</link><description>HTTP request desynchronization in Ping Identity PingAccess, all versions prior to 8.0.1 affected allows an attacker to send specially crafted http header requests to create a request smuggling condition for proxied requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5564 | Libndp: buffer overflow in route information length field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libndp. This flaw allows a local malicious user to cause a buffer overflow in NetworkManager, triggered by sending a malformed IPv6 router advertisement packet. This issue occurred as libndp was not correctly validating the route length information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31030 | An issue in coap_msg.c in Keith Cullen's FreeCoAP v.0.7 allows remote attackers to cause a Denial of Service or potentially disclose informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31030</link><description>An issue in coap_msg.c in Keith Cullen's FreeCoAP v.0.7 allows remote attackers to cause a Denial of Service or potentially disclose information via a specially crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-44534 | Insufficient user input filtering leads to arbitrary file read by non-authenticated attacker, which results in sensitive information disclos...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-44534</link><description>Insufficient user input filtering leads to arbitrary file read by non-authenticated attacker, which results in sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38042 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability in Ivanti Secure Access Client for Windows allows a low privileged user to execute code as SYSTEM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38042</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability in Ivanti Secure Access Client for Windows allows a low privileged user to execute code as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38551 | A CRLF Injection vulnerability in Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) allows an authenticated high-privileged user to inject malicious code on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38551</link><description>A CRLF Injection vulnerability in Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) allows an authenticated high-privileged user to inject malicious code on a victim’s browser, thereby leading to cross-site scripting attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46810 | A local privilege escalation vulnerability in Ivanti Secure Access Client for Linux before 22.7R1, allows a low privileged user to execute c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46810</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability in Ivanti Secure Access Client for Linux before 22.7R1, allows a low privileged user to execute code as root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22058 | A buffer overflow allows a low privilege user on the local machine that has the EPM Agent installed to execute arbitrary code with elevated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22058</link><description>A buffer overflow allows a low privilege user on the local machine that has the EPM Agent installed to execute arbitrary code with elevated permissions in Ivanti EPM 2021.1 and older.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22059 | A SQL injection vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Neurons for ITSM allows a remote authenticated user to read/modify/delete informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22059</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Neurons for ITSM allows a remote authenticated user to read/modify/delete information in the underlying database. This may also lead to DoS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22060 | An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Neurons for ITSM allows a remote, authenticated, high privileged user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22060</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Neurons for ITSM allows a remote, authenticated, high privileged user to write arbitrary files into sensitive directories of ITSM server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29822 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29822</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29823 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29823</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29824 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29824</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29825 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29825</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29826 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29826</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29827 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the sam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29827</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29828 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29828</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29829 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29829</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29830 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29830</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29846 | An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29846</link><description>An unspecified SQL Injection vulnerability in Core server of Ivanti EPM 2022 SU5 and prior allows an authenticated attacker within the same network to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29848 | An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.x allows an authenticated, privileged user to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29848</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in web component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.x allows an authenticated, privileged user to execute arbitrary commands as SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35196 | Slack integration leaks sensitive information in logs in Sentry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35196</link><description>Sentry is a developer-first error tracking and performance monitoring platform. Sentry's Slack integration incorrectly records the incoming request body in logs. This request data can contain sensitive information, including the deprecated Slack verification token. With this verification token, it is possible under specific configurations, an attacker can forge requests and act as the Slack integration. The request body is leaked in log entries matching `event == "slack.*" &amp;&amp; name == "sentry.integrations.slack" &amp;&amp; request_data == *`. The deprecated slack verification token, will be found in the `request_data.token` key. **SaaS users** do not need to take any action. **Self-hosted users** should upgrade to version 24.5.0 or higher, rotate their Slack verification token, and use the Slack Signing Secret instead of the verification token. For users only using the `slack.signing-secret` in their self-hosted configuration, the legacy verification token is not used to verify the webhook payload. It is ignored. Users unable to upgrade should either set the `slack.signing-secret` instead of `slack.verification-token`. The signing secret is Slack's recommended way of authenticating webhooks. By having `slack.singing-secret` set, Sentry self-hosted will no longer use the verification token for authentication of the webhooks, regardless of whether `slack.verification-token` is set or not. Alternatively if the self-hosted instance is unable to be upgraded or re-configured to use the `slack.signing-secret`, the logging configuration can be adjusted to not generate logs from the integration. The default logging configuration can be found in `src/sentry/conf/server.py`. **Services should be restarted once the configuration change is saved.**</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5176 | Vulnerability in Welch Allyn Configuration Tool Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5176</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability in Baxter Welch Allyn Configuration Tool may allow Remote Services with Stolen Credentials.This issue affects Welch Allyn Configuration Tool: versions 1.9.4.1 and prior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1275 | Vulnerability in Baxter Welch Allyn Connex Spot Monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1275</link><description>Use of Default Cryptographic Key vulnerability in Baxter Welch Ally Connex Spot Monitor may allow Configuration/Environment Manipulation.This issue affects Welch Ally Connex Spot Monitor in all versions prior to 1.52.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35140 | IBM Security Verify Access privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35140</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0 through 10.0.6 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to improper certificate validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  292416.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35142 | IBM Security Verify Access privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35142</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0 through 10.0.6 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to execution of unnecessary privileges.  IBM X-Force ID:  292418.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36120 | javascript-deobfuscator crafted payload can lead to code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36120</link><description>### Impact
Crafted payloads targeting expression simplification can lead to code execution. An example is
```
!'hello\\"+alert(`Hello World`)//"'
```

### Patches
Fix has been released in v1.1.0.

### Workarounds
Upgrade or disable expression simplification feature.

### References
Vulnerability was reported by [SteakEnthusiast](https://github.com/SteakEnthusiast)</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25037 | An issue in wanEditor v4.7.11 and fixed in v.4.7.12 and v.5 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the ima...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25037</link><description>An issue in wanEditor v4.7.11 and fixed in v.4.7.12 and v.5 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the image upload function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-25038 | wanEditor v4.7.11 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the video upload function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-25038</link><description>wanEditor v4.7.11 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the video upload function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:25:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28736 | An issue in Debezium Community debezium-ui v.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the refresh page function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28736</link><description>An issue in Debezium Community debezium-ui v.2.5 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the refresh page function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 15:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36108 | Multiple Broken Function-Level Authorization vulnerabilities in casgate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36108</link><description>casgate is an Open Source Identity and Access Management system. In affected versions `casgate` allows remote unauthenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information via GET request to an API endpoint. This issue has been addressed in PR #201 which is pending merge. An attacker could use `id` parameter of GET requests with value `anonymous/ anonymous` to bypass authorization on certain API endpoints. Successful exploitation of the vulnerability could lead to account takeover, privilege escalation or provide attacker with credential to other services. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7073 | Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail) &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7073</link><description>The Auto Featured Image (Auto Post Thumbnail) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 via the upload_to_library AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5565 | Prompt Injection in &amp;quot;ask&amp;quot; API with visualization leads to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5565</link><description>The Vanna library uses a prompt function to present the user with visualized results, it is possible to alter the prompt using prompt injection and run arbitrary Python code instead of the intended visualization code. Specifically - allowing external input to the library’s “ask” method with "visualize" set to True (default behavior) leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31907 | IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31907</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  289889.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31908 | IBM Planning Analytics Local cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31908</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  289890.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31889 | IBM Planning Analytics Local cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31889</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics Local 2.0 and 2.1 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  288136.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22338 | IBM Security Verify Access OIDC Provider information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22338</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access OIDC Provider 22.09 through 23.03 could disclose sensitive information to a local user due to hazardous input validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  279978.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23692 | Rejetto HTTP File Server 2.3m Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23692</link><description>Rejetto HTTP File Server, up to and including version 2.3m, is vulnerable to a template injection vulnerability. This vulnerability allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system by sending a specially crafted HTTP request. As of the CVE assignment date, Rejetto HFS 2.3m is no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4160 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.2.90 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpdm-all-packages Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4160</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpdm-all-packages' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.90 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5041 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.10.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Accordion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5041</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ha-ia-content-button’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5347 | Happy Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.10.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Navigation Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5347</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'arrow' attribute within the plugin's Post Navigation widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5436 | Type Confusion in Snapchat Lenscore</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5436</link><description>Type confusion in Snapchat LensCore could lead to denial of service or arbitrary code execution prior to version 12.88. We recommend upgrading to version 12.88 or above.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 08:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5523 | SQL injection vulnerability in Astrotalks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5523</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Astrotalks affecting version 10/03/2023. This vulnerability could allow an authenticated local user to send a specially crafted SQL query to the 'searchString' parameter and retrieve all information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5524 | Information exposure vulnerability in Astrotalks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5524</link><description>Information exposure vulnerability in Astrotalks affecting version 10/03/2023. This vulnerability allows unregistered users to access all internal links of the application without providing any credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5525 | Improper privilege management vulnerability in Astrotalks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5525</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Astrotalks affecting version 10/03/2023. This vulnerability allows a local user to access the application as an administrator without any provided credentials, allowing the attacker to perform administrative actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5427 | WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Reservation Form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5427</link><description>The WPCafe – Online Food Ordering, Restaurant Menu, Delivery, and Reservations for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Reservation Form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23847 | Incorrect default permissions issue exists in Unifier and Unifier Cast Version.5.0 or later, and the patch "20240527" not applied. If this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23847</link><description>Incorrect default permissions issue exists in Unifier and Unifier Cast Version.5.0 or later, and the patch "20240527" not applied. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with LocalSystem privilege. As a result, a malicious program may be installed, data may be modified or deleted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36246 | Missing authorization vulnerability exists in Unifier and Unifier Cast Version.5.0 or later, and the patch "20240527" not applied. If this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36246</link><description>Missing authorization vulnerability exists in Unifier and Unifier Cast Version.5.0 or later, and the patch "20240527" not applied. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed with LocalSystem privilege. As a result, a malicious program may be installed, data may be modified or deleted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:28:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4469 | Migration Backup Restore &amp;lt; 3.5.0 - Admin+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4469</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin  WordPress plugin before 3.5.0 does not prevent users with the administrator role from pinging conducting SSRF attacks, which may be a problem in multisite configurations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4205 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.31 - Missing Authorization to Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4205</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_template_content() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve Elementor template data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4376 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.31 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Fancy Text Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4376</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Fancy Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. While 4.10.32 is patched, it is recommended to update to 4.10.33 because 4.10.32 caused a fatal error.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4379 | Premium Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.10.31 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Global Tooltip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4379</link><description>The Premium Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Global Tooltip widget in all versions up to, and including, 4.10.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2793 | Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp;amp; Project Management – Atarim &amp;lt;= 3.30 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2793</link><description>The Visual Website Collaboration, Feedback &amp; Project Management – Atarim plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via comments in all versions up to, and including, 3.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37032 | Ollama before 0.1.34 does not validate the format of the digest (sha256 with 64 hex digits) when getting the model path, and thus mishandles...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37032</link><description>Ollama before 0.1.34 does not validate the format of the digest (sha256 with 64 hex digits) when getting the model path, and thus mishandles the TestGetBlobsPath test cases such as fewer than 64 hex digits, more than 64 hex digits, or an initial ../ substring.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:18:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5345 | Responsive Owl Carousel for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5345</link><description>The Responsive Owl Carousel for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 via the layout parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. The inclusion is limited to PHP files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5418 | DethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via slitems Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5418</link><description>The DethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'slitems' attribute within the plugin's De Product Tab &amp; Slide widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32850 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('Command Injection') exists in SkyBridge MB-A100/MB-A110 firmware Ver. 4.2.2 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32850</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('Command Injection') exists in SkyBridge MB-A100/MB-A110 firmware Ver. 4.2.2 and earlier and SkyBridge BASIC MB-A130 firmware Ver. 1.5.5 and earlier. If the remote monitoring and control function is enabled on the product, an attacker with access to the product may execute an arbitrary command or login to the product with the administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37018 | The OpenDaylight 0.15.3 controller allows topology poisoning via API requests because an application can manipulate the path that is taken b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37018</link><description>The OpenDaylight 0.15.3 controller allows topology poisoning via API requests because an application can manipulate the path that is taken by discovery packets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 01:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>