<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:39:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15003 | SeaCMS admin_video.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file admin_video.php. Performing manipulation of the argument e_id results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15002 | SeaCMS mysqli.class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15002</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SeaCMS up to 13.3. The affected element is an unknown function of the file js/player/dmplayer/dmku/class/mysqli.class.php. Such manipulation of the argument page/limit leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62901 | WordPress WP Microdata plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tormorten WP Microdata allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Microdata: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62926 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62926</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Stored XSS.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62955 | WordPress TempTool plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62955</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in HappyDevs TempTool allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects TempTool: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14995 | Tenda FH1201 SetIpBind sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14995</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda FH1201 1.2.0.14(408). Affected is the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetIpBind. Such manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 08:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14800 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Copy via move_file_to_upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14800</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'move_file_to_upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to copy arbitrary files on the affected site's server. If 'allow_url_fopen' is set to 'On', it is possible to upload a remote file to the server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14855 | SureForms &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14855</link><description>The SureForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form field parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14994 | Tenda FH1201/FH1206 HTTP Request webtypelibrary strcat stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14994</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda FH1201 and FH1206 1.2.0.14(408)/1.2.0.8(8155). This impacts the function strcat of the file /goform/webtypelibrary of the component HTTP Request Handler. This manipulation of the argument webSiteId causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14993 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request SetDlnaCfg sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14993</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. This affects the function sprintf of the file /goform/SetDlnaCfg of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument scanList results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14992 | Tenda AC18 HTTP Request GetParentControlInfo strcpy stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14992</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. The impacted element is the function strcpy of the file /goform/GetParentControlInfo of the component HTTP Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument mac leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12398 | Product Table for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12398</link><description>The Product Table for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'search_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12654 | Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.9.120 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary Directory Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12654</link><description>The Migration, Backup, Staging – WPvivid Backup &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary directory creation in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.120. This is due to the check_filesystem_permissions() function not properly restricting the directories that can be created, or in what location. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to create arbitrary directories.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13220 | Ultimate Member &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13220</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13361 | Web to SugarCRM Lead &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Custom Field Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13361</link><description>The Web to SugarCRM Lead plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the custom field deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete custom fields via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13693 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;Custom Scripts&amp;#x27; Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13693</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'Custom scripts' setting in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14991 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System bwdates-reports-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14991</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. Executing manipulation of the argument fromdate can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9343 | ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp;amp; Customer Ticketing System &amp;lt;= 3.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9343</link><description>The ELEX WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Customer Ticketing System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ticket subjects in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14990 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14990</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. Performing manipulation of the argument viewid results in sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68644 | Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68644</link><description>Yealink RPS before 2025-06-27 allows unauthorized access to information, including AutoP URL addresses. This was fixed by deploying an enhanced authentication mechanism through a security update to all cloud instances.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11496 | Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11496</link><description>The Five Star Restaurant Reservations – WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'rtb-name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12980 | Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12980</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks for News, Magazines, Blog Websites – PostX plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the '/ultp/v2/get_dynamic_content/' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve sensitive user metadata, including password hashes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13838 | WishSuite &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;button_text&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13838</link><description>The WishSuite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'button_text' parameter of the 'wishsuite_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14043 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Metadata Section Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14043</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized metadata section creation due to missing authorization checks in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the `create_item_permissions_check()` function unconditionally returning true, which bypasses authentication and authorization validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary metadata sections for any collection via the public REST API granted they can access the WordPress site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14054 | WC Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;heading_color&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14054</link><description>The WC Builder – WooCommerce Page Builder for WPBakery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'heading_color' parameter (and multiple other styling parameters) of the `wpbforwpbakery_product_additional_information` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14071 | Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection via dslc_module_posts_output Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14071</link><description>The Live Composer – Free WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input in the dslc_module_posts_output shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14080 | Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Post Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14080</link><description>The Frontend Post Submission Manager Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This is due to missing authorization checks on the post update functionality in the fpsml_form_process AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify arbitrary posts by providing a post_id parameter via the guest posting form, allowing them to change post titles, content, excerpts, and remove post authors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25445 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25445</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25446 | WordPress HappyFiles Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25446</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HappyFiles HappyFiles Pro happyfiles-pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HappyFiles Pro: from n/a through 1.8.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47232 | WordPress WP Affiliate Disclosure plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47232</link><description>Vulnerability in mojofywp WP Affiliate Disclosure wp-affiliate-disclosure.This issue affects WP Affiliate Disclosure: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 02:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25068 | WordPress Magazine Edge theme &amp;lt;= 1.13 - Authenticated Arbitrary Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25068</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mapro Collins Magazine Edge allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Magazine Edge: from n/a through 1.13.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14989 | Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System search-invoices.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14989</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Campcodes Complete Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-invoices.php. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 23:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34290 | Versa SASE Client for Windows &amp;lt; 7.9.5 Arbitrary Folder Deletion Leading to Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34290</link><description>Versa SASE Client for Windows versions released between 7.8.7 and 7.9.4 contain a local privilege escalation vulnerability in the audit log export functionality. The client communicates user-controlled file paths to a privileged service, which performs file system operations without impersonating the requesting user. Due to improper privilege handling and a time-of-check time-of-use race condition combined with symbolic link and mount point manipulation, a local authenticated attacker can coerce the service into deleting arbitrary directories with SYSTEM privileges. This can be exploited to delete protected system folders such as C:\\Config.msi and subsequently achieve execution as NT AUTHORITY\\SYSTEM via MSI rollback techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7733 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Authenticated (Candidate+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7733</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 7.7 via the 'cs_update_application_status_callback' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate-level access and above, to send a site-generated email with injected HTML to any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7782 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Candidate+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;status&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7782</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress, used by the JobCareer theme, is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'cs_update_application_status_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 7.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Candidate-level access and above, to inject cross-site scripting into the 'status' parameter of applied jobs for any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12492 | Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp;amp; Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12492</link><description>The Ultimate Member – User Profile, Registration, Login, Member Directory, Content Restriction &amp; Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.0 via the ajax_get_members function. This is due to the use of a predictable low-entropy token (5 hex characters derived from md5 of post ID) to identify member directories and insufficient authorization checks on the unauthenticated AJAX endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including usernames, display names, user roles (including administrator accounts), profile URLs, and user IDs by enumerating predictable directory_id values or brute-forcing the small 16^5 token space.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14298 | FiboSearch – Ajax Search for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.32.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via thegem_te_search Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14298</link><description>The FiboSearch – Ajax Search for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `thegem_te_search` shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.32.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This vulnerability requires TheGem theme (premium) to be installed with Header Builder mode enabled, and the FiboSearch "Replace search bars" option enabled for TheGem integration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13619 | Flex Store Users &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13619</link><description>The Flex Store Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to the 'fsUserHandle::signup' and the 'fsSellerRole::add_role_seller' functions not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site. Note: The vulnerability can be exploited with the 'fs_type' parameter if the Flex Store Seller plugin is also activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12820 | Pure WC Variation Swatches &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Unauthenticated Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12820</link><description>The Pure WC Variation Swatches WordPress plugin through 1.1.7 does not have an authorization check when updating its settings, which could allow any authenticated users to update them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 06:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12581 | Attachments Handler &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12581</link><description>The Attachments Handler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12898 | Pretty Google Calendar &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Google API Key Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12898</link><description>The Pretty Google Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the pgcal_ajax_handler() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the Google API key set in the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13329 | File Uploader for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via add-image-data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13329</link><description>The File Uploader for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the callback function for the 'add-image-data' REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files to the Uploadcare service and subsequently download them on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13365 | WP Hallo Welt &amp;lt;= 1.4. - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13365</link><description>The WP Hallo Welt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'hallo_welt_seite' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Due to the insufficient input sanitization and output escaping, this can lead to Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13624 | Overstock Affiliate Links &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_SERVER[&amp;#x27;PHP_SELF&amp;#x27;]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13624</link><description>The Overstock Affiliate Links plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the `$_SERVER['PHP_SELF']` parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14164 | Quran Gateway &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14164</link><description>The Quran Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5. This is due to missing nonce validation in the quran_gateway_options function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's display settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14168 | WP DB Booster &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Database Cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14168</link><description>The WP DB Booster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the cleanup_all AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete database records including post drafts, revisions, comments, and metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14591 | PII Leak Due to Change in EOR Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14591</link><description>After a recent bug fix to correctly handle CR+LF (Windows and DOS) End-of-Record (EOR) characters in delimited files, an issue was identified: using an incorrect EOR configuration can cause inaccurate parsing and leave personally identifiable information (PII) unmasked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14633 | F70 Lead Document Download &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Media File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14633</link><description>The F70 Lead Document Download plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'file_download' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download any file from the WordPress media library by guessing or enumerating WordPress attachment IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14721 | Responsive and Swipe slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Editor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14721</link><description>The Responsive and Swipe slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's rsSlider shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14734 | Amazon affiliate lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14734</link><description>The Amazon affiliate lite Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ADAL_settings_page' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14735 | Amazon affiliate lite Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14735</link><description>The "Amazon affiliate lite Plugin" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 03:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14299 | Improper Content-Length Validation in HTTPS Requests on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14299</link><description>The HTTPS server on Tapo C200 V3 does not properly validate the Content-Length header, which can lead to an integer overflow. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send crafted HTTPS requests to trigger excessive memory allocation, causing the device to crash and resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14300 | Unauthenticated Access to connectAP API Endpoint on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14300</link><description>The HTTPS service on Tapo C200 V3 exposes a connectAP interface without proper authentication. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can exploit this to modify the device’s Wi-Fi configuration, resulting in loss of connectivity and denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8065 | Buffer Overflow in ONVIF XML Parser on Tapo C200</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8065</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the ONVIF XML parser of Tapo C200 V3. An unauthenticated attacker on the same local network segment can send specially crafted SOAP XML requests, causing memory overflow and device crash, resulting in denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68613 | n8n Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Expression Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68613</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Versions starting with 0.211.0 and prior to 1.120.4, 1.121.1, and 1.122.0 contain a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in their workflow expression evaluation system. Under certain conditions, expressions supplied by authenticated users during workflow configuration may be evaluated in an execution context that is not sufficiently isolated from the underlying runtime. An authenticated attacker could abuse this behavior to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the n8n process. Successful exploitation may lead to full compromise of the affected instance, including unauthorized access to sensitive data, modification of workflows, and execution of system-level operations. This issue has been fixed in versions 1.120.4, 1.121.1, and 1.122.0. Users are strongly advised to upgrade to a patched version, which introduces additional safeguards to restrict expression evaluation. If upgrading is not immediately possible, administrators should consider the following temporary mitigations: Limit workflow creation and editing permissions to fully trusted users only; and/or deploy n8n in a hardened environment with restricted operating system privileges and network access to reduce the impact of potential exploitation. These workarounds do not fully eliminate the risk and should only be used as short-term measures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:37:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53945 | BrainyCP 1.0 Remote Code Execution via Authenticated Crontab Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53945</link><description>BrainyCP 1.0 contains an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability that allows logged-in users to inject arbitrary commands through the crontab configuration interface. Attackers can exploit the crontab endpoint by adding a malicious command that spawns a reverse shell to a specified IP and port.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53946 | Arcsoft PhotoStudio 6.0.0.172 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53946</link><description>Arcsoft PhotoStudio 6.0.0.172 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability in the ArcSoft Exchange Service that allows local attackers to escalate privileges. Attackers can place a malicious executable in the unquoted path and trigger the service to execute arbitrary code with system-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53947 | OCS Inventory NG 2.3.0.0 Unquoted Service Path Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53947</link><description>OCS Inventory NG 2.3.0.0 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to escalate privileges to system level. Attackers can place a malicious executable in the unquoted service path and trigger the service restart to execute code with elevated system privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53948 | Lilac-Reloaded for Nagios 2.0.8 Remote Code Execution via Autodiscovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53948</link><description>Lilac-Reloaded for Nagios 2.0.8 contains a remote code execution vulnerability in the autodiscovery feature that allows attackers to inject arbitrary commands. Attackers can exploit the lack of input filtering in the nmap_binary parameter to execute a reverse shell by sending a crafted POST request to the autodiscovery endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53949 | AspEmail 5.6.0.2 Local Privilege Escalation via Binary Permission Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53949</link><description>AspEmail 5.6.0.2 contains a binary permission vulnerability that allows local users to escalate privileges through the Persits Software EmailAgent service. Attackers can exploit full write permissions in the BIN directory to replace the service executable and gain elevated system access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53950 | InnovaStudio WYSIWYG Editor 5.4 Unrestricted File Upload via Filename Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53950</link><description>InnovaStudio WYSIWYG Editor 5.4 contains an unrestricted file upload vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass file extension restrictions through filename manipulation. Attackers can upload malicious ASP shells by using null byte techniques and alternate file extensions to circumvent upload controls in the asset manager.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53951 | Ever Gauzy v0.281.9 JWT Authentication Weakness via HMAC Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53951</link><description>Ever Gauzy v0.281.9 contains a JWT authentication vulnerability that allows attackers to exploit weak HMAC secret key implementation. Attackers can leverage the exposed JWT token to authenticate and gain unauthorized access with administrative permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53952 | Dotclear 2.25.3 Authenticated Remote Code Execution via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53952</link><description>Dotclear 2.25.3 contains a remote code execution vulnerability that allows authenticated attackers to upload malicious PHP files with .phar extension through the blog post creation interface. Attackers can upload files containing PHP system commands that execute when the uploaded file is accessed, enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53953 | WebsiteBaker 2.13.3 Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Page Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53953</link><description>WebsiteBaker 2.13.3 contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability that allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts when creating web pages. Attackers can craft malicious payloads in page titles that execute arbitrary JavaScript when the page is viewed by other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53954 | ActFax 10.10 Unquoted Path Services Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53954</link><description>ActFax 10.10 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially escalate privileges by exploiting the ActiveFaxServiceNT service configuration. Attackers with write permissions to Program Files directories can inject a malicious ActSrvNT.exe executable to gain elevated system access when the service restarts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53956 | Flatnux 2021-03.25 Authenticated File Upload Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53956</link><description>Flatnux 2021-03.25 contains an authenticated file upload vulnerability that allows administrative users to upload arbitrary PHP files through the file manager. Attackers with admin credentials can upload malicious PHP scripts to the web root directory, enabling remote code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53957 | Kimai 1.30.10 SameSite Cookie Vulnerability Session Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53957</link><description>Kimai 1.30.10 contains a SameSite cookie vulnerability that allows attackers to steal user session cookies through malicious exploitation. Attackers can trick victims into executing a crafted PHP script that captures and writes session cookie information to a file, enabling potential session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53958 | LDAP Tool Box Self Service Password 1.5.2 Account Takeover via HTTP Host Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53958</link><description>LDAP Tool Box Self Service Password 1.5.2 contains a password reset vulnerability that allows attackers to manipulate HTTP Host headers during token generation. Attackers can craft malicious password reset requests that generate tokens sent to a controlled server, enabling potential account takeover by intercepting and using stolen reset tokens.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53959 | FileZilla Client 3.63.1 DLL Hijacking via Missing TextShaping.dll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53959</link><description>FileZilla Client 3.63.1 contains a DLL hijacking vulnerability that allows attackers to execute malicious code by placing a crafted TextShaping.dll in the application directory. Attackers can generate a reverse shell payload using msfvenom and replace the missing DLL to achieve remote code execution when the application launches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68481 | FastAPI Users Vulnerable to 1-click Account Takeover in Apps Using FastAPI SSO</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68481</link><description>FastAPI Users allows users to quickly add a registration and authentication system to their FastAPI project. Prior to version 15.0.2, the OAuth login state tokens are completely stateless and carry no per-request entropy or any data that could link them to the session that initiated the OAuth flow. `generate_state_token()` is always called with an empty `state_data` dict, so the resulting JWT only contains the fixed audience claim plus an expiration timestamp. On callback, the library merely checks that the JWT verifies under `state_secret` and is unexpired; there is no attempt to match the state value to the browser that initiated the OAuth request, no correlation cookie, and no server-side cache. Any attacker can hit `/authorize`, capture the server-generated state, finish the upstream OAuth flow with their own provider account, and then trick a victim into loading `.../callback?code=&amp;amp;state=`. Because the state JWT is valid for any client for \~1 hour, the victim’s browser will complete the flow. This leads to login CSRF. Depending on the app’s logic, the login CSRF can lead to an account takeover of the victim account or to the victim user getting logged in to the attacker's account. Version 15.0.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14968 | code-projects Simple Stock System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14968</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /market/update.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67712 | HTML injection issue in ArcGIS Web App Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67712</link><description>There is an HTML injection issue in Esri ArcGIS Web AppBuilder developer edition versions prior to 2.30 that allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to potentially entice a user to click a link that causes arbitrary HTML to render in a victim's browser. There is no evidence of JavaScript execution, which limits the impact. At the time of submission, ArcGIS Web App Builder developer edition is retired and unsupported. ArcGIS Web App Builder 2.30 is not susceptible to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12874 | HTTP Request Smuggling in Quest Coexistence Manager for Notes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12874</link><description>Inconsistent Interpretation of HTTP Requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') vulnerability in Quest Coexistence Manager for Notes (Free/Busy Connector modules) allows HTTP Request Smuggling via the Content-Length-Transfer-Encoding (CL.TE) attack vector. This could allow an attacker to bypass access controls, poison web caches, hijack sessions, or trigger unintended internal requests. This issue affects Coexistence Manager for Notes 3.8.2045. Other versions may also be affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14966 | FastAdmin Backend Controller Backend.php selectpage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14966</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in FastAdmin up to 1.7.0.20250506. Affected is the function selectpage of the file application/common/controller/Backend.php of the component Backend Controller. Executing manipulation of the argument custom/searchField can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14967 | itsourcecode Student Management System candidates_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14967</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode Student Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /candidates_report.php. The manipulation of the argument school_year leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14965 | 1541492390c yougou-mall ResourceController.java upload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14965</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1541492390c yougou-mall up to 0a771fa817c924efe52c8fe0a9a6658eee675f9f. This impacts the function Upload of the file src/main/java/per/ccm/ygmall/extra/controller/ResourceController.java. Performing manipulation results in path traversal. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14964 | TOTOLINK T10 cstecgi.cgi sprintf stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14964</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK T10 4.1.8cu.5083_B20200521. This affects the function sprintf of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument loginAuthUrl leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14961 | code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System editedcampaign.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14961</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /editedcampaign.php. The manipulation of the argument campaignname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14962 | code-projects Simple Stock System chatuser.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14962</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /market/chatuser.php. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:48:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14959 | code-projects Simple Stock System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14959</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Simple Stock System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /market/signup.php. Executing manipulation of the argument Username can lead to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14960 | code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System editeddonor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14960</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Simple Blood Donor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /editeddonor.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14958 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_pipeline_common_init heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14958</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in floooh sokol up to 33e2271c431bf21de001e972f72da17a984da932. This vulnerability affects the function _sg_pipeline_common_init in the library sokol_gfx.h. Performing manipulation results in heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The patch is named 33e2271c431bf21de001e972f72da17a984da932. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68430 | CVAT vulnerable to directory traversal via mounted share listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68430</link><description>CVAT is an open source interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions 2.8.1 through 2.52.0, an attacker with an account on a CVAT instance is able to retrieve the contents of any file system directory accessible to the CVAT server. The exposed information is names of contained files and subdirectories. The contents of files are not accessible. Version 2.53.0 contains a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68478 | Langflow Vulnerable to External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68478</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.7.0, if an arbitrary path is specified in the request body's `fs_path`, the server serializes the Flow object into JSON and creates/overwrites a file at that path. There is no path restriction, normalization, or allowed directory enforcement, so absolute paths (e.g., /etc/poc.txt) are interpreted as is. Version 1.7.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14957 | WebAssembly Binaryen IRBuilder wasm-ir-builder.cpp makeLocalTee null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14957</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WebAssembly Binaryen up to 125. This affects the function IRBuilder::makeLocalGet/IRBuilder::makeLocalSet/IRBuilder::makeLocalTee of the file src/wasm/wasm-ir-builder.cpp of the component IRBuilder. Such manipulation of the argument Index leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The name of the patch is 6fb2b917a79578ab44cf3b900a6da4c27251e0d4. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63665 | An issue in GT Edge AI Platform Versions before v2.0.10-dev allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted JSON payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63665</link><description>An issue in GT Edge AI Platform Versions before v2.0.10-dev allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted JSON payload into the Prompt window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14809 | Address bar spoofing risk in ArcSearch on Android</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14809</link><description>ArcSearch for Android versions prior to 1.12.6 could display a different domain in the address bar than the content being shown, enabling address bar spoofing after user interaction via crafted web content.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68457 | Orejime has executable code in HTML attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68457</link><description>Orejime is a consent manager that focuses on accessibility. On HTML elements handled by Orejime prior to version 2.3.2, one could run malicious code by embedding `javascript:` code within data attributes. When consenting to the related purpose, Orejime would turn data attributes into unprefixed ones (i.e. `data-href` into `href`), thus executing the code. This shouldn't have any impact on most setups, as elements handled by Orejime are generally hardcoded. The problem would only arise if somebody could inject HTML code within pages. The problem has been patched in version 2.3.2. As a workaround, the problem can be fixed outside of Orejime by sanitizing attributes which could contain executable code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68477 | Langflow vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68477</link><description>Langflow is a tool for building and deploying AI-powered agents and workflows. Prior to version 1.7.0, Langflow provides an API Request component that can issue arbitrary HTTP requests within a flow. This component takes a user-supplied URL, performs only normalization and basic format checks, and then sends the request using a server-side httpx client. It does not block private IP ranges (127[.]0[.]0[.]1, the 10/172/192 ranges) or cloud metadata endpoints (169[.]254[.]169[.]254), and it returns the response body as the result. Because the flow execution endpoints (/api/v1/run, /api/v1/run/advanced) can be invoked with just an API key, if an attacker can control the API Request URL in a flow, non-blind SSRF is possible—accessing internal resources from the server’s network context. This enables requests to, and collection of responses from, internal administrative endpoints, metadata services, and internal databases/services, leading to information disclosure and providing a foothold for further attacks. Version 1.7.0 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30971 | Gaia unauthenticated endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30971</link><description>Gotham Gaia application was found to be exposing multiple unauthenticated endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49587 | Glutton V1 endpoints missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49587</link><description>Glutton V1 service endpoints were exposed without any authentication on Gotham stacks, this could have allowed users that did not have any permission to hit glutton backend directly and read/update/delete data. The affected service has been patched and automatically deployed to all Apollo-managed Gotham Instances</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14812 | Address bar spoofing risk in Arc Search on iOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14812</link><description>ArcSearch for iOS versions prior to 1.45.2 could display a different domain in the address bar than the content being shown after an iframe-triggered URI-scheme navigation, increasing spoofing risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14955 | Open5GS PFCP handler.c ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr initialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14955</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr in the library lib/pfcp/handler.c of the component PFCP. The manipulation results in improper initialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is identified as 773117aa5472af26fc9f80e608d3386504c3bdb7. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14956 | WebAssembly Binaryen wasm-binary.cpp readExport heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14956</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in WebAssembly Binaryen up to 125. Affected by this issue is the function WasmBinaryReader::readExport of the file src/wasm/wasm-binary.cpp. This manipulation causes heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: 4f52bff8c4075b5630422f902dd92a0af2c9f398. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58053 | Galette has a privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58053</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Prior to version 1.2.0, while updating any existing account with a self forged POST request, one can gain higher privileges. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65035 | GLPI Database Inventory Plugin Vulnerable to Stored Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65035</link><description>pluginsGLPI's Database Inventory Plugin "manages" the Teclib' inventory agents in order to perform an inventory of the databases present on the workstation. Prior to version 1.1.2, in certain conditions (database write access must first be obtained through another vulnerability or misconfiguration), user-controlled data is stored insecurely in the database via computergroup, and is later unserialized on every page load, allowing arbitrary PHP object instantiation. Version 1.1.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66580 | Dive has Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability that can escalate to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66580</link><description>Dive is an open-source MCP Host Desktop Application that enables integration with function-calling LLMs. A critical Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in versions prior to 0.11.1 in the Mermaid diagram rendering component. The application allows the execution of arbitrary JavaScript via `javascript:`. An attacker can exploit this to inject a malicious Model Context Protocol (MCP) server configuration, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the victim's machine when the node is clicked. Version 0.11.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58052 | Galette has groups managers access control bypass on Members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58052</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Starting in version 0.9.6 and prior to version 1.2.0, attackers with group manager role can bypass intended restrictions allowing unauthorized access and changes despite role-based controls. Since it requires privileged access initially, exploitation is restricted to malicious insiders or compromised group managers accounts. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14953 | Open5GS FAR-ID handler.c ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14953</link><description>A flaw has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. This impacts the function ogs_pfcp_handle_create_pdr in the library lib/pfcp/handler.c of the component FAR-ID Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to null pointer dereference. The attack may be performed from remote. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called 93a9fd98a8baa94289be3b982028201de4534e32. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14954 | Open5GS QER/FAR/URR/PDR context.c ogs_pfcp_qer_find_or_add assertion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14954</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open5GS up to 2.7.5. Affected is the function ogs_pfcp_pdr_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_far_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_urr_find_or_add/ogs_pfcp_qer_find_or_add in the library lib/pfcp/context.c of the component QER/FAR/URR/PDR. The manipulation leads to reachable assertion. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 442369dcd964f03d95429a6a01a57ed21f7779b7. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67442 | EVE-NG 6.4.0-13-PRO is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The /api/export interface allows authenticated users to export lab files. This int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67442</link><description>EVE-NG 6.4.0-13-PRO is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. The /api/export interface allows authenticated users to export lab files. This interface lacks effective input validation and filtering when processing file path parameters submitted by users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34433 | AVideo &amp;lt; 20.1 Unauthenticated RCE via Predictable Installation Salt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34433</link><description>AVideo versions 14.3.1 prior to 20.1 contain an unauthenticated remote code execution vulnerability caused by predictable generation of an installation salt using PHP uniqid(). The installation timestamp is exposed via a public endpoint, and a derived hash identifier is accessible through unauthenticated API responses, allowing attackers to brute-force the remaining entropy. The recovered salt can then be used to encrypt a malicious payload supplied to a notification API endpoint that evaluates attacker-controlled input, resulting in arbitrary code execution as the web server user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66905 | The Takes web framework's TkFiles take thru 2.0-SNAPSHOT fails to canonicalize HTTP request paths before resolving them against the filesyst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66905</link><description>The Takes web framework's TkFiles take thru 2.0-SNAPSHOT fails to canonicalize HTTP request paths before resolving them against the filesystem. A remote attacker can include ../ sequences in the request path to escape the configured base directory and read arbitrary files from the host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53922 | Galette has access control bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53922</link><description>Galette is a membership management web application for non profit organizations. Starting in version 1.1.4 and prior to version 1.2.0, a user who is logged in as group manager may bypass intended restrictions on Contributions and Transactions. Version 1.2.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66906 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Turms Admin API thru v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain escalated privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66906</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Turms Admin API thru v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT allows attackers to gain escalated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50681 | igmpproxy 0.4 before commit 2b30c36 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted IGMPv3 membership...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50681</link><description>igmpproxy 0.4 before commit 2b30c36 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted IGMPv3 membership report packet with a malicious source address. Due to insufficient validation in the `recv_igmp()` function in src/igmpproxy.c, an invalid group record type can trigger a NULL pointer dereference when logging the address using `inet_fmtsrc()`. This vulnerability can be exploited by sending malformed multicast traffic to a host running igmpproxy, leading to a crash. igmpproxy is used in various embedded networking environments and consumer-grade IoT devices (such as home routers and media gateways) to handle multicast traffic for IPTV and other streaming services. Affected devices that rely on unpatched versions of igmpproxy may be vulnerable to remote denial-of-service attacks across a LAN .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66910 | Turms Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a plaintext password storage vulnerability in the administrator authentication system. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66910</link><description>Turms Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a plaintext password storage vulnerability in the administrator authentication system. The BaseAdminService class caches administrator passwords in plaintext within AdminInfo objects to optimize authentication performance. Upon successful login, raw passwords are stored unencrypted in memory in the rawPassword field. Attackers with local system access can extract these passwords through memory dumps, heap analysis, or debugger attachment, bypassing bcrypt protection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14952 | Campcodes Supplier Management System add_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14952</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_category.php. Performing manipulation of the argument txtCategoryName results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66908 | Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an improper file type validation vulnerability in the OCR image upload functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66908</link><description>Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an improper file type validation vulnerability in the OCR image upload functionality. The OcrController in turms-ai-serving/src/main/java/im/turms/ai/domain/ocr/controller/OcrController.java uses the @FormData(contentType = MediaTypeConst.IMAGE) annotation to restrict uploads to image files, but this constraint is not properly enforced. The system relies solely on client-provided Content-Type headers and file extensions without validating actual file content using magic bytes (file signatures). An attacker can upload arbitrary file types including executables, scripts, HTML, or web shells by setting the Content-Type header to "image/*" or using an image file extension. This bypass enables potential server-side code execution, stored XSS, or information disclosure depending on how uploaded files are processed and served.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14951 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14951</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /home.php. Such manipulation of the argument post_content leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66909 | Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an image decompression bomb denial of service vulnerability. The ExtendedOpenC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66909</link><description>Turms AI-Serving module v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains an image decompression bomb denial of service vulnerability. The ExtendedOpenCVImage class in ai/djl/opencv/ExtendedOpenCVImage.java loads images using OpenCV's imread() function without validating dimensions or pixel count before decompression. An attacker can upload a specially crafted compressed image file (e.g., PNG) that is small when compressed but expands to gigabytes of memory when loaded. This causes immediate memory exhaustion, OutOfMemoryError, and service crash. No authentication is required if the OCR service is publicly accessible. Multiple requests can completely deny service availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66911 | Turms IM Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a broken access control vulnerability in the user online status query functionality. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66911</link><description>Turms IM Server v0.10.0-SNAPSHOT and earlier contains a broken access control vulnerability in the user online status query functionality. The handleQueryUserOnlineStatusesRequest() method in UserServiceController.java allows any authenticated user to query the online status, device information, and login timestamps of arbitrary users without proper authorization checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14950 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System delete_post.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14950</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /delete_post.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:43:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14946 | Libnbd: libnbd: arbitrary code execution via ssh argument injection through a malicious uri</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14946</link><description>A flaw was found in libnbd. A malicious actor could exploit this by convincing libnbd to open a specially crafted Uniform Resource Identifier (URI). This vulnerability arises because non-standard hostnames starting with '-o' are incorrectly interpreted as arguments to the Secure Shell (SSH) process, rather than as hostnames. This could lead to arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the user running libnbd.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14881 | Insecure direct object reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14881</link><description>Multiple API endpoints allowed access to sensitive files from other users by knowing the UUID of the file that were not intended to be accessible by UUID only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14882 | Insecure direct object reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14882</link><description>An API endpoint allowed access to sensitive files from other users by knowing the UUID of the file that were not intended to be accessible by UUID only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:06:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1928 | Improper Authentication in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1928</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Password Recovery Exploitation.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1927 | CSRF in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1927</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1885 | Open Redirect in Restajet&amp;#x27;s Online Food Delivery System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1885</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Restajet Information Technologies Inc. Online Food Delivery System allows Phishing, Forceful Browsing.This issue affects Online Food Delivery System: through 19122025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14847 | Zlib compressed protocol header length confusion may allow memory read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14847</link><description>Mismatched length fields in Zlib compressed protocol headers may allow a read of uninitialized heap memory by an unauthenticated client. This issue affects all MongoDB Server v7.0 prior to 7.0.28 versions, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.17, MongoDB Server v8.2 versions prior to 8.2.3, MongoDB Server v6.0 versions prior to 6.0.27, MongoDB Server v5.0 versions prior to 5.0.32, MongoDB Server v4.4 versions prior to 4.4.30, MongoDB Server v4.2 versions greater than or equal to 4.2.0, MongoDB Server v4.0 versions greater than or equal to 4.0.0, and MongoDB Server v3.6 versions greater than or equal to 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12361 | myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program &amp;lt;= 2.9.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12361</link><description>The myCred – Points Management System For Gamification, Ranks, Badges, and Loyalty Program plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 2.9.7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive information including user IDs, display names, and email addresses of all users on the site via the get_bank_accounts AJAX action. Passwords are not exposed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14455 | Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid &amp;lt;= 3.6.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Gallery Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14455</link><description>The Image Photo Gallery Final Tiles Grid plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform actions on gallery management functions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete, modify, or clone galleries created by any user, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66524 | Apache NiFi: Deserialization of Untrusted Data in GetAsanaObject Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66524</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.20.0 through 2.6.0 include the GetAsanaObject Processor, which requires integration with a configurable Distribute Map Cache Client Service for storing and retrieving state information. The GetAsanaObject Processor used generic Java Object serialization and deserialization without filtering. Unfiltered Java object deserialization does not provide protection against crafted state information stored in the cache server configured for GetAsanaObject. Exploitation requires an Apache NiFi system running with the GetAsanaObject Processor, and direct access to the configured cache server. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 2.7.0 is the recommended mitigation, which replaces Java Object serialization with JSON serialization. Removing the GetAsanaObject Processor located in the nifi-asana-processors-nar bundle also prevents exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11747 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.345 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11747</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the colibri_blog_posts shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.345 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14151 | SlimStat Analytics &amp;lt;= 5.3.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14151</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'outbound_resource' parameter in the slimtrack AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.2. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66502 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Page Templates Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66502</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Page Templates feature. A crafted payload can be stored as the template name, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes each time the affected PDF is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66519 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Layer Import Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66519</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Layer Import functionality. A crafted payload can be injected into the “Create new Layer” field during layer import and is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes when the Layers panel is accessed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66520 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Portfolio SVG Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66520</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Portfolio feature of the Foxit PDF Editor cloud (pdfonline.foxit.com). User-supplied SVG files are not properly sanitized or validated before being inserted into the HTML structure. As a result, embedded HTML or JavaScript within a crafted SVG may execute whenever the Portfolio file list is rendered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66521 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Trusted Certificates Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66521</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Trusted Certificates feature. A crafted payload can be injected as the certificate name, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script executes each time the Trusted Certificates view is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66522 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Digital IDs Common Name Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66522</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Digital IDs functionality of the Foxit PDF Editor Cloud (pdfonline.foxit.com). The application does not properly sanitize or encode the Common Name field of Digital IDs before inserting user-supplied content into the DOM. As a result, embedded HTML or JavaScript may execute whenever the Digital IDs dialog is accessed or when the affected PDF is loaded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66500 | Foxit webplugins.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting via postMessage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66500</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in webplugins.foxit.com. A postMessage handler fails to validate the message origin and directly assigns externalPath to a script source, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript when a crafted postMessage is received.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66501 | Foxit pdfonline.foxit.com Stored Cross-Site Scripting in eSign Predefined Text Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66501</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in pdfonline.foxit.com within the Predefined Text feature of the Foxit eSign section. A crafted payload can be stored via the Identity “First Name” field, which is later rendered into the DOM without proper sanitization. As a result, the injected script may execute when predefined text is used or when viewing document properties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13008 | Session Token Disclosure in M-Files Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13008</link><description>An information disclosure vulnerability in M-Files Server before versions 25.12.15491.7, 25.8 LTS SR3, 25.2 LTS SR3 and 24.8 LTS SR5 allows an authenticated attacker using M-Files Web to capture session tokens of other active users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66493 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66493</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the AcroForm handling of Foxit PDF Reader and Foxit PDF Editor before 2025.2.1,14.0.1 and 13.2.1 

on Windows

. When opening a PDF containing specially crafted JavaScript, a pointer to memory that has already been freed may be accessed or dereferenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66494 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66494</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the PDF file parsing of Foxit PDF Reader before 2025.2.1, 14.0.1, and 13.2.1 on Windows. A PDF object managed by multiple parent objects could be freed while still being referenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66495 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66495</link><description>A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader before 2025.2.1, 14.0.1, and 13.2.1 on Windows and MacOS. When opening a PDF containing specially crafted JavaScript, a pointer to memory that has already been freed may be accessed or dereferenced, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66496 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66496</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing PRC data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66497 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66497</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing PRC data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66498 | Foxit PDF Reader 3D Annotation Out-of-Bounds Memory Access Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66498</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability exists in the 3D annotation handling of Foxit PDF Reader due to insufficient bounds checking when parsing U3D data. When opening a PDF file containing malformed or specially crafted PRC content, out-of-bounds memory access may occur, resulting in memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66499 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66499</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the PDF parsing of Foxit PDF Reader when processing specially crafted JBIG2 data. An integer overflow in the calculation of the image buffer size may occur, potentially allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13754 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9.16 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13754</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9.16. This is due to the plugin exposing its admin embed endpoint at `/wp-json/ssa/v1/embed-inner-admin` without authentication, which leaks plugin settings including staff names, business names, and configuration data that are not publicly displayed on the booking form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract private business configuration. In premium versions with integrations configured, this might also expose other sensitive data including API keys for external services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13999 | HTML5 Audio Player – The Ultimate No-Code Podcast, MP3 &amp;amp; Audio Player 2.4.0 - 2.5.1 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13999</link><description>The HTML5 Audio Player – The Ultimate No-Code Podcast, MP3 &amp; Audio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions from 2.4.0 up to, and including, 2.5.1 via the getIcyMetadata() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14449 | BA Book Everything &amp;lt;= 1.8.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via babe-search-form Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14449</link><description>The BA Book Everything plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's babe-search-form shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66173 | There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66173</link><description>There is a privilege escalation vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the serial port, an attacker with physical access could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the affected products and gaining access to an unrestricted shell environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66174 | There is an improper authentication vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66174</link><description>There is an improper authentication vulnerability in some Hikvision DVR products. Due to the improper implementation of authentication for the serial port, an attacker with physical access could exploit this vulnerability by connecting to the affected products and run a series of commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14267 | Unintended temporary cached data included in a structure only copy intended to be empty of data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14267</link><description>Incomplete removal of sensitive information before transfer vulnerability in M-Files Corporation M-Files Server allows data leak exposure affecting versions before 25.12.15491.7</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13307 | Ocean Modal Window &amp;lt; 2.3.3 - Editor+ Remote Code Execution via Modal Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13307</link><description>The Ocean Modal Window WordPress plugin before 2.3.3 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via the modal display logic. These modals can be displayed under user-controlled conditions that Editors and Administrators can set (edit_pages capability). The conditions are then executed as part of an eval statement executed on every site page. This leads to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 06:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14546 | Versions of the package fastapi-sso before 0.19.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) due to the improper validation of the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14546</link><description>Versions of the package fastapi-sso before 0.19.0 are vulnerable to Cross-site Request Forgery (CSRF) due to the improper validation of the OAuth state parameter during the authentication callback. While the get_login_url method allows for state generation, it does not persist the state or bind it to the user's session. Consequently, the verify_and_process method accepts the state received in the query parameters without verifying it against a trusted local value. This allows a remote attacker to trick a victim into visiting a malicious callback URL, which can result in the attacker's account being linked to the victim's internal account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 05:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14939 | code-projects Online Appointment Booking System deletemanager.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14939</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Appointment Booking System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/deletemanager.php. The manipulation of the argument managername results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14940 | code-projects Scholars Tracking System delete_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14940</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Scholars Tracking System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_user.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13941 | Foxit PDF Reader Update Service Incorrect Permission Assignment Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13941</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the Foxit PDF Reader/Editor Update Service. During plugin installation, incorrect file system permissions are assigned to resources used by the update service. A local attacker with low privileges could modify or replace these resources, which are later executed by the service, resulting in execution of arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14910 | Edimax BR-6208AC FTP Daemon Service handle_retr path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14910</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Edimax BR-6208AC 1.02. This impacts the function handle_retr of the component FTP Daemon Service. The manipulation results in path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. Edimax confirms this issue: "This product is no longer available in the market and has been discontinued for five years. Consequently, Edimax no longer provides technical support, firmware updates, or security patches for this specific model. However, to ensure the safety of our remaining active users, we acknowledge this report and will take the following mitigation actions: (A) We will issue an official security advisory on our support website. (B) We will strongly advise users to disable the FTP service on this device to mitigate the reported risk, by which the product will still work for common use. (C) We will recommend users upgrade to newer, supported models." This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52692 | Bypass Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52692</link><description>Successful exploitation of the vulnerability could allow an attacker with local network access to send a specially crafted URL to access certain administration functions without login credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67842 | The Static Asset API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the subdomain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67842</link><description>The Static Asset API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the subdomain parameter because any tenant's assets can be served on any other tenant's documentation site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67843 | A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the MDX Rendering Engine in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67843</link><description>A Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in the MDX Rendering Engine in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via inline JSX expressions in an MDX file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67844 | The GitHub Integration API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive repository metadata via the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67844</link><description>The GitHub Integration API in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive repository metadata via the repository owner and name fields. It fails to validate that the repository owner and name fields provided during configuration belong to the specific GitHub App Installation ID associated with the user's organization.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67845 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability in the Static Asset Proxy Endpoint in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67845</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability in the Static Asset Proxy Endpoint in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted URL containing path traversal sequences.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67846 | The Deployment Infrastructure in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to bypass security patches and execute downgrad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67846</link><description>The Deployment Infrastructure in Mintlify Platform before 2025-11-15 allows remote attackers to bypass security patches and execute downgrade attacks via predictable deployment identifiers on the Vercel preview domain. An attacker can identify the URL structure of a previous deployment that contains unpatched vulnerabilities. By browsing directly to the specific git-ref or deployment-id subdomain, the attacker can force the application to load the vulnerable version.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14909 | JeecgBoot SysUserOnlineController.java SysUserOnlineController user session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14909</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The impacted element is the function SysUserOnlineController of the file jeecg-boot/jeecg-module-system/jeecg-system-biz/src/main/java/org/jeecg/modules/system/controller/SysUserOnlineController.java. Executing manipulation can lead to manage user sessions. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called b686f9fbd1917edffe5922c6362c817a9361cfbd. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14908 | JeecgBoot Multi-Tenant Management SysTenantController.java improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14908</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file jeecg-boot/jeecg-module-system/jeecg-system-biz/src/main/java/org/jeecg/modules/system/controller/SysTenantController.java of the component Multi-Tenant Management Module. Performing manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The patch is named e1c8f00bf2a2e0edddbaa8119afe1dc92d9dc1d2/67795493bdc579e489d3ab12e52a1793c4f8a0ee. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11774 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in the Software Keyboard Function of GENESIS64, ICONICS Suite, Mobile HMI, and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11774</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in the software keyboard function (hereinafter referred to as "keypad function") of Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions GENESIS64 versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric ICONICS Suite versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions ICONICS Suite versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric MobileHMI versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, Mitsubishi Electric Iconics Digital Solutions MobileHMI versions 10.97.2 CFR3 and prior, and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary executable files (EXE) when a legitimate user uses the keypad function by tampering with the configuration file for the function. This could allow the attacker to disclose, tamper with, delete, or destroy information stored on the PC where the affected product is installed, or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the system, through the execution of the EXE.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14733 | WatchGuard Firebox iked Out of Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14733</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects both the Mobile User VPN with IKEv2 and the Branch Office VPN using IKEv2 when configured with a dynamic gateway peer.This vulnerability affects Fireware OS 11.10.2 up to and including 11.12.4_Update1, 12.0 up to and including 12.11.5 and 2025.1 up to and including 2025.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14899 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint stateadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14899</link><description>A weakness has been identified in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/stateadd.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14900 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System Administrator Endpoint userdelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14900</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/userdelete.php of the component Administrator Endpoint. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:04:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>