<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-54263 | Adobe Commerce | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54263</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and maintain unauthorized access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54264 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54264</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a high-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. A successful attacker can abuse this to achieve session takeover, increasing the confidentiality, and integrity impact to high. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. Scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54265 | Adobe Commerce | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54265</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized read access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54266 | Adobe Commerce | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54266</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a high-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must browse to the page containing the vulnerable field. Scope is changed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54267 | Adobe Commerce | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54267</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. A low-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized access to elevated privileges that increase integrity impact to high. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54277 | Adobe Commerce | Incorrect Authorization (CWE-863)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54277</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.9-alpha2, 2.4.8-p2, 2.4.7-p7, 2.4.6-p12, 2.4.5-p14, 2.4.4-p15 and earlier are affected by an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass security measures and gain limited unauthorized read access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62374 | Parse Javascript SDK vulnerable to prototype pollution in `Parse.Object` and internal APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62374</link><description>Parse Javascript SDK provides access to the powerful Parse Server backend from your JavaScript app. Prior to 7.0.0, injection of malicious payload allows attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code.  ParseObject.fromJSON, ParseObject.pin, ParseObject.registerSubclass, ObjectStateMutations (internal), and encode/decode (internal) are affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60374 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Perfex CRM chatbot before 3.3.1 allows attackers to inject arbitrary HTML/JavaScript. The payload is ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60374</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Perfex CRM chatbot before 3.3.1 allows attackers to inject arbitrary HTML/JavaScript. The payload is executed in the browsers of users viewing the chat, resulting in client-side code execution, potential session token theft, and other malicious actions. A different vulnerability than CVE-2024-8867.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61802 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61802</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61803 | Substance3D - Stager | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61803</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61805 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61805</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61806 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61806</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61807 | Substance3D - Stager | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61807</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.1.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34267 | Flowise Authenticated Command Execution and Sandbox Bypass via Puppeteer &amp;amp; Playwright Packages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34267</link><description>Flowise v3.0.1 &lt; 3.0.8 and all versions after with 'ALLOW_BUILTIN_DEP' enabled contain an authenticated remote code execution vulnerability and node VM sandbox escape due to insecure use of integrated modules (Puppeteer and Playwright) within the nodevm execution environment. An authenticated attacker able to create or run a tool that leverages Puppeteer/Playwright can specify attacker-controlled browser binary paths and parameters. When the tool executes, the attacker-controlled executable/parameters are run on the host and circumvent the intended nodevm sandbox restrictions, resulting in execution of arbitrary code in the context of the host. This vulnerability was incorrectly assigned as a duplicate CVE-2025-26319 by the developers and should be considered distinct from that identifier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61675 | FreePBX Endpoint Manager vulnerable to authenticated SQL injection in multiple configuration parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61675</link><description>FreePBX Endpoint Manager is a module for managing telephony endpoints in FreePBX systems. In versions prior to 16.0.92 for FreePBX 16 and versions prior to 17.0.6 for FreePBX 17, the Endpoint Manager module contains authenticated SQL injection vulnerabilities affecting multiple parameters in the basestation, model, firmware, and custom extension configuration functionality areas. Authentication with a known username is required to exploit these vulnerabilities. Successful exploitation allows authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL queries against the database, potentially enabling access to sensitive data or modification of database contents. This issue has been patched in version 16.0.92 for FreePBX 16 and version 17.0.6 for FreePBX 17.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61678 | FreePBX Endpoint Manager vulnerable to authenticated arbitrary file upload via fwbrand parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61678</link><description>FreePBX Endpoint Manager is a module for managing telephony endpoints in FreePBX systems. In versions prior to 16.0.92 for FreePBX 16 and versions prior to 17.0.6 for FreePBX 17, the Endpoint Manager module contains an authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability affecting the fwbrand parameter. The fwbrand parameter allows an attacker to change the file path. Combined, these issues can result in a webshell being uploaded. Authentication with a known username is required to exploit this vulnerability. Successful exploitation allows authenticated users to upload arbitrary files to attacker-controlled paths on the server, potentially leading to remote code execution. This issue has been patched in version 16.0.92 for FreePBX 16 and version 17.0.6 for FreePBX 17.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61798 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61798</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61799 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61799</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61800 | Dimension | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61800</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61801 | Dimension | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61801</link><description>Dimension versions 4.1.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54283 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54283</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.7, 28.7.9 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54284 | Illustrator | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54284</link><description>Illustrator versions 29.7, 28.7.9 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59429 | FreePBX core module vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting via Asterisk HTTP Status page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59429</link><description>FreePBX is an open source GUI for managing Asterisk. In versions prior to 16.0.68.39 for FreePBX 16 and versions prior to 17.0.18.38 for FreePBX 17, a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability is present on the Asterisk HTTP Status page. The Asterisk HTTP status page is exposed by FreePBX and is available by default on version 16 via any bound IP address at port 8088. By default on version 17, the binding is only to localhost IP, making it significantly less vulnerable. The vulnerability can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers to obtain cookies from logged-in users, allowing them to hijack a session of an administrative user. The theft of admin session cookies allows attackers to gain control over the FreePBX admin interface, enabling them to access sensitive data, modify system configurations, create backdoor accounts, and cause service disruption. This issue has been patched in version 16.0.68.39 for FreePBX 16 and version 17.0.18.38 for FreePBX 17.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33177 | NVIDIA Jetson Linux and IGX OS contain a vulnerability in NvMap, where improper tracking of memory allocations could allow a local attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33177</link><description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux and IGX OS contain a vulnerability in NvMap, where improper tracking of memory allocations could allow a local attacker to cause memory overallocation. A successful exploitation of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54276 | Substance3D - Modeler | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54276</link><description>Substance3D - Modeler versions 1.22.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54281 | Adobe Framemaker | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54281</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.9, 2022.7 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54282 | Adobe Framemaker | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54282</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.9, 2022.7 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59051 | FreePBX Endpoint Manager command injection via Network Scanning feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59051</link><description>The FreePBX Endpoint Manager module includes a Network Scanning feature that provides web-based access to nmap functionality for network device discovery. In Endpoint Manager 16 before 16.0.92 and 17 before 17.0.6, insufficiently sanitized user-supplied input allows authenticated OS command execution as the asterisk user. Authentication with a known username is required. Updating to Endpoint Manager 16.0.92 or 17.0.6 addresses the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60540 | karakeep v0.26.0 to v0.7.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60540</link><description>karakeep v0.26.0 to v0.7.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF).</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33182 | NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in UEFI, where improper authentication may allow a privileged user to cause corruption of the L...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33182</link><description>NVIDIA Jetson Linux contains a vulnerability in UEFI, where improper authentication may allow a privileged user to cause corruption of the Linux Device Tree. A successful exploitation of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering, denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54273 | Substance3D - Viewer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54273</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54274 | Substance3D - Viewer | Stack-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-121)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54274</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.2 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54275 | Substance3D - Viewer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54275</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could lead to application denial-of-service. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application or make it unavailable. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54280 | Substance3D - Viewer | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54280</link><description>Substance3D - Viewer versions 0.25.2 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60536 | An issue in the Configure New Cluster interface of kafka-ui v0.6.0 to v0.7.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via uploadi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60536</link><description>An issue in the Configure New Cluster interface of kafka-ui v0.6.0 to v0.7.2 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via uploading a crafted configuration file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60537 | Improper input validation in the component /kafka/ui/serdes/CustomSerdeLoader.java of kafka-ui v0.6.0 to v0.7.2 allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60537</link><description>Improper input validation in the component /kafka/ui/serdes/CustomSerdeLoader.java of kafka-ui v0.6.0 to v0.7.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via supplying crafted data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23356 | NVIDIA Isaac Lab contains a vulnerability in SB3 configuration parsing. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23356</link><description>NVIDIA Isaac Lab contains a vulnerability in SB3 configuration parsing. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11736 | itsourcecode Online Examination System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11736</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php. This manipulation of the argument Username causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57563 | A path traversal in StarNet Communications Corporation FastX v.4 through v4.1.51 allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57563</link><description>A path traversal in StarNet Communications Corporation FastX v.4 through v4.1.51 allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57618 | A path traversal vulnerability in FastX3 thru 3.3.67 allows an unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server. By leveraging...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57618</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in FastX3 thru 3.3.67 allows an unauthenticated attacker to read arbitrary files on the server. By leveraging this vulnerability, it is possible to access the application's configuration files, which contain the secret key used to sign JSON Web Tokens as well as existing JTIs. With this information, an attacker can forge valid JWTs, impersonate the root user, and achieve remote code execution in privileged context via authenticated endpoints.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8459 | A user with low privileges can inject XSS in the Monitoring Recurrent downtimes page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8459</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Monitoring recurrent downtime scheduler modules) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24052 | Windows Agere Modem Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24052</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24990 | Windows Agere Modem Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24990</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25004 | PowerShell Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25004</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37140 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerabilities in CLI Binary of AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37140</link><description>Arbitrary file download vulnerabilities exist in the CLI binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37141 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerabilities in CLI Binary of AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37141</link><description>Arbitrary file download vulnerabilities exist in the CLI binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37142 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerabilities in CLI Binary of AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37142</link><description>Arbitrary file download vulnerabilities exist in the CLI binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37143 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability in CLI Binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web Interface (Physical Access Required)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37143</link><description>An arbitrary file download vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an Authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37144 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerabilities in a Low-Level Interface Library Affecting AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37144</link><description>Arbitrary file download vulnerabilities exist in a low-level interface library in AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37145 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Download Vulnerabilities in a Low-Level Interface Library Affecting AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37145</link><description>Arbitrary file download vulnerabilities exist in a low-level interface library in AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to download arbitrary files through carefully constructed exploits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47979 | Microsoft Failover Cluster Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47979</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47989 | Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47989</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48004 | Microsoft Brokering File System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48004</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48813 | Virtual Secure Mode Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48813</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49708 | Microsoft Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49708</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50152 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50152</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50174 | Windows Device Association Broker Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50174</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50175 | Windows Digital Media Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50175</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53139 | Windows Hello Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53139</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53150 | Windows Digital Media Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53150</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53717 | Windows Virtualization-Based Security (VBS) Enclave Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53717</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53768 | Xbox IStorageService Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53768</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53782 | Microsoft Exchange Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53782</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54603 | An incorrect OIDC authentication flow in Claroty Secure Access 3.3.0 through 4.0.2 can result in unauthorized user creation or impersonation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54603</link><description>An incorrect OIDC authentication flow in Claroty Secure Access 3.3.0 through 4.0.2 can result in unauthorized user creation or impersonation of existing OIDC users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55240 | Visual Studio Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55240</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55247 | .NET Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55247</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55248 | .NET, .NET Framework, and Visual Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55248</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55315 | ASP.NET Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55315</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55320 | Configuration Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55320</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55325 | Windows Storage Management Provider Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55325</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55326 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service (Cdpsvc) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55326</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55328 | Windows Hyper-V Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55328</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55330 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55330</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55331 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55331</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55332 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55332</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55333 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55333</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55334 | Windows Kernel Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55334</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55335 | Windows NTFS Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55335</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55336 | Windows Cloud Files Mini Filter Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55336</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55337 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55337</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55338 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55338</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55339 | Windows Network Driver Interface Specification Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55339</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55340 | Windows Remote Desktop Protocol Security Feature Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55340</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55676 | Windows USB Video Class System Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55676</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55677 | Windows Device Association Broker Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55677</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55678 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55678</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55679 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55679</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55680 | Windows Cloud Files Mini Filter Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55680</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55681 | Desktop Windows Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55681</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55682 | Windows BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55682</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55683 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55683</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55684 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55684</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55685 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55685</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55686 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55686</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55687 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55687</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55688 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55688</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55689 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55689</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55690 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55690</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55691 | Windows PrintWorkflowUserSvc Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55691</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55692 | Windows Error Reporting Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55692</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55693 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55693</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55694 | Windows Error Reporting Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55694</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55695 | Windows WLAN AutoConfig Service Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55695</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55696 | NtQueryInformation Token function (ntifs.h) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55696</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55697 | Azure Local Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55697</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55698 | DirectX Graphics Kernel Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55698</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55699 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55699</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55700 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55700</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55701 | Windows Authentication Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55701</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58714 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58714</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58715 | Windows Speech Runtime Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58715</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58716 | Windows Speech Runtime Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58716</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58717 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58717</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58718 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58718</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58719 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58719</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58720 | Windows Cryptographic Services Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58720</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58722 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58722</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58724 | Arc Enabled Servers - Azure Connected Machine Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58724</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58725 | Windows COM+ Event System Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58725</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58726 | Windows SMB Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58726</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58727 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58727</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58728 | Windows Bluetooth Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58728</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58729 | Windows Local Session Manager (LSM) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58729</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58730 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58730</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58731 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58731</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58732 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58732</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58733 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58733</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58734 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58734</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58735 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58735</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58736 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58736</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58737 | Remote Desktop Protocol Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58737</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58738 | Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58738</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58739 | Microsoft Windows File Explorer Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58739</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59184 | Storage Spaces Direct Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59184</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59185 | NTLM Hash Disclosure Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59185</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59186 | Windows Kernel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59186</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59187 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59187</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59188 | Microsoft Failover Cluster Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59188</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59189 | Microsoft Brokering File System Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59189</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59190 | Windows Search Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59190</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59191 | Windows Connected Devices Platform Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59191</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59192 | Storport.sys Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59192</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59193 | Windows Management Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59193</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59194 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59194</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59195 | Microsoft Graphics Component Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59195</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59196 | Windows Simple Search and Discovery Protocol (SSDP) Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59196</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59197 | Windows ETL Channel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59197</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59198 | Windows Search Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59198</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59199 | Software Protection Platform (SPP) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59199</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59200 | Data Sharing Service Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59200</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59201 | Network Connection Status Indicator (NCSI) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59201</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59202 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59202</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59203 | Windows State Repository API Server File Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59203</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59204 | Windows Management Services Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59204</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59205 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59205</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59206 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Deduplication Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59206</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59207 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59207</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59208 | Windows MapUrlToZone Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59208</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59209 | Windows Push Notification Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59209</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59210 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Deduplication Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59210</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59211 | Windows Push Notification Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59211</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59213 | Configuration Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59213</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59214 | Microsoft Windows File Explorer Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59214</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59221 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59221</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59222 | Microsoft Word Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59222</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59223 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59223</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59224 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59224</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59225 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59225</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59226 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59226</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59227 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59227</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59228 | Microsoft SharePoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59228</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59229 | Microsoft Office Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59229</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59230 | Windows Remote Access Connection Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59230</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59231 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59231</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59232 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59232</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59233 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59233</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59234 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59234</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59235 | Microsoft Excel Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59235</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59236 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59236</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59237 | Microsoft SharePoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59237</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59238 | Microsoft PowerPoint Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59238</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59241 | Windows Health and Optimized Experiences Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59241</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59242 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59242</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59243 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59243</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59244 | NTLM Hash Disclosure Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59244</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59248 | Microsoft Exchange Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59248</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59249 | Microsoft Exchange Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59249</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59250 | JDBC Driver for SQL Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59250</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59253 | Windows Search Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59253</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59254 | Microsoft DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59254</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59255 | Windows DWM Core Library Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59255</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59257 | Windows Local Session Manager (LSM) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59257</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59258 | Windows Active Directory Federation Services (ADFS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59258</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59259 | Windows Local Session Manager (LSM) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59259</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59260 | Microsoft Failover Cluster Virtual Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59260</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59261 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59261</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59275 | Windows Authentication Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59275</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59277 | Windows Authentication Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59277</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59278 | Windows Authentication Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59278</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59280 | Windows SMB Client Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59280</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59281 | Xbox Gaming Services Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59281</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59282 | Internet Information Services (IIS) Inbox COM Objects (Global Memory) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59282</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59284 | Windows NTLM Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59284</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59285 | Azure Monitor Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59285</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59287 | Windows Server Update Service (WSUS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59287</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59288 | Playwright Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59288</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59289 | Windows Bluetooth Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59289</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59290 | Windows Bluetooth Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59290</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59291 | Confidential Azure Container Instances Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59291</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59292 | Azure Compute Gallery Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59292</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59294 | Windows Taskbar Live Preview Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59294</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59295 | Windows URL Parsing Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59295</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59494 | Azure Monitor Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59494</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59497 | Microsoft Defender for Linux Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59497</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59502 | Remote Procedure Call Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59502</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60535 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /endpoints/currency/currency of Wallos v4.1.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary ope...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60535</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the component /endpoints/currency/currency of Wallos v4.1.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37132 | Authenticated Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface via Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37132</link><description>An arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in the web-based management interface of both the AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating systems. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to upload arbitrary files and execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37133 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface via the CLI Binaryalong with accounting controls for tracking and logging user activities and resource usage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37133</link><description>An authenticated command injection vulnerability exists in the CLI binary of an AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating system. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37134 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in the Low-Level Interface Library Affecting AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37134</link><description>An authenticated command injection vulnerability exists in the CLI binary of an AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor operating system. Successful exploitation could allow an authenticated malicious actor to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37135 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerabilities in AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37135</link><description>Arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities have been identified in the command-line interface of an AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an authenticated remote malicious actor to delete arbitrary files within the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37136 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerabilities in AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37136</link><description>Arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities have been identified in the command-line interface of an AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an authenticated remote malicious actor to delete arbitrary files within the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37137 | Authenticated Arbitrary File Deletion Vulnerabilities in AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37137</link><description>Arbitrary file deletion vulnerabilities have been identified in the command-line interface of an AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor. Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an authenticated remote malicious actor to delete arbitrary files within the affected system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37138 | Authenticated Command Injection Vulnerability in CLI Binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controller/Mobility Conductor Web-Based Management Interface (Physical Access Required)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37138</link><description>An authenticated command injection vulnerability exists in the command line interface binary of AOS-10 GW and AOS-8 Controllers/Mobility Conductor operating system. Exploitation of this vulnerability requires physical access to the hardware controllers. A successful attack could allow an authenticated malicious actor with physical access to execute arbitrary commands as a privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37139 | Vulnerability in AOS firmware allows for Authenticated Local malicious actor to Permanently Disable Boot</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37139</link><description>A vulnerability in an AOS firmware binary allows an authenticated malicious actor to permanently delete necessary boot information. Successful exploitation may render the system unbootable, resulting in a Denial of Service that can only be resolved by replacing the affected hardware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8430 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Commands Connectors configuration configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8430</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Commands Connectors configuration modules) allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11548 | ibi WebFOCUS - Unauthenticated RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11548</link><description>A remote, unauthenticated privilege escalation in ibi WebFOCUS allows an attacker to gain administrative access to the application which may lead to unauthenticated Remote Code Execution</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37146 | Unauthorized Filesystem Operations in System Firmware allow Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37146</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of network access point configuration services could allow an authenticated remote attacker to perform remote command execution. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37147 | Secure Boot Bypass allows for Compromise of Hardware Root of Trust</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37147</link><description>A Secure Boot Bypass Vulnerability exists in affected Access Points that allows an adversary to bypass the hardware root of trust verification in place to ensure only vendor-signed firmware can execute on the device. An adversary can exploit this vulnerability to run modified or custom firmware on affected Access Points.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37148 | Kernel Panic triggered by Modified Ethernet Frames leads to Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37148</link><description>A vulnerability in the parsing of ethernet frames in AOS-8 Instant and AOS 10 could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to conduct a denial of service attack. Successful exploitation could allow an attacker to potentially disrupt network services and require manual intervention to restore functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36730 | Windsurf Prompt Injection via Filename</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36730</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability exists in Windsurft version 1.10.7 in Write mode using SWE-1 model.

It is possible to create a file name that will be appended to the user prompt causing Windsurf to follow its instructions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37149 | A potential 

out-of-bound reads vulnerability in HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 Server's UEFI firmware.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37149</link><description>A potential 

out-of-bound reads vulnerability in HPE ProLiant RL300 Gen11 Server's UEFI firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11577 | Clevo UEFI firmware exposed Boot Guard private keys, enabling potential abuse of the Boot Guard trust chain</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11577</link><description>Clevo’s UEFI firmware update packages, including B10717.exe, inadvertently contained private signing keys used for Boot Guard and Boot Policy Manifest verification. The exposure of these keys could allow attackers to sign malicious firmware that appears trusted by affected systems, undermining the integrity of the early boot process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46718 | A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.7 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.12 and 6.4.6 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46718</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.7 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.12 and 6.4.6 through 6.4.15 and 6.2.9 through 6.2.16 and 6.0.13 through 6.0.18 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26008 | An improper check or handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability [CWE-703] in FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3 and before 7.2.7, For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26008</link><description>An improper check or handling of exceptional conditions vulnerability [CWE-703] in FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3 and before 7.2.7, FortiProxy version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3 and before 7.2.9, FortiPAM before 1.2.0 and FortiSwitchManager version 7.2.0 through 7.2.3 and version 7.0.0 through 7.0.3 fgfm daemon may allow an unauthenticated attacker to repeatedly reset the fgfm connection via crafted SSL encrypted TCP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33507 | An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] and an incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiIsolator 2.4.0 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33507</link><description>An insufficient session expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] and an incorrect authorization vulnerability [CWE-863] in FortiIsolator 2.4.0 through 2.4.4, 2.3 all versions, 2.2.0, 2.1 all versions, 2.0 all versions authentication mechanism may allow remote unauthenticated attacker to deauthenticate logged in admins via crafted cookie and remote authenticated read-only attacker to gain write privilege via crafted cookie.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47569 | A insertion of sensitive information into sent data in Fortinet FortiManager Cloud 7.4.1 through 7.4.3, FortiVoice 7.0.0 through 7.0.4, 6.4....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47569</link><description>A insertion of sensitive information into sent data in Fortinet FortiManager Cloud 7.4.1 through 7.4.3, FortiVoice 7.0.0 through 7.0.4, 6.4.0 through 6.4.9, 6.0.7 through 6.0.12, FortiMail 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.9, FortiOS 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.15, 6.4.0 through 6.4.15, 6.2.0 through 6.2.17, 6.0.0 through 6.0.18, FortiWeb 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 6.4.0 through 6.4.3, FortiRecorder 7.2.0 through 7.2.1, 7.0.0 through 7.0.4, FortiNDR 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2.0 through 7.2.5, 7.1.0 through 7.1.1, 7.0.0 through 7.0.7, 1.5.0 through 1.5.3, FortiPAM 1.3.0 through 1.3.1, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3, FortiTester 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.3.0 through 7.3.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.1.0 through 7.1.1, 7.0.0, 4.2.0 through 4.2.1, FortiProxy 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.21, 2.0.0 through 2.0.14, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7, FortiManager 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.1 through 7.4.3 allows attacker to disclose sensitive information via specially crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50571 | A heap-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.16, 6.4.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50571</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.16, 6.4.0 through 6.4.15, 6.2.0 through 6.2.17, FortiManager Cloud 7.6.2, 7.4.1 through 7.4.5, 7.2.1 through 7.2.8, 7.0.1 through 7.0.13, 6.4.1 through 6.4.7, FortiAnalyzer Cloud 7.4.1 through 7.4.5, 7.2.1 through 7.2.8, 7.0.1 through 7.0.13, 6.4.1 through 6.4.7, FortiProxy 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.12, 7.0.0 through 7.0.19, 2.0.0 through 2.0.14, 1.2.0 through 1.2.13, 1.1.0 through 1.1.6, 1.0.0 through 1.0.7, FortiAnalyzer 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, 6.4.0 through 6.4.15, 6.2.0 through 6.2.13, 6.0.0 through 6.0.12, FortiManager 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.0 through 7.2.9, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, 6.4.0 through 6.4.15, 6.2.0 through 6.2.13, 6.0.0 through 6.0.12 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25252 | An Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] in FortiOS SSL VPN 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25252</link><description>An Insufficient Session Expiration vulnerability [CWE-613] in FortiOS SSL VPN 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.16, 6.4 all versions may allow a remote attacker (e.g. a former admin whose account was removed and whose session was terminated) in possession of the SAML record of a user session to access or re-open that session via re-use of SAML record.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25255 | An Improperly Implemented Security Check for Standard vulnerability [CWE-358] in FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4 all versions, 7.2 all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25255</link><description>An Improperly Implemented Security Check for Standard vulnerability [CWE-358] in FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4 all versions, 7.2 all versions, 7.0.1 through 7.0.21, and FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3 explicit web proxy may allow an authenticated proxy user to bypass the domain fronting protection feature via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31365 | An Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability [CWE-94] in FortiClientMac 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.1 through 7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31365</link><description>An Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability [CWE-94] in FortiClientMac 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.1 through 7.2.8 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim's host via tricking the user into visiting a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31514 | An Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability [CWE-532] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4 all versions, 7.2 all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31514</link><description>An Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability [CWE-532] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4 all versions, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions may allow an attacker with at least read-only privileges to retrieve sensitive 2FA-related information via observing logs or via diagnose command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46774 | An Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability [CWE-347] in FortiClient MacOS installer version 7.4.2 and below, version ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46774</link><description>An Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability [CWE-347] in FortiClient MacOS installer version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.9 and below, 7.0 all versions may allow a local user to escalate their privileges via FortiClient related executables.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53845 | An improper authentication vulnerability [CWE-287] in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer version 7.6.0 through 7.6.3 and before 7.4.6 allows an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53845</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability [CWE-287] in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer version 7.6.0 through 7.6.3 and before 7.4.6 allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain information pertaining to the device's health and status, or cause a denial of service via crafted OFTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54822 | An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and before 7.2.8 &amp; Fortinet FortiProxy bef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54822</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and before 7.2.8 &amp; Fortinet FortiProxy before version 7.4.8 allows an authenticated attacker to access static files of others VDOMs via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54893 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the Hosts templates configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54893</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Hosts templates configuration modules) allows Stored 

 XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54973 | A concurrent execution using shared resource with improper synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability [CWE-362] in Fortinet FortiAnaly...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54973</link><description>A concurrent execution using shared resource with improper synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability [CWE-362] in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer version 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 and before 7.0.13 allows an attacker to attempt to win a race condition to bypass the FortiCloud SSO authorization via crafted FortiCloud SSO requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57716 | An Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability [CWE-427] in FortiClient Windows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0 all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57716</link><description>An Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability [CWE-427] in FortiClient Windows 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0 all versions may allow a local low privileged user to perform a DLL hijacking attack via placing a malicious DLL to the FortiClient Online Installer installation folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59921 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in Fortinet FortiADC version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59921</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in Fortinet FortiADC version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.1.4 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive data via crafted HTTP or HTTPs requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62366 | Mailgen vulnerable to HTML injection and cross-site scripting via plaintext email generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62366</link><description>mailgen is a Node.js package that generates responsive HTML e-mails for sending transactional mail. Mailgen versions through 2.0.30 contain an HTML injection vulnerability in plaintext emails produced by the generatePlaintext method when user‑generated content is supplied. The function attempts to remove HTML tags, but if tags are provided as encoded HTML entities they are not removed and are later decoded, resulting in active HTML (for example an img tag with an event handler) in the supposed plaintext output. In contexts where the generated plaintext string is subsequently rendered as HTML, this can allow execution of attacker‑controlled JavaScript. Versions 2.0.31 and later contain a fix. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8429 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the ACL Action access configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8429</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (ACL Action access configuration modules) allows Stored 

 XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48891 | An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiSOAR 7.6.0 thro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48891</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiSOAR 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.5.0 through 7.5.1, 7.4 all versions, 7.3 all versions may allow an attacker who has already obtained a non-login low privileged shell access (via another hypothetical vulnerability) to perform a local privilege escalation via crafted commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22258 | A heap-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiSRA 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, FortiPAM 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, 1.3.0 through 1.3.1, 1.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22258</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow in Fortinet FortiSRA 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, FortiPAM 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, 1.3.0 through 1.3.1, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3, FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, 7.2.0 through 7.2.10, 7.0.2 through 7.0.16, FortiSwitchManager 7.2.1 through 7.2.5 allows attackers to escalate their privilege via specially crafted http requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25253 | An Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch vulnerability [CWE-297] in FortiProxy version 7.6.1 and below, version 7.4.8 and be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25253</link><description>An Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch vulnerability [CWE-297] in FortiProxy version 7.6.1 and below, version 7.4.8 and below, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions and FortiOS version 7.6.2 and below, version 7.4.8 and below, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions ZTNA proxy may allow an unauthenticated attacker in a man-in-the middle position to intercept and tamper with connections to the ZTNA proxy</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31366 | An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31366</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.7, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions; FortiSASE 25.3.a may allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform a reflected cross site scripting (XSS) via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47890 | An URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerabilities [CWE-601] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47890</link><description>An URL Redirection to Untrusted Site vulnerabilities [CWE-601] in FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.2, 7.4.0 through 7.4.8, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; FortiProxy 7.6.0 through 7.6.3, 7.4 all versions, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions; FortiSASE 25.2.a may allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform an open redirect attack via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49201 | A weak authentication in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, 1.3.0 through 1.3.1, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49201</link><description>A weak authentication in Fortinet FortiPAM 1.5.0, 1.4.0 through 1.4.2, 1.3.0 through 1.3.1, 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3, FortiSwitchManager 7.2.0 through 7.2.4 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted http requests</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57740 | An Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability [CWE-122] in FortiOS version 7.6.2 and below, version 7.4.7 and below, version 7.2.10 and below,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57740</link><description>An Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability [CWE-122] in FortiOS version 7.6.2 and below, version 7.4.7 and below, version 7.2.10 and below, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions; FortiPAM version 1.5.0, version 1.4.2 and below, 1.3 all versions, 1.2 all versions, 1.1 all versions, 1.0 all versions and FortiProxy version 7.6.2 and below, version 7.4.3 and below, 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions RDP bookmark connection may allow an authenticated user to execute unauthorized code via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57741 | An Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability [CWE-732] in FortiClientMac 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57741</link><description>An Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability [CWE-732] in FortiClientMac 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, 7.0 all versions may allow a local attacker to run arbitrary code or commands via LaunchDaemon hijacking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58324 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiSIEM 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.1 all versions, 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58324</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiSIEM 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.1 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.7 all versions, 6.6 all versions, 6.5 all versions, 6.4 all versions, 6.3 all versions, 6.2 all versions may allow an authenticated attacker to perform a stored cross site scripting (XSS) attack via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58325 | An Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability [CWE-684] in FortiOS 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.5 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58325</link><description>An Incorrect Provision of Specified Functionality vulnerability [CWE-684] in FortiOS 7.6.0, 7.4.0 through 7.4.5, 7.2.5 through 7.2.10, 7.0.0 through 7.0.15, 6.4 all versions may allow a local authenticated attacker to execute system commands via crafted CLI commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58903 | An Unchecked Return Value vulnerability [CWE-252] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.6.0 through 7.6.3 and before 7.4.8 API allows an authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58903</link><description>An Unchecked Return Value vulnerability [CWE-252] in Fortinet FortiOS version 7.6.0 through 7.6.3 and before 7.4.8 API allows an authenticated user to cause a  Null Pointer Dereference, crashing the http daemon via a specialy crafted request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62172 | Home Assistant vulnerable to Stored XSS in Energy dashboard from Energy Entity Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62172</link><description>Home Assistant is open source home automation software that puts local control and privacy first. In versions 2025.1.0 through 2025.10.1, the energy dashboard is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. An authenticated user can inject malicious JavaScript code into an energy entity's name field, which is then executed when any user hovers over data points in the energy dashboard graph tooltips. The vulnerability exists because entity names containing HTML are not properly sanitized before being rendered in graph tooltips. This could allow an attacker with authentication to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of other users' sessions. Additionally, if an energy provider (such as Tibber) supplies a malicious default name for an entity, the vulnerability can be exploited without direct user action when the default name is used. This issue has been patched in version 2025.10.2. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54891 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the ACL Resource Access configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54891</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (ACL Resource access configuration modules) allows Stored 

XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62157 | Argo Workflows exposes artifact repository credentials in workflow-controller logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62157</link><description>Argo Workflows is an open source container-native workflow engine for orchestrating parallel jobs on Kubernetes. Argo Workflows versions prior to 3.6.12 and versions 3.7.0 through 3.7.2 expose artifact repository credentials in plaintext in workflow-controller pod logs. An attacker with permissions to read pod logs in a namespace running Argo Workflows can read the workflow-controller logs and obtain credentials to the artifact repository. Update to versions 3.6.12 or 3.7.3 to remediate the vulnerability. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54892 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the SNMP traps group configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54892</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (SNMP traps group configuration modules) 

allows Stored XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54889 | A user with elevated privileges can inject XSS in the SNMP traps manufacturer configuration page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (SNMP traps manufacturer configuration modules) allows Stored XSS by users with elevated privileges.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62156 | argo-workflows Zip Slip path traversal allows arbitrary file write and container configuration overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62156</link><description>Argo Workflows is an open source container-native workflow engine for orchestrating parallel jobs on Kubernetes. Versions prior to 3.6.12 and versions 3.7.0 through 3.7.2 contain a Zip Slip path traversal vulnerability in artifact extraction. During artifact extraction the unpack/untar logic (workflow/executor/executor.go) uses filepath.Join(dest, filepath.Clean(header.Name)) without validating that header.Name stays within the intended extraction directory. A malicious archive entry can supply a traversal or absolute path that, after cleaning, overrides the destination directory and causes files to be written outside the /work/tmp extraction path and into system directories such as /etc inside the container. The vulnerability enables arbitrary file creation or overwrite in system configuration locations (for example /etc/passwd, /etc/hosts, /etc/crontab), which can lead to privilege escalation or persistence within the affected container. Update to 3.6.12 or 3.7.3 to remediate the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0033 | Improper access control within AMD SEV-SNP could allow an admin privileged attacker to write to the RMP during SNP initialization, potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0033</link><description>Improper access control within AMD SEV-SNP could allow an admin privileged attacker to write to the RMP during SNP initialization, potentially resulting in a loss of SEV-SNP guest memory integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56747 | Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability in the Api_instructor controller where regul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56747</link><description>Creativeitem Academy LMS up to and including 5.13 contains a privilege escalation vulnerability in the Api_instructor controller where regular authenticated users can access instructor-only functions without proper role validation, allowing unauthorized course creation and management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:51:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44088 | Apache Geode: Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44088</link><description>Malicious script injection ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Geode web-api (REST). This vulnerability allows an attacker that tricks a logged-in user into clicking a specially-crafted link to execute code on the returned page, which could lead to theft of the user's session information and even account takeover.



This issue affects Apache Geode: all versions prior to 1.15.2

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.15.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59428 | EspoCRM allows arbitrary user creation via stored SVG injection and CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59428</link><description>EspoCRM is an open source customer relationship management application. In versions before 9.1.9, a vulnerability allows arbitrary user creation, including administrative accounts, through a combination of stored SVG injection and lack of CSRF protection. An attacker with Knowledge Base edit permissions can embed a malicious SVG element containing a link in the body field of an article. When an authenticated user clicks the malicious link, they are redirected to an attacker-controlled HTML page that executes a CSRF request against the api/v1/User endpoint. If the victim is prompted for and enters their credentials, an attacker-controlled account is created with privileges determined by the CSRF payload. This issue has been patched in version 9.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10985 | OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10985</link><description>OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10986 | Path traversal in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacker with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10986</link><description>Path traversal in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to write data in unintended locations on disk.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5946 | RCE via the poller reload feature available only to user with high privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5946</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (Poller reload setup in the configuration modules) allows OS Command Injection.
On the poller parameters page, a user with high privilege is able to concatenate custom instructions into the poller reload command.

This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8428 | XSS found in the HTTP loader widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Centreon Infra Monitoring (HTTP Loader widget modules) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Infra Monitoring: from 24.10.0 before 24.10.13, from 24.04.0 before 24.04.18, from 23.10.0 before 23.10.28.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10242 | OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10242</link><description>OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10243 | OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10243</link><description>OS command injection in the admin panel of Ivanti EPMM before version 12.6.0.2, 12.5.0.4, and 12.4.0.4 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27906 | IBM Content Navigator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27906</link><description>IBM Content Navigator 3.0.11, 3.0.15, 3.1.0, and 3.2.0 could expose the directory listing of the application upon using an application URL. Application files and folders are visible in the browser to a user; however, the contents of the files cannot be read obtained or modified.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22831 | Buffer Overflow in NTFS when parsing the VOLUME_NAME</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22831</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause an Out-of-bounds Write by local. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to data corruption and loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22832 | Buffer Overflow in NTFS when parsing the ATTRIBUTE_LIST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22832</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause an Out-of-bounds Write by local. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to data corruption and loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:15:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22833 | FixupArray Pointer Validation in NTFS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22833</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause a Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input by local accessing. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33044 | exFat Memory Corruption Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33044</link><description>APTIOV contains a vulnerability in BIOS where an attacker may cause an Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer by local means. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to memory corruption and impact Integrity and Availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47856 | Two improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiVoi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47856</link><description>Two improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabilities [CWE-78] in Fortinet FortiVoice version 7.2.0, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6 and before 6.4.10 allows a privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via crafted HTTP/HTTPS or CLI requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9177 | Rockwell Automation 1715 EtherNet/IP Comms Module Denial-Of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9177</link><description>A denial-of-service security issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue stems from a high number of requests sent to the web server. This could result in a web server crash however; this does not impact I/O control or communication . A power cycle is required to recover and utilize the webpage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9178 | Rockwell Automation 1715 EtherNet/IP Comms Module Denial-Of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9178</link><description>A denial-of-service security issue exists in the affected product and version. The security issue is caused through CIP communication using crafted payloads. The security issue could result in no CIP communication with 1715 EtherNet/IP Adapter.A restart is required to recover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10610 | SQLi in SFS Winsure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SFS Consulting Information Processing Industry and Foreign Trade Inc. Winsure allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Winsure: through Version dated 21.08.2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11498 | CSV Formula Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11498</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability exists in System Diagnostics Manager (SDM) of B&amp;amp;R Automation Runtime versions before 6.4 enabling a remote attacker to inject formula data into a generated CSV file. The exploitation of this vulnerability requires the attacker to create a malicious link. The user would need to click on this link, after which the resulting CSV file addi-tionally needs to be manually opened.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11708 | Use-after-free in MediaTrackGraphImpl::GetInstance() This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11708</link><description>Use-after-free in MediaTrackGraphImpl::GetInstance() This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11710 | A compromised web process using malicious IPC messages could have caused the privileged browser process to reveal blocks of its memory to th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11710</link><description>A compromised web process using malicious IPC messages could have caused the privileged browser process to reveal blocks of its memory to the compromised process. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.29, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11711 | There was a way to change the value of JavaScript Object properties that were supposed to be non-writeable. This vulnerability affects Firef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11711</link><description>There was a way to change the value of JavaScript Object properties that were supposed to be non-writeable. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.29, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11712 | A malicious page could have used the type attribute of an OBJECT tag to override the default browser behavior when encountering a web resour...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11712</link><description>A malicious page could have used the type attribute of an OBJECT tag to override the default browser behavior when encountering a web resource served without a content-type. This could have contributed to an XSS on a site that unsafely serves files without a content-type header. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11713 | Insufficient escaping in the “Copy as cURL” feature could have been used to trick a user into executing unexpected code on Windows. This did...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11713</link><description>Insufficient escaping in the “Copy as cURL” feature could have been used to trick a user into executing unexpected code on Windows. This did not affect Firefox running on other operating systems. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11714 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.28, Firefox ESR 140.3, Thunderbird ESR 140.3, Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. Some of these b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11714</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.28, Firefox ESR 140.3, Thunderbird ESR 140.3, Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.29, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11715 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.3, Thunderbird ESR 140.3, Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. Some of these bugs showed evidence ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11715</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.3, Thunderbird ESR 140.3, Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11716 | Links in a sandboxed iframe could open an external app on Android without the required "allow-" permission. This vulnerability affects Firef...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11716</link><description>Links in a sandboxed iframe could open an external app on Android without the required "allow-" permission. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144 and Thunderbird &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11717 | When switching between Android apps using the card carousel Firefox shows a black screen as its card image when a password-related screen wa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11717</link><description>When switching between Android apps using the card carousel Firefox shows a black screen as its card image when a password-related screen was the last one being used. Prior to Firefox 144 the password edit screen was visible. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11718 | When the address bar was hidden due to scrolling on Android, a malicious page could create a fake address bar to fool the user in response t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11718</link><description>When the address bar was hidden due to scrolling on Android, a malicious page could create a fake address bar to fool the user in response to a visibilitychange event This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11719 | Starting in Firefox 143, the use of the native messaging API by web extensions on Windows could lead to crashes caused by use-after-free mem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11719</link><description>Starting in Firefox 143, the use of the native messaging API by web extensions on Windows could lead to crashes caused by use-after-free memory corruption. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144 and Thunderbird &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11720 | The Firefox and Firefox Focus UI for the Android custom tab feature only showed the "site" that was loaded, not the full hostname. User supp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11720</link><description>The Firefox and Firefox Focus UI for the Android custom tab feature only showed the "site" that was loaded, not the full hostname. User supplied content hosted on a subdomain of a site could have been used to fool a user into thinking it was content from a different subdomain of that site. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11721 | Memory safety bug present in Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11721</link><description>Memory safety bug present in Firefox 143 and Thunderbird 143. This bug showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort this could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144 and Thunderbird &lt; 144.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7328 | Rockwell Automation Comms - 1783-NATR Multiple Broken Authentication Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7328</link><description>Multiple Broken Authentication security issues exist in the affected product. The security issues are due to missing authentication checks on critical functions. These could result in potential denial-of-service, admin account takeover, or NAT rule modifications. Devices would no longer be able to communicate through NATR as a result of denial-of-service or NAT rule modifications. NAT rule modification could also result in device communication to incorrect endpoints. Admin account takeover could allow modification of configuration and require physical access to restore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7329 | Rockwell Automation Comms - 1783-NATR Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7329</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting security issue exists in the affected product that could potentially allow a malicious user to view and modify sensitive data or make the webpage unavailable. The vulnerability stems from missing special character filtering and encoding. Successful exploitation requires an attacker to be able to update configuration fields behind admin login.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7330 | Rockwell Automation 1783-NATR Cross-Site Request Forgery Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7330</link><description>A cross-site request forgery security issue exists in the product and version listed. The vulnerability stems from missing CSRF checks on the impacted form. This allows for unintended configuration modification if an attacker can convince a logged in admin to visit a crafted link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11709 | A compromised web process was able to trigger out of bounds reads and writes in a more privileged process using manipulated WebGL textures. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11709</link><description>A compromised web process was able to trigger out of bounds reads and writes in a more privileged process using manipulated WebGL textures. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 144, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.29, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.4, Thunderbird &lt; 144, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9063 | Rockwell Automation PanelView Plus 7 Performance Series B Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9063</link><description>An authentication bypass security issue exists within FactoryTalk View Machine Edition  Web Browser ActiveX control. Exploitation of this vulnerability allows unauthorized access to the PanelView Plus 7 Series B, including access to the file system, retrieval of diagnostic information, event logs, and more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9064 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk View Machine Edition Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9064</link><description>A path traversal security issue exists within FactoryTalk View Machine Edition, allowing unauthenticated attackers on the same network as the device to delete any file within the panels operating system. Exploitation of this vulnerability is dependent on the knowledge of filenames to be deleted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9066 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® ViewPoint XXE to Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9066</link><description>A security issue was discovered within FactoryTalk® ViewPoint, allowing unauthenticated attackers to achieve XXE. Certain SOAP requests can be abused to perform XXE, resulting in a temporary denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9067 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Linx Privilege Escalation Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9067</link><description>A security issue exists within the x86 Microsoft Installer File (MSI), installed with FTLinx. Authenticated attackers with valid Windows user credentials can initiate a repair and hijack the resulting console window. This allows the launching of a command prompt running with SYSTEM-level privileges, allowing full access to all files, processes, and system resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9068 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Linx Privilege Escalation Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9068</link><description>A security issue exists within the Rockwell Automation Driver Package x64 Microsoft Installer File (MSI) repair functionality, installed with FTLinx. Authenticated attackers with valid Windows Users credentials can initiate a repair and hijack the resulting console window for vbpinstall.exe. This allows the launching of a command prompt running with SYSTEM-level privileges, allowing full access to all files, processes, and system resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9124 | Rockwell Automation Compact GuardLogix® 5370 Denial-Of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9124</link><description>A denial-of-service security issue in the affected product. The security issue stems from a fault occurring when a crafted CIP unconnected explicit message is sent. This can result in a major non-recoverable fault.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9437 | Rockwell Automation ArmorStart® AOP Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9437</link><description>A security issue exists within the Studio 5000 Logix Designer add-on profile (AOP) for the ArmorStart Classic distributed motor controller, resulting in denial-of-service. This vulnerability is possible due to the input of invalid values into Component Object Model (COM) methods.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-20001 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V1 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.3), SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-20001</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V1 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.3), SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V2 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.3). The web server interface of affected devices improperly processes incoming malformed HTTP traffic at high rate. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to force the device entering the stop/defect state, thus creating a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-20002 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V1 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.2), SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-20002</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V1 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.2), SIMATIC S7-1200 CPU V2 family (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V2.0.2). Affected controllers are vulnerable to capture-replay in the communication with the engineering software. This could allow an on-path attacker between the engineering software and the controller to execute any previously recorded commands at a later time (e.g. set the controller to STOP), regardless whether or not the controller had a password configured.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10228 | Session Hijacking in Rolantis Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Agentis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10228</link><description>Session Fixation vulnerability in Rolantis Information Technologies Agentis allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Agentis: before 4.44.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20709 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20709</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00415809; Issue ID: MSV-3405.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20710 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20710</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00418785; Issue ID: MSV-3515.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20711 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20711</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00422399; Issue ID: MSV-3748.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20712 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20712</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00422323; Issue ID: MSV-3810.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20713 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20713</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00432661; Issue ID: MSV-3904.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20714 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20714</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00432659; Issue ID: MSV-3902.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20715 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20715</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00421152; Issue ID: MSV-3731.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20716 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20716</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00421149; Issue ID: MSV-3728.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20717 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20717</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00419946; Issue ID: MSV-3582.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20718 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20718</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00419945; Issue ID: MSV-3581.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20719 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20719</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00418955; Issue ID: MSV-3570.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20720 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20720</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00418954; Issue ID: MSV-3569.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20721 | In imgsensor, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20721</link><description>In imgsensor, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS10089545; Issue ID: MSV-4279.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20722 | In gnss driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20722</link><description>In gnss driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09920036; Issue ID: MSV-3798.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20723 | In gnss driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20723</link><description>In gnss driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09920033; Issue ID: MSV-3797.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20724 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20724</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00418894; Issue ID: MSV-3475.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40755 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V4.0 SP1). Affected applications are vulnerable to SQL injection through ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40755</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V4.0 SP1). Affected applications are vulnerable to SQL injection through getTotalAndFilterCounts endpoint. An authenticated low privileged attacker could exploit to insert data and achieve privilege escalation. (ZDI-CAN-26570)</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40765 | A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic V3.1 (All versions &gt;= V3.1.2.2 &lt; V3.1.2.3). The affected application contain...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40765</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in TeleControl Server Basic V3.1 (All versions &gt;= V3.1.2.2 &lt; V3.1.2.3). The affected application contains an information disclosure vulnerability. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to obtain password hashes of users and to login to and perform authenticated operations of the database service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40771 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1542SP-1 (6GK7542-6UX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIMATIC CP 1542SP-1 IRC (6GK7542-6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40771</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1542SP-1 (6GK7542-6UX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIMATIC CP 1542SP-1 IRC (6GK7542-6VX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIMATIC CP 1543SP-1 (6GK7543-6WX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIPLUS ET 200SP CP 1542SP-1 IRC TX RAIL (6AG2542-6VX00-4XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIPLUS ET 200SP CP 1543SP-1 ISEC (6AG1543-6WX00-7XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24), SIPLUS ET 200SP CP 1543SP-1 ISEC TX RAIL (6AG2543-6WX00-4XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.24). Affected devices do not properly authenticate configuration connections. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to access the configuration data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40772 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications are vulnerable to stored Cross-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40772</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications are vulnerable to stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), allowing an attacker to inject malicious code that can be executed by other users when they visit the affected page.

Successful exploitation allows an attacker to impersonate other users within the application and steal their session data. This could enable unauthorized access to accounts and potentially lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40773 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications contains a broken access contro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40773</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications contains a broken access control vulnerability. The authorization mechanism lacks sufficient server-side checks, allowing an attacker to execute a specific API request.

Successful exploitation allows an attacker to potentially manipulate data belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40774 | A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications store user passwords encrypted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40774</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SiPass integrated (All versions &lt; V3.0). Affected server applications store user passwords encrypted in its database. Decryption keys are accessible to users with administrative privileges, allowing them to recover passwords.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to obtain and use valid user passwords. This can lead to unauthorized access to user accounts, data breaches, and potential system compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40809 | A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40809</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 6). The affected applications contains an out of bounds write vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40810 | A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40810</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 6). The affected applications contains an out of bounds write vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40811 | A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40811</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 6). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40812 | A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40812</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Solid Edge SE2024 (All versions &lt; V224.0 Update 14), Solid Edge SE2025 (All versions &lt; V225.0 Update 6). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted PRT files. This could allow an attacker to crash the application or execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46581 | ZTE ZXCDN product has a Struts RCE Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46581</link><description>ZTE's ZXCDN product  is affected by a Struts remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can remotely execute commands with non-root privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41699 | Phoenix Contact: Security Advisory for CHARX SEC-3xxx charging controllers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41699</link><description>An low privileged remote attacker with an account for the Web-based management can change the system configuration to perform a command injection as root, resulting in a total loss of confidentiality, availability and integrity due to improper control of generation of code ('Code Injection').</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41718 | Murrelektronik: Unprotected Transport of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41718</link><description>A cleartext transmission of sensitive information vulnerability in the affected products allows an unauthorized remote attacker to gain login credentials and access the Web-UI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41703 | Phoenix Contact: UPS Shutdown via Unauthenticated Modbus Command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41703</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can cause a Denial of Service by turning off the output of the UPS via Modbus command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41704 | Phoenix Contact: Unauthenticated Modbus Service DoS via Crafted Function Code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41704</link><description>An unauthanticated remote attacker can perform a DoS of the Modbus service by sending a specific function and sub-function code without affecting the core functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41705 | Phoenix Contact: WebSocket Message Interception Leaks Webfrontend Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41705</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker (MITM) can intercept the websocket messages to gain access to the login credentials for the Webfrontend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41706 | Phoenix Contact: Webserver Denial of Service through Malformed Content-Length</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41706</link><description>The webserver is vulnerable to a denial of service condition. An unauthenticated remote attacker can craft a special GET request with an over-long content-length to trigger the issue without affecting the core functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41707 | Phoenix Contact: WebSocket Handler Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41707</link><description>The websocket handler is vulnerable to a denial of service condition. An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a crafted websocket message to trigger the issue without affecting the core functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 08:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55078 | Incomplete validation of kernel object pointers in system calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55078</link><description>In Eclipse ThreadX before version 6.4.3, an attacker can cause a denial of service (crash) by providing a pointer to a reserved or unmapped memory region. Vulnerable system calls had a check of pointers, but that check wasn't verifying whether the pointer is outside the module memory region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 07:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10357 | Simple SEO &amp;lt; 2.0.32 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10357</link><description>The Simple SEO WordPress plugin before 2.0.32 does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputing them in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 06:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11731 | Libxslt: type confusion in exsltfuncresultcompfunction of libxslt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11731</link><description>A flaw was found in the exsltFuncResultComp() function of libxslt, which handles EXSLT  elements during stylesheet parsing. Due to improper type handling, the function may treat an XML document node as a regular XML element node, resulting in a type confusion. This can cause unexpected memory reads and potential crashes. While difficult to exploit, the flaw could lead to application instability or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 06:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8594 | Pz-LinkCard &amp;lt; 2.5.7 - Contributor+ SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8594</link><description>The Pz-LinkCard WordPress plugin before 2.5.7 does not validate a parameter before making a request to it, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform SSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 06:39:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10732 | SureForms – Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.12.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10732</link><description>The SureForms – Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.1. This is due to improper access control implementation on the '/wp-json/sureforms/v1/srfm-global-settings' REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive information including API keys for Google reCAPTCHA, Cloudflare Turnstile, hCaptcha, admin email addresses, and security-related form settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 05:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59889 | Improper authentication of library files in the Eaton IPP software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker with the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59889</link><description>Improper authentication of library files in the Eaton IPP software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker with the access to the software package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 05:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42901 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP Application Server for ABAP (BAPI Browser)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42901</link><description>SAP Application Server for ABAP allows an authenticated attacker to store malicious JavaScript payloads which could be executed in victim user's browser when accessing the affected functionality of BAPI explorer. This has low impact on confidentiality and integrity with no impact on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42902 | Memory Corruption vulnerability in SAP Netweaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42902</link><description>Due to the memory corruption vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform, an unauthenticated attacker can send a corrupted SAP Logon Ticket or SAP Assertion Ticket to the SAP application server. This leads to a dereference of NULL which makes the work process crash. As a result, it has a low impact on the availability but no impact on the confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42903 | User Enumeration and Sensitive Data Exposure via RFC Function in SAP Financial Service Claims Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42903</link><description>A vulnerability in SAP Financial Service Claims Management RFC function ICL_USER_GET_NAME_AND_ADDRESS allows user enumeration and potential disclosure of personal data through response discrepancies, causing low impact on confidentiality with no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42906 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42906</link><description>SAP Commerce Cloud contains a path traversal vulnerability that may allow users to access web applications such as the Administration Console from addresses where the Administration Console is not explicitly deployed. This could potentially bypass configured access restrictions, resulting in a low impact on confidentiality, with no impact on the integrity or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42908 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42908</link><description>Due to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP, an authenticated attacker could initiate transactions directly via the session manager, bypassing the first transaction screen and the associated authorization check. This vulnerability could allow the attacker to perform actions and execute transactions that would normally require specific permissions, compromising the integrity and confidentiality of the system by enabling unauthorized access to restricted functionality. There is no impact to availability from this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42909 | Security Misconfiguration vulnerability in SAP Cloud Appliance Library Appliances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42909</link><description>SAP Cloud Appliance Library Appliances allows an attacker with high privileges to leverage an insecure S/4HANA default profile setting in an existing SAP CAL appliances to gain access to other appliances. This has low impact on confidentiality of the application, integrity and availability is not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42910 | Unrestricted File Upload Vulnerability in SAP Supplier Relationship Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42910</link><description>Due to missing verification of file type or content, SAP Supplier Relationship Management allows an authenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files. These files could include executables which might be downloaded and executed by the user which could host malware. On successful exploitation an attacker could cause high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42937 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in SAP Print Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42937</link><description>SAP Print Service (SAPSprint) performs insufficient validation of path information provided by users. An unauthenticated attacker could traverse to the parent directory and over-write system files causing high impact on confidentiality integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42939 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP S/4HANA (Manage Processing Rules - For Bank Statements)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42939</link><description>SAP S/4HANA (Manage Processing Rules - For Bank Statements) allows an authenticated attacker with basic privileges to delete conditions from any shared rule of any user by tampering the request parameter. Due to missing authorization check, the attacker can delete shared rule conditions that should be restricted, compromising the integrity of the application without affecting its confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62365 | LibreNMS vulnerable to Reflected-XSS in `report_this` function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62365</link><description>LibreNMS is an open-source, PHP/MySQL/SNMP-based network monitoring system. Prior to 25.7.0, there is a reflected-XSS in `report_this` function in `librenms/includes/functions.php`. The `report_this` function had improper filtering (`htmlentities` function was incorrectly use in a href environment), which caused the `project_issues` parameter to trigger an XSS vulnerability. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62362 | Name and e-mail of employee that has done a publication is discoverable in gpp-burgerportaal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62362</link><description>gpp-burgerportaal is a Dutch government citizen portal application. In versions before 2.0.3, 3.0.2, and 4.0.1, the name and email address of employees who publish content are exposed in network responses and can be discovered by viewing the browser's developer tools network tab. This information disclosure may violate employee privacy expectations and could be used for targeted attacks or unwanted contact. This issue has been patched in versions 2.0.3, 3.0.2, and 4.0.1. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62363 | yt-grabber-tui allows arbitrary code execution via configurable yt-dlp path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62363</link><description>yt-grabber-tui is a terminal user interface application for downloading videos. In versions before 1.0-rc, the application allows users to configure the path to the yt-dlp executable via the path_to_yt_dlp configuration setting. An attacker with write access to the configuration file or the filesystem location of the configured executable can replace the executable with malicious code or create a symlink to an arbitrary executable. When the application invokes yt-dlp, the malicious code is executed with the privileges of the user running yt-grabber-tui. This vulnerability has been patched in version 1.0-rc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62361 | WeGIA Open Redirect Vulnerability in `control.php` endpoint `nextPage` parameter (metodo=listarTodos nomeClasse=AlmoxarifeControle)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62361</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.0, an Open Redirect vulnerability was identified in the control.php endpoint of the WeGIA application, specifically in the nextPage parameter (metodo=listarTodos nomeClasse=AlmoxarifeControle). This vulnerability allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary external domains, enabling phishing campaigns, malicious payload distribution, or user credential theft. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62251 | Liferay Portal 7.3.0 through 7.4.3.119, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 7.4 GA through update 92 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62251</link><description>Liferay Portal 7.3.0 through 7.4.3.119, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 7.4 GA through update 92 and 7.3 GA though update 36 shows content to users who do not have permission to view it via the Menu Display Widget. This security flaw could result in sensitive information being exposed to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62359 | WeGIA Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Reflected endpoint id_pet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62359</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.0, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /pet/profile_pet.php?id_pet= endpoint of the WeGIA application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts in the id_pet parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62360 | WeGIA SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;id_dependente&amp;#x27; param at endpoint `/html/funcionario/dependente_documento.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62360</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users.Prior to 3.5.1, a SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the /html/funcionario/dependente_documento.php endpoint, specifically in the id_dependente parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the database. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11623 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11623</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62177 | WeGIA vulnerable to SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;id_funcionario&amp;#x27; param at endpoint `/html/funcionario/dependente_listar.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62177</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.1, a SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the /html/funcionario/dependente_listar.php endpoint, specifically in the id_funcionario parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the database. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62178 | WeGIA Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Reflected endpoint &amp;#x27;/html/atendido/cadastro_atendido_parentesco_pessoa_nova.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;idatendido&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62178</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.1, a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the /html/atendido/cadastro_atendido_parentesco_pessoa_nova.php endpoint of the WeGIA application. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts in the idatendido parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62179 | WeGIA SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;cpf&amp;#x27; param at endpoint `/html/funcionario/cadastro_funcionario_pessoa_existente.php`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62179</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.1, a SQL Injection vulnerability was identified in the /html/funcionario/cadastro_funcionario_pessoa_existente.php endpoint, specifically in the cpf parameter. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the database. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62358 | WeGIA Reflected XSS to Account TakeOver at /html/configuracao/configuracao_geral.php via log parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62358</link><description>WeGIA is an open source Web Manager for Institutions with a focus on Portuguese language users. Prior to 3.5.1, the log parameter in configuracao_geral.php is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript, which executes in the victim’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.5.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62383 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62383</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62384 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62384</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62385 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62385</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62386 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62386</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62387 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62387</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62388 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62388</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62389 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62389</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62390 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62390</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62391 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62391</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62392 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62392</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11622 | Insecure deserialization in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11622</link><description>Insecure deserialization in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62176 | Mastadon streaming server allows OAuth clients without the `read` scope to subscribe to public channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62176</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. In Mastodon before 4.4.6, 4.3.14, and 4.2.27, the streaming server accepts serving events for public timelines to clients using any valid authentication token, even if those tokens lack the read:statuses scope. This allows OAuth clients without the read scope to subscribe to public channels and receive public timeline events. The impact is limited, as this only affects new public posts published on the public timelines and requires an otherwise valid token, but this may lead to unexpected access to public posts in a limited-federation setting. This issue has been patched in versions 4.4.6, 4.3.14, and 4.2.27. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9713 | Path traversal in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9713</link><description>Path traversal in Ivanti Endpoint Manager allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution. User interaction is required.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62174 | Mastodon allows continued access after password reset via CLI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62174</link><description>Mastodon is an open source, federated social media platform. In Mastodon before 4.4.6, 4.3.14, and 4.2.27, when an administrator resets a user account's password via the command-line interface using `bin/tootctl accounts modify --reset-password`, active sessions and access tokens for that account are not revoked. This allows an attacker with access to a previously compromised session or token to continue using the account after the password has been reset. This issue has been patched in versions 4.2.27, 4.3.14, and 4.4.6. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62175 | Mastodon streaming API fails to disconnect disabled and suspended users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62175</link><description>Mastodon is an open source, federated social network server. In versions before 4.4.6, 4.3.14, and 4.2.27, disabling or suspending a user account does not disconnect the account from the streaming API. This allows disabled or suspended accounts to continue receiving real-time updates through existing streaming connections and to establish new streaming connections, even though they cannot interact with other API endpoints. This undermines moderation actions, as administrators expect disabled or suspended accounts to be fully disconnected from the service. This issue has been patched in versions 4.4.6, 4.3.14, and 4.2.27. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:08:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59836 | Omni is Vulnerable to DoS via Empty Create/Update Resource Requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59836</link><description>Omni manages Kubernetes on bare metal, virtual machines, or in a cloud. Prior to 1.1.5 and 1.0.2, there is a nil pointer dereference vulnerability in the Omni Resource Service allows unauthenticated users to cause a server panic and denial of service by sending empty create/update resource requests through the API endpoints. The vulnerability exists in the isSensitiveSpec function which calls grpcomni.CreateResource without checking if the resource's metadata field is nil. When a resource is created with an empty Metadata field, the CreateResource function attempts to access resource.Metadata.Version causing a segmentation fault. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.5 and 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61688 | Omni leaks information via the API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61688</link><description>Omni manages Kubernetes on bare metal, virtual machines, or in a cloud. Prior to 1.1.5 and 1.0.2, Omni might leak sensitive information via an API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62252 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62252</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions allows remote authenticated users in one virtual instance to assign an organization to a user in a different virtual instance via the _com_liferay_users_admin_web_portlet_UsersAdminPortlet_addUserIds parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62364 | text-generation-webui allows arbitrary file read via symbolic link upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62364</link><description>text-generation-webui is an open-source web interface for running Large Language Models. In versions through 3.13, a Local File Inclusion vulnerability exists in the character picture upload feature. An attacker can upload a text file containing a symbolic link to an arbitrary file path. When the application processes the upload, it follows the symbolic link and serves the contents of the targeted file through the web interface. This allows an unauthenticated attacker to read sensitive files on the server, potentially exposing system configurations, credentials, and other confidential information. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62246 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62246</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions allow remote authenticated users to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a user’s first, middle or last name text field to (1) page comments widget, (2) blog entry comments, (3) document and media document comments, (4) message board messages, (5) wiki page comments or (6) other widgets/apps that supports mentions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58084 | Mattermost Desktop App crashes when clicking on malformed external URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58084</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;= 5.13.0 fail to validate URLs external to the configured Mattermost servers, allowing an attacker on a server the user has configured to crash the user's application by sending the user a malformed URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:14:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62241 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with shipment addresses in Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.1 through 2023.Q4.5 allows remote authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62241</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with shipment addresses in Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.1 through 2023.Q4.5 allows remote authenticated users to from one virtual instance to view the shipment addresses of different virtual instance via the _com_liferay_commerce_order_web_internal_portlet_CommerceOrderPortlet_commerceOrderId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62242 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with account addresses in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62242</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with account addresses in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated users to from one account to view addresses from a different account via the _com_liferay_account_admin_web_internal_portlet_AccountEntriesAdminPortlet_addressId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62170 | rAthena map-server use-after-free vulnerability in RODEX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62170</link><description>rAthena is an open-source cross-platform MMORPG server. A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the RODEX functionality of rAthena's map-server in versions prior to commit af2f3ba. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability via a specific attacking scenario to cause a denial of service by crashing the map-server. This issue has been patched in commit af2f3ba. There are no known workarounds aside from manually applying the patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61775 | Vicekey&amp;#x27;s unexpired email confirmation link can be reused to send repeated confirmation emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61775</link><description>Vickey is a Misskey-based microblogging platform. A vulnerability exists in Vickey prior to version 2025.10.0 where unexpired email confirmation links can be reused multiple times to send repeated confirmation emails to a verified email address. Under certain conditions, a verified email address could receive repeated confirmation messages if the verification link was accessed multiple times. This issue may result in unintended email traffic but does not expose user data. The issue was addressed in version 2025.10.0 by improving validation logic to ensure verification links behave as expected after completion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62243 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62243</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to view publication comments via the _com_liferay_change_tracking_web_portlet_PublicationsPortlet_value parameter.

Publications comments in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 does not properly check user permissions, which allows remote authenticated users to edit publication comments via crafted URLs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62244 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.3.1 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62244</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.3.1 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92, and 7.3 GA through update 36 allows remote authenticated attackers to view the edit page of a publication via the _com_liferay_change_tracking_web_portlet_PublicationsPortlet_ctCollectionId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11695 | Configuration may unexpectedly disable certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11695</link><description>When tlsInsecure=False appears in a connection string, certificate validation is disabled.

This vulnerability affects MongoDB Rust Driver versions prior to v3.2.5</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7707 | World-Writable NLTK Cache Directory Vulnerability in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7707</link><description>The llama_index library version 0.12.33 sets the NLTK data directory to a subdirectory of the codebase by default, which is world-writable in multi-user environments. This configuration allows local users to overwrite, delete, or corrupt NLTK data files, leading to potential denial of service, data tampering, or privilege escalation. The vulnerability arises from the use of a shared cache directory instead of a user-specific one, making it susceptible to local data tampering and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43991 | SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.8.2 and prior and SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.3 and prior, contain an UNIX Symbolic Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43991</link><description>SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.8.2 and prior and SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.3 and prior, contain an UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) following vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access to the system could potentially exploit this vulnerability to delete arbitrary files only in that affected system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39964 | crypto: af_alg - Disallow concurrent writes in af_alg_sendmsg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39964</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: af_alg - Disallow concurrent writes in af_alg_sendmsg

Issuing two writes to the same af_alg socket is bogus as the
data will be interleaved in an unpredictable fashion.  Furthermore,
concurrent writes may create inconsistencies in the internal
socket state.

Disallow this by adding a new ctx-&gt;write field that indiciates
exclusive ownership for writing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39965 | xfrm: xfrm_alloc_spi shouldn&amp;#x27;t use 0 as SPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39965</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xfrm: xfrm_alloc_spi shouldn't use 0 as SPI

x-&gt;id.spi == 0 means "no SPI assigned", but since commit
94f39804d891 ("xfrm: Duplicate SPI Handling"), we now create states
and add them to the byspi list with this value.

__xfrm_state_delete doesn't remove those states from the byspi list,
since they shouldn't be there, and this shows up as a UAF the next
time we go through the byspi list.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37729 | Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37729</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine in Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) can lead to a malicious actor with Admin access exfiltrating sensitive information and issuing commands via a specially crafted string where Jinjava variables are evaluated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9902 | IDOR in Akınsoft QRMenu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9902</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in AKIN Software Computer Import Export Industry and Trade Co. Ltd. QRMenu allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects QRMenu: from 1.05.12 before Version dated 05.09.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6919 | SQLi in Cats Informatics&amp;#x27; Aykome</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Cats Information Technology Software Development Technologies Aykome License Tracking System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Aykome License Tracking System: through 06.10.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10720 | WP Private Content Plus &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Password Protection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10720</link><description>The WP Private Content Plus through 3.6.2 provides a global content protection feature that requires a password. However, the access control check is based only on the presence of an unprotected client-side cookie. As a result, an unauthenticated attacker can completely bypass the password protection by manually setting the cookie value in their browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9336 | A stack buffer overflow has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by input manipulation, may leading ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9336</link><description>A stack buffer overflow has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by input manipulation, may leading to a system crash (BSOD) or other potentially undefined execution. 
Refer to the 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9337 | A null pointer dereference has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specially crafted input, whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9337</link><description>A null pointer dereference has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specially crafted input, which may lead to a system crash (BSOD).
Refer to the 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11183 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in QWC2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11183</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in attribute table in QGIS QWC2 &lt;2025.08.14
allows an authorized attacker to plant arbitrary JavaScript code in the page</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11184 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in QWC2 Registration GUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11184</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in QGIS QWC2 Registration GUI &lt;=v2025.03.31
allows an authorized attacker to plant arbitrary JavaScript code in the page</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9968 | A link following vulnerability exists in the UnifyScanner component of Armoury Crate. This vulnerability may be triggered by creating a spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9968</link><description>A link following vulnerability exists in the UnifyScanner component of Armoury Crate. This vulnerability may be triggered by creating a specially crafted junction, potentially leading to local privilege escalation.
For more information, please refer to section 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' in the ASUS Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11668 | code-projects Automated Voting System update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11668</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Automated Voting System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_user.php. This manipulation of the argument Password causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11675 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11675</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11674 | PiExtract｜SOOP-CLM - Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11674</link><description>SOOP-CLM developed by PiExtract has a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to read server files or probe internal network information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10552 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10552</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10556 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Specification Management in ENOVIA Specification Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10556</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Specification Management in ENOVIA Specification Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10557 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10557</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10558 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSearch in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10558</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSearch in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11667 | code-projects Automated Voting System add_candidate_modal.php. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11667</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Automated Voting System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_candidate_modal.php.. The manipulation of the argument firstname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11672 | EBM Technologies｜Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11672</link><description>Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer developed by EBM Technologies has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access a specific page to obtain user group names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11673 | PiExtract ｜SOOP-CLM - Hidden Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11673</link><description>SOOP-CLM developed by PiExtract has a Hidden Functionality vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to exploit a hidden functionality to execute arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9976 | OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting Station Launcher App in 3DEXPERIENCE platform from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9976</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting Station Launcher App in 3DEXPERIENCE platform from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11671 | EBM Technologies｜Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11671</link><description>Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer developed by EBM Technologies has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access a specific page to obtain information such as account names and IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11666 | Tenda RP3 Pro Firmware Update force_upgrade.sh hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11666</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda RP3 Pro up to 22.5.7.93. This impacts an unknown function of the file force_upgrade.sh of the component Firmware Update Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument current_force_upgrade_pwd can lead to use of hard-coded password. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8915 | Hardcoded TLS private key in Kiloview N30 firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8915</link><description>Hardcoded TLS private key and certificate in firmware in Kiloview N30 2.02.246 allows malicious adversary to do a Mann-in-the-middle attack via the network</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9265 | API Authentication Bypass via Header Spoofing vulnerability in Kiloview NDI N30 Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9265</link><description>A broken authorization vulnerability in Kiloview NDI N30 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to deactivate user verification, giving them access to state changing actions that should only be initiated by administratorsThis issue affects 

 Kiloview NDI N30

and was fixed in Firmware version later than  2.02.0246</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11665 | D-Link DAP-2695 Firmware Update rgbin fwupdater_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11665</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DAP-2695 2.00RC131. This affects the function fwupdater_main of the file rgbin of the component Firmware Update Handler. Performing manipulation results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0636 | Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability in Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0636</link><description>EMCLI contains a high severity vulnerability where improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command could be exploited leading to Arbitrary Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27258 | Ericsson Network Manager: escalation of privilege vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27258</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager (ENM) versions prior to ENM 25.1 GA contain a vulnerability, if exploited, can result in an escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27259 | Ericsson Network Manager: improper neutralization of user controlled input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27259</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager versions prior to ENM 25.2 GA contain a vulnerability that, if exploited, can exfiltrate limited data or redirect victims to other sites or domains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11664 | Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System search-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11664</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9698 | The Plus Addons for Elementor &amp;lt; 6.3.16 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9698</link><description>The Plus Addons for Elementor  WordPress plugin before 6.3.16 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which could allow users with minimum role access as Author to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11663 | Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System manage-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11663</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-services.php. This manipulation of the argument sername causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11662 | SourceCodester Best Salon Management System booking.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11662</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Best Salon Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /booking.php. The manipulation of the argument serv_id results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31995 | HCL Unica MaxAI Workbench is vulnerable to improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31995</link><description>HCL Unica MaxAI Workbench is vulnerable to improper input validation.  This allows attackers to exploit vulnerabilities such as SQL Injection, XSS, or command injection, leading to unauthorized access or data breaches, etc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11661 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This affects an unknown part. Performing manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11660 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System uploadSllyabus.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11660</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /assets/uploadSllyabus.php. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31994 | HCL Unica Campaign is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31994</link><description>HCL Unica Campaign 12.1.10 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) where an attacker injects malicious script into an HTTP request, which is then reflected unsafely in the server's immediate response to the victim's browser, executing the script as if it originated from the trusted website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31996 | Unprotected files are impacting HCL Unica Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31996</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is affected by unprotected files due to improper access controls.   These files may contain sensitive information such as private or system information that can be exploited by attackers to compromise the application, infrastructure, or users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11659 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System uploadNotes.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11659</link><description>A flaw has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /assets/uploadNotes.php. This manipulation of the argument File causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11658 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System changeSllyabus.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11658</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected is an unknown function of the file /assets/changeSllyabus.php. The manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11657 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System createNotice.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11657</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This impacts an unknown function of the file /assets/createNotice.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11656 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System editNotes.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11656</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This affects an unknown function of the file /assets/editNotes.php. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11655 | Total.js Flow SVG File unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11655</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Total.js Flow up to 673ef9144dd25d4f4fd4fdfda5af27f230198924. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component SVG File Handler. Performing manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11654 | yousaf530 Inferno Online Clothing Store log.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11654</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in yousaf530 Inferno Online Clothing Store up to 827dd42bfbe380e8de76fdc67958c24cf1246208. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /log.php. Such manipulation of the argument cemail/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11653 | UTT HiPER 2620G fNTP strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11653</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 2620G up to 3.1.4. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/fNTP. This manipulation of the argument NTPServerIP causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36087 | IBM Security Verify Access hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36087</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.9, 11.0.0, IBM Verify Identity Access Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.9, and 11.0.0, under certain configurations, contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11652 | UTT 进取 518G formTaskEdit_ap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 518G up to V3v3.2.7-210919-161313. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/formTaskEdit_ap. The manipulation of the argument txtMin2 results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11651 | UTT 进取 518G formRemoteControl sub_4247AC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11651</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 进取 518G up to V3v3.2.7-210919-161313. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4247AC of the file /goform/formRemoteControl. The manipulation of the argument Profile leads to buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11650 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Password shadow weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11650</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow of the component Password Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to use of weak hash. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11649 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Root Account hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11649</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Root Account Handler. Performing manipulation results in use of hard-coded password. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11648 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Interface URL TF_FQDN.json server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11648</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Impacted is an unknown function of the file TF_FQDN.json of the component GATT Interface URL Handler. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11647 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11647</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component GATT Service. This manipulation of the argument DeviceToken causes information disclosure. The attack is only possible within the local network. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11646 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Service access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11646</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component GATT Service. The manipulation results in improper access controls. The attack can only be performed from the local network. The exploit is now public and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11645 | Tomofun Furbo Mobile App Authentication Token sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11645</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tomofun Furbo Mobile App up to 7.57.0a on Android. This affects an unknown part of the component Authentication Token Handler. The manipulation leads to insecure storage of sensitive information. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11644 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini UART sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11644</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component UART Interface. Executing manipulation can lead to insecure storage of sensitive information. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11643 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini MQTT Client Certificate furbo_img hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11643</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /squashfs-root/furbo_img of the component MQTT Client Certificate. Performing manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11642 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11642</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected is an unknown function of the component Registration Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be executed directly on the physical device. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11641 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Trial Restriction access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11641</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This impacts an unknown function of the component Trial Restriction Handler. This manipulation causes improper access controls. It is feasible to perform the attack on the physical device. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11640 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Bluetooth Low Energy cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This affects an unknown function of the component Bluetooth Low Energy. The manipulation results in cleartext transmission of sensitive information. Access to the local network is required for this attack. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11639 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Debug Log S3 Bucket collect_logs.sh sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11639</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file collect_logs.sh of the component Debug Log S3 Bucket Handler. The manipulation leads to insecure storage of sensitive information. An attack has to be approached locally. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11638 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Bluetooth denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11638</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Bluetooth Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attacker needs to be present on the local network. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11637 | Tomofun Furbo 360 Audio race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11637</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Audio Handler. Performing manipulation results in race condition. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11636 | Tomofun Furbo 360 Account server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11636</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Account Handler. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11635 | Tomofun Furbo 360 File Upload resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11635</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component File Upload. This manipulation causes resource consumption. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2138 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next data modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2138</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 

could allow an authenticated user on the network to delete comments from other users due to client-side enforcement of server-side security.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2139 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2139</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to delete reviews from other users due to client-side enforcement of server-side security.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2140 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2140</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to spoof email identity of the sender due to improper verification of source data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33096 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33096</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service by uploading specially crafted files using uncontrolled recursion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11634 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini UART information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11634</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This affects an unknown part of the component UART Interface. The manipulation results in information disclosure. An attack on the physical device is feasible. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11633 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini HTTP Traffic certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11633</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component HTTP Traffic Handler. The manipulation leads to improper certificate validation. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 12:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52615 | HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52615</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers.  This can lead to less secure browser default treatment for the policies controlled by these headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11631 | RainyGao DocSys deleteDoc.do path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11631</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Doc/deleteDoc.do. Executing manipulation of the argument path can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52614 | HCL Unica Platform is affected by a Cookie without HTTPOnly Flag Set vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52614</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is affected by a Cookie without HTTPOnly Flag Set vulnerability.  A malicious agent may be able to induce this event by feeding a user suitable links, either directly or via another web site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31969 | HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31969</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured Content Security Policy (CSP).  These can result in malicious resources getting loaded and browsers may come across certain types of attacks, such as cross-site scripting and clickjacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11630 | RainyGao DocSys File Upload uploadDoc.do updateRealDoc path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11630</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. Affected is the function updateRealDoc of the file /Doc/uploadDoc.do of the component File Upload. Performing manipulation of the argument path results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11629 | RainyGao DocSys getUserList.do getUserList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11629</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. This impacts the function getUserList of the file /Manage/getUserList.do. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31992 | HCL MaxAI Assistant is susceptible to a HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31992</link><description>HCL Unica MaxAI Assistant is susceptible to a HTML injection vulnerability.  An attacker could insert special characters that are processed client-side in the context of the user's session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 06:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11628 | jimit105 Project-Online-Shopping-Website Product Inventory delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11628</link><description>A flaw has been found in jimit105 Project-Online-Shopping-Website up to 7d892f442bd8a96dd242dbe2b9bd5ed641e13e64. This affects an unknown function of the file /delete.php of the component Product Inventory Handler. This manipulation of the argument product_code causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 05:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52616 | HCL Unica 12.1.10 is affected by an exposure of sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52616</link><description>HCL Unica 12.1.10 can expose sensitive system information.  An attacker could use this information to form an attack plan by leveraging known vulnerabilities in the application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 04:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31993 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to a potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31993</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to a potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). An attacker can exploit improper input validation by submitting maliciously crafted input to a target application running on a server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31997 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31997</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR).  An attacker can bypass authorization and access resources in the system directly, for example database records or files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31998 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to poor unhandled exceptions which exposes sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31998</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to poor unhandled exceptions which exposes sensitive information.  An attacker can exploit use this information to exploit known vulnerabilities launch targeted attacks, such as remote code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61884 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61884</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>