<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10750 | PowerBI Embed Reports &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10750</link><description>The PowerBI Embed Reports plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.0. This is due to missing capability checks and authentication verification on the 'testUser' endpoint accessible via the mo_epbr_admin_observer() function hooked on 'init'. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access sensitive Azure AD user information including personal identifiable information (PII) such as displayName, mail, phones, department, or detailed OAuth error data including Azure AD Application/Client IDs, error codes, trace IDs, and correlation IDs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11256 | Kognetiks Chatbot &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Uploads and Conversation Erasing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11256</link><description>The Kognetiks Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on several functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload limited safe files and erase conversations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 07:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10006 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10006</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rev_slider_vc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when RevSlider is also installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10187 | GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.17.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10187</link><description>The GSpeech TTS – WordPress Text To Speech Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'field' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.17.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11270 | Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp;amp; Patterns &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11270</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'titleTag' attribute in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11372 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Database Table Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11372</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to modification of data in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.9.2. This is due to missing capability checks on the Admin Tools REST endpoints which are registered with permission_callback set to __return_true. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to perform destructive database operations including dropping indexes on any table (including WordPress core tables like wp_options), creating duplicate configuration entries, and degrading site performance via the /wp-json/lp/v1/admin/tools/create-indexs endpoint granted they can provide table names.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11391 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11391</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the image cropper functionality in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. While the vulnerable code is in the free version, this only affected users with the paid version of the software installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11510 | FileBird &amp;lt;= 6.4.9 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11510</link><description>The FileBird – WordPress Media Library Folders &amp; File Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the /filebird/v1/fb-wipe-clear-all-data function in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to reset all of the plugin's configuration data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11517 | Event Tickets and Registration &amp;lt;= 5.26.5 - Unauthenticated Ticket Payment Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11517</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to payment bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.26.5. This is due to the /wp-json/tribe/tickets/v1/commerce/free/order endpoint not verifying that a ticket type should be free allowing the user to bypass the payment. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain access to paid tickets, without paying for them, causing a loss of revenue for the target.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11519 | Image optimization service by Optimole &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Media Offload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11519</link><description>The Optimole – Optimize Images | Convert WebP &amp; AVIF | CDN &amp; Lazy Load | Image Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 via the /wp-json/optml/v1/move_image REST API endpoint due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to offload media that doesn't belong to them.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11691 | PPOM – Product Addons &amp;amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 33.0.15 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11691</link><description>The PPOM – Product Addons &amp; Custom Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the PPOM_Meta::get_fields_by_id() function in all versions up to, and including, 33.0.15 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This is only exploitable when the Enable Legacy Price Calculations setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11703 | WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) &amp;lt;= 9.0.48 - Unauthenticated Cache Poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11703</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cache Poisoning in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.48. This is due to the plugin not serving cached data from server-side responses and instead relying on user-input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to poison the cache location for location search results.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11741 | WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Private Product Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11741</link><description>The WPC Smart Quick View for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5 via the 'woosq_quickview' AJAX endpoint due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft products that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9562 | Redirection for Contact Form 7 &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via qs_date Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9562</link><description>The Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's qs_date shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11738 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.29 - Unauthenticated Limited File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11738</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to limited file reading in all versions up to, and including, 3.29 via the mla-stream-image.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary ai/eps/pdf/ps files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11742 | WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11742</link><description>The WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wishlist_quickview' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view other user's wishlist data and information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11857 | XX2WP Integration Tools &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11857</link><description>The XX2WP Integration Tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mxp_fb2wp_display_embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9. This is due to the plugin not properly sanitizing user input and output of the 'post_id' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11937 | Stored XSS through a system message in SecurePoll</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11937</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - SecurePoll Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62666 | DoS vector through the cirrusbuilddoc query API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62666</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension allows HTTP DoS.This issue affects Mediawiki - CirrusSearch Extension: from master before 1.43.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62667 | Stored XSS through article extracts in GrowthExperiments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62667</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:56:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62668 | Insufficient permission checks in action=growthsetmentor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62668</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - GrowthExperiments Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62669 | UserInfoCard: activeLocalBlocksAllWikis does not do permissions checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62669</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension allows Resource Leak Exposure.This issue affects Mediawiki - CentralAuth Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11361 | Essential Blocks &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11361</link><description>The Gutenberg Essential Blocks – Page Builder for Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.7.1 via the eb_save_ai_generated_image function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62670 | Stored XSS through a system message in FlexDiagrams</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62670</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - FlexDiagrams Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62671 | Stored XSS through wikitext in Cargo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62671</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Cargo Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Cargo Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62662 | Stored XSS through system messages in AdvancedSearch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - AdvancedSearch Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62663 | Stored XSS through a system message in UploadWizard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62663</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - UploadWizard Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62664 | Stored XSS through a system message in ImageRating</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - ImageRating Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62665 | Stored XSS through system messages in Skin:BlueSky</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Skin:BlueSky: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 04:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20206 | Appointments &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20206</link><description>The Appointments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `wpmudev_appointments` cookie. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20207 | Flickr Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20207</link><description>The Flickr Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the `pager ` parameter. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. Attackers were actively exploiting this vulnerability with the WP_Theme() class to create backdoors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20208 | RegistrationMagic - Custom Registration Forms &amp;lt;= 3.7.9.2 - PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20208</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to 3.7.9.3 (exclusive) via deserialization of untrusted input from the is_expired_by_date() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to fetch a remote file and install it on the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36853 | 10WebMapBuilder &amp;lt;= 1.0.63 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36853</link><description>The 10WebMapBuilder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Plugin Settings Change in versions up to, and including, 1.0.63 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and a lack of capability checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36854 | Async JavaScript &amp;lt;= 2.19.07.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36854</link><description>The Async JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including,  2.19.07.14. This is due to missing authorization checks on the aj_steps AJAX aciton along with a lack on sanitization on the settings saved via the function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber level permissions and above to inject malicious web scripts into a page that execute whenever a user accesses that page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11378 | ShortPixel Image Optimizer &amp;lt;= 6.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Settings Import/Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11378</link><description>The ShortPixel Image Optimizer – Optimize Images, Convert WebP &amp; AVIF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'shortpixel_ajaxRequest' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to export and import site options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 03:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62655 | SQL injection in Cargo via Special:CargoExport</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki Cargo extension allows SQL Injection.This issue affects MediaWiki Cargo extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62654 | Stored XSS through system messages in QuizGame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62654</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki QuizGame extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki QuizGame extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62653 | Stored XSS through system messages in PollNY</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki PollNY extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki PollNY extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62652 | Stored XSS in WebAuthn key name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki WebAuthn extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki WebAuthn extension: 1.39, 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:35:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62650 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for use of the diagnost...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62650</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for use of the diagnostic screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62651 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 does not implement access control for the bathroom rating in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62651</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 does not implement access control for the bathroom rating interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11914 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceFileReport.do download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11914</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected by this issue is the function Download of the file /DeviceFileReport.do?Action=Download. Performing manipulation of the argument FilePath results in path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62515 | Remote Code Execution by Pickle Deserialization via FlightServer in pyquokka</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62515</link><description>pyquokka is a framework for making data lakes work for time series. In versions 0.3.1 and prior, the FlightServer class directly uses pickle.loads() to deserialize action bodies received from Flight clients without any sanitization or validation in the do_action() method. The vulnerable code is located in pyquokka/flight.py at line 283 where arbitrary data from Flight clients is directly passed to pickle.loads(). When FlightServer is configured to listen on 0.0.0.0, this allows attackers across the entire network to perform arbitrary remote code execution by sending malicious pickled payloads through the set_configs action. Additional vulnerability points exist in the cache_garbage_collect, do_put, and do_get functions where pickle.loads is used to deserialize untrusted remote data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62647 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 provides the functionality of returning a JWT that can be us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62647</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 provides the functionality of returning a JWT that can be used to call an API to return a signed AWS upload URL, for any store's path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62648 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to adjust Drive Thru speaker audio v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62648</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to adjust Drive Thru speaker audio volume.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62649 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for submission of equip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62649</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 relies on client-side authentication for submission of equipment orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62508 | Citizen vulnerable to stored XSS in sticky header button messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62508</link><description>Citizen is a MediaWiki skin that makes extensions part of the cohesive experience. Citizen from 3.3.0 to 3.9.0 are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting in the sticky header button message handling. In stickyHeader.js the copyButtonAttributes function assigns innerHTML from a source element’s textContent when copying button labels. This causes escaped HTML in system message content (such as citizen-share, citizen-view-history, citizen-view-edit, and nstab-talk) to be interpreted as HTML in the sticky header, allowing injection of arbitrary script by a user with the ability to edit interface messages. The vulnerability allows a user with the editinterface right but without the editsitejs right (by default the sysop group has editinterface but may not have editsitejs) to execute arbitrary JavaScript in other users’ sessions, enabling unauthorized access to sensitive data or actions. The issue is fixed in 3.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62642 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has an "Anyone Can Join This Party" signup API that does not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62642</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has an "Anyone Can Join This Party" signup API that does not verify user account creation, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to create a user account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62643 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 transmits passwords of user accounts in cleartext e-mail mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62643</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 transmits passwords of user accounts in cleartext e-mail messages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62644 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has a Global Store Directory that shares personal informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62644</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 has a Global Store Directory that shares personal information among authenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62645 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain a token wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62645</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain a token with administrative privileges for the entire platform via the createToken GraphQL mutation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62646 | The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to review the stored audio of conver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62646</link><description>The Restaurant Brands International (RBI) assistant platform through 2025-09-06 allows remote attackers to review the stored audio of conversations between associates and Drive Thru customers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11912 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceState.do Query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11912</link><description>A flaw has been found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected is the function Query of the file /DeviceState.do?Action=Query. This manipulation of the argument orderField causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11913 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus Service.do download path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11913</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Download of the file /Service.do?Action=Download. Such manipulation of the argument Path leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11925 | Incorrect Content-Type Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11925</link><description>Incorrect Content-Type header in one of the APIs (`text/html` instead of `application/json`) replies may potentially allow injection of HTML/JavaScript into reply.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62511 | yt-grabber-tui local arbitrary file overwrite via TOCTOU race in config file creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62511</link><description>yt-grabber-tui is a C++ terminal user interface application for downloading YouTube content. yt-grabber-tui version 1.0 contains a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition (CWE-367) in the creation of the default configuration file config.json. In version 1.0, load_json_settings in Settings.hpp checks for the existence of config.json using boost::filesystem::exists and, if the file is missing, calls create_json_settings which writes the JSON configuration with boost::property_tree::write_json. A local attacker with write access to the application’s configuration directory (~/.config/yt-grabber-tui on Linux or the current working directory on Windows) can create a symbolic link between the existence check and the subsequent write so that the write operation follows the symlink and overwrites an attacker-chosen file accessible to the running process. This enables arbitrary file overwrite within the privileges of the application process, which can corrupt files and cause loss of application or user data. If the application is executed with elevated privileges, this could extend to system file corruption. The issue is fixed in version 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11910 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus MemoryState.do query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11910</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. This affects the function Query of the file /MemoryState.do?Action=Query. The manipulation of the argument orderField leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11911 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus DeviceFault.do Query sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11911</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. This impacts the function Query of the file /DeviceFault.do?Action=Query. The manipulation of the argument sortField results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31573 | XMLUnit for Java before 2.10.0, in the default configuration, might allow code execution via an untrusted stylesheet (used for an XSLT trans...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31573</link><description>XMLUnit for Java before 2.10.0, in the default configuration, might allow code execution via an untrusted stylesheet (used for an XSLT transformation), because XSLT extension functions are enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11908 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus FileDir.do uploadFile unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11908</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. The affected element is the function uploadFile of the file /FileDir.do?Action=Upload. Performing manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11909 | Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus RepairRecord.do queryLast sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11909</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Shenzhen Ruiming Technology Streamax Crocus 1.3.40. The impacted element is the function queryLast of the file /RepairRecord.do?Action=QueryLast. Executing manipulation of the argument orderField can lead to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34281 | ThingsBoard &amp;lt; v4.2.1 SVG Image Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34281</link><description>ThingsBoard versions &lt; 4.2.1 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the dashboard's Image Upload Gallery feature. An attacker can upload an SVG file containing malicious JavaScript, which may be executed when the file is rendered in the UI. This issue results from insufficient sanitization and improper content-type validation of uploaded SVG files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34282 | ThingsBoard &amp;lt; v4.2.1 SVG Image SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34282</link><description>ThingsBoard versions &lt; 4.2.1 contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the dashboard's Image Upload Gallery feature. An attacker can upload a malicious SVG file that references a remote URL. If the server processes the SVG file in a way that parses external references, it may initiate unintended outbound requests. This can be used to access internal services or resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56221 | A lack of rate limiting in the login mechanism of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56221</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the login mechanism of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56218 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56218</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PDF file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56316 | A SQL injection vulnerability in the content_title parameter of the /cms/content/list endpoint in MCMS 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56316</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the content_title parameter of the /cms/content/list endpoint in MCMS 5.5.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries via unsanitized input in the FreeMarker template rendering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56320 | Enterprise Contract Management Portal v.22.4.0 is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in its chat box component. This allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56320</link><description>Enterprise Contract Management Portal v.22.4.0 is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in its chat box component. This allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62505 | SSRF in lobehub/lobe-chat with native web fetch module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62505</link><description>LobeChat is an open source chat application platform. The web-crawler package in LobeChat version 1.136.1 allows server-side request forgery (SSRF) in the tools.search.crawlPages tRPC endpoint. A client can supply an arbitrary urls array together with impls containing the value naive. The service passes the user URLs to Crawler.crawl and the naive implementation performs a server-side fetch of each supplied URL without validating or restricting internal network addresses (such as localhost, 127.0.0.1, private IP ranges, or cloud instance metadata endpoints). This allows an attacker with a valid user token (or in development mode using a bypass header) to make the server disclose responses from internal HTTP services, potentially exposing internal API data or cloud metadata credentials. Version 1.136.2 fixes the issue. Update to version 1.136.2. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60514 | Tillywork v0.1.3 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in app/common/helpers/query.builder.helper.ts.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60514</link><description>Tillywork v0.1.3 and below is vulnerable to SQL Injection in app/common/helpers/query.builder.helper.ts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57164 | Flowise through v3.0.4 is vulnerable to remote code execution via unsanitized evaluation of user input in the "Supabase RPC Filter" field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57164</link><description>Flowise through v3.0.4 is vulnerable to remote code execution via unsanitized evaluation of user input in the "Supabase RPC Filter" field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62430 | ClipBucket v5 stored XSS via video/photo fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62430</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. ClipBucket v5 through build 5.5.2 #145 allows stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in multiple video and photo metadata fields. For videos the Tags field and the Genre, Actors, Producer, Executive Producer, and Director fields in Movieinfos accept user supplied values without adequate sanitization. For photos the Photo Title and Photo Tags fields accept user supplied values without adequate sanitization. A regular user who can edit a video or photo can inject script (for example by supplying a value such as a closing delimiter followed by a script element). The injected script executes when any user, including an unauthenticated visitor or an administrator, views the affected video or photo page. Although cookies are set with the HttpOnly attribute and cannot be read directly, the injected script can issue fetch requests to endpoints such as admin_area pages and exfiltrate their contents or trigger unintended actions. Version 5.5.2 build #146 and later contain a fix. Update to build 5.5.2 #146 or later. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62424 | ClipBucket path traversal vulnerability in template editor allows arbitrary file read and write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62424</link><description>ClipBucket is a web-based video-sharing platform. In ClipBucket version 5.5.2 - #146 and earlier, the /admin_area/template_editor.php endpoint is vulnerable to path traversal. The validation of the file-loading path is inadequate, allowing authenticated administrators to read and write arbitrary files outside the intended template directory by inserting path traversal sequences into the folder parameter. An attacker with administrator privileges can exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive files such as /etc/passwd and modify writable files on the system, potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure and compromise of the application or server. This issue is fixed in version 5.5.2 - #147.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62419 | DataEase vulnerable to JDBC URL injection in DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62419</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC URL injection vulnerability exists in the DB2 and MongoDB data source configuration handlers. In the DB2 data source handler, when the extraParams field is empty, the HOSTNAME, PORT, and DATABASE values are directly concatenated into the JDBC URL without filtering illegal parameters. This allows an attacker to inject a malicious JDBC string into the HOSTNAME field to bypass previously patched vulnerabilities CVE-2025-57773 and CVE-2025-58045. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62420 | DataEase vulnerable to remote code execution via H2 JDBC driver bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62420</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a JDBC driver bypass vulnerability exists in the H2 database connection handler. The getJdbc function in H2.java checks if the jdbcUrl starts with jdbc:h2 but returns a separate jdbc field as the actual connection URL. An attacker can provide a jdbcUrl that starts with jdbc:h2 while supplying a different jdbc field with an arbitrary JDBC driver and connection string. This allows an authenticated attacker to trigger arbitrary JDBC connections with malicious drivers, potentially leading to remote code execution. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62421 | DataEase vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting via file upload bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62421</link><description>DataEase is a data visualization and analytics platform. In DataEase versions through 2.10.13, a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists due to improper file upload validation and authentication bypass. The StaticResourceApi interface defines a route upload/{fileId} that uses a URL path parameter where both the filename and extension of uploaded files are controllable by users. During permission validation, the TokenFilter invokes the WhitelistUtils#match method to determine if the URL path is in the allowlist. If the requestURI ends with .js or similar extensions, it is directly deemed safe and bypasses permission checks. This allows an attacker to access "upload/1.js" while specifying arbitrary file extensions, enabling the upload of HTML files containing malicious JavaScript. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62422 | DataEase SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62422</link><description>DataEase is an open source data visualization and analytics platform. In versions 2.10.13 and earlier, the /de2api/datasetData/tableField interface is vulnerable to SQL injection. An attacker can construct a malicious tableName parameter to execute arbitrary SQL commands. This issue is fixed in version 2.10.14. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62171 | ImageMagick vulnerable to denial of service via integer overflow in BMP decoder on 32-bit systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62171</link><description>ImageMagick is an open source software suite for displaying, converting, and editing raster image files. In ImageMagick versions prior to 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32, an integer overflow vulnerability exists in the BMP decoder on 32-bit systems. The vulnerability occurs in coders/bmp.c when calculating the extent value by multiplying image columns by bits per pixel. On 32-bit systems with size_t of 4 bytes, a malicious BMP file with specific dimensions can cause this multiplication to overflow and wrap to zero. The overflow check added to address CVE-2025-57803 is placed after the overflow occurs, making it ineffective. A specially crafted 58-byte BMP file with width set to 536,870,912 and 32 bits per pixel can trigger this overflow, causing the bytes_per_line calculation to become zero. This vulnerability only affects 32-bit builds of ImageMagick where default resource limits for width, height, and area have been manually increased beyond their defaults. 64-bit systems with size_t of 8 bytes are not vulnerable, and systems using default ImageMagick resource limits are not vulnerable. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 7.1.2-7 and 6.9.13-32.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62168 | Squid vulnerable to information disclosure via authentication credential leakage in error handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62168</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. In Squid versions prior to 7.2, a failure to redact HTTP authentication credentials in error handling allows information disclosure. The vulnerability allows a script to bypass browser security protections and learn the credentials a trusted client uses to authenticate. This potentially allows a remote client to identify security tokens or credentials used internally by a web application using Squid for backend load balancing. These attacks do not require Squid to be configured with HTTP authentication. The vulnerability is fixed in version 7.2. As a workaround, disable debug information in administrator mailto links generated by Squid by configuring squid.conf with email_err_data off.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59043 | OpenBao vulnerable to denial of service via malicious JSON request processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59043</link><description>OpenBao is an open source identity-based secrets management system. In OpenBao versions prior to 2.4.1, JSON objects after decoding may use significantly more memory than their serialized version. It is possible to craft a JSON payload to maximize the factor between serialized memory usage and deserialized memory usage, similar to a zip bomb, with factors reaching approximately 35. This can be used to circumvent the max_request_size configuration parameter which is intended to protect against denial of service attacks. The request body is parsed into a map very early in the request handling chain before authentication, which means an unauthenticated attacker can send a specifically crafted JSON object and cause an out-of-memory crash. Additionally, for requests with large numbers of strings, the audit subsystem can consume large quantities of CPU. The vulnerability is fixed in version 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8414 | Zigbee Green Power Host Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8414</link><description>Due to improper input validation, a buffer overflow vulnerability is present in 

Zigbee EZSP Host Applications. If the buffer overflows, stack corruption is possible. In certain

conditions, this could lead to arbitrary code execution. Access to a network key is required to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58747 | Dify MCP OAuth Flow Vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58747</link><description>Dify is an LLM application development platform. In Dify versions through 1.9.1, the MCP OAuth component is vulnerable to cross-site scripting when a victim connects to an attacker-controlled remote MCP server. The vulnerability exists in the OAuth flow implementation where the authorization_url provided by a remote MCP server is directly passed to window.open without validation or sanitization. An attacker can craft a malicious MCP server that returns a JavaScript URI (such as javascript:alert(1)) in the authorization_url field, which is then executed when the victim attempts to connect to the MCP server. This allows the attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the Dify application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11905 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS gather.js getArticle code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11905</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This vulnerability affects the function getArticle of the file app\modules\cms\controller\gather.js. The manipulation results in code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62356 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62356</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Qodo Qodo Gen IDE enables a threat actor to read arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26625 | Git LFS may write to arbitrary files via crafted symlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26625</link><description>Git LFS is a Git extension for versioning large files. In Git LFS versions 0.5.2 through 3.7.0, when populating a Git repository's working tree with the contents of Git LFS objects, certain Git LFS commands may write to files visible outside the current Git working tree if symbolic or hard links exist which collide with the paths of files tracked by Git LFS. The git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands do not check for symbolic links before writing to files in the working tree, allowing an attacker to craft a repository containing symbolic or hard links that cause Git LFS to write to arbitrary file system locations accessible to the user running these commands. As well, when the git lfs checkout and git lfs pull commands are run in a bare repository, they could write to files visible outside the repository. The vulnerability is fixed in version 3.7.1. As a workaround, support for symlinks in Git may be disabled by setting the core.symlinks configuration option to false, after which further clones and fetches will not create symbolic links. However, any symbolic or hard links in existing repositories will still provide the opportunity for Git LFS to write to their targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49655 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49655</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions of the Keras framework running versions 3.11.0 up to but not including 3.11.3, enabling a maliciously uploaded Keras file containing a TorchModuleWrapper class to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when loaded despite safe mode being enabled. The vulnerability can be triggered through both local and remote files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57567 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the def...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57567</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the PluXml CMS theme editor, specifically in the minify.php file located under the default theme directory (/themes/defaut/css/minify.php). An authenticated administrator user can overwrite this file with arbitrary PHP code via the admin panel, enabling execution of system commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62353 | A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and out...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62353</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in all versions of the Windsurf IDE enables a threat actor to read and write arbitrary local files in and outside of current projects on an end user’s system. The vulnerability can be reached directly and through indirect prompt injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60279 | A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60279</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Illia Cloud illia-Builder before v4.8.5 allows authenticated users to send arbitrary requests to internal services via the API. An attacker can leverage this to enumerate open ports based on response discrepancies and interact with internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11904 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS hasUse sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11904</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. This affects the function hasUse of the file /cms/model/hasUse. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55085 | Web http client: Unchecked Server-Side Malicious Packet Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55085</link><description>In NextX Duo before 6.4.4, in the HTTP client module, the network support code for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, the parsing of HTTP header fields was missing bounds verification. A crafted server response could cause undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60361 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60361</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function bochs_open.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48087 | WordPress Memberlite Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48087</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jason C. Memberlite Shortcodes memberlite-shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Memberlite Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11902 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS findField sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11902</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this vulnerability is the function findField of the file /cms/article/findField. Performing manipulation of the argument cid results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11903 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11903</link><description>A flaw has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.3.2. Affected by this issue is the function update of the file /cms/article/update. Executing manipulation of the argument cid can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60359 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60359</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r_bin_object_new.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60360 | radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60360</link><description>radare2 v5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function r2r_subprocess_init.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48044 | Authorization bypass when bypass policy condition evaluates to true</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48044</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in ash-project ash allows Authentication Bypass. This vulnerability is associated with program files lib/ash/policy/policy.ex and program routines 'Elixir.Ash.Policy.Policy':expression/2.

This issue affects ash: from pkg:hex/ash@3.6.3 before pkg:hex/ash@3.7.1, from 3.6.3 before 3.7.1, from 79749c2685ea031ebb2de8cf60cc5edced6a8dd0 before 8b83efa225f657bfc3656ad8ee8485f9b2de923d.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28815 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28815</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product contain insufficient parameter validation, resulting in a command injection vulnerability. Attackers may exploit this to gain platform privileges and execute arbitrary commands on the system.iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28814 | Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28814</link><description>Some versions of Hikvision's iSecure Center Product have an improper file upload control vulnerability. Due to the improper verification of file to be uploaded, attackers may upload malicious files to the server. iSecure Center is software released for China's domestic market only, with no overseas release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11895 | Binary MLM Plan &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11895</link><description>The Binary MLM Plan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to insecure direct object reference in versions up to, and including, 3.0. This is due to the bmp_user_payout_detail_of_current_user() function selecting payout records solely by id without verifying ownership. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with the bmp_user role (often subscribers) to view other members' payout summaries via direct requests to the /bmp-account-detail/ endpoint with a crafted payout-id parameter granted they can access the shortcode output.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 09:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55087 | In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55087</link><description>In NextX Duo's snmp addon versions before 6.4.4, a part of the Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, an attacker could cause an out-of-bound read by a crafted SNMPv3 security parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 06:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55097 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55097</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_streaming_sampling_get() when parsing a descriptor of an USB streaming device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55098 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55098</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_device_type_get()
      when parsing a descriptor of an USB audio device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55099 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55099</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio_alternate_setting_locate() when parsing a descriptor with attacker-controlled frequency fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55100 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55100</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_audio10_sam_parse_func() when parsing a list of sampling frequencies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55094 | Potential out-of-bounds read in _nx_icmpv6_validate_options()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55094</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in  _nx_icmpv6_validate_options() when handling a packet with ICMP6 options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55096 | Inadequate bounds check and potential underflow in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55096</link><description>In USBX before 6.4.3, the USB support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _ux_host_class_hid_report_descriptor_get()
 when parsing a descriptor of an USB HID device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55092 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_ipv4_option_process()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55092</link><description>In Eclipse Foundation NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_option_process() when processing an IPv4 packet with the timestamp option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55093 | Out of bound read and write in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55093</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() when handling unicast DHCP messages that could cause corruption of 4 bytes of memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11849 | Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11849</link><description>Versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth from 0.3.25 and before 1.11.0; versions of the package mammoth before 1.11.0; versions of the package org.zwobble.mammoth:mammoth before 1.11.0 are vulnerable to Directory Traversal due to the lack of path or file type validation when processing a docx file containing an image with an external link (r:link attribute instead of embedded r:embed). The library resolves the URI to a file path and after reading, the content is encoded as base64 and included in the HTML output as a data URI. An attacker can read arbitrary files on the system where the conversion is performed or cause an excessive resources consumption by crafting a docx file that links to special device files such as /dev/random or /dev/zero.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11898 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11898</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Arbitrary File Reading vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit Relative Path Traversal to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11899 | Flowring Technology｜Agentflow - Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11899</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Use of Hard-coded Cryptographic Key vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit the fixed key to generate verification information, thereby logging into the system as any user. Attacker must first obtain an user ID in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11900 | HGiga｜iSherlock - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11900</link><description>The iSherlock developed by HGiga has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary OS commands and execute them on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6949 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6949</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A critical authorization flaw in the API allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to create a new administrator account, including accounts with usernames identical to existing users. In certain scenarios, this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain full administrative control over the affected device, leading to potential account impersonation. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6950 | An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6950</link><description>An Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. The system employs a hard-coded secret key to sign JSON Web Tokens (JWT) used for authentication. This insecure implementation allows an unauthenticated attacker to forge valid tokens, thereby bypassing authentication controls and impersonating any user. Exploitation of this vulnerability can result in complete system compromise, enabling unauthorized access, data theft, and full administrative control over the affected device. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6893 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in brok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6893</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in broken access control has been identified in the /api/v1/setting/data endpoint of the affected device. This flaw allows a low-privileged authenticated user to call the API without the required permissions, thereby gaining the ability to access or modify system configuration data. Successful exploitation may lead to privilege escalation, allowing the attacker to access or modify sensitive system settings. While the overall impact is high, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6894 | An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6894</link><description>An Execution with Unnecessary Privileges vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authorization logic of the affected device allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to execute the administrative `ping` function, which is restricted to higher-privileged roles. This vulnerability enables the user to perform internal network reconnaissance, potentially discovering internal hosts or services that would otherwise be inaccessible. Repeated exploitation could lead to minor resource consumption. While the overall impact is limited, it may result in some loss of confidentiality and availability on the affected device. There is no impact on the integrity of the device, and the vulnerability does not affect any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6892 | An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6892</link><description>An Incorrect Authorization vulnerability has been identified in Moxa’s network security appliances and routers. A flaw in the API authentication mechanism allows unauthorized access to protected API endpoints, including those intended for administrative functions. This vulnerability can be exploited after a legitimate user has logged in, as the system fails to properly validate session context or privilege boundaries. An attacker may leverage this flaw to perform unauthorized privileged operations. While successful exploitation can severely impact the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the affected device itself, there is no loss of confidentiality or integrity within any subsequent systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 02:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11896 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF CMap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11896</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in a CMap, via the "UseCMap" entry, leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62504 | Envoy Lua filter use-after-free when oversized rewritten response body causes crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62504</link><description>Envoy is an open source edge and service proxy. Envoy versions earlier than 1.36.2, 1.35.6, 1.34.10, and 1.33.12 contain a use-after-free vulnerability in the Lua filter. When a Lua script executing in the response phase rewrites a response body so that its size exceeds the configured per_connection_buffer_limit_bytes (default 1MB), Envoy generates a local reply whose headers override the original response headers, leaving dangling references and causing a crash. This results in denial of service. Updating to versions 1.36.2, 1.35.6, 1.34.10, or 1.33.12 fixes the issue. Increasing per_connection_buffer_limit_bytes (and for HTTP/2 the initial_stream_window_size) or increasing per_request_buffer_limit_bytes / request_body_buffer_limit can reduce the likelihood of triggering the condition but does not correct the underlying memory safety flaw.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62506 | MinIO vulnerable to privilege escalation via session policy bypass in service accounts and STS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62506</link><description>MinIO is a high-performance object storage system. In all versions prior to RELEASE.2025-10-15T17-29-55Z, a privilege escalation vulnerability allows service accounts and STS (Security Token Service) accounts with restricted session policies to bypass their inline policy restrictions when performing operations on their own account, specifically when creating new service accounts for the same user. The vulnerability exists in the IAM policy validation logic where the code incorrectly relied on the DenyOnly argument when validating session policies for restricted accounts. When a session policy is present, the system should validate that the action is allowed by the session policy, not just that it is not denied. An attacker with valid credentials for a restricted service or STS account can create a new service account for itself without policy restrictions, resulting in a new service account with full parent privileges instead of being restricted by the inline policy. This allows the attacker to access buckets and objects beyond their intended restrictions and modify, delete, or create objects outside their authorized scope. The vulnerability is fixed in version RELEASE.2025-10-15T17-29-55Z.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11864 | NucleoidAI Nucleoid Outbound Request cluster.ts extension.apply server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11864</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in NucleoidAI Nucleoid up to 0.7.10. The impacted element is the function extension.apply of the file /src/cluster.ts of the component Outbound Request Handler. Such manipulation of the argument https/ip/port/path/headers leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:21:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42192 | HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a credential leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42192</link><description>HCL Traveler for Microsoft Outlook (HTMO) is susceptible to a credential leakage which could allow an attacker to access other computers or applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60358 | radare2 v.5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function _load_relocations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60358</link><description>radare2 v.5.9.8 and before contains a memory leak in the function _load_relocations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61554 | A divide-by-zero in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61554</link><description>A divide-by-zero in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (host hypervisor crash) via a crafted PCI configuration space access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11492 | HTTP Configuration and Encryption in Transit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11492</link><description>In the ConnectWise Automate Agent, communications could be configured to use HTTP instead of HTTPS. In such cases, an on-path threat actor with a man-in-the-middle network position could intercept, modify, or replay agent-server traffic. Additionally, the encryption method used to obfuscate some communications over the HTTP channel is updated in the Automate 2025.9 patch to enforce HTTPS for all agent communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11493 | Self-Update Verification Mechanism Process in ConnectWise Automate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11493</link><description>The ConnectWise Automate Agent does not fully verify the authenticity of files downloaded from the server, such as updates, dependencies, and integrations. This creates a risk where an on-path attacker could perform a man-in-the-middle attack and substitute malicious files for legitimate ones by impersonating a legitimate server. This risk is mitigated when HTTPS is enforced and is related to CVE-2025-11492.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11852 | Apeman ID71 ONVIF Service device_service missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11852</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apeman ID71 218.53.203.117. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /onvif/device_service of the component ONVIF Service. Performing manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11853 | Sismics Teedy API Endpoint file access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11853</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Sismics Teedy up to 1.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /api/file of the component API Endpoint. Executing manipulation can lead to improper access controls. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61553 | An out-of-bounds write in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61553</link><description>An out-of-bounds write in VirtIO network device emulation in BitVisor from commit 108df6 (2020-05-20) to commit 480907 (2025-07-06) allows local attackers to cause a denial of service (host hypervisor crash) via a crafted PCI configuration space access. Given it's a heap overflow in a privileged hypervisor context, exploitation may enable arbitrary code execution or guest-to-host privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34253 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34253</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to improper sanitization of the 'Network' field when editing the configuration, creating a profile, and adding a network. An authenticated attacker can inject arbitrary JavaScript to be executed in the context of other users viewing the profile entry. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34254 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Login Account Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34254</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain an observable response discrepancy vulnerability. The application's 'Login' endpoint returns distinct JSON responses depending on whether the supplied username is associated with an existing account. Because the responses differ in the `error.message`string value, an unauthenticated remote attacker can enumerate valid usernames/accounts on the server. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34255 | D-Link Nuclias Connect &amp;lt;= v1.3.1.4 Forgot Password Account Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34255</link><description>D-Link Nuclias Connect firmware versions &lt;= 1.3.1.4 contain an observable response discrepancy vulnerability. The application's 'Forgot Password' endpoint returns distinct JSON responses depending on whether the supplied email address is associated with an existing account. Because the responses differ in the `data.exist` boolean value, an unauthenticated remote attacker can enumerate valid email addresses/accounts on the server. NOTE: D-Link states that a fix is under development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62428 | Drawing-Captcha APP Host Header Injection in `/register` and `/confirm-email` Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62428</link><description>Drawing-Captcha APP provides interactive, engaging verification for Web-Based Applications. The vulnerability is a Host Header Injection in the /register and /confirm-email endpoints. It allows an attacker to manipulate the Host header in HTTP requests to generate malicious email confirmation links. These links can redirect users to attacker-controlled domains. This vulnerability affects all users relying on email confirmation for account registration or verification. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.5-alpha-patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62425 | Matrix Authentication Service account password can be changed using an authenticated session without supplying the current password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62425</link><description>MAS (Matrix Authentication Service) is a user management and authentication service for Matrix homeservers, written and maintained by Element. A logic flaw in matrix-authentication-service 0.20.0 through 1.4.0 allows an attacker with access to an authenticated MAS session to perform sensitive operations without entering the current password. These include changing the current password, adding or removing an e-mail address and deactivating the account. The vulnerability only affects instances which have the local password database feature enabled (passwords section in the config). Patched in matrix-authentication-service 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62427 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in Angular SSR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62427</link><description>The Angular CLI is a command-line interface tool for Angular applications. The vulnerability is a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) flaw within the URL resolution mechanism of Angular's Server-Side Rendering package (@angular/ssr) before 19.2.18, 20.3.6, and 21.0.0-next.8. The function createRequestUrl uses the native URL constructor. When an incoming request path (e.g., originalUrl or url) begins with a double forward slash (//) or backslash (\\), the URL constructor treats it as a schema-relative URL. This behavior overrides the security-intended base URL (protocol, host, and port) supplied as the second argument, instead resolving the URL against the scheme of the base URL but adopting the attacker-controlled hostname. This allows an attacker to specify an external domain in the URL path, tricking the Angular SSR environment into setting the page's virtual location (accessible via DOCUMENT or PlatformLocation tokens) to this attacker-controlled domain. Any subsequent relative HTTP requests made during the SSR process (e.g., using HttpClient.get('assets/data.json')) will be incorrectly resolved against the attacker's domain, forcing the server to communicate with an arbitrary external endpoint. This vulnerability is fixed in 19.2.18, 20.3.6, and 21.0.0-next.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61514 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SageMath, Inc CoCalc before commit 0d2ff58 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61514</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in SageMath, Inc CoCalc before commit 0d2ff58 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62414 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Create New Customer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62414</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the “Create New Customer” feature (in the admin panel) is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). An attacker with access to the admin create-customer form can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into certain input fields. These payloads may later execute in the context of an admin’s browser or another user viewing the customer data, enabling session theft or admin-level actions. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62415 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in TinyMCE Image Upload (HTML)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62415</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the TinyMCE image upload functionality allows an attacker with sufficient privileges (e.g. admin) to upload a crafted HTML file containing embedded JavaScript. When viewed, the malicious code executes in the context of the admin/user’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62416 | bagisto - Server Side Template Injection (SSTI) in Product Description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62416</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. Bagisto v2.3.7 is vulnerable to Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) due to unsanitized user input being processed by the server-side templating engine when rendering product descriptions. This allows an attacker with product creation privileges to inject arbitrary template expressions that are evaluated by the backend — potentially leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the server. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62417 | bagisto - CSV Formula Injection in Create New Product</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62417</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. When product data that begins with a spreadsheet formula character (for example =, +, -, or @) is accepted and later exported or saved into a CSV and opened in spreadsheet software, the spreadsheet will interpret that cell as a formula. This allows an attacker to supply a CSV field (e.g., product name) that contains a formula which may be evaluated by a victim’s spreadsheet application — potentially leading to data exfiltration and remote command execution (via older Excel exploits / OLE/cmd constructs or Excel macros). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62418 | bagisto - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in TinyMCE Image Upload (SVG)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62418</link><description>Bagisto is an open source laravel eCommerce platform. In Bagisto v2.3.7, the TinyMCE image upload functionality allows an attacker with sufficient privileges (e.g. admin) to upload a crafted SVG file containing embedded JavaScript. When viewed, the malicious code executes in the context of the admin/user’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62423 | ClipBucket V5 Blind SQL injection in the Admin Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62423</link><description>ClipBucket V5 provides open source video hosting with PHP. In version5.5.2 - #140 and earlier, a Blind SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Admin Area’s “/admin_area/login_as_user.php” file. Exploiting this vulnerability requires access privileges to the Admin Area.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60855 | Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W performs insufficient validation of firmware update signatures. This allows attackers to load ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60855</link><description>Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W performs insufficient validation of firmware update signatures. This allows attackers to load malicious firmware images, resulting in arbitrary code execution with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60639 | Hardcoded credentials in gsigel14 ATLAS-EPIC commit f29312c (2025-05-26).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60639</link><description>Hardcoded credentials in gsigel14 ATLAS-EPIC commit f29312c (2025-05-26).</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62413 | MQTTX vulnerable to cross-site scripting via improper message payload rendering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62413</link><description>MQTTX is an MQTT 5.0 desktop client and MQTT testing tool. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was introduced in MQTTX v1.12.0 due to improper handling of MQTT message payload rendering. Malicious payloads containing HTML or JavaScript could be rendered directly in the MQTTX message viewer. If exploited, this could allow attackers to execute arbitrary scripts in the context of the application UI — for example, attempting to access MQTT connection credentials or trigger unintended actions through script injection. This vulnerability is especially relevant when MQTTX is used with brokers in untrusted or multi-tenant environments, where message content cannot be fully controlled. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.12.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34512 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34512</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in index.php that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34513 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34513</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an OS command injection vulnerability in mbus_build_from_csv.php that allows an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34514 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Authenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34514</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain authenticated OS command injection vulnerabilities in multiple web-accessible PHP scripts that call exec() and allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34515 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Root Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34515</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an execution with unnecessary privileges vulnerability in sync_project.sh that allows an attacker to escalate privileges to root. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34516 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34516</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a use of default credentials vulnerability that allows an unauthenticated attacker to obtain remote access. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34517 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Absolute Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34517</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an absolute path traversal vulnerability in get_file_content.php that allows an attacker to read arbitrary files. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34518 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Relative Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34518</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain a relative path traversal vulnerability in get_file_content.php that allows an attacker to read arbitrary files. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34519 | Ilevia EVE X1 Server 4.7.18.0.eden Insecure Hashing Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34519</link><description>Ilevia EVE X1 Server firmware versions ≤ 4.7.18.0.eden contain an insecure hashing algorithm vulnerability. The product stores passwords using the MD5 hash function without applying a per‑password salt. Because MD5 is a fast, unsalted hash, an attacker who obtains the password database can efficiently perform offline dictionary, rainbow‑table, or brute‑force attacks to recover the original passwords. Ilevia has declined to service this vulnerability, and recommends that customers not expose port 8080 to the internet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62412 | LibreNMS alert-rules Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62412</link><description>LibreNMS  is a community-based GPL-licensed network monitoring system. The alert rule name in the Alerts &gt; Alert Rules page is not properly sanitized, and can be used to inject HTML code. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60641 | The file mexcel.php in the Vfront 0.99.52 codebase contains a vulnerable call to unserialize(base64_decode($_POST['mexcel'])), where $_POST[...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60641</link><description>The file mexcel.php in the Vfront 0.99.52 codebase contains a vulnerable call to unserialize(base64_decode($_POST['mexcel'])), where $_POST['mexcel'] is user-controlled input. This input is decoded from base64 and deserialized without validation or use of the allowed_classes option, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary PHP objects. This can lead to malicious behavior, such as Remote Code Execution (RCE), SQL Injection, Path Traversal, or Denial of Service, depending on the availability of exploitable classes in the Vfront codebase or its dependencies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62409 | Envoy allows large requests and responses to cause TCP connection pool crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62409</link><description>Envoy is a cloud-native, open source edge and service proxy. Prior to 1.36.1, 1.35.5, 1.34.9, and 1.33.10, large requests and responses can potentially trigger TCP connection pool crashes due to flow control management in Envoy. It will happen when the connection is closing but upstream data is still coming, resulting in a buffer watermark callback nullptr reference. The vulnerability impacts TCP proxy and HTTP 1 &amp; 2 mixed use cases based on ALPN. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.36.1, 1.35.5, 1.34.9, and 1.33.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62411 | Stored XSS in Alert Transport name field in LibreNMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62411</link><description>LibreNMS &lt;= 25.8.0 contains a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Alert Transports management functionality. When an administrator creates a new Alert Transport, the value of the Transport name field is stored and later rendered in the Transports column of the Alert Rules page without proper input validation or output encoding. This leads to arbitrary JavaScript execution in the admin’s browser. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61330 | A hard-coded weak password vulnerability has been discovered in all Magic-branded devices from Chinese network equipment manufacturer H3C. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61330</link><description>A hard-coded weak password vulnerability has been discovered in all Magic-branded devices from Chinese network equipment manufacturer H3C. The vulnerability stems from the use of a hard-coded weak password for the root account in the /etc/shadow configuration or even the absence of any password at all. Some of these devices have the Telnet service enabled by default, or users can choose to enable the Telnet service in other device management interfaces (e.g. /debug.asp or /debug_telnet.asp). In addition, these devices have related interfaces called Virtual Servers, which can map the devices to the public network, posing the risk of remote attacks. Therefore, attackers can obtain the highest root privileges of the devices through the Telnet service using the weak password hardcoded in the firmware (or without a password), and remote attacks are possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62407 | Frappe has an Open Redirect on Login Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62407</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 14.98.0 and 15.83.0, an open redirect was possible  through the redirect argument on the login page, if a specific type of URL was passed in. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.98.0 and 15.83.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61923 | PrestaShop Checkout Backoffice directory traversal allows arbitrary file disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61923</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, the backoffice is missing validation on input resulting in a directory traversal and arbitrary file disclosure. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61924 | PrestaShop Checkout Target PayPal merchant account hijacking from backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61924</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, the Target PayPal merchant account hijacking from backoffice due to wrong usage of the PHP array_search(). The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61909 | Icinga 2 signals sent as root to processes based on PID file written by the Icinga 2 daemon user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61909</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. From 2.10.0 to before 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13, the safe-reload script (also used during systemctl reload icinga2) and logrotate configuration shipped with Icinga 2 read the PID of the main Icinga 2 process from a PID file writable by the daemon user, but send the signal as the root user. This can allow the Icinga user to send signals to processes it would otherwise not permitted to. A fix is included in the following Icinga 2 versions: 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61922 | PrestaShop Checkout allows customer account takeover via email</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61922</link><description>PrestaShop Checkout is the PrestaShop official payment module in partnership with PayPal. In versions prior to 4.4.1 and 5.0.5, missing validation on the Express Checkout feature allows silent login, enabling account takeover via email. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 4.4.1 and 5.0.5. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62586 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress unauthenticated administrator password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62586</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to reset the administrator password. Fixed in FOIAXpress version 11.13.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61907 | Icinga 2 API users could access restricted values in filter expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61907</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. In Icinga 2 versions 2.4 through 2.15.0, filter expressions provided to the various /v1/objects endpoints could access variables or objects that would otherwise be inaccessible for the user. This allows authenticated API users to learn information that should be hidden from them, including global variables not permitted by the variables permission and objects not permitted by the corresponding objects/query permissions. The vulnerability is fixed in versions 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61908 | Icinga 2 Denial of Service (DoS) By Dereferencing Invalid Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61908</link><description>Icinga 2 is an open source monitoring system. From 2.10.0 to before 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13, when creating an invalid reference, such as a reference to null, dereferencing results in a segmentation fault. This can be used by any API user with access to an API endpoint that allows specifying a filter expression to crash the Icinga 2 daemon. A fix is included in the following Icinga 2 versions: 2.15.1, 2.14.7, and 2.13.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61789 | Icinga DB Web hidden/protected custom variables are prone to filter enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61789</link><description>Icinga DB Web provides a graphical interface for Icinga monitoring. Before 1.1.4 and 1.2.3, an authorized user with access to Icinga DB Web, can use a custom variable in a filter that is either protected by icingadb/protect/variables or hidden by icingadb/denylist/variables, to guess values assigned to it. Versions 1.1.4 and 1.2.3 respond with an error if such a custom variable is used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36128 | IBM MQ denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36128</link><description>IBM MQ 9.1, 9.2, 9.3, 9.4 LTS and 9.3, 9.4 CD is vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by improper enforcement of the timeout on individual read operations. By conducting slowloris-type attacks, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58051 | Nextcloud Tables app allowed to include local file via PhpSpreadsheet when importing a table</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58051</link><description>Nextcloud Tables allows you to create your own tables with individual columns. Prior 0.7.6, 0.8.8, and 0.9.5, when importing a table, a user was able to specify files on the server and when their format is supported by the used PhpSpreadsheet library they would be included and their content leaked to the user. It is recommended that the Nextcloud Tables app is upgraded to 0.7.6, 0.8.8 or 0.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56699 | SQL injection vulnerability in the cmd component of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows an unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56699</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the cmd component of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows an unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the sender parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53092 | Strapi core vulnerable to sensitive data exposure via CORS misconfiguration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53092</link><description>Strapi is an open source headless content management system. Strapi versions prior to 5.20.0 contain a CORS misconfiguration vulnerability in default installations. By default, Strapi reflects the value of the Origin header back in the Access-Control-Allow-Origin response header without proper validation or whitelisting. This allows an attacker-controlled site to send credentialed requests to the Strapi backend. An attacker can exploit this by hosting a malicious site on a different origin (e.g., different port) and sending requests with credentials to the Strapi API. The vulnerability is fixed in version 5.20.0. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56700 | Boolean SQL injection vulnerability in the web app of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows a low level privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56700</link><description>Boolean SQL injection vulnerability in the web app of Base Digitale Group spa product Centrax Open PSIM version 6.1 allows a low level priviliged user that has access to the platform, to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the datafine parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25298 | Missing Maximum Password Length Validation in Strapi Password Hashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25298</link><description>Strapi is an open source headless CMS. The @strapi/core package before version 5.10.3 does not enforce a maximum password length when using bcryptjs for password hashing. Bcryptjs ignores any bytes beyond 72, so passwords longer than 72 bytes are silently truncated. A user can create an account with a password exceeding 72 bytes and later authenticate with only the first 72 bytes. This reduces the effective entropy of overlong passwords and may mislead users who believe characters beyond 72 bytes are required, creating a low likelihood of unintended authentication if an attacker can obtain or guess the truncated portion. Long over‑length inputs can also impose unnecessary processing overhead. The issue is fixed in version 5.10.3. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56143 | Strapi Allows Unauthorized Access to Private Fields via parms.lookup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56143</link><description>Strapi is an open-source headless content management system. In versions from 5.0.0 to before 5.5.2, the lookup operator provided by the document service does not properly sanitize query parameters for private fields. An attacker can access private fields, including admin passwords and reset tokens, by crafting queries with the lookup parameter. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11851 | Apeman ID71 set_alias.cgi cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11851</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Apeman ID71 EN75.8.53.20. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /set_alias.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument alias leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62490 | Use-after-free in js_print_object in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62490</link><description>In quickjs, in js_print_object, when printing an array, the function first fetches the array length and then loops over it. The issue is, printing a value is not side-effect free. An attacker-defined callback could run during js_print_value, during which the array could get resized and len1 become out of bounds. This results in a use-after-free.A second instance occurs in the same function during printing of a map or set objects. The code iterates over ms-&gt;records list, but once again, elements could be removed from the list during js_print_value call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62491 | Use-after-free in js_std_promise_rejection_check in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62491</link><description>A Use-After-Free (UAF) vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's standard library when iterating over the global list of unhandled rejected promises (ts-&gt;rejected_promise_list).

  *  The function js_std_promise_rejection_check attempts to iterate over the rejected_promise_list to report unhandled rejections using a standard list loop.


  *  The reason for a promise rejection is processed inside the loop, including calling js_std_dump_error1(ctx, rp-&gt;reason).


  *  If the promise rejection reason is an Error object that defines a custom property getter (e.g., via Object.defineProperty), this getter is executed during the error dumping process.


  *  The malicious custom getter can execute JavaScript code that calls catch() on the same rejected promise being processed.


  *  Calling catch() internally triggers js_std_promise_rejection_tracker, which then removes and frees the current promise entry (JSRejectedPromiseEntry) from the rejected_promise_list.


  *  Since the list iteration continues using the now-freed memory pointer (el), the subsequent loop access results in a Use-After-Free condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62492 | Heap out-of-bounds read in js_typed_array_indexOf in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62492</link><description>A vulnerability stemming from floating-point arithmetic precision errors exists in the QuickJS engine's implementation of TypedArray.prototype.indexOf() when a negative fromIndex argument is supplied.

  *  The fromIndex argument (read as a double variable, $d$) is used to calculate the starting position for the search.


  *  If d is negative, the index is calculated relative to the end of the array by adding the array's length (len) to d:



$$d_{new} = d + \text{len}$$


  *  Due to the inherent limitations of floating-point arithmetic, if the negative value $d$ is extremely small (e.g., $-1 \times 10^{-20}$), the addition $d + \text{len}$ can result in a loss of precision, yielding an outcome that is exactly equal to $\text{len}$.


  *  The result is then converted to an integer index $k$: $k = \text{len}$.


  *  The search function proceeds to read array elements starting from index $k$. Since valid indices are $0$ to $\text{len}-1$, starting the read at index $\text{len}$ is one element past the end of the array.


This allows an attacker to cause an Out-of-Bounds Read of one element immediately following the buffer. While the scope of this read is small (one element), it can potentially lead to Information Disclosure of adjacent memory contents, depending on the execution environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62493 | Heap out-of-bounds read in js_bigint_to_string1 in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62493</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's BigInt string conversion logic (js_bigint_to_string1) due to an incorrect calculation of the required number of digits, which in turn leads to reading memory past the allocated BigInt structure.

  *  The function determines the number of characters (n_digits) needed for the string representation by calculating:

$$ \\ \text{n\_digits} = (\text{n\_bits} + \text{log2\_radix} - 1) / \text{log2\_radix}$$

$$$$This formula is off-by-one in certain edge cases when calculating the necessary memory limbs. For instance, a 127-bit BigInt using radix 32 (where $\text{log2\_radix}=5$) is calculated to need $\text{n\_digits}=26$.


  *  The maximum number of bits actually stored is $\text{n\_bits}=127$, which requires only two 64-bit limbs ($\text{JS\_LIMB\_BITS}=64$).


  *  The conversion loop iterates $\text{n\_digits}=26$ times, attempting to read 5 bits in each iteration, totaling $26 \times 5 = 130$ bits.


  *  In the final iterations of the loop, the code attempts to read data that spans two limbs:

C



c = (r-&gt;tab[pos] &gt;&gt; shift) | (r-&gt;tab[pos + 1] &lt;&lt; (JS_LIMB_BITS - shift));









  *  Since the BigInt was only allocated two limbs, the read operation for r-&gt;tab[pos + 1] becomes an Out-of-Bounds Read when pos points to the last valid limb (e.g., $pos=1$).


This vulnerability allows an attacker to cause the engine to read and process data from the memory immediately following the BigInt buffer. This can lead to Information Disclosure of sensitive data stored on the heap adjacent to the BigInt object.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62494 | Type confusion in string addition in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62494</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability exists in the handling of the string addition (+) operation within the QuickJS engine.

  *  The code first checks if the left-hand operand is a string.


  *  It then attempts to convert the right-hand operand to a primitive value using JS_ToPrimitiveFree. This conversion can trigger a callback (e.g., toString or valueOf).


  *  During this callback, an attacker can modify the type of the left-hand operand in memory, changing it from a string to a different type (e.g., an object or an array).


  *  The code then proceeds to call JS_ConcatStringInPlace, which still treats the modified left-hand value as a string.


This mismatch between the assumed type (string) and the actual type allows an attacker to control the data structure being processed by the concatenation logic, resulting in a type confusion condition. This can lead to out-of-bounds memory access, potentially resulting in memory corruption and arbitrary code execution in the context of the QuickJS runtime.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62495 | Type confusion in string addition in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62495</link><description>An integer overflow vulnerability exists in the QuickJS regular expression engine (libregexp) due to an inconsistent representation of the bytecode buffer size.

  *  The regular expression bytecode is stored in a DynBuf structure, which correctly uses a $\text{size}\_\text{t}$ (an unsigned type, typically 64-bit) for its size member.


  *  However, several functions, such as re_emit_op_u32 and other internal parsing routines, incorrectly cast or store this DynBuf $\text{size}\_\text{t}$ value into a signed int (typically 32-bit).


  *  When a large or complex regular expression (such as those generated by a recursive pattern in a Proof-of-Concept) causes the bytecode size to exceed $2^{31}$ bytes (the maximum positive value for a signed 32-bit integer), the size value wraps around, resulting in a negative integer when stored in the int variable (Integer Overflow).


  *  This negative value is subsequently used in offset calculations. For example, within functions like re_parse_disjunction, the negative size is used to compute an offset (pos) for patching a jump instruction.


  *  This negative offset is then incorrectly added to the buffer pointer (s-&gt;byte\_code.buf + pos), leading to an out-of-bounds write on the first line of the snippet below:

put_u32(s-&gt;byte_code.buf + pos, len);</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62496 | Integer overflow in js_bigint_from_string in QuickJS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62496</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the QuickJS engine's BigInt string parsing logic (js_bigint_from_string) when attempting to create a BigInt from a string with an excessively large number of digits.

The function calculates the necessary number of bits (n_bits) required to store the BigInt using the formula:

$$\text{n\_bits} = (\text{n\_digits} \times 27 + 7) / 8 \quad (\text{for radix 10})$$

  *  For large input strings (e.g., $79,536,432$ digits or more for base 10), the intermediate calculation $(\text{n\_digits} \times 27 + 7)$ exceeds the maximum value of a standard signed 32-bit integer, resulting in an Integer Overflow.


  *  The resulting n_bits value becomes unexpectedly small or even negative due to this wrap-around.


  *  This flawed n_bits is then used to compute n_limbs, the number of memory "limbs" needed for the BigInt object. Since n_bits is too small, the calculated n_limbs is also significantly underestimated.


  *  The function proceeds to allocate a JSBigInt object using this underestimated n_limbs.


  *  When the function later attempts to write the actual BigInt data into the allocated object, the small buffer size is quickly exceeded, leading to a Heap Out-of-Bounds Write as data is written past the end of the allocated r-&gt;tab array.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11840 | GNU Binutils ldmisc.c vfinfo out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11840</link><description>A weakness has been identified in GNU Binutils 2.45. The affected element is the function vfinfo of the file ldmisc.c. Executing manipulation can lead to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This patch is called 16357. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11842 | Shazwazza Smidge Bundle path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11842</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Shazwazza Smidge up to 4.5.1. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Bundle Handler. The manipulation of the argument Version leads to path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. Upgrading to version 4.6.0 is sufficient to resolve this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9559 | Pega Platform versions 8.7.5 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Insecure Direct Object Reference issue in a user interface component that can only be used to read data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9559</link><description>Pega Platform versions 8.7.5 to Infinity 24.2.2 are affected by a Insecure Direct Object Reference issue in a user interface component that can only be used to read data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55035 | Mattermost Desktop DoS when user has basic authentication server configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55035</link><description>Mattermost Desktop App versions &lt;=5.13.0 fail to manage modals in the Mattermost Desktop App that stops a user with a server that uses basic authentication from accessing their server which allows an attacker that provides a malicious server to the user to deny use of the Desktop App via having the user configure the malicious server and forcing a modal popup that cannot be closed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36002 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36002</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 and IBM Sterling File Gateway 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.5, and 6.2.1.0 stores user credentials in configuration files which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41254 | Spring Framework STOMP CSRF Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41254</link><description>STOMP over WebSocket applications may be vulnerable to a security bypass that allows an attacker to send unauthorized messages.

Affected Spring Products and VersionsSpring Framework:

  *  6.2.0 - 6.2.11
  *  6.1.0 - 6.1.23
  *  6.0.x - 6.0.29
  *  5.3.0 - 5.3.45
  *  Older, unsupported versions are also affected.


MitigationUsers of affected versions should upgrade to the corresponding fixed version.

Affected version(s)Fix versionAvailability6.2.x6.2.12OSS6.1.x6.1.24 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ 6.0.xN/A Out of support https://spring.io/projects/spring-framework#support 5.3.x5.3.46 Commercial https://enterprise.spring.io/ No further mitigation steps are necessary.

CreditThis vulnerability was discovered and responsibly reported by Jannis Kaiser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61536 | FelixRiddle dev-jobs-handlebars 1.0 uses absolute password-reset (magic) links using the untrusted `req.headers.host` header and forces the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61536</link><description>FelixRiddle dev-jobs-handlebars 1.0 uses absolute password-reset (magic) links using the untrusted `req.headers.host` header and forces the `http://` scheme. An attacker who can control the `Host` header (or exploit a misconfigured proxy/load-balancer that forwards the header unchanged) can cause reset links to point to attacker-controlled domains or be delivered via insecure HTTP, enabling token theft, phishing, and account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61541 | Webmin 2.510 is vulnerable to a Host Header Injection in the password reset functionality (forgot_send.cgi). The reset link sent to users is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61541</link><description>Webmin 2.510 is vulnerable to a Host Header Injection in the password reset functionality (forgot_send.cgi). The reset link sent to users is constructed using the HTTP Host header via get_webmin_email_url(). An attacker can manipulate the Host header to inject a malicious domain into the reset email. If a victim follows the poisoned link, the attacker can intercept the reset token and gain full control of the target account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61543 | A Host Header Injection vulnerability exists in the password reset functionality of CraftMyCMS 4.0.2.2. The system uses `$_SERVER['HTTP_HOST...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61543</link><description>A Host Header Injection vulnerability exists in the password reset functionality of CraftMyCMS 4.0.2.2. The system uses `$_SERVER['HTTP_HOST']` directly to construct password reset links sent via email. An attacker can manipulate the Host header to send malicious reset links, enabling phishing attacks or account takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22381 | Aggie 2.6.1 has a Host Header injection vulnerability in the forgot password functionality, allowing an attacker to reset a user's password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22381</link><description>Aggie 2.6.1 has a Host Header injection vulnerability in the forgot password functionality, allowing an attacker to reset a user's password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61539 | Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the u_name parameter in lostpassword.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61539</link><description>Cross site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the u_name parameter in lostpassword.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61540 | SQL injection vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the username field in lostpassword.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61540</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Ultimate PHP Board 2.2.7 via the username field in lostpassword.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41253 | Spring Cloud Gateway Webflux SpEL Injection Vulnerability Allowing Exposure of Environment Variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41253</link><description>The following versions of Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux may be vulnerable to the ability to expose environment variables and system properties to attackers.

An application should be considered vulnerable when all the following are true:

  *  The application is using Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux (Spring Cloud Gateway Server WebMVC is not vulnerable).
  *  An admin or untrusted third party using Spring Expression Language (SpEL) to access environment variables or system properties via routes.
  *  An untrusted third party could create a route that uses SpEL to access environment variables or system properties if:  *  The Spring Cloud Gateway Server Webflux actuator web endpoint is enabled via management.endpoints.web.exposure.include=gateway and management.endpoint.gateway.enabled=trueor management.endpoint.gateway.access=unrestricte.
  *  The actuator endpoints are available to attackers.
  *  The actuator endpoints are unsecured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11839 | GNU Binutils prdbg.c tg_tag_type return value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11839</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in GNU Binutils 2.45. Impacted is the function tg_tag_type of the file prdbg.c. Performing manipulation results in unchecked return value. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46752 | A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiDLP 12.0.0 through 12.0.5, 11.5.1, 11.4.6, 11.4.5 allows attacker to inf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46752</link><description>A insertion of sensitive information into log file in Fortinet FortiDLP 12.0.0 through 12.0.5, 11.5.1, 11.4.6, 11.4.5 allows attacker to information disclosure via re-using the enrollment code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53950 | An Exposure of Private Personal Information ('Privacy Violation') vulnerability [CWE-359] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53950</link><description>An Exposure of Private Personal Information ('Privacy Violation') vulnerability [CWE-359] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for MacOS and Windows 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1. through 11.1.2 and 11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated administrator to collect current user's email information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53951 | An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outloo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53951</link><description>An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for Windows 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1 through 11.1.2 and  11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated attacker to escalate their privilege to LocalService via sending a crafted request to a local listening port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54658 | An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outloo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54658</link><description>An Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability [CWE-22] in Fortinet FortiDLP Agent's Outlookproxy plugin for MacOS 11.5.1 and 11.4.2 through 11.4.6 and 11.3.2 through 11.3.4 and 11.2.0 through 11.2.3 and 11.1.1 through 11.1.2 and 11.0.1 and 10.5.1 and 10.4.0, and 10.3.1 may allow an authenticated attacker to escalate their privilege to Root via sending a crafted request to a local listening port.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9152 | Improper Privilege Management in Multiple WSO2 API Manager via keymanager-operations DCR Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9152</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability exists in WSO2 API Manager due to missing authentication and authorization checks in the keymanager-operations Dynamic Client Registration (DCR) endpoint.

A malicious user can exploit this flaw to generate access tokens with elevated privileges, potentially leading to administrative access and the ability to perform unauthorized operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9804 | Improper Access Control in Multiple WSO2 Products via Internal SOAP Admin Services and System REST APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9804</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in multiple WSO2 products due to insufficient permission enforcement in certain internal SOAP Admin Services and System REST APIs. A low-privileged user may exploit this flaw to perform unauthorized operations, including accessing server-level information.

This vulnerability affects only internal administrative interfaces. APIs exposed through the WSO2 API Manager's API Gateway remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10611 | Potential Broken Access Control in Multiple WSO2 Products via System REST APIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10611</link><description>Due to an insufficient access control implementation in multiple WSO2 Products, authentication and authorization checks for certain REST APIs can be bypassed, allowing them to be invoked without proper validation.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could lead to a malicious actor gaining administrative access and performing unauthenticated and unauthorized administrative operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9955 | Improper Access Control in WSO2 Enterprise Integrator Product via SOAP Admin Services for Logs and User-Store Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9955</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in WSO2 Enterprise Integrator product due to insufficient permission restrictions on internal SOAP admin services related to system logs and user-store configuration. A low-privileged user can access log data and user-store configuration details that are not intended to be exposed at that privilege level.

While no credentials or sensitive user information are exposed, this vulnerability may allow unauthorized visibility into internal operational details, which could aid in further exploitation or reconnaissance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3930 | Lack of JWT Expiration after Log Out in Strapi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3930</link><description>Strapi uses JSON Web Tokens (JWT) for authentication. After logout or account deactivation, the JWT is not invalidated, which allows an attacker who has stolen or intercepted the token to freely reuse it until its expiration date (which is set to 30 days by default, but can be changed). 
The existence of /admin/renew-token endpoint allows anyone to renew near-expiration tokens indefinitely, further increasing the impact of this attack. 

This issue has been fixed in version 5.24.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24833 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO versions V4.0R1.0–V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24833</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO versions V4.0R1.0–V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52583 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's Web Server allows execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52583</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's Web Server allows execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54760 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54760</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54859 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54859</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V9.0R2.0 and earlier allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55072 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V2.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55072</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in desknet's NEO V2.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allow execution of arbitrary JavaScript in a user’s web browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58079 | Improper Protection of Alternate Path (CWE-424) in the AppSuite of desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allows an attacker to create malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58079</link><description>Improper Protection of Alternate Path (CWE-424) in the AppSuite of desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58426 | desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 contains a hard-coded cryptographic key, which allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applicatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58426</link><description>desknet's NEO V4.0R1.0 to V9.0R2.0 contains a hard-coded cryptographic key, which allows an attacker to create malicious AppSuite applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6338 | Possible denial of service with multiple incoming connections to a Schannel based server with a TLS backend</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6338</link><description>There is an incomplete cleanup vulnerability in Qt Network's Schannel support on Windows which can lead to a Denial of Service over a long period.This issue affects Qt from 5.15.0 through 6.8.3, from 6.9.0 before 6.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53858 | ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Chat Rooms. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53858</link><description>ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Chat Rooms. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is accessing the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54461 | ChatLuck contains an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability in Invitation of Guest Users. If exploited, an uninvited guest...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54461</link><description>ChatLuck contains an insufficient granularity of access control vulnerability in Invitation of Guest Users. If exploited, an uninvited guest user may register itself as a guest user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58115 | ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Guest User Sign-up. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58115</link><description>ChatLuck contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Guest User Sign-up. If exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is accessing the product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41410 | Slack import bypasses email verification for team access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41410</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to validate email ownership during Slack import process which allows attackers to create verified user accounts with arbitrary email domains via malicious Slack import data to bypass email-based team access restrictions</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58073 | Arbitrary Mattermost Team can be joined by manipulating the OAuth state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58073</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.1, 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10 fail to verify a user has permission to join a Mattermost team using the original invite token which allows any attacked to join any team on a Mattermost server regardless of restrictions via manipulating the OAuth state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61581 | Apache Traffic Control: ReDoS issue in Traffic Router configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61581</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Inefficient Regular Expression Complexity vulnerability in Apache Traffic Control.

This issue affects Apache Traffic Control: all versions.

People with access to the management interface of the Traffic Router component could specify malicious patterns and cause unavailability.

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0277 | HCL BigFix Mobile is affected by an insecure Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0277</link><description>HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier are vulnerable to certain insecure directives within the Content Security Policy (CSP).  An attacker could trick users into performing actions by not properly restricting the sources of scripts and other content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0276 | HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) is affected by an insecure Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0276</link><description>HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier are vulnerable to certain insecure directives within the Content Security Policy (CSP).  An attacker could trick users into performing actions by not properly restricting the sources of scripts and other content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10545 | Guest user can add unauthorized team users to private channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10545</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to properly validate guest user permissions when adding channel members which allows guest users to add any team members to their private channels via the `/api/v4/channels/{channel_id}/members` endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54499 | Insecure string comparison enables timing attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54499</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to use constant-time comparison for sensitive string comparisons which allows attackers to exploit timing oracles to perform byte-by-byte brute force attacks via response time analysis on Cloud API keys and OAuth client secrets</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54539 | Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP Client: Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54539</link><description>A Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists in the Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP Client.

This issue affects all versions of Apache ActiveMQ NMS AMQP up to and including 2.3.0, when establishing connections to untrusted AMQP servers. Malicious servers could exploit unbounded deserialization logic present in the client to craft responses that may lead to arbitrary code execution on the client side.

Although version 2.1.0 introduced a mechanism to restrict deserialization via allow/deny lists, the protection was found to be bypassable under certain conditions.

In line with Microsoft’s deprecation of binary serialization in .NET 9, the project is evaluating the removal of .NET binary serialization support from the NMS API entirely in future releases.

Mitigation and Recommendations:
Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade to version 2.4.0 or later, which resolves the issue. Additionally, projects depending on NMS-AMQP should migrate away from .NET binary serialization as part of a long-term hardening strategy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58075 | Arbitrary Mattermost Team can be joined by manipulating the SAML RelayState</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58075</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.1, 10.10.x &lt;= 10.10.2, 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10 fail to verify a user has permission to join a Mattermost team using the original invite token which allows any attacked to join any team on a Mattermost server regardless of restrictions via manipulating the RelayState</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41443 | Guest user can discover active public channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41443</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.5.x &lt;= 10.5.10, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.2 fail to properly validate guest user permissions when accessing channel information which allows guest users to discover active public channels and their metadata via the `/api/v4/teams/{team_id}/channels/ids` endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41018 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41018</link><description>SQL injection in Sergestec's Exito v8.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases through the 'cat' parameter in '/public.php'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41019 | SQL injection vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41019</link><description>SQL injection in Sergestec's SISTICK v7.2. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update, and delete databases through the 'id' parameter in '/index.php?view=ticket_detail'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41020 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41020</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Sergestec's Exito v8.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to access data belonging to other customers through the 'id' parameter in '/admin/ticket_a4.php'.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41021 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sergestec&amp;#x27;s Exito</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41021</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Sergestec's Exito v8.0, consisting of a stored XSS due to a lack of proper validation of user input by sending a POST request using the 'obs' parameter in '/admin/index.php?action=product_update'. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their cookie session details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55091 | Potential out of bound read in _nx_ip_packet_receive()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55091</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ip_packet_receive() function when received an Ethernet with type set as IP but no IP data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10706 | Classified Pro &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10706</link><description>The Classified Pro theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check in the 'cwp_addons_update_plugin_cb' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to install arbitrary plugins on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Note: The required nonce for the vulnerability is in the CubeWP Framework plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10742 | Truelysell Core &amp;lt;= 1.8.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10742</link><description>The Truelysell Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change in versions up to, and including, 1.8.6. This is due to the plugin providing user-controlled access to objects, letting a user bypass authorization and access system resources. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts. Note: This can only be exploited unauthenticated if the attacker knows which page contains the 'truelysell_edit_staff' shortcode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10849 | Felan Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Activation/Deactivation via process_plugin_actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10849</link><description>The Felan Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'process_plugin_actions' function called via an AJAX action in versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to activate or deactivate arbitrary plugins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10850 | Felan Framework &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Hardcoded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10850</link><description>The Felan Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to improper authentication in versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This is due to the hardcoded password in the 'fb_ajax_login_or_register' function and in the 'google_ajax_login_or_register' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, if they registered with facebook or google social login and did not change their password.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62583 | Whale Browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to escape the iframe sandbox in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62583</link><description>Whale Browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to escape the iframe sandbox in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62584 | Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Same-Origin Policy in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62584</link><description>Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Same-Origin Policy in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62585 | Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Content Security Policy via a specific scheme in a dual-tab environment.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62585</link><description>Whale browser before 4.33.325.17 allows an attacker to bypass the Content Security Policy via a specific scheme in a dual-tab environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55090 | Potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive()  in NetX Duo</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55090</link><description>In NetX Duo before 6.4.4, the networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a potential out of bound read issue in _nx_ipv4_packet_receive() function when received an Ethernet frame with less than 4 bytes of IP packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55084 | Out of bound read in _nx_secure_tls_proc_clienthello_supported_versions_extension()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55084</link><description>In NetX Duo version before 6.4.4, the component of Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was an incorrect bound check in_nx_secure_tls_proc_clienthello_supported_versions_extension() in the extension version field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55089 | Eclipse ThreadX FileX RAM disk driver buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55089</link><description>In FileX before 6.4.2, the file support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, there was a possible buffer overflow in the FileX RAM disk driver. It could cause a remote execurtion after receiving a crafted sequence of packets</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58778 | Multiple versions of RG-EST300 provided by Ruijie Networks provide SSH server functionality. It is not documented in the manual, and enabled...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58778</link><description>Multiple versions of RG-EST300 provided by Ruijie Networks provide SSH server functionality. It is not documented in the manual, and enabled in the initial configuration. Anyone with the knowledge of the related credentials can log in to the affected device, leading to information disclosure, altering the system configurations, or causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 06:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0275 | HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0275</link><description>HCL BigFix Mobile 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control.  Unauthorized users can access a small subset of endpoint actions, potentially allowing access to select internal functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0274 | HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0274</link><description>HCL BigFix Modern Client Management (MCM) 3.3 and earlier is affected by improper access control.  Unauthorized users can access a small subset of endpoint actions, potentially allowing access to select internal functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 05:12:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11814 | Ultimate Addons for WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt; 3.21.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11814</link><description>The Ultimate Addons for WPBakery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to 3.21.1 (exclusive) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 04:45:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10700 | Ally - Web Accessibility &amp;amp; Usability &amp;lt;= 3.8.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10700</link><description>The Ally – Web Accessibility &amp; Usability plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the enable_unfiltered_files_upload function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable unfiltered file upload and add svg files to the upload list via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62579 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62579</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62580 | ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62580</link><description>ASDA-Soft Stack-based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11683 | YAML::Syck versions before 1.36 for Perl has missing Null-Terminators which causes Out-of-Bounds Read and potential Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11683</link><description>YAML::Syck versions before 1.36 for Perl has missing null-terminators which causes out-of-bounds read and potential information disclosure

Missing null terminators in token.c leads to but-of-bounds read which allows adjacent variable to be read

The issue is seen with complex YAML files with a hash of all keys and empty values.  There is no indication that the issue leads to accessing memory outside that allocated to the module.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>