<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:25:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-62242 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with account addresses in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62242</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability with account addresses in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.4 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated users to from one account to view addresses from a different account via the _com_liferay_account_admin_web_internal_portlet_AccountEntriesAdminPortlet_addressId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62170 | rAthena map-server use-after-free vulnerability in RODEX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62170</link><description>rAthena is an open-source cross-platform MMORPG server. A use-after-free vulnerability exists in the RODEX functionality of rAthena's map-server in versions prior to commit af2f3ba. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability via a specific attacking scenario to cause a denial of service by crashing the map-server. This issue has been patched in commit af2f3ba. There are no known workarounds aside from manually applying the patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61775 | Vicekey&amp;#x27;s unexpired email confirmation link can be reused to send repeated confirmation emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61775</link><description>Vickey is a Misskey-based microblogging platform. A vulnerability exists in Vickey prior to version 2025.10.0 where unexpired email confirmation links can be reused multiple times to send repeated confirmation emails to a verified email address. Under certain conditions, a verified email address could receive repeated confirmation messages if the verification link was accessed multiple times. This issue may result in unintended email traffic but does not expose user data. The issue was addressed in version 2025.10.0 by improving validation logic to ensure verification links behave as expected after completion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62243 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62243</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 allows remote authenticated attackers to view publication comments via the _com_liferay_change_tracking_web_portlet_PublicationsPortlet_value parameter.

Publications comments in Liferay Portal 7.4.1 through 7.4.3.112, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92 does not properly check user permissions, which allows remote authenticated users to edit publication comments via crafted URLs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62244 | Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.3.1 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62244</link><description>Insecure direct object reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Publications in Liferay Portal 7.3.1 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.5, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.8, and 7.4 GA through update 92, and 7.3 GA through update 36 allows remote authenticated attackers to view the edit page of a publication via the _com_liferay_change_tracking_web_portlet_PublicationsPortlet_ctCollectionId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11695 | Configuration may unexpectedly disable certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11695</link><description>When tlsInsecure=False appears in a connection string, certificate validation is disabled.

This vulnerability affects MongoDB Rust Driver versions prior to v3.2.5</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7707 | World-Writable NLTK Cache Directory Vulnerability in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7707</link><description>The llama_index library version 0.12.33 sets the NLTK data directory to a subdirectory of the codebase by default, which is world-writable in multi-user environments. This configuration allows local users to overwrite, delete, or corrupt NLTK data files, leading to potential denial of service, data tampering, or privilege escalation. The vulnerability arises from the use of a shared cache directory instead of a user-specific one, making it susceptible to local data tampering and denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43991 | SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.8.2 and prior and SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.3 and prior, contain an UNIX Symbolic Li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43991</link><description>SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.8.2 and prior and SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.3 and prior, contain an UNIX Symbolic Link (Symlink) following vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access to the system could potentially exploit this vulnerability to delete arbitrary files only in that affected system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39964 | crypto: af_alg - Disallow concurrent writes in af_alg_sendmsg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39964</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: af_alg - Disallow concurrent writes in af_alg_sendmsg

Issuing two writes to the same af_alg socket is bogus as the
data will be interleaved in an unpredictable fashion.  Furthermore,
concurrent writes may create inconsistencies in the internal
socket state.

Disallow this by adding a new ctx-&gt;write field that indiciates
exclusive ownership for writing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39965 | xfrm: xfrm_alloc_spi shouldn&amp;#x27;t use 0 as SPI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39965</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xfrm: xfrm_alloc_spi shouldn't use 0 as SPI

x-&gt;id.spi == 0 means "no SPI assigned", but since commit
94f39804d891 ("xfrm: Duplicate SPI Handling"), we now create states
and add them to the byspi list with this value.

__xfrm_state_delete doesn't remove those states from the byspi list,
since they shouldn't be there, and this shows up as a UAF the next
time we go through the byspi list.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37729 | Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37729</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine in Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE) can lead to a malicious actor with Admin access exfiltrating sensitive information and issuing commands via a specially crafted string where Jinjava variables are evaluated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9902 | IDOR in Akınsoft QRMenu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9902</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in AKIN Software Computer Import Export Industry and Trade Co. Ltd. QRMenu allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects QRMenu: from 1.05.12 before Version dated 05.09.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6919 | SQLi in Cats Informatics&amp;#x27; Aykome</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6919</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Cats Information Technology Software Development Technologies Aykome License Tracking System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Aykome License Tracking System: through 06.10.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10720 | WP Private Content Plus &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Password Protection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10720</link><description>The WP Private Content Plus through 3.6.2 provides a global content protection feature that requires a password. However, the access control check is based only on the presence of an unprotected client-side cookie. As a result, an unauthenticated attacker can completely bypass the password protection by manually setting the cookie value in their browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:51:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9336 | A stack buffer overflow has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by input manipulation, may leading ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9336</link><description>A stack buffer overflow has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. This vulnerability can be triggered by input manipulation, may leading to a system crash (BSOD) or other potentially undefined execution. 
Refer to the 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9337 | A null pointer dereference has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specially crafted input, whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9337</link><description>A null pointer dereference has been identified in the AsIO3.sys driver. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specially crafted input, which may lead to a system crash (BSOD).
Refer to the 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11183 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in QWC2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11183</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in attribute table in QGIS QWC2 &lt;2025.08.14
allows an authorized attacker to plant arbitrary JavaScript code in the page</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11184 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in QWC2 Registration GUI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11184</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in QGIS QWC2 Registration GUI &lt;=v2025.03.31
allows an authorized attacker to plant arbitrary JavaScript code in the page</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9968 | A link following vulnerability exists in the UnifyScanner component of Armoury Crate. This vulnerability may be triggered by creating a spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9968</link><description>A link following vulnerability exists in the UnifyScanner component of Armoury Crate. This vulnerability may be triggered by creating a specially crafted junction, potentially leading to local privilege escalation.
For more information, please refer to section 'Security Update for Armoury Crate App' in the ASUS Security Advisory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11668 | code-projects Automated Voting System update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11668</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Automated Voting System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_user.php. This manipulation of the argument Password causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11675 | Ragic｜Enterprise Cloud Database - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11675</link><description>Enterprise Cloud Database developed by Ragic has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 08:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11674 | PiExtract｜SOOP-CLM - Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11674</link><description>SOOP-CLM developed by PiExtract has a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to read server files or probe internal network information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10552 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10552</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSwym in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10556 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Specification Management in ENOVIA Specification Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10556</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Specification Management in ENOVIA Specification Manager from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2023x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10557 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10557</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting Issue Management in ENOVIA Collaborative Industry Innovator from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10558 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSearch in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10558</link><description>A stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting 3DSearch in 3DSwymer on Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x allows an attacker to execute arbitrary script code in user's browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11667 | code-projects Automated Voting System add_candidate_modal.php. sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11667</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Automated Voting System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/add_candidate_modal.php.. The manipulation of the argument firstname results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11672 | EBM Technologies｜Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11672</link><description>Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer developed by EBM Technologies has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access a specific page to obtain user group names.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11673 | PiExtract ｜SOOP-CLM - Hidden Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11673</link><description>SOOP-CLM developed by PiExtract has a Hidden Functionality vulnerability, allowing privileged remote attackers to exploit a hidden functionality to execute arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9976 | OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting Station Launcher App in 3DEXPERIENCE platform from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9976</link><description>An OS Command Injection vulnerability affecting Station Launcher App in 3DEXPERIENCE platform from Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2022x through Release 3DEXPERIENCE R2025x could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the user's machine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11671 | EBM Technologies｜Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11671</link><description>Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer developed by EBM Technologies has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to access a specific page to obtain information such as account names and IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11666 | Tenda RP3 Pro Firmware Update force_upgrade.sh hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11666</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda RP3 Pro up to 22.5.7.93. This impacts an unknown function of the file force_upgrade.sh of the component Firmware Update Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument current_force_upgrade_pwd can lead to use of hard-coded password. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8915 | Hardcoded TLS private key in Kiloview N30 firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8915</link><description>Hardcoded TLS private key and certificate in firmware in Kiloview N30 2.02.246 allows malicious adversary to do a Mann-in-the-middle attack via the network</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9265 | API Authentication Bypass via Header Spoofing vulnerability in Kiloview NDI N30 Products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9265</link><description>A broken authorization vulnerability in Kiloview NDI N30 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to deactivate user verification, giving them access to state changing actions that should only be initiated by administratorsThis issue affects 

 Kiloview NDI N30

and was fixed in Firmware version later than  2.02.0246</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11665 | D-Link DAP-2695 Firmware Update rgbin fwupdater_main os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11665</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DAP-2695 2.00RC131. This affects the function fwupdater_main of the file rgbin of the component Firmware Update Handler. Performing manipulation results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0636 | Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability in Ericsson RAN Compute and Site Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0636</link><description>EMCLI contains a high severity vulnerability where improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command could be exploited leading to Arbitrary Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27258 | Ericsson Network Manager: escalation of privilege vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27258</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager (ENM) versions prior to ENM 25.1 GA contain a vulnerability, if exploited, can result in an escalation of privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27259 | Ericsson Network Manager: improper neutralization of user controlled input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27259</link><description>Ericsson Network Manager versions prior to ENM 25.2 GA contain a vulnerability that, if exploited, can exfiltrate limited data or redirect victims to other sites or domains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11664 | Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System search-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11664</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9698 | The Plus Addons for Elementor &amp;lt; 6.3.16 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9698</link><description>The Plus Addons for Elementor  WordPress plugin before 6.3.16 does not sanitize SVG file contents, which could allow users with minimum role access as Author to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11663 | Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System manage-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11663</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Beauty Parlor Management System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-services.php. This manipulation of the argument sername causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11662 | SourceCodester Best Salon Management System booking.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11662</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Best Salon Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /booking.php. The manipulation of the argument serv_id results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31995 | HCL Unica MaxAI Workbench is vulnerable to improper input validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31995</link><description>HCL Unica MaxAI Workbench is vulnerable to improper input validation.  This allows attackers to exploit vulnerabilities such as SQL Injection, XSS, or command injection, leading to unauthorized access or data breaches, etc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 05:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11661 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This affects an unknown part. Performing manipulation results in missing authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11660 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System uploadSllyabus.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11660</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /assets/uploadSllyabus.php. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31994 | HCL Unica Campaign is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31994</link><description>HCL Unica Campaign 12.1.10 is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) where an attacker injects malicious script into an HTTP request, which is then reflected unsafely in the server's immediate response to the victim's browser, executing the script as if it originated from the trusted website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31996 | Unprotected files are impacting HCL Unica Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31996</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is affected by unprotected files due to improper access controls.   These files may contain sensitive information such as private or system information that can be exploited by attackers to compromise the application, infrastructure, or users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 04:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11659 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System uploadNotes.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11659</link><description>A flaw has been found in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /assets/uploadNotes.php. This manipulation of the argument File causes unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11658 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System changeSllyabus.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11658</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. Affected is an unknown function of the file /assets/changeSllyabus.php. The manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11657 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System createNotice.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11657</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This impacts an unknown function of the file /assets/createNotice.php. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11656 | ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System editNotes.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11656</link><description>A weakness has been identified in ProjectsAndPrograms School Management System up to 6b6fae5426044f89c08d0dd101c7fa71f9042a59. This affects an unknown function of the file /assets/editNotes.php. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11655 | Total.js Flow SVG File unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11655</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Total.js Flow up to 673ef9144dd25d4f4fd4fdfda5af27f230198924. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component SVG File Handler. Performing manipulation results in unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11654 | yousaf530 Inferno Online Clothing Store log.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11654</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in yousaf530 Inferno Online Clothing Store up to 827dd42bfbe380e8de76fdc67958c24cf1246208. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /log.php. Such manipulation of the argument cemail/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11653 | UTT HiPER 2620G fNTP strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11653</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 2620G up to 3.1.4. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/fNTP. This manipulation of the argument NTPServerIP causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36087 | IBM Security Verify Access hard coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36087</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access 10.0.0 through 10.0.9, 11.0.0, IBM Verify Identity Access Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.9, and 11.0.0, under certain configurations, contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11652 | UTT 进取 518G formTaskEdit_ap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UTT 进取 518G up to V3v3.2.7-210919-161313. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/formTaskEdit_ap. The manipulation of the argument txtMin2 results in buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11651 | UTT 进取 518G formRemoteControl sub_4247AC buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11651</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in UTT 进取 518G up to V3v3.2.7-210919-161313. This vulnerability affects the function sub_4247AC of the file /goform/formRemoteControl. The manipulation of the argument Profile leads to buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11650 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Password shadow weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11650</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /etc/shadow of the component Password Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to use of weak hash. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11649 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Root Account hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11649</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Root Account Handler. Performing manipulation results in use of hard-coded password. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is described as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11648 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Interface URL TF_FQDN.json server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11648</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Impacted is an unknown function of the file TF_FQDN.json of the component GATT Interface URL Handler. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:16:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11647 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11647</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component GATT Service. This manipulation of the argument DeviceToken causes information disclosure. The attack is only possible within the local network. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11646 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini GATT Service access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11646</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component GATT Service. The manipulation results in improper access controls. The attack can only be performed from the local network. The exploit is now public and may be used. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11645 | Tomofun Furbo Mobile App Authentication Token sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11645</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tomofun Furbo Mobile App up to 7.57.0a on Android. This affects an unknown part of the component Authentication Token Handler. The manipulation leads to insecure storage of sensitive information. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11644 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini UART sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11644</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component UART Interface. Executing manipulation can lead to insecure storage of sensitive information. The physical device can be targeted for the attack. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11643 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini MQTT Client Certificate furbo_img hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11643</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /squashfs-root/furbo_img of the component MQTT Client Certificate. Performing manipulation results in hard-coded credentials. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11642 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11642</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected is an unknown function of the component Registration Handler. Such manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be executed directly on the physical device. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11641 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Trial Restriction access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11641</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This impacts an unknown function of the component Trial Restriction Handler. This manipulation causes improper access controls. It is feasible to perform the attack on the physical device. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:43:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11640 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Bluetooth Low Energy cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This affects an unknown function of the component Bluetooth Low Energy. The manipulation results in cleartext transmission of sensitive information. Access to the local network is required for this attack. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 18:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11639 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Debug Log S3 Bucket collect_logs.sh sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11639</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file collect_logs.sh of the component Debug Log S3 Bucket Handler. The manipulation leads to insecure storage of sensitive information. An attack has to be approached locally. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11638 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini Bluetooth denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11638</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Bluetooth Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to denial of service. The attacker needs to be present on the local network. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:17:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11637 | Tomofun Furbo 360 Audio race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11637</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. Impacted is an unknown function of the component Audio Handler. Performing manipulation results in race condition. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11636 | Tomofun Furbo 360 Account server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11636</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Account Handler. Such manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 15:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11635 | Tomofun Furbo 360 File Upload resource consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11635</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component File Upload. This manipulation causes resource consumption. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2138 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next data modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2138</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 

could allow an authenticated user on the network to delete comments from other users due to client-side enforcement of server-side security.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2139 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2139</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to delete reviews from other users due to client-side enforcement of server-side security.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2140 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2140</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to spoof email identity of the sender due to improper verification of source data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33096 | IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33096</link><description>IBM Engineering Requirements Management Doors Next 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service by uploading specially crafted files using uncontrolled recursion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11634 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini UART information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11634</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. This affects an unknown part of the component UART Interface. The manipulation results in information disclosure. An attack on the physical device is feasible. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 12:56:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11633 | Tomofun Furbo 360/Furbo Mini HTTP Traffic certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11633</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tomofun Furbo 360 and Furbo Mini. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component HTTP Traffic Handler. The manipulation leads to improper certificate validation. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The firmware versions determined to be affected are Furbo 360 up to FB0035_FW_036 and Furbo Mini up to MC0020_FW_074. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 12:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52615 | HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52615</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers.  This can lead to less secure browser default treatment for the policies controlled by these headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11631 | RainyGao DocSys deleteDoc.do path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11631</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Doc/deleteDoc.do. Executing manipulation of the argument path can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52614 | HCL Unica Platform is affected by a Cookie without HTTPOnly Flag Set vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52614</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is affected by a Cookie without HTTPOnly Flag Set vulnerability.  A malicious agent may be able to induce this event by feeding a user suitable links, either directly or via another web site.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 08:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31969 | HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured Content Security Policy (CSP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31969</link><description>HCL Unica Platform is impacted by misconfigured Content Security Policy (CSP).  These can result in malicious resources getting loaded and browsers may come across certain types of attacks, such as cross-site scripting and clickjacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11630 | RainyGao DocSys File Upload uploadDoc.do updateRealDoc path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11630</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. Affected is the function updateRealDoc of the file /Doc/uploadDoc.do of the component File Upload. Performing manipulation of the argument path results in path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11629 | RainyGao DocSys getUserList.do getUserList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11629</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RainyGao DocSys up to 2.02.36. This impacts the function getUserList of the file /Manage/getUserList.do. Such manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 07:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31992 | HCL MaxAI Assistant is susceptible to a HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31992</link><description>HCL Unica MaxAI Assistant is susceptible to a HTML injection vulnerability.  An attacker could insert special characters that are processed client-side in the context of the user's session.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 06:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11628 | jimit105 Project-Online-Shopping-Website Product Inventory delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11628</link><description>A flaw has been found in jimit105 Project-Online-Shopping-Website up to 7d892f442bd8a96dd242dbe2b9bd5ed641e13e64. This affects an unknown function of the file /delete.php of the component Product Inventory Handler. This manipulation of the argument product_code causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 05:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52616 | HCL Unica 12.1.10 is affected by an exposure of sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52616</link><description>HCL Unica 12.1.10 can expose sensitive system information.  An attacker could use this information to form an attack plan by leveraging known vulnerabilities in the application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 04:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31993 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to a potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31993</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to a potential Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). An attacker can exploit improper input validation by submitting maliciously crafted input to a target application running on a server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31997 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31997</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR).  An attacker can bypass authorization and access resources in the system directly, for example database records or files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31998 | HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to poor unhandled exceptions which exposes sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31998</link><description>HCL Unica Centralized Offer Management is vulnerable to poor unhandled exceptions which exposes sensitive information.  An attacker can exploit use this information to exploit known vulnerabilities launch targeted attacks, such as remote code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61884 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61884</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11615 | SourceCodester Best Salon Management System add_invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11615</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Best Salon Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /panel/add_invoice.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ServiceId results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 21:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11614 | SourceCodester Best Salon Management System edit-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11614</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester Best Salon Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /panel/edit-appointment.php. Such manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 20:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11613 | code-projects Simple Food Ordering System addcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument cname results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11612 | code-projects Simple Food Ordering System addproduct.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11612</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Simple Food Ordering System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /addproduct.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11611 | SourceCodester Simple Inventory System user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11611</link><description>A weakness has been identified in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /user.php. This manipulation of the argument uemail causes sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11610 | SourceCodester Simple Inventory System brand.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11610</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in SourceCodester Simple Inventory System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /brand.php. The manipulation of the argument editBrandName results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11609 | code-projects Hospital Management System express-session hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11609</link><description>A flaw has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is the function session of the component express-session. This manipulation of the argument secret with the input secret causes use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 17:43:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11608 | code-projects E-Banking System POST Parameter register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11608</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects E-Banking System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /register.php of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11607 | harry0703 MoneyPrinterTurbo API Endpoint music.py upload_music path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11607</link><description>A weakness has been identified in harry0703 MoneyPrinterTurbo up to 1.2.6. The impacted element is the function upload_music of the file app/controllers/v1/music.py of the component API Endpoint. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to path traversal. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 16:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11606 | iPynch Social Network Website Search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11606</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in iPynch Social Network Website up to b6933b6d7f82c84819abe458ccf0e59d61119541. The affected element is an unknown function of the component Search. Performing manipulation results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:15:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11605 | code-projects Client Details System update-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11605</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Client Details System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin/update-profile.php. Such manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11604 | projectworlds Online Ordering Food System all-orders.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11604</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in projectworlds Online Ordering Food System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /all-orders.php. This manipulation of the argument Status causes sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11603 | code-projects Simple Food Ordering System editproduct.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11603</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Food Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /editproduct.php. The manipulation of the argument Category results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11601 | SourceCodester Online Student Result System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11601</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester Online Student Result System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. Performing manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:17:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11600 | code-projects Simple Food Ordering System editcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11600</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Simple Food Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file editcategory.php. Such manipulation of the argument cname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11599 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11599</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /forgot-password.php. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:19:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11597 | code-projects E-Commerce Website product_add_qty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11597</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /pages/product_add_qty.php. The manipulation of the argument prod_id leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11596 | code-projects E-Commerce Website delete_order_details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11596</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects E-Commerce Website 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /pages/delete_order_details.php. Executing manipulation of the argument order_id can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10129 | WordPress Live Webcam Widget &amp;amp; Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10129</link><description>The WordPress Live Webcam Widget &amp; Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'webcam' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10167 | Stock History &amp;amp; Reports Manager for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10167</link><description>The Stock History &amp; Reports Manager for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'alg_wc_stock_snapshot_restocked shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10175 | WP Links Page &amp;lt;= 4.9.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10175</link><description>The WP Links Page plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10190 | WP Easy Toggles &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10190</link><description>The WP Easy Toggles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'toggles' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10375 | Web Accessibility By accessiBe &amp;lt;= 2.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10375</link><description>The Web Accessibility By accessiBe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10. This is due to missing nonce validation on multiple AJAX actions including accessibe_signup, accessibe_login, accessibe_license_trial, accessibe_modify_config, and accessibe_add_verification_page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings and create verification files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10376 | Course Redirects for Learndash Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10376</link><description>The Course Redirects for Learndash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.4. This is due to missing nonce validation when processing form submissions on the settings page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify plugin settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11595 | Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11595</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /admin-profile.php. Performing manipulation of the argument mobilenumber results in sql injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6439 | WooCommerce Designer Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.26 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6439</link><description>The WooCommerce Designer Pro plugin for WordPress, used by the Pricom - Printing Company &amp; Design Services WordPress theme, is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'wcdp_save_canvas_design_ajax' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.26. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete all files in an arbitrary directory on the server, which can lead to remote code execution, data loss, or site unavailability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7652 | Easy Plugin Stats &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7652</link><description>The Easy Plugin Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'eps' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8484 | Code Quality Control Tool &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure via Log Files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8484</link><description>The Code Quality Control Tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in version 0.1 through publicly exposed log files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view potentially sensitive information contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8593 | GSheetConnector For Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 1.3.27 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8593</link><description>The GSheetConnector For Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in versions less than, or equal to, 1.3.27. This is due to a missing capability check on the 'install_plugin' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above to install plugins on the target site and potentially achieve arbitrary code execution on the server under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8606 | GSheetConnector For Gravity Forms &amp;lt;= 1.3.23 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Plugin Activation/Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8606</link><description>The GSheetConnector For Gravity Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions less than, or equal to, 1.3.23. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the activate_plugin and deactivate_plugin functions. This makes it possible for attackers to trick authenticated administrators into activating or deactivating specified plugins via a forged request, such as clicking on a malicious link or visiting a compromised page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8682 | Newsup &amp;lt;= 5.0.10 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8682</link><description>The Newsup theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the newsup_admin_info_install_plugin() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install the ansar-import plugin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9621 | WidgetPack Comment System &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9621</link><description>The WidgetPack Comment System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the wpcmt_sync action in the wpcmt_request_handler function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger comment synchronization events via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9626 | Page Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9626</link><description>The Page Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the admin_process_widget_page_change function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify widget page block configurations via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9947 | Custom 404 Pro &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via `path` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9947</link><description>The Custom 404 Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘path’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9950 | Error Log Viewer by BestWebSoft &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9950</link><description>The Error Log Viewer by BestWebSoft plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 via the rrrlgvwr_get_file function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9975 | WP Scraper &amp;lt;= 5.8.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9975</link><description>The WP Scraper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.8.1 via the wp_scraper_extract_content function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services. On Cloud instances, this issue allows for metadata retrieving.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58289 | Vulnerability of improper exception handling in the print module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58289</link><description>Vulnerability of improper exception handling in the print module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58293 | Vulnerability of improper exception handling in the print module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58293</link><description>Vulnerability of improper exception handling in the print module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58301 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the device management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58301</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the device management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58300 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the device management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58300</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the device management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11594 | ywxbear PHP-Bookstore-Website-Example Quantity index.php improper validation of specified quantity in input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11594</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ywxbear PHP-Bookstore-Website-Example and PHP Basic BookStore Website up to 0e0b9f542f7a2d90a8d7f8c83caca69294e234e4. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component Quantity Handler. Such manipulation leads to improper validation of specified quantity in input. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58298 | Data processing error vulnerability in the package management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58298</link><description>Data processing error vulnerability in the package management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58299 | Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the storage management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58299</link><description>Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the storage management module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58297 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the sensor service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58297</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the sensor service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58287 | Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58287</link><description>Use After Free (UAF) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58288 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58288</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58290 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58290</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58291 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58291</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58292 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58292</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58295 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the development framework module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58295</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the development framework module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58286 | Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58286</link><description>Denial of service (DoS) vulnerability in the office service. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:55:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11167 | CM Registration – Tailored tool for seamless login and invitation-based registrations &amp;lt;= 2.5.6 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11167</link><description>The CM Registration – Tailored tool for seamless login and invitation-based registrations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Open Redirect in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.6. This is due to insufficient validation on the redirect url supplied via the 'redirect_url' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11254 | Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote &amp;amp; Sell with PayPal and Stripe &amp;lt;= 27.0.3 - Unauthenticated CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11254</link><description>The Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote &amp; Sell with PayPal and Stripe plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV Injection in all versions up to, and including, 27.0.3 via gallery submissions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to embed untrusted input into exported CSV files, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11518 | WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.0.3 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Wishlist Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11518</link><description>The WPC Smart Wishlist for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.3 via several wishlist AJAX functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key that is exposed when wishlists are shared. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to empty and add to other user's wishlists, if they have access to the key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6553 | Ovatheme Events Manager &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6553</link><description>The Ovatheme Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the process_checkout() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10048 | My Auctions Allegro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.31 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10048</link><description>The My auctions allegro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.31 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10185 | NEX-Forms – Ultimate Forms Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 9.1.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10185</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Forms Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the  'orderby' parameter in the action nf_load_form_entries in all versions up to, and including, 9.1.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This may be exploitable by lower-level users if access is granted by a site administrator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11197 | Draft List &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11197</link><description>The Draft List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'drafts' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11533 | WP Freeio &amp;lt;= 1.2.21 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11533</link><description>The WP Freeio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.21. This is due to the process_register() function not restricting what user roles a user can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to supply the 'administrator' role during registration and gain administrator access to the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9196 | Trinity Audio &amp;lt;= 5.21.0 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9196</link><description>The Trinity Audio – Text to Speech AI audio player to convert content into audio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.21.0 via the ~/admin/inc/phpinfo.php file that gets created on install. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including configuration data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9496 | Enable Media Replace &amp;lt;= 4.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via file_modified Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9496</link><description>The Enable Media Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's file_modified shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11593 | CodeAstro Gym Management System delete-equipment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11593</link><description>A flaw has been found in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/actions/delete-equipment.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11592 | CodeAstro Gym Management System edit-equipmentform.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11592</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-equipmentform.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11591 | CodeAstro Gym Management System delete-member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11591</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/actions/delete-member.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 05:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58284 | Permission control vulnerability in the network module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58284</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the network module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58285 | Permission control vulnerability in the media module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58285</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the media module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 04:17:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58278 | Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the Gallery app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58278</link><description>Identity authentication bypass vulnerability in the Gallery app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58282 | Permission control vulnerability in the camera module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58282</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the camera module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58283 | Permission control vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58283</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the Wi-Fi module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58277 | Permission verification bypass vulnerability in the Camera app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58277</link><description>Permission verification bypass vulnerability in the Camera app. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11380 | Everest Backup &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11380</link><description>The Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'everest_process_status' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve back-up file locations that can be subsequently accessed and downloaded. This does require a back-up to be running in order for an attacker to retrieve the back-up location.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9560 | Colibri Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.0.334 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via colibri_newsletter Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9560</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's colibri_newsletter shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.334 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54654 | Permission control vulnerability in the Gallery module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54654</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the Gallery module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11590 | CodeAstro Gym Management System equipment-entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11590</link><description>A weakness has been identified in CodeAstro Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/equipment-entry.php. Executing manipulation of the argument ename can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31717 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31717</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31718 | In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no addit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31718</link><description>In modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 01:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>