<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-56312 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboard name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to injec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56312</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project Dashboard name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the name field of a Project Dashboard. When a user clicks on the project Dashboard name, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56313 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar feature of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56313</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Calendar feature of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the Notes field of a calendar event. When the event is viewed, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56314 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56314</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Project name of REDCap through 15.0.0 allows authenticated users to inject malicious scripts into the name field of a Project. When a user clicks on the project name to access it, the crafted payload is executed, potentially enabling the execution of arbitrary web scripts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56310 | REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Project Dashboards name, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56310</link><description>REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Project Dashboards name, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An attacker can exploit this by luring users into clicking on a Project Dashboards name that contains the malicious payload, which triggers a logout request and terminates their session. This vulnerability stems from the absence of CSRF protections on the logout functionality, allowing malicious actions to be executed without user consent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56311 | REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Notes section of calendar events, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56311</link><description>REDCap through 15.0.0 has a security flaw in the Notes section of calendar events, exposing users to a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) attack. An attacker can exploit this by luring users into accessing a calendar event's notes, which triggers a logout request and terminates their session. This vulnerability stems from the absence of CSRF protections on the logout functionality, allowing malicious actions to be executed without user consent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12895 | TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt checkflag.php console_log sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12895</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt up to 963e0e0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function console_log of the file TreasureHunt/checkflag.php. The manipulation of the argument problema leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier of the patch is 8bcc649abc35b7734951be084bb522a532faac4e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 14:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12894 | TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt acesso.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12894</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TreasureHuntGame TreasureHunt up to 963e0e0. Affected is an unknown function of the file TreasureHunt/acesso.php. The manipulation of the argument usuario leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 8bcc649abc35b7734951be084bb522a532faac4e. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 12:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12893 | Portabilis i-Educar Tipo de Usuário Page 2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12893</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar up to 2.9. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /usuarios/tipos/2 of the component Tipo de Usuário Page. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 08:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12892 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System sign.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12892</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sign.php?q=account.php. The manipulation of the argument name/gender/college leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 07:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12891 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12891</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /account.php?q=quiz&amp;amp;step=2. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 06:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12890 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12890</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /update.php?q=quiz&amp;amp;step=2. The manipulation of the argument eid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 06:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11852 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp;amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.12 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11852</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the get_layouts() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to obtain a detailed listing of layout templates.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 02:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12884 | Codezips E-Commerce Website login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12884</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips E-Commerce Website 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 14:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51463 | IBM i server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51463</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 

is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51464 | IBM i improper HTTP header neutralization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51464</link><description>IBM i 7.3, 7.4, and 7.5 is vulnerable to bypassing Navigator for i interface restrictions.  By sending a specially crafted request, an authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability to remotely perform operations that the user is not allowed to perform when using Navigator for i.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12883 | code-projects Job Recruitment _email.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12883</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /_email.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 13:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12875 | Easy Digital Downloads &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12875</link><description>The Easy Digital Downloads – eCommerce Payments and Subscriptions made easy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 via the file download functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 11:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10453 | Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.25.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Typography Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10453</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Typography Settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11688 | LaTeX2HTML &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11688</link><description>The LaTeX2HTML plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ver' or 'date' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11722 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.25.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11722</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This requires an unauthenticated user to have been given permission to view form submissions, and the form submission shortcode be added to a page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12408 | WP on AWS &amp;lt;= 5.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12408</link><description>The WP on AWS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via $_POST data in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12558 | WP BASE Booking of Appointments, Services and Events &amp;lt;= 4.9.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Exposure via app_export_db</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12558</link><description>The WP BASE Booking of Appointments, Services and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_db function in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose sensitive information from the database, such as the hashed administrator password.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12591 | MagicPost &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wb_share_social Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12591</link><description>The MagicPost plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wb_share_social shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 09:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10797 | Full Screen Menu for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10797</link><description>The Full Screen Menu for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 via the  Full Screen Menu Elementor Widget due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11808 | Pingmeter Uptime Monitoring &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11808</link><description>The Pingmeter Uptime Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the '_wpnonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12588 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Staff Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12588</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Staff widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9545 | Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme &amp;lt;= 2.16.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via aux_contact_box and aux_gmaps Shortcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9545</link><description>The Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's aux_contact_box and aux_gmaps shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.16.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 08:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11196 | Multi-column Tag Map &amp;lt;= 17.0.33 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via mctagmap Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11196</link><description>The Multi-column Tag Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's mctagmap shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 17.0.33 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11287 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8001 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11287</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.8001. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11682 | G Web Pro Store Locator &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11682</link><description>The G Web Pro Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'q' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11938 | One Click Upsell Funnel for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wps_wocuf_pro_yes Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11938</link><description>The One Click Upsell Funnel for WooCommerce –  Funnel Builder for WordPress, Create WooCommerce Upsell, Post-Purchase Upsell &amp; Cross Sell Offers that Boost Sales &amp; Increase Profits with Sales Funnel Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wps_wocuf_pro_yes shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11975 | Reactflow Visitor Recording and Heatmaps &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11975</link><description>The Reactflow Visitor Recording and Heatmaps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation affecting the _wpnonce parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts  via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12066 | SMSA Shipping(official) &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12066</link><description>The SMSA Shipping(official) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the smsa_delete_label() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12262 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8001 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;step&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12262</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'step' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.8001 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12635 | WP Docs &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Time-Based SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;dir_id&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12635</link><description>The WP Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the 'dir_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12697 | real.Kit &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12697</link><description>The real.Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12721 | Custom Product Tabs For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12721</link><description>The Custom Product Tabs For WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'wb_custom_tabs' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12771 | eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.3.43 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12771</link><description>The eCommerce Product Catalog Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.43. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'customer_panel_password_reset' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the password of any administrator or customer account via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 07:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11607 | GTPayment Donations &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11607</link><description>The GTPayment Donations WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11977 | kk Star Ratings – Rate Post &amp;amp; Collect User Feedbacks &amp;lt;= 5.4.10 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11977</link><description>The The kk Star Ratings – Rate Post &amp; Collect User Feedbacks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.10. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 05:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12846 | Emlog Pro link.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12846</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/link.php. The manipulation of the argument siteurl/icon leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 05:09:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11349 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 5.1.6 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11349</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.6. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them through the sb_login_user_with_otp_fun() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as arbitrary users, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 04:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31280 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31280</link><description>An AirVantage online Warranty Checker tool vulnerability could allow an attacker to 
perform bulk enumeration of IMEI and Serial Numbers pairs. The AirVantage Warranty Checker is updated to no longer return the IMEI and Serial 
Number in addition to the warranty status when the Serial Number or IMEI is used to look up 
warranty status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 23:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31279 | Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31279</link><description>The AirVantage platform is vulnerable to an unauthorized attacker registering previously unregistered 
devices on the AirVantage platform when the owner has not disabled the AirVantage Management 
Service on the devices or registered the device. This could enable an attacker to configure, manage, 
and execute AT commands on an unsuspecting user’s devices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 23:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11811 | Feedify – Web Push Notifications &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11811</link><description>The Feedify – Web Push Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'platform', 'phone', 'email', and 'store_url' parameters. in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 22:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-40959 | A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in MONITORAPP Application Insight Web Application Firewall (AIWAF) &lt;= 4.1.6 and &lt;=5.0 was ide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-40959</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in MONITORAPP Application Insight Web Application Firewall (AIWAF) &lt;= 4.1.6 and &lt;=5.0 was identified on the subpage `/process_management/process_status.xhr.php`. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts that execute in the context of the victim's session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 22:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-13712 | MGOS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-13712</link><description>A command injection is possible through the user interface, allowing arbitrary command execution as 
the root user. oMG2000 running MGOS 3.15.1 or earlier is affected. 

MG90 running MGOS 4.2.1 or earlier is affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12845 | Emlog Pro common.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12845</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library /include/lib/common.php. The manipulation of the argument msg leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12844 | Emlog Pro store.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12844</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/store.php. The manipulation of the argument tag leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55509 | SQL injection vulnerability in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55509</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via the id parameter of the delete.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:58:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12843 | Emlog Pro plugin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/plugin.php. The manipulation of the argument filter leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56357 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability through custom widget URLs and form redirect URLs in grist-core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56357</link><description>grist-core is a spreadsheet hosting server. A user visiting a malicious document or submitting a malicious form could have their account compromised, because it was possible to use the `javascript:` scheme with custom widget URLs and form redirect URLs. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should avoid visiting documents or forms prepared by people they do not trust.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56358 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability through svg attachment previews in grist-core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56358</link><description>grist-core is a spreadsheet hosting server. A user visiting a malicious document and previewing an attachment could have their account compromised, because JavaScript in an SVG file would be evaluated in the context of their current page. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should avoid previewing attachments in documents prepared by people they do not trust.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56359 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability through HyperLink cells in grist-core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56359</link><description>grist-core is a spreadsheet hosting server. A user visiting a malicious document and clicking on a link in a HyperLink cell using a control modifier (meaning for example Ctrl+click) could have their account compromised, since the link could use the javascript: scheme and be evaluated in the context of their current page. This issue has been patched in version 1.3.2. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should avoid clicking on HyperLink cell links using a control modifier in documents prepared by people they do not trust.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40875 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console prior to 13.52</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40875</link><description>There is a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the
management console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.52. Attackers
with system administrator permissions can interfere with another system
administrator’s use of the management console when the second administrator logs
in. Attack complexity is high, attack requirements are present, privileges
required are high, user interaction required is none. The impact to
confidentiality is none, the impact to availability is low, and the impact to
system integrity is high.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56334 | Command injection vulnerability in getWindowsIEEE8021x (SSID) function in systeminformation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56334</link><description>systeminformation is a System and OS information library for node.js. In affected versions SSIDs are not sanitized when before they are passed as a parameter to cmd.exe in the `getWindowsIEEE8021x` function. This means that malicious content in the SSID can be executed as OS commands. This vulnerability may enable an attacker, depending on how the package is used, to perform remote code execution or local privilege escalation. This issue has been addressed in version 5.23.7 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56335 | Privilege escalation allows organization groups to be updated/deleted if their UUID is known in vaultwarden</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56335</link><description>vaultwarden is an unofficial Bitwarden compatible server written in Rust, formerly known as bitwarden_rs. In affected versions an attacker is capable of updating or deleting groups from an organization given a few conditions: 1. The attacker has a user account in the server. 2. The attacker's account has admin or owner permissions in an unrelated organization. 3. The attacker knows the target organization's UUID and the target group's UUID. Note that this vulnerability is related to group functionality and as such is only applicable for servers who have enabled the `ORG_GROUPS_ENABLED` setting, which is disabled by default. This attack can lead to different situations: 1. Denial of service, the attacker can limit users from accessing the organization's data by removing their membership from the group. 2. Privilege escalation, if the attacker is part of the victim organization, they can escalate their own privileges by joining a group they wouldn't normally have access to. For attackers that aren't part of the organization, this shouldn't lead to any possible plain-text data exfiltration as all the data is encrypted client side. This vulnerability is patched in Vaultwarden `1.32.7`, and users are recommended to update as soon as possible. If it's not possible to update to `1.32.7`,  some possible workarounds are: 1. Disabling `ORG_GROUPS_ENABLED`, which would disable groups functionality on the server. 2. Disabling `SIGNUPS_ALLOWED`, which would not allow an attacker to create new accounts on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56330 | Session VNC may be accessed by other sessions on the same host in stardust</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56330</link><description>Stardust is a platform for streaming isolated desktop containers. With this exploit, inter container communication (ICC) is not disabled. This would allow users within a container to access another containers agent, therefore compromising access.The problem has been patched in any Stardust build past 12/20/24. Users are advised to upgrade. Users may also manually disable ICC if they are unable to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12842 | Emlog Pro user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56329 | Account Takeover Vulnerability in Social Account Linking in joelbutcher/socialstream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56329</link><description>Socialstream is a third-party package for Laravel Jetstream. It replaces the published authentication and profile scaffolding provided by Laravel Jetstream, with scaffolding that has support for Laravel Socialite. When linking a social account to an already authenticated user, the lack of a confirmation step introduces a security risk. This is exacerbated if -&gt;stateless() is used in the Socialite configuration, bypassing state verification and making the exploit easier. Developers should ensure that users explicitly confirm account linking and avoid configurations that skip critical security checks. Socialstream v6.2 introduces a new custom route that requires a user to "Confirm" or "Deny" a request to link a social account. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56331 | Local File Inclusion (LFI) via Improper URL Handling in uptime-kuma&amp;#x27;s `Real-Browser` monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56331</link><description>Uptime Kuma is an open source, self-hosted monitoring tool. An **Improper URL Handling Vulnerability** allows an attacker to access sensitive local files on the server by exploiting the `file:///` protocol. This vulnerability is triggered via the **"real-browser"** request type, which takes a screenshot of the URL provided by the attacker. By supplying local file paths, such as `file:///etc/passwd`, an attacker can read sensitive data from the server. This vulnerability arises because the system does not properly validate or sanitize the user input for the URL field. Specifically: 1. The URL input (`&lt;input class="form-control" id="url" pattern="https?://.+" required="" type="url" /&gt;`) allows users to input arbitrary file paths, including those using the `file:///` protocol, without server-side validation. 2. The server then uses the user-provided URL to make a request, passing it to a browser instance that performs the "real-browser" request, which takes a screenshot of the content at the given URL. If a local file path is entered (e.g., `file:///etc/passwd`), the browser fetches and captures the file’s content. Since the user input is not validated, an attacker can manipulate the URL to request local files (e.g., `file:///etc/passwd`), and the system will capture a screenshot of the file's content, potentially exposing sensitive data. Any **authenticated user** who can submit a URL in "real-browser" mode is at risk of exposing sensitive data through screenshots of these files. This issue has been addressed in version 1.23.16 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56333 | Remote code execution in onyxia-api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56333</link><description>Onyxia is a web app that aims at being the glue between multiple open source backend technologies to provide a state of art working environment for data scientists. This critical vulnerability allows authenticated users to remotely execute code within the Onyxia-API, leading to potential consequences such as unauthorized access to other user environments and denial of service attacks. This issue has been patched in api versions 4.2.0, 3.1.1, and 2.8.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12867 | Server-Side Request Forgery in Arctic Hub URL Mapper allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to exfiltrate and modify configurations and data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12867</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery in URL Mapper in Arctic Security's Arctic Hub versions 3.0.1764-5.6.1877 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to exfiltrate and modify configurations and data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55341 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Piranha CMS 11.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web bro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55341</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Piranha CMS 11.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the web browser of a user, by creating a page via the /manager/pages and then adding a markdown content with the XSS payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37758 | Improper access control in the endpoint /RoleMenuMapping/AddRoleMenu of Digiteam v4.21.0.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37758</link><description>Improper access control in the endpoint /RoleMenuMapping/AddRoleMenu of Digiteam v4.21.0.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55342 | A file upload functionality in Piranha CMS 11.1 allows authenticated remote attackers to upload a crafted PDF file to /manager/media. This P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55342</link><description>A file upload functionality in Piranha CMS 11.1 allows authenticated remote attackers to upload a crafted PDF file to /manager/media. This PDF can contain malicious JavaScript code, which is executed when a victim user opens or interacts with the PDF in their web browser, leading to a XSS vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 18:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12841 | Emlog Pro tag.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12841</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/tag.php. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 18:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12677 | Delta Electronics DTM Soft Deserialization of Untrusted Data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12677</link><description>Delta Electronics DTM Soft deserializes objects, which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 16:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10385 | Stored XSS in DirectAdmin Evo Skin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10385</link><description>Ticket management system in DirectAdmin Evolution Skin is vulnerable to XSS (Cross-site Scripting), which allows a low-privileged user to inject and store malicious JavaScript code.
If an admin views the ticket, the script might perform actions with their privileges, including command execution. 
This issue has been fixed in version 1.668 of DirectAdmin Evolution Skin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12840 | Http proxies: satellite: service side request forgery in http proxies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12840</link><description>A server-side request forgery exists in Satellite. When a PUT HTTP request is made to /http_proxies/test_connection, when supplied with the http_proxies variable set to localhost, the attacker can fetch the localhost banner.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55470 | Oqtane Framework 6.0.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. By manipulating the entityid parameter, attackers can bypass passcode vali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55470</link><description>Oqtane Framework 6.0.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. By manipulating the entityid parameter, attackers can bypass passcode validation and successfully log into the application or access restricted data without proper authorization. The lack of server-side validation exacerbates the issue, as the application relies on client-side information for authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56337 | Apache Tomcat: RCE due to TOCTOU issue in JSP compilation - CVE-2024-50379 mitigation was incomplete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56337</link><description>Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition vulnerability in Apache Tomcat.

This issue affects Apache Tomcat: from 11.0.0-M1 through 11.0.1, from 10.1.0-M1 through 10.1.33, from 9.0.0.M1 through 9.0.97.

The mitigation for CVE-2024-50379 was incomplete.

Users running Tomcat on a case insensitive file system with the default servlet write enabled (readonly initialisation 
parameter set to the non-default value of false) may need additional configuration to fully mitigate CVE-2024-50379 depending on which version of Java they are using with Tomcat:
- running on Java 8 or Java 11: the system property sun.io.useCanonCaches must be explicitly set to false (it defaults to true)
- running on Java 17: the system property sun.io.useCanonCaches, if set, must be set to false (it defaults to false)
- running on Java 21 onwards: no further configuration is required (the system property and the problematic cache have been removed)

Tomcat 11.0.3, 10.1.35 and 9.0.99 onwards will include checks that sun.io.useCanonCaches is set appropriately before allowing the default servlet to be write enabled on a case insensitive file system. Tomcat will also set sun.io.useCanonCaches to false by default where it can.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55471 | Oqtane Framework is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Oqtane.Controllers.UserController. This allows unauthorized use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55471</link><description>Oqtane Framework is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) in Oqtane.Controllers.UserController. This allows unauthorized users to access sensitive information of other users by manipulating the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55186 | An IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) vulnerability exists in oqtane Framework 6.0.0, allowing a logged-in user to access inbox message...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55186</link><description>An IDOR (Insecure Direct Object Reference) vulnerability exists in oqtane Framework 6.0.0, allowing a logged-in user to access inbox messages of other users by manipulating the notification ID in the request URL. By changing the notification ID, an attacker can view sensitive mail details belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56348 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 improper access control allowed viewing details of unauthorized agents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56348</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 improper access control allowed viewing details of unauthorized agents</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56349 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 improper access control allowed unauthorized users to modify build logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56349</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 improper access control allowed unauthorized users to modify build logs</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56350 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 build credentials allowed unauthorized viewing of projects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56350</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 build credentials allowed unauthorized viewing of projects</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56351 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 access tokens were not revoked after removing user roles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56351</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 access tokens were not revoked after removing user roles</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56352 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 stored XSS was possible via image name on the agent details page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56352</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 stored XSS was possible via image name on the agent details page</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56353 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 backup file exposed user credentials and session cookies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56353</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 backup file exposed user credentials and session cookies</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56354 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 password field value were accessible to users with view settings permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56354</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 password field value were accessible to users with view settings permission</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56355 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 missing Content-Type header in RemoteBuildLogController response could lead to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56355</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 missing Content-Type header in RemoteBuildLogController response could lead to XSS</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56356 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 insecure XMLParser configuration could lead to potential XXE attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56356</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.12 insecure XMLParser configuration could lead to potential XXE attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28767 | IBM Security Directory Integrator command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28767</link><description>IBM Security Directory Integrator 7.2.0 through 7.2.0.13 and 10.0.0 through 10.0.3 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40695 | IBM Cognos Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40695</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 FP4 and 

12.0.0 through 12.0.4



could be vulnerable to malicious file upload by not validating the content of the file uploaded to the web interface. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system, and it can be sent to victim for performing further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51466 | IBM Cognos Analytics expression language injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51466</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0 through 11.2.4 FP4 and 

12.0.0 through 12.0.4

is vulnerable to an Expression Language (EL) Injection vulnerability. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information, consume memory resources, and/or cause the server to crash when using a specially crafted EL statement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12014 | Path Traversal and IDOR Vulnerabilities in eSignaViewer Allow Unauthorized File Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12014</link><description>Path Traversal and Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerabilities in the eSignaViewer component in eSigna product versions 1.0 to 1.5 on all platforms allow an unauthenticated attacker to access arbitrary files in the document system via manipulation of file paths and object identifiers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 13:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7726 | Arbitrary Code execution via exposed JTAG port in Kioxia CM6, PM6, PM7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7726</link><description>There exists an unauthenticated accessible JTAG port on the Kioxia PM6, PM7 and CM6 devices - On the Kioxia CM6, PM6 and PM7 disk drives it was discovered that the 2 main CPU cores of the SoC can be accessed via an open JTAG debug port that is exposed on the drive’s circuit board. Due to the wide cutout of the enclosures, the JTAG port can be accessed without having to open the disk enclosure. Utilizing the JTAG debug port, an attacker with (temporary) physical access can get full access to the firmware and memory on the 2 main CPU cores within the drive including the execution of arbitrary code, the modification of firmware execution flow and data or bypassing the firmware signature verification during boot-up.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11297 | Page Restriction WordPress (WP) – Protect WP Pages/Post &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11297</link><description>The Page Restriction WordPress (WP) – Protect WP Pages/Post plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11331 | isee-products-extractor &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 -  Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11331</link><description>The استخراج محصولات ووکامرس برای آیسی plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg &amp; remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11411 | Spotlightr &amp;lt;= 0.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11411</link><description>The Spotlightr plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spotlightr-v' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11774 | Outdooractive Embed &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11774</link><description>The Outdooractive Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'list2go' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11775 | Particle Background &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11775</link><description>The Particle Background plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'particleground' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11783 | Financial Calculator &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11783</link><description>The Financial Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'finance_calculator' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11784 | Sell Tickets Online – TicketSource Ticket Shop for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11784</link><description>The Sell Tickets Online – TicketSource Ticket Shop for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ticketshop' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11806 | PKT1 Centro de envios &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11806</link><description>The PKT1 Centro de envios plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'success' and 'error' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11812 | Wtyczka SeoPilot dla WP &amp;lt;= 3.3.091 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11812</link><description>The Wtyczka SeoPilot dla WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.091. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the SeoPilot_Admin_Options() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11878 | Category Post Slider &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11878</link><description>The Category Post Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'category-post-slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11893 | Spoki – Chat Buttons and WooCommerce Notifications &amp;lt;= 2.15.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11893</link><description>The Spoki – Chat Buttons and WooCommerce Notifications plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spoki_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12506 | NACC WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12506</link><description>The NACC WordPress Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'nacc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12509 | Embed Twine &amp;lt;= 0.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12509</link><description>The Embed Twine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'embed_twine' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12571 | Store Locator &amp;lt;= 3.98.10 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12571</link><description>The Store Locator for WordPress with Google Maps – LotsOfLocales plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in version 3.98.9 via the 'sl_engine' parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9503 | Maintenance &amp;amp; Coming Soon Redirect Animation &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Missing Authorization to Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9503</link><description>The Maintenance &amp; Coming Soon Redirect Animation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wploti_add_whitelisted_roles_option',  'wploti_remove_whitelisted_roles_option', 'wploti_add_whitelisted_users_option', 'wploti_remove_whitelisted_users_option', and 'wploti_uploaded_animation_save_option' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify certain plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9619 | WP SHAPES &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9619</link><description>The WP SHAPES plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 07:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10555 | MaxButtons &amp;lt; 9.8.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Button Width</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10555</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons WordPress plugin before 9.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 06:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10706 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.3.03 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10706</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.3.03 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 06:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11108 | Serious Slider &amp;lt; 1.2.7 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11108</link><description>The Serious Slider WordPress plugin before 1.2.7 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 06:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8968 | MaxButtons &amp;lt; 9.8.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Text Color</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8968</link><description>The WordPress Button Plugin MaxButtons WordPress plugin before 9.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 06:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5955 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix ePolicy Orchestrator prior to ePO 5.10 Service Pack 1 Update 3 allows a remote authenticated a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5955</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trellix ePolicy Orchestrator prior to ePO 5.10 Service Pack 1 Update 3 allows a remote authenticated attacker to craft requests causing arbitrary content to be injected into the response when accessing the epolicy Orchestrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 05:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21549 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.3 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21549</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.3 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through the setUrl method. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by utilizing view-source:file://, which allows for arbitrary file reading on a local file.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is a bypass of the fix for [CVE-2024-21544](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-PHP-SPATIEBROWSERSHOT-8496745).</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 05:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44195 | A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44195</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44211 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44211</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of symlinks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44223 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An attacker with physical access to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44223</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An attacker with physical access to a Mac may be able to view protected content from the Login Window.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44231 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A person with physical access to a Ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44231</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A person with physical access to a Mac may be able to bypass Login Window during a software update.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44292 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44292</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44293 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A user may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44293</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. A user may be able to view sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44298 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44298</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.1. An app may be able to access information about a user's contacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 04:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42867 | This issue was addressed with improved validation of the process entitlement and Team ID. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.9. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42867</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved validation of the process entitlement and Team ID. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.9. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 03:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11776 | PCRecruiter Extensions &amp;lt;= 1.4.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11776</link><description>The PCRecruiter Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'PCRecruiter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32203 | There is a command injection vulnerability in Huawei terminal printer product. Successful exploitation could result in the highest privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32203</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in Huawei terminal printer product. Successful exploitation could result in the highest privileges of the printer. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-51773)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32203.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32204 | There is an improper input verification vulnerability in Huawei printer product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32204</link><description>There is an improper input verification vulnerability in Huawei printer product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause service abnormal. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-87185)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32204.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34159 | Huawei printers have an input verification vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause device service exceptions....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34159</link><description>Huawei printers have an input verification vulnerability. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause device service exceptions. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-80078)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-34159.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-9250 | There is an insufficient authentication vulnerability in some Huawei smart phone. An unauthenticated, local attacker can crafts software pac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-9250</link><description>There is an insufficient authentication vulnerability in some Huawei smart phone. An unauthenticated, local attacker can crafts software package to exploit this vulnerability. Due to insufficient verification, successful exploitation may impact the service. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2019-12302)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2020-9250.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-32144 | There is an insufficient input verification vulnerability in Huawei product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-32144</link><description>There is an insufficient input verification vulnerability in Huawei product. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to service abnormal. (Vulnerability ID: HWPSIRT-2022-76192)

This vulnerability has been assigned a Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) ID: CVE-2022-32144.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12678 | Nomad Allocations Vulnerable To Privilege Escalation Within A Namespace Using Unredacted Workload Identity Tokens</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12678</link><description>Nomad Community and Nomad Enterprise ("Nomad") allocations are vulnerable to privilege escalation within a namespace through unredacted workload identity tokens. This vulnerability, identified as CVE-2024-12678, is fixed in Nomad Community Edition 1.9.4 and Nomad Enterprise 1.9.4, 1.8.8, and 1.7.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 02:07:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12829 | Arista NG Firewall ExecManagerImpl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12829</link><description>Arista NG Firewall ExecManagerImpl Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ExecManagerImpl class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-24015.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12830 | Arista NG Firewall custom_handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12830</link><description>Arista NG Firewall custom_handler Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the custom_handler method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-24019.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12831 | Arista NG Firewall uvm_login Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12831</link><description>Arista NG Firewall uvm_login Incorrect Authorization Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the uvm_login module. The issue results from incorrect authorization. An attacker can leverage this to escalate privileges to resources normally protected from the user. Was ZDI-CAN-24324.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12832 | Arista NG Firewall ReportEntry SQL Injection Arbitrary File Read and Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12832</link><description>Arista NG Firewall ReportEntry SQL Injection Arbitrary File Read and Write Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files and disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Arista NG Firewall. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the ReportEntry class. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the www-data user. Was ZDI-CAN-24325.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54538 | A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54538</link><description>A denial-of-service issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in visionOS 2.1, iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1, iOS 17.7.1 and iPadOS 17.7.1, tvOS 18.1, macOS Sonoma 14.7.1, watchOS 11.1, macOS Ventura 13.7.1. A remote attacker may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>