<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-56328 | HTMLi(XSS without CSP) via Onebox urls in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56328</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. An attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users' browsers by posting a maliciously crafted onebox url. This issue only affects sites with CSP disabled. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should enable CSP, disable inline Oneboxes globally, or allow specific domains for Oneboxing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22601 | Client Side Path Traversal using activate account route in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22601</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can trick a target user to make changes to their own username via carefully crafted link using the `activate-account` route. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22602 | Stored DOM-based XSS (without CSP) via video placeholders in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22602</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users' browsers by posting a malicious video placeholder html element. This issue only affects sites with CSP disabled. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should enable CSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:58:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23023 | Anonymous cache poisoning via request headers in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23023</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. In affected versions an attacker can carefully craft a request with the right request headers to poison the anonymous cache (for example, the cache may have a response with missing  preloaded data). This issue only affects anonymous visitors of the site. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may disable anonymous cache by setting the `DISCOURSE_DISABLE_ANON_CACHE` environment variable to a non-empty value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35138 | IBM Security Verify Access cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35138</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 is vulnerable to cross-site request forgery which could allow an attacker to execute malicious and unauthorized actions transmitted from a user that the website trusts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43187 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43187</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 transmits sensitive or security-critical data in cleartext in a communication channel that can be sniffed by unauthorized actors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45657 | IBM Security Verify Access incorrect privilege assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45657</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a local privileged user to perform unauthorized actions due to incorrect permissions assignment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40700 | IBM Security Verify Access cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40700</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45658 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45658</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0509 | Signing Checks Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0509</link><description>A security issue was found in Sparkle before version 2.64. An attacker can replace an existing signed update with another payload, bypassing Sparkle’s (Ed)DSA signing checks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0630 | Western Telematic Inc NPS Series, DSM Series, CPM Series External Control of File Name or Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0630</link><description>Multiple Western Telematic (WTI) products contain a web interface that is vulnerable to a local file inclusion attack (LFI), where any authenticated user has privileged access to files on the device's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0960 | AutomationDirect C-more EA9 HMI Classic Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0960</link><description>AutomationDirect C-more EA9 HMI contains a function with bounds checks that can be skipped, which could result in an attacker abusing the function to cause a denial-of-service condition or achieving remote code execution on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24963 | Browser mode serves arbitrary files in vitest</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24963</link><description>Vitest is a testing framework powered by Vite. The `__screenshot-error` handler on the browser mode HTTP server that responds any file on the file system. Especially if the server is exposed on the network by `browser.api.host: true`, an attacker can send a request to that handler from remote to get the content of arbitrary files.This `__screenshot-error` handler on the browser mode HTTP server responds any file on the file system. This code was added by commit `2d62051`. Users explicitly exposing the browser mode server to the network by `browser.api.host: true` may get any files exposed. This issue has been addressed in versions 2.1.9 and 3.0.4. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24964 | Remote Code Execution when accessing a malicious website while Vitest API server is listening</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24964</link><description>Vitest is a testing framework powered by Vite. Affected versions are subject to arbitrary remote Code Execution when accessing a malicious website while Vitest API server is listening by Cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) attacks. When `api` option is enabled (Vitest UI enables it), Vitest starts a WebSocket server. This WebSocket server did not check Origin header and did not have any authorization mechanism and was vulnerable to CSWSH attacks. This WebSocket server has `saveTestFile` API that can edit a test file and `rerun` API that can rerun the tests. An attacker can execute arbitrary code by injecting a code in a test file by the `saveTestFile` API and then running that file by calling the `rerun` API. This vulnerability can result in remote code execution for users that are using Vitest serve API. This issue has been patched in versions 1.6.1, 2.1.9 and 3.0.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24966 | HTML Injection in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24966</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. HTML Injection occurs when an application improperly validates or sanitizes user inputs, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary HTML code. In this scenario, the vulnerability exists in the "Add Target" functionality of the application, where the Target Organization and Target Description fields accept HTML payloads. The injected HTML is rendered and executed in the target area, potentially leading to malicious actions. Exploitation of HTML Injection can compromise the application's integrity and user trust. Attackers can execute unauthorized actions, steal sensitive information, or trick users into performing harmful actions. The organization's reputation, customer trust, and regulatory compliance could be negatively affected. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.2.0. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24967 | Stored XSS on Admin Panel When Deleting a User in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24967</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the admin panel's user management functionality. An attacker can exploit this issue by injecting malicious payloads into the username field during user creation. This vulnerability allows unauthorized script execution whenever the admin views or interacts with the affected user entry, posing a significant risk to sensitive admin functionalities. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.20. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24968 | Business Logic And Unrestricted Project Deletion Lead To Take Over the System in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24968</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. An unrestricted project deletion vulnerability allows attackers with specific roles, such as `penetration_tester` or `auditor` to delete all projects in the system. This can lead to a complete system takeover by redirecting the attacker to the onboarding page, where they can add or modify users, including Sys Admins, and configure critical settings like API keys and user preferences. This issue affects all versions up to and including 2.20. Users are advised to monitor the project for future releases which address this issue. There are no known workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0444 | Use after free in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0444</link><description>Use after free in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0445 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0445</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0451 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to eng...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0451</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.53 allowed a remote attacker who convinced a user to engage in specific UI gestures to perform UI spoofing via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24971 | OS Command Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;/upload/init&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;filename&amp;#x27; (RCE) in DumpDrop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24971</link><description>DumpDrop is a stupid simple file upload application that provides an interface for dragging and dropping files. An OS Command Injection vulnerability was discovered in the DumbDrop application, `/upload/init` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code remotely when the **Apprise Notification** enabled. This issue has been addressed in commit `4ff8469d` and all users are advised to patch. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24373 | Unrestricted Access to PDF Documents via URL Manipulation in woocommerce-pdf-invoices-packing-slips</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24373</link><description>woocommerce-pdf-invoices-packing-slips is an extension which allows users to create, print &amp; automatically email PDF invoices &amp; packing slips for WooCommerce orders. This vulnerability allows unauthorized users to access any PDF document from a store if they: 1. Have access to a guest document link and 2. Replace the URL variable `my-account` with `bulk`. The issue occurs when: 1. The store's document access is set to "guest." and 2. The user is logged out. This vulnerability compromises the confidentiality of sensitive documents, affecting all stores using the plugin with the guest access option enabled. This issue has been addressed in version 4.0.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48019 | Apache Doris: allows admin users to read arbitrary files through the REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48019</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal'), Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability in Apache Doris.


Application administrators can read arbitrary
files from the server filesystem through path traversal.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.1.8, 3.0.3 or later, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25039 | Authenticated Remote Command Injection in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25039</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM) allows remote authenticated users to run arbitrary commands on the underlying host. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands as a lower privileged user on the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23058 | Authenticated Broken Access Control Vulnerability in ClearPass Policy Manager Web-Based Management Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23058</link><description>A vulnerability in the ClearPass Policy Manager web-based management interface allows a low-privileged (read-only) authenticated remote attacker to gain unauthorized access to data and the ability to execute functions that should be restricted to administrators only with read/write privileges. Successful exploitation could enable a low-privileged user to execute administrative functions leading to an escalation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23059 | Sensitive Information Disclosure in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23059</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager exposes directories containing sensitive information. If exploited successfully, this vulnerability allows an authenticated remote attacker with high privileges to access and retrieve sensitive data, potentially compromising the integrity and security of the entire system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23060 | Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23060</link><description>A vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager may, under certain circumstances, expose sensitive unencrypted information. Exploiting this vulnerability could allow an attacker to perform a man-in-the-middle attack, potentially granting unauthorized access to network resources as well as enabling data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0364 | BigAntSoft BigAnt Server Account Registration Bypass to File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0364</link><description>BigAntSoft BigAnt Server, up to and including version 5.6.06, is vulnerable to unauthenticated remote code execution via account registration. An unauthenticated remote attacker can create an administrative user through the default exposed SaaS registration mechanism. Once an administrator, the attacker can upload and execute arbitrary PHP code using the "Cloud Storage Addin," leading to unauthenticated code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45659 | IBM Security Verify Access information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45659</link><description>IBM Security Verify Access Appliance and Container 10.0.0 through 10.0.8 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9644 | Four-Faith F3x36 bapply.cgi Auth Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9644</link><description>The Four-Faith F3x36 router using firmware v2.0.0 is vulnerable to an 
authentication bypass vulnerability in the administrative web server. Authentication is not enforced on some administrative functionality when using the "bapply.cgi" endpoint instead of the normal "apply.cgi" endpoint. A remote and unauthenticated can use this vulnerability to modify settings or chain with existing authenticated vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9643 | Four-Faith F3x36 Hidden Debug Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9643</link><description>The Four-Faith F3x36 router using firmware v2.0.0 is vulnerable to authentication bypass due to hard-coded credentials in the administrative web server. An attacker with knowledge of the credentials can gain administrative access via crafted HTTP requests. This issue appears similar to CVE-2023-32645.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23690 | EOL Netgear FVS336v3 Telnet Configuration Backup Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23690</link><description>The end-of-life Netgear FVS336Gv2 and FVS336Gv3 are affected by a command injection vulnerability in the Telnet interface. An authenticated and remote attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands as root over Telnet by sending crafted "util backup_configuration" commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22206 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.2 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22206</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.2 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'fieldfor' parameter in the GDPR Field feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22641 | WordPress FM Notification Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prem Tiwari FM Notification Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FM Notification Bar: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22642 | WordPress Dynamic Conditions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RTO GmbH Dynamic Conditions allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Dynamic Conditions: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22643 | WordPress OnePress theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22643</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FameThemes OnePress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects OnePress: from n/a through 2.3.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22653 | WordPress Music Press Pro plugin &amp;lt;=1.4.6 -  Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in templaza Music Press Pro allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Music Press Pro: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22662 | WordPress SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22662</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SendPulse SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SendPulse Email Marketing Newsletter: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22664 | WordPress Survey Maker Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22664</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 5.1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22674 | WordPress Product Blocks for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Get Bowtied Product Blocks for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Product Blocks for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22675 | WordPress Alert Box Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22675</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Alert Box Block – Display notice/alerts in the front end: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22696 | WordPress Document Block – Upload &amp;amp; Embed Docs, PDF, PPT, XLS or Any Documents plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22696</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EmbedPress Document Block – Upload &amp; Embed Docs. This issue affects Document Block – Upload &amp; Embed Docs: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22697 | WordPress Responsive Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CyberChimps Responsive Blocks allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Responsive Blocks: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22699 | WordPress Traveler Code plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary SQL Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22699</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Code. This issue affects Traveler Code: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22700 | WordPress Traveler Code plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary SQL Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Code. This issue affects Traveler Code: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22730 | WordPress Ksher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22730</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ksher Ksher allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ksher: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22794 | WordPress World Cup Predictor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22794</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Landoweb Programador World Cup Predictor allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects World Cup Predictor: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23645 | WordPress Find Content IDs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23645</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Optimize Worldwide Find Content IDs allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Find Content IDs: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24598 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.17.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.17.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24599 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.9.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24602 | WordPress WP24 Domain Check plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP24 WP24 Domain Check allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP24 Domain Check: from n/a through 1.10.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24648 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.2.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24648</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in wpase.com Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE): from n/a through 7.6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24677 | WordPress Post/Page Copying Tool to Export and Import post/page for Cross site Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24677</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in WPSpins Post/Page Copying Tool allows Remote Code Inclusion. This issue affects Post/Page Copying Tool: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0825 | CRLF injection in Cpp-httplib</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0825</link><description>cpp-httplib version v0.17.3 through v0.18.3 fails to filter CRLF characters ("\r\n") when those are prefixed with a null byte. This enables attackers to exploit CRLF injection that could further lead to HTTP Response Splitting, XSS, and more.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:30:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0510 | Thunderbird displayed an incorrect sender address if the From field of an email used the invalid group name syntax that is described in CVE-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0510</link><description>Thunderbird displayed an incorrect sender address if the From field of an email used the invalid group name syntax that is described in CVE-2024-49040. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.7 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1009 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via crafted XSLT data, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1009</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via crafted XSLT data, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1010 | An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via the Custom Highlight API, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1010</link><description>An attacker could have caused a use-after-free via the Custom Highlight API, leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1011 | A bug in WebAssembly code generation could have lead to a crash. It may have been possible for an attacker to leverage this to achieve code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1011</link><description>A bug in WebAssembly code generation could have lead to a crash. It may have been possible for an attacker to leverage this to achieve code execution. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1012 | A race during concurrent delazification could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1012</link><description>A race during concurrent delazification could have led to a use-after-free. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1013 | A race condition could have led to private browsing tabs being opened in normal browsing windows. This could have resulted in a potential pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1013</link><description>A race condition could have led to private browsing tabs being opened in normal browsing windows. This could have resulted in a potential privacy leak. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1014 | Certificate length was not properly checked when added to a certificate store. In practice only trusted data was processed. This vulnerabili...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1014</link><description>Certificate length was not properly checked when added to a certificate store. In practice only trusted data was processed. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1015 | The Thunderbird Address Book URI fields contained unsanitized links. This could be used by an attacker to create and export an address book ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1015</link><description>The Thunderbird Address Book URI fields contained unsanitized links. This could be used by an attacker to create and export an address book containing a malicious payload in a field. For example, in the “Other” field of the Instant Messaging section. If another user imported the address book, clicking on the link could result in opening a web page inside Thunderbird, and that page could execute (unprivileged) JavaScript. This vulnerability affects Thunderbird &lt; 128.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1016 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 115.19, Firefox ESR 128.6, Thunderbird 115.19, and Thunderbird 128.6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1016</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 115.19, Firefox ESR 128.6, Thunderbird 115.19, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.20, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1017 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 128.6, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1017</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134, Thunderbird 134, Firefox ESR 128.6, and Thunderbird 128.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.7, Thunderbird &lt; 128.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1018 | The fullscreen notification is prematurely hidden when fullscreen is re-requested quickly by the user. This could have been leveraged to per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1018</link><description>The fullscreen notification is prematurely hidden when fullscreen is re-requested quickly by the user. This could have been leveraged to perform a potential spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1019 | The z-order of the browser windows could be manipulated to hide the fullscreen notification. This could potentially be leveraged to perform ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1019</link><description>The z-order of the browser windows could be manipulated to hide the fullscreen notification. This could potentially be leveraged to perform a spoofing attack. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1020 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134 and Thunderbird 134. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1020</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 134 and Thunderbird 134. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 135 and Thunderbird &lt; 135.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11623 | Stored XSS in authentik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11623</link><description>Authentik project is vulnerable to Stored XSS attacks through uploading crafted SVG files that are used as application icons. 
This action could only be performed by an authenticated admin user.
The issue was fixed in 2024.10.4 release.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13699 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13699</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘cursor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in versions 1.8.5, 1.8.6, and 1.8.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 12:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27137 | Apache Cassandra: unrestricted deserialization of JMX authentication credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27137</link><description>In Apache Cassandra it is possible for a local attacker without access
 to the Apache Cassandra process or configuration files to manipulate 
the RMI registry to perform a man-in-the-middle attack and capture user 
names and passwords used to access the JMX interface. The attacker can 
then use these credentials to access the JMX interface and perform 
unauthorized operations.


This is same vulnerability that CVE-2020-13946 was issued for, but the Java option was changed in JDK10.


This issue affects Apache Cassandra from 4.0.2 through 5.0.2 running Java 11.


Operators are recommended to upgrade to a release equal to or later than 4.0.15, 4.1.8, or 5.0.3 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24860 | Apache Cassandra: CassandraNetworkAuthorizer and CassandraCIDRAuthorizer can be bypassed allowing access to different network regions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24860</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in Apache Cassandra allowing users to access a datacenter or IP/CIDR groups they should not be able to when using CassandraNetworkAuthorizer or CassandraCIDRAuthorizer.

Users with restricted data center access can update their own permissions via data control language (DCL) statements on affected versions.




This issue affects Apache Cassandra: from 4.0.0 through 4.0.15 and from 4.1.0 through 4.1.7 for CassandraNetworkAuthorizer, and from 5.0.0 through 5.0.2 for both CassandraNetworkAuthorizer and CassandraCIDRAuthorizer.




Operators using CassandraNetworkAuthorizer or CassandraCIDRAuthorizer on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches. Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 4.0.16, 4.1.8, 5.0.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0890 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
Insecure default credentials for the Telnet function in the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0890</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
Insecure default credentials for the Telnet function in the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an attacker to log in to the management interface if the administrators have the option to change the default credentials but fail to do so.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40891 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the management commands of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40891</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the management commands of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device via Telnet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40890 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40890</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED**
A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in the CGI program of the legacy DSL CPE Zyxel VMG4325-B10A firmware version 1.00(AAFR.4)C0_20170615 could allow an authenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands on an affected device by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23015 | Apache Cassandra: User with MODIFY permission on ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser via unsafe actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23015</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions vulnerability in Apache Cassandra. An user with MODIFY permission ON ALL KEYSPACES can escalate privileges to superuser within a targeted Cassandra cluster via unsafe actions to a system resource. Operators granting data MODIFY permission on all keyspaces on affected versions should review data access rules for potential breaches.

This issue affects Apache Cassandra through 3.0.30, 3.11.17, 4.0.15, 4.1.7, 5.0.2.

Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 3.0.31, 3.11.18, 4.0.16, 4.1.8, 5.0.3, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13356 | DSGVO All in one for WP &amp;lt;= 4.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Account Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13356</link><description>The DSGVO All in one for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the user_remove_form.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete admin user accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13510 | ShopSite &amp;lt;= 1.5.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13510</link><description>The ShopSite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13529 | SocialV - Social Network and Community BuddyPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Missing Authorization to Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13529</link><description>The SocialV - Social Network and Community BuddyPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'socialv_send_download_file' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download arbitrary files from the target system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13733 | SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13733</link><description>The SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's skt-blocks/post-carousel block in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 09:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13403 | WPForms Lite &amp;lt;= 1.9.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via fieldHTML Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13403</link><description>The WPForms – Easy Form Builder for WordPress – Contact Forms, Payment Forms, Surveys, &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘fieldHTML’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10237 | SMC BMC Firmware Image Authentication Design Issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10237</link><description>There is a vulnerability in the BMC firmware image authentication design 

 at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6

. An attacker can modify the firmware to bypass BMC inspection and bypass the signature verification process</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10238 | fld-&amp;gt;used_bytes without sanity check causes stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10238</link><description>A security issue in the firmware image verification implementation 

 at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6. An attacker can upload a specially crafted image that will cause a stack overflow is caused by not checking fld-&gt;used_bytes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10239 | fld-&amp;gt;used_bytes without sanity check causes stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10239</link><description>A security issue in the firmware image verification implementation at Supermicro MBD-X12DPG-OA6 . An attacker with administrator privileges can upload a specially crafted image, which can cause a stack overflow due to the unchecked fat-&gt;fsd.max_fld.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 08:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12046 | Medical Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12046</link><description>The Medical Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 via the 'namedical_elementor_template' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the content of draft, pending, and private posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13514 | B Slider- Gutenberg Slider Block for WP &amp;lt;= 1.1.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Private Post Disclosure via bsb-slider Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13514</link><description>The B Slider- Gutenberg Slider Block for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.5 via the 'bsb-slider' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20904 | Out-of-bounds write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20904</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20905 | Out-of-bounds read and write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read and write out-of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20905</link><description>Out-of-bounds read and write in mPOS TUI trustlet prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read and write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20906 | Improper Export of Android Application Components in Settings prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable ADB.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20906</link><description>Improper Export of Android Application Components in Settings prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to enable ADB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20907 | Improper privilege management in Samsung Find prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to disable Samsung Find.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20907</link><description>Improper privilege management in Samsung Find prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to disable Samsung Find.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22204 | Extension - regularlabs.com - Remote code execution vulnerability in the Sourcerer extensions &amp;lt; 12.0.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22204</link><description>Improper control of generation of code in the sourcerer extension for Joomla in versions before 11.0.0 lead to a remote code execution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22205 | Extension - admiror-design-studio.com - Path traversal in the Admiror Gallery 4.x component for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22205</link><description>Improper handling of input variables lead to multiple path traversal vulnerabilities in the Admiror Gallery extension for Joomla in version branch 4.x.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20881 | Out-of-bounds write in accessing buffer storing the decoded video frames in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20881</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in accessing buffer storing the decoded video frames in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20882 | Out-of-bounds write in accessing uninitialized memory for svc1td in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20882</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in accessing uninitialized memory for svc1td in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20883 | Improper access control in SoundPicker prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20883</link><description>Improper access control in SoundPicker prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20884 | Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20884</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Message prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20885 | Out-of-bounds write in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20885</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20886 | Inclusion of sensitive information in test code in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get test ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20886</link><description>Inclusion of sensitive information in test code in softsim TA prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get test key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20887 | Out-of-bounds read in accessing table used for svp8t in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20887</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in accessing table used for svp8t in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20888 | Out-of-bounds write in handling the block size for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20888</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in handling the block size for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20889 | Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to rea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20889</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream for smp4vtd in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20890 | Out-of-bounds write in decoding frame buffer in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20890</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in decoding frame buffer in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code with privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20891 | Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream of video thumbnails in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20891</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in decoding malformed bitstream of video thumbnails in libsthmbc.so prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary memory. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20892 | Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to allow to execute fastboot command. U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20892</link><description>Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows physical attackers to allow to execute fastboot command. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20893 | Improper access control in NotificationManager prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to change the configuration of notific...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20893</link><description>Improper access control in NotificationManager prior to SMR Jan-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to change the configuration of notifications.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20894 | Improper access control in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.97.1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20894</link><description>Improper access control in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.97.1 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20895 | Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.87.6 allows physical attackers to install arbitrary appli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20895</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.87.6 allows physical attackers to install arbitrary applications to bypass restrictions of Setupwizard.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20896 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.18 allows local attackers to access sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20896</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.18 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20897 | Improper access control in Secure Folder prior to version 1.9.20.50 in Android 14, 1.8.11.0 in Android 13, and 1.7.04.0 in Android 12 allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20897</link><description>Improper access control in Secure Folder prior to version 1.9.20.50 in Android 14, 1.8.11.0 in Android 13, and 1.7.04.0 in Android 12 allows local attacker to access data in Secure Folder.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20898 | Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.2.00.12 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20898</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Members prior to version 5.2.00.12 allows physical attackers to access data across multiple user profiles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20899 | Improper access control in PushNotification prior to version 13.0.00.15 in Android 12, 14.0.00.7 in Android 13, and 15.1.00.5 in Android 14 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20899</link><description>Improper access control in PushNotification prior to version 13.0.00.15 in Android 12, 14.0.00.7 in Android 13, and 15.1.00.5 in Android 14 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20900 | Out-of-bounds write in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20900</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20901 | Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20901</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in Blockchain Keystore prior to version 1.3.16.5 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20902 | Improper access control in Media Controller prior to version 1.0.24.5282 allows local attacker to launch activities in MediaController's pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20902</link><description>Improper access control in Media Controller prior to version 1.0.24.5282 allows local attacker to launch activities in MediaController's privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12597 | HT Mega &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via block_css and inner_css</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12597</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'block_css' and 'inner_css' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13607 | JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp;amp; Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.8 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13607</link><description>The JS Help Desk – The Ultimate Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.8 via the 'exportusereraserequest' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level permissions and above, to export ticket data for any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13114 | WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13114</link><description>The WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13115 | WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13115</link><description>The WP Projects Portfolio with Client Testimonials WordPress plugin through 3.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13325 | Glossy &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13325</link><description>The Glossy WordPress plugin through 2.3.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13326 | iBuildApp &amp;lt;= 0.2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13326</link><description>The iBuildApp WordPress plugin through 0.2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13327 | Musicbox &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13327</link><description>The Musicbox WordPress plugin through 2.0.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13328 | Giga Messenger Bots &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13328</link><description>The Giga Messenger  WordPress plugin through 2.3.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13329 | Solidres &amp;lt;= 0.9.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13329</link><description>The Solidres  WordPress plugin through 0.9.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13330 | Justrows Free &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13330</link><description>The JustRows free WordPress plugin through 0.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13331 | WP Dream Carousel &amp;lt;= 1.0.1b - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13331</link><description>The WP Dream Carousel WordPress plugin through 1.0.1b does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13332 | TransFinanz &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13332</link><description>The TransFinanz WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0368 | Banner Garden Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0368</link><description>The Banner Garden Plugin for WordPress plugin through 0.1.3 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0466 | Sensei LMS &amp;lt; 4.24.4 - Unauthenticated sensei_email/sensei_message Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0466</link><description>The Sensei LMS  WordPress plugin before 4.24.4 does not properly protect some its REST API routes, allowing unauthenticated attackers to leak sensei_email and sensei_message Information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24982 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Activity Log WinterLock versions prior to 1.2.5. If a user views a malicious page while l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24982</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in Activity Log WinterLock versions prior to 1.2.5. If a user views a malicious page while logged in, the log data may be deleted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 04:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22475 | Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.10 contains a use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Impl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22475</link><description>Dell PowerProtect DD, versions prior to DDOS 8.3.0.0, 7.10.1.50, and 7.13.1.10 contains a use of a Cryptographic Primitive with a Risky Implementation vulnerability. A remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 02:52:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1003 | HP Anyware Agent for Linux – Potential Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1003</link><description>A potential vulnerability has been identified in HP Anyware Agent for Linux which might allow for authentication bypass which may result in escalation of privilege. HP is releasing a software update to mitigate this potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0148 | Zoom Jenkins Marketplace plugin - Missing Password Field Masking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0148</link><description>Missing password field masking in the Zoom Jenkins Marketplace plugin before version 1.6 may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via adjacent network access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24901 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;deletar_permissao.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;c&amp;#x27;, &amp;#x27;a&amp;#x27;, &amp;#x27;r&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24901</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `deletar_permissao.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24902 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;salvar_cargo.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_cargo&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24902</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `salvar_cargo.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24905 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;get_codigobarras_cobranca.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;codigo&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24905</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `get_codigobarras_cobranca.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24906 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;get_detalhes_cobranca.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;codigo&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24906</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `get_detalhes_cobranca.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24957 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;get_detalhes_socio.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_socio&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24957</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `get_detalhes_socio.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24958 | SQL Injection endpoint &amp;#x27;salvar_tag.php&amp;#x27; parameter &amp;#x27;id_tag&amp;#x27; in WeGIA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24958</link><description>WeGIA is a Web Manager for Charitable Institutions. A SQL Injection vulnerability was discovered in the WeGIA application, `salvar_tag.php` endpoint. This vulnerability could allow an authorized attacker to execute arbitrary SQL queries, allowing access to  or deletion of sensitive information. This issue has been addressed in version 3.2.12 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35177 | Improper Access Control in wazuh-agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35177</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. It is capable of protecting workloads across on-premises, virtualized, containerized, and cloud-based environments. The wazuh-agent for Windows is vulnerable to a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability due to improper ACL of the non-default installation directory. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability by placing one of the many DLL that are loaded and not present on the system in the installation folder of the agent OR by replacing the service executable binary itself with a malicious one. The root cause is an improper ACL applied on the installation folder when a non-default installation path is specified (e.g,: C:\wazuh). Many DLLs are loaded from the installation folder and by creating a malicious DLLs that exports the functions of a legit one (and that is not found on the system where the agent is installed, such as rsync.dll) it is possible to escalate privileges from a low-privileged user and obtain code execution under the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM. This issue has been addressed in version 4.9.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47770 | Ability to view Agent list with no privilege access in wazuh-dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47770</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. It is capable of protecting workloads across on-premises, virtualized, containerized, and cloud-based environments. This vulnerability occurs when the system has weak privilege access, that allows an attacker to do privilege escalation. In this case the attacker is able to view agent list on Wazuh dashboard with no privilege access. This issue has been addressed in release version 4.9.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22129 | Initial effort field does not respect field permissions in the Taskboard REST card representation in Tuleap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22129</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. In affected versions an unauthorized user might get access to restricted information. This issue has been addressed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.3.99.1736242932, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.2-5, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.3-2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24029 | Artifact permissions are not verified in the Cross Tracker Search widget in Tuleap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24029</link><description>Tuleap is an Open Source Suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Users (possibly anonymous ones if the widget is used in the dashboard of a public project) might get access to artifacts they should not see. This issue has been addressed in Tuleap Community Edition 16.3.99.1737562605 as well as Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.3-5 and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 16.2-7. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:35:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23210 | Bypass XSS sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters in phpoffice/phpspreadsheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23210</link><description>phpoffice/phpspreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Affected versions have been found to have a Bypass of the Cross-site Scripting (XSS) sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters. This issue has been addressed in versions 3.9.0, 2.3.7, 2.1.8, and 1.29.9. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24371 | Malicious peer can make node stuck in blocksync in github.com/cometbft/cometbft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24371</link><description>CometBFT is a distributed, Byzantine fault-tolerant, deterministic state machine replication engine. In the `blocksync` protocol peers send their `base` and `latest` heights when they connect to a new node (`A`), which is syncing to the tip of a network. `base` acts as a lower ground and informs `A` that the peer only has blocks starting from height `base`. `latest` height informs `A` about the latest block in a network. Normally, nodes would only report increasing heights. If `B` fails to provide the latest block, `B` is removed and the `latest` height (target height) is recalculated based on other nodes `latest` heights. The existing code however doesn't check for the case where `B` first reports `latest` height `X` and immediately after height `Y`, where `X &gt; Y`. `A` will be trying to catch up to 2000 indefinitely. This condition requires the introduction of malicious code in the full node first reporting some non-existing `latest` height, then reporting lower `latest` height and nodes which are syncing using `blocksync` protocol. This issue has been patched in versions 1.0.1 and 0.38.17 and all users are advised to upgrade. Operators may attempt to ban malicious peers from the network as a workaround.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52163 | Digiever DS-2105 Pro 3.1.0.71-11 devices allow time_tzsetup.cgi Command Injection. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52163</link><description>Digiever DS-2105 Pro 3.1.0.71-11 devices allow time_tzsetup.cgi Command Injection. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52164 | access_device.cgi on Digiever DS-2105 Pro 3.1.0.71-11 devices allows arbitrary file read. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products tha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52164</link><description>access_device.cgi on Digiever DS-2105 Pro 3.1.0.71-11 devices allows arbitrary file read. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24370 | Django-Unicorn Class Pollution Vulnerability, Leading to XSS, DoS and Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24370</link><description>Django-Unicorn adds modern reactive component functionality to Django templates. Affected versions of Django-Unicorn are vulnerable to python class pollution vulnerability. The vulnerability arises from the core functionality `set_property_value`, which can be remotely triggered by users by crafting appropriate component requests and feeding in values of second and third parameter to the vulnerable function, leading to arbitrary changes to the python runtime status. With this finding at least five ways of vulnerability exploitation have been observed, stably resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), Denial of Service (DoS), and Authentication Bypass attacks in almost every Django-Unicorn-based application. This issue has been addressed in version 0.62.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24899 | Disclosure of Sensitive User Information via API in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24899</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. A vulnerability was discovered in reNgine, where **an insider attacker with any role** (such as Auditor, Penetration Tester, or Sys Admin) **can extract sensitive information from other reNgine users.** After running a scan and obtaining vulnerabilities from a target, the attacker can retrieve details such as `username`, `password`, `email`, `role`, `first name`, `last name`, `status`, and `activity information` by making a GET request to `/api/listVulnerability/`. This issue has been addressed in version 2.2.0 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24962 | Command Injection in reNgine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24962</link><description>reNgine is an automated reconnaissance framework for web applications. In affected versions a user can inject commands via the nmap_cmd parameters. This issue has been addressed in commit `c28e5c8d` and is expected in the next versioned release. Users are advised to filter user input and monitor the project for a new release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22918 | Polycom RealPresence Group 500 &lt;=20 has Insecure Permissions due to automatically loaded cookies. This allows for the use of administrator f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22918</link><description>Polycom RealPresence Group 500 &lt;=20 has Insecure Permissions due to automatically loaded cookies. This allows for the use of administrator functions, resulting in the leakage of sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56898 | Incorrect access control in Geovision GV-ASWeb version 6.1.0.0 or less allows unauthorized attackers with low-level privileges to manage and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56898</link><description>Incorrect access control in Geovision GV-ASWeb version 6.1.0.0 or less allows unauthorized attackers with low-level privileges to manage and create new user accounts via supplying a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56901 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the Account Management component of Geovision GV-ASWeb version 6.1.1.0 or less allows attackers to ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56901</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in the Account Management component of Geovision GV-ASWeb version 6.1.1.0 or less allows attackers to arbitrarily create Admin accounts via a crafted GET request method.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56902 | An issue in Geovision GV-ASWeb with version 6.1.0.0 or less allows unauthorized attackers with low-level privileges to be able to request in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56902</link><description>An issue in Geovision GV-ASWeb with version 6.1.0.0 or less allows unauthorized attackers with low-level privileges to be able to request information about other accounts via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56903 | A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Geovision GV-ASWeb with the version 6.1.1.0 or less allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56903</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in Geovision GV-ASWeb with the version 6.1.1.0 or less allows attackers to execute arbitrary operations via supplying a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24959 | Environment Variable Injection for dotenv API in zx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24959</link><description>zx is a tool for writing better scripts. An attacker with control over environment variable values can inject unintended environment variables into `process.env`. This can lead to arbitrary command execution or unexpected behavior in applications that rely on environment variables for security-sensitive operations. Applications that process untrusted input and pass it through `dotenv.stringify` are particularly vulnerable. This issue has been patched in version 8.3.2. Users should immediately upgrade to this version to mitigate the vulnerability. If upgrading is not feasible, users can mitigate the vulnerability by sanitizing user-controlled environment variable values before passing them to `dotenv.stringify`. Specifically, avoid using `"`, `'`, and backticks in values, or enforce strict validation of environment variables before usage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24960 | Missing Input validation for filename in backups endpoint in Jellystat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24960</link><description>Jellystat is a free and open source Statistics App for Jellyfin. In affected versions Jellystat is directly using a user input in the route(s). This can lead to Path Traversal Vulnerabilities. Since this functionality is only for admin(s), there is very little scope for abuse. However, the `DELETE` `files/:filename` can be used to delete any file. This issue has been addressed in version 1.1.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24961 | Insecure path traversal in filesystem and filesystem-nio2 storage backends in org.gaul S3Proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24961</link><description>org.gaul S3Proxy implements the S3 API and proxies requests. Users of the filesystem and filesystem-nio2 storage backends could unintentionally expose local files to users. This issue has been addressed in version 2.6.0. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34896 | An issue in Nedis SmartLife Video Doorbell (WIFICDP10GY), Nedis SmartLife IOS v1.4.0 causes users who are disconnected from a previous peer-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34896</link><description>An issue in Nedis SmartLife Video Doorbell (WIFICDP10GY), Nedis SmartLife IOS v1.4.0 causes users who are disconnected from a previous peer-to-peer connection with the device to still have access to live video feed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34897 | Nedis SmartLife android app v1.4.0 was discovered to contain an API key disclosure vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34897</link><description>Nedis SmartLife android app v1.4.0 was discovered to contain an API key disclosure vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44449 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quorum onQ OS v.6.0.0.5.2064 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the msg para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44449</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Quorum onQ OS v.6.0.0.5.2064 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the msg parameter in the Login page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57451 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has a directory traversal vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController#getFileList, which allows attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57451</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has a directory traversal vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController#getFileList, which allows attackers to view any directory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56946 | Denial of service in DNS-over-QUIC in Technitium DNS Server &lt;= v13.2.2 allows remote attackers to permanently stop the server from accepting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56946</link><description>Denial of service in DNS-over-QUIC in Technitium DNS Server &lt;= v13.2.2 allows remote attackers to permanently stop the server from accepting new DNS-over-QUIC connections by triggering unhandled exceptions in listener threads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57097 | ClassCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in class/admin/channel.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57097</link><description>ClassCMS 4.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in class/admin/channel.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57450 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via the Create template function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57450</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 is vulnerable to File Upload via the Create template function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57452 | ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController, which allows attackers to delete ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57452</link><description>ChestnutCMS &lt;=1.5.0 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in contentcore.controller.FileController, which allows attackers to delete any file and folder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57498 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sayski ForestBlog 20241223 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the article editing fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57498</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in sayski ForestBlog 20241223 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the article editing function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57098 | Moss v0.1.3 version has an SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject carefully designed payloads into the order parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57098</link><description>Moss v0.1.3 version has an SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to inject carefully designed payloads into the order parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57099 | ClassCMS v4.8 has a code execution vulnerability. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a payload in the classview parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57099</link><description>ClassCMS v4.8 has a code execution vulnerability. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by constructing a payload in the classview parameter of the model management feature, allowing them to execute arbitrary code and potentially take control of the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22978 | eladmin &lt;=2.7 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the exception log download module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22978</link><description>eladmin &lt;=2.7 is vulnerable to CSV Injection in the exception log download module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11132 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11132</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 3.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11133 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Event Ticket Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11133</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'handle_pdf_download_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download event tickets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11134 | Eventer &amp;lt;= 3.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Bookings Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11134</link><description>The Eventer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'eventer_export_bookings_csv' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber-level permissions or above, to download bookings, which contains customers' personal data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12511 | SMB/FTP Address Book Scan Pass-back attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12511</link><description>With address book access, SMB/FTP settings could be modified, redirecting scans and possibly capturing credentials. This requires enabled scan functions and printer access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12859 | BoomBox Theme Extensions &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12859</link><description>The BoomBox Theme Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 via the 'boombox_listing' shortcode 'type' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level and above permissions, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php file type can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56921 | An issue was discovered in Open5gs v2.7.2. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect err...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56921</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open5gs v2.7.2. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect error handling of gmm_state_exception() function upon receipt of the Nausf_UEAuthentication_Authenticate response.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25065 | SSRF vulnerability in the RSS feed parser in Zimbra Collaboration 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, and 10.1.x before 10.1.4 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25065</link><description>SSRF vulnerability in the RSS feed parser in Zimbra Collaboration 9.0.0 before Patch 43, 10.0.x before 10.0.12, and 10.1.x before 10.1.4 allows unauthorized redirection to internal network endpoints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25181 | A SQL injection vulnerability in timeoutWarning.asp in Advantive VeraCore through 2025.1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25181</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in timeoutWarning.asp in Advantive VeraCore through 2025.1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the PmSess1 parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25064 | SQL injection vulnerability in the ZimbraSyncService SOAP endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration 10.0.x before 10.0.12 and 10.1.x before 10.1.4.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25064</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in the ZimbraSyncService SOAP endpoint in Zimbra Collaboration 10.0.x before 10.0.12 and 10.1.x before 10.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57669 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Zrlog backup-sql-file.jar v.3.0.31 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the Bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57669</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Zrlog backup-sql-file.jar v.3.0.31 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the BackupController.java file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57968 | Advantive VeraCore before 2024.4.2.1 allows remote authenticated users to upload files to unintended folders (e.g., ones that are accessible...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57968</link><description>Advantive VeraCore before 2024.4.2.1 allows remote authenticated users to upload files to unintended folders (e.g., ones that are accessible during web browsing by other users). upload.aspx can be used for this.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57237 | Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57237</link><description>Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability arises because the cmd parameter does not properly sanitize input and the response is served with a Content-Type of text/html. This behavior allows the browser to execute injected JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57238 | Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57238</link><description>Prolink 4G LTE Mobile Wi-Fi DL-7203E V4.0.0B05 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in in the /reqproc/proc_get endpoint. The vulnerability allows an attacker to manipulate SQL queries by injecting malicious SQL code into the order_by parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12510 | LDAP Authentication Sever Pass-back attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12510</link><description>If LDAP settings are accessed, authentication could be redirected to another server, potentially exposing credentials. This requires admin access and an active LDAP setup.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50656 | itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50656</link><description>itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57004 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Roundcube Webmail 1.6.9 allows remote authenticated users to upload a malicious file as an email...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57004</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Roundcube Webmail 1.6.9 allows remote authenticated users to upload a malicious file as an email attachment, leading to the triggering of the XSS by visiting the SENT session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24898 | rust openssl ssl::select_next_proto use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24898</link><description>rust-openssl is a set of OpenSSL bindings for the Rust programming language. In affected versions `ssl::select_next_proto` can return a slice pointing into the `server` argument's buffer but with a lifetime bound to the `client` argument. In situations where the `sever` buffer's lifetime is shorter than the `client` buffer's, this can cause a use after free. This could cause the server to crash or to return arbitrary memory contents to the client. The crate`openssl` version 0.10.70 fixes the signature of `ssl::select_next_proto` to properly constrain the output buffer's lifetime to that of both input buffers. Users are advised to upgrade. In standard usage of `ssl::select_next_proto` in the callback passed to `SslContextBuilder::set_alpn_select_callback`, code is only affected if the `server` buffer is constructed *within* the callback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53943 | An issue was discovered in NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to XSS via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53943</link><description>An issue was discovered in NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to XSS via the 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz name parameters, allowing an attacker to execute JavaScript within the context of the current user by injecting JavaScript into the SSID field. If an administrator logs into the device, the injected script runs in their browser, executing the malicious payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:56:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57967 | PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 has potentially elevated privileges in LDAP m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57967</link><description>PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 has potentially elevated privileges in LDAP mapping.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36437 | The com.enflick.android.TextNow (aka TextNow: Call + Text Unlimited) application 24.17.0.2 for Android enables any installed application (wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36437</link><description>The com.enflick.android.TextNow (aka TextNow: Call + Text Unlimited) application 24.17.0.2 for Android enables any installed application (with no permissions) to place phone calls without user interaction by sending a crafted intent via the com.enflick.android.TextNow.activities.DialerActivity component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53942 | An issue was discovered on NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to command in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53942</link><description>An issue was discovered on NRadio N8-180 NROS-1.9.2.n3.c5 devices. The /cgi-bin/luci/nradio/basic/radio endpoint is vulnerable to command injection via the 2.4 GHz and 5 GHz name parameters, allowing a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands on the device (with root-level permissions) via crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57175 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the PHPGURUKUL Online Birth Certificate System v1.0 via the profile name...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57175</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the PHPGURUKUL Online Birth Certificate System v1.0 via the profile name to /user/certificate-form.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56161 | Improper signature verification in AMD CPU ROM microcode patch loader may allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56161</link><description>Improper signature verification in AMD CPU ROM microcode patch loader may allow an attacker with local administrator privilege to load malicious CPU microcode resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity of a confidential guest running under AMD SEV-SNP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54840 | PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 does not properly address environment issues ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54840</link><description>PVWA (Password Vault Web Access) in CyberArk Privileged Access Manager Self-Hosted before 14.4 does not properly address environment issues that can contribute to Host header injection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:26:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38404 | Buffer Over-read in Multi Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38404</link><description>Transient DOS when registration accept OTA is received with incorrect ciphering key data IE in modem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38411 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38411</link><description>Memory corruption while registering a buffer from user-space to kernel-space using IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38412 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38412</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from user-space to kernel-space to handle session errors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38413 | Improper Input Validation in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38413</link><description>Memory corruption while processing frame packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38414 | Buffer Over-read in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38414</link><description>Information disclosure while processing information on firmware image during core initialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38416 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38416</link><description>Information disclosure during audio playback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38417 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive Multimedia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38417</link><description>Information disclosure while processing IO control commands.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38418 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38418</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing the memory map info in IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38420 | Improper Input Validation in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38420</link><description>Memory corruption while configuring a Hypervisor based input virtual device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45560 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45560</link><description>Memory corruption while taking a snapshot with hardware encoder due to unvalidated userspace buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45561 | Use After Free in Windows WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45561</link><description>Memory corruption while handling  IOCTL call from user-space to set latency level.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45569 | Improper Validation of Array Index in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45569</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing the ML IE due to invalid frame content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45571 | Use After Free in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45571</link><description>Memory corruption may occour occur when stopping the WLAN interface after processing a WMI command from the interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45573 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Display</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45573</link><description>Memory corruption may occour while generating test pattern due to negative indexing of display ID.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45582 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45582</link><description>Memory corruption while validating number of devices in Camera kernel .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45584 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Automotive Android OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45584</link><description>Memory corruption can occur when a compat IOCTL call is followed by a normal IOCTL call from userspace.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49832 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49832</link><description>Memory corruption in Camera due to unusually high number of nodes passed to AXI port.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49833 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49833</link><description>Memory corruption can occur in the camera when an invalid CID is used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49834 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49834</link><description>Memory corruption while power-up or power-down sequence of the camera sensor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49837 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Automotive OS Platform QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49837</link><description>Memory corruption while reading CPU state data during guest VM suspend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49838 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49838</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing the OCI IE with invalid length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49839 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Cmn</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49839</link><description>Memory corruption during management frame processing due to mismatch in T2LM info element.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49840 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49840</link><description>Memory corruption while Invoking IOCTL calls from user-space to validate FIPS encryption or decryption functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49843 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Graphics_Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49843</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL from user space to handle GPU AHB bus error.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55456 | lunasvg v3.0.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_find_cell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55456</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.1 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_find_cell</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:55:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43333 | WordPress Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.2.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43333</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in NotFound Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro allows Privilege Escalation. This issue affects Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) Pro: from n/a through 7.6.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50500 | WordPress Phlox Core Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 2.17.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50500</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in By Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.17.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22260 | WordPress Meta Tag Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22260</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pixelite Meta Tag Manager. This issue affects Meta Tag Manager: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22292 | WordPress Powerful Auto Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Felipe Peixoto Powerful Auto Chat allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Powerful Auto Chat: from n/a through 1.9.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22677 | WordPress Uix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Arbitrary Shortcode Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22677</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in UIUX Lab Uix Shortcodes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Uix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22679 | WordPress Job Board Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.60 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Job Board Manager allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Job Board Manager: from n/a through 2.1.60.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22681 | WordPress Content Cloner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22681</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xfinity Soft Content Cloner allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Content Cloner: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22682 | WordPress Hesabfa Accounting Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22682</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hesabfa Hesabfa Accounting allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Hesabfa Accounting: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22683 | WordPress NotificationX plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22683</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper NotificationX allows Stored XSS. This issue affects NotificationX: from n/a through 2.9.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22684 | WordPress WP BASE Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22684</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hakan Ozevin WP BASE Booking allows Stored XSS. This issue affects WP BASE Booking: from n/a through 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22685 | WordPress Tags to Keywords plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22685</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CheGevara Tags to Keywords allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Tags to Keywords: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22686 | WordPress CF7 Google Sheets Connector plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.17 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22686</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GSheetConnector CF7 Google Sheets Connector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects CF7 Google Sheets Connector: from n/a through 5.0.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22688 | WordPress Unlimited Page Sidebars plugin &amp;lt;= 0.2.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22688</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ederson Peka Unlimited Page Sidebars allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Unlimited Page Sidebars: from n/a through 0.2.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22690 | WordPress DigiTimber cPanel Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22690</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DigiTimber DigiTimber cPanel Integration allows Stored XSS. This issue affects DigiTimber cPanel Integration: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22691 | WordPress WP Travel plugin &amp;lt;= 10.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22691</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WP Travel WP Travel allows SQL Injection. This issue affects WP Travel: from n/a through 10.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22693 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 25.1.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Contest Gallery Contest Gallery allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through 25.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22694 | WordPress Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22694</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theDotstore Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce. This issue affects Hide Shipping Method For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22695 | WordPress Nirweb support plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22695</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in NirWp Team Nirweb support. This issue affects Nirweb support: from n/a through 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22701 | WordPress Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22701</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in NotFound Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor. This issue affects Traveler Layout Essential For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22703 | WordPress Forge – Front-End Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22703</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in manuelvicedo Forge – Front-End Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Forge – Front-End Page Builder: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22704 | WordPress Signature plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery ( CSRF ) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22704</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Abinav Thakuri WordPress Signature allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WordPress Signature: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22775 | WordPress Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp;amp; Crawler Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22775</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in idIA Tech Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp; Crawler allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Catalog Importer, Scraper &amp; Crawler: from n/a through 5.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23491 | WordPress VSTEMPLATE Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23491</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vikashsrivastava1111989 VSTEMPLATE Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects VSTEMPLATE Creator: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23527 | WordPress WC Wallet plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23527</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hemnath Mouli WC Wallet allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WC Wallet: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23561 | WordPress MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MLL Audio Player MP3 Ajax: from n/a through 0.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23581 | WordPress Demo User DZS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23581</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digital Zoom Studio Demo User DZS allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Demo User DZS: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23582 | WordPress Bulk Categories Assign plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23582</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Haider Ali Bulk Categories Assign allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bulk Categories Assign: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23588 | WordPress WOW Best CSS Compiler plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23588</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WOW WordPress WOW Best CSS Compiler allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WOW Best CSS Compiler: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23590 | WordPress Dezdy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23590</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Burtay Arat Dezdy allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dezdy: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23591 | WordPress blu Logistics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23591</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blu Logistics Pte. Ltd. blu Logistics allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects blu Logistics: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23593 | WordPress EmailPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23593</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound EmailPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EmailPress: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23594 | WordPress Google Map With Fancybox plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23594</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in uzzal mondal Google Map With Fancybox allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Google Map With Fancybox: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23599 | WordPress eMarksheet plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23599</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound eMarksheet allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects eMarksheet: from n/a through 5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23614 | WordPress WordPress Additional Logins plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nik Sudan WordPress Additional Logins allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress Additional Logins: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23685 | WordPress RomanCart On WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23685</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound RomanCart allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects RomanCart: from n/a through 0.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23747 | WordPress Awesome Timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23747</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nitesh Singh Awesome Timeline allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Awesome Timeline: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23755 | WordPress PAFacile plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23755</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound PAFacile allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PAFacile: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23799 | WordPress .TUBE Video Curator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23799</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in .TUBE gTLD .TUBE Video Curator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects .TUBE Video Curator: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23819 | WordPress WP Cloud plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23819</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound WP Cloud allows Absolute Path Traversal. This issue affects WP Cloud: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23920 | WordPress ApplicantPro Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23920</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ApplicantPro ApplicantPro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ApplicantPro: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23923 | WordPress Lockets Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.999 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23923</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Lockets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Lockets: from n/a through 0.999.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23984 | WordPress Dynamic URL SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23984</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brainvireinfo Dynamic URL SEO allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Dynamic URL SEO: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24536 | WordPress ThriveDesk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThriveDesk ThriveDesk allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ThriveDesk: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24541 | WordPress DK White Label plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Emili Castells DK White Label allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects DK White Label: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24544 | WordPress Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24544</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alexandros Georgiou Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bitcoin and Altcoin Wallets: from n/a through 6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24545 | WordPress BSK Forms Validation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BannerSky.com BSK Forms Validation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BSK Forms Validation: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24556 | WordPress MooWoodle plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24556</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in DualCube MooWoodle allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects MooWoodle: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24557 | WordPress PlainInventory plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24557</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in plainware.com PlainInventory allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PlainInventory: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24559 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.15.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24559</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.15.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24569 | WordPress PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24569</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in RedefiningTheWeb PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder allows Path Traversal. This issue affects PDF Generator Addon for Elementor Page Builder: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24574 | WordPress PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects PeproDev WooCommerce Receipt Uploader: from n/a through 2.6.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24576 | WordPress Landing Page Cat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24576</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fatcat Apps Landing Page Cat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Landing Page Cat: from n/a through 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24605 | WordPress WOLF plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.5 - Path Traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24605</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in realmag777 WOLF allows Path Traversal. This issue affects WOLF: from n/a through 1.0.8.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24620 | WordPress AIO Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24620</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound AIO Shortcodes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects AIO Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24629 | WordPress Import Excel to Gravity Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24629</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPGear Import Excel to Gravity Forms allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Import Excel to Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24630 | WordPress Sikshya LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.21 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MantraBrain Sikshya LMS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Sikshya LMS: from n/a through 0.0.21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24631 | WordPress BP Email Assign Templates Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PhiloPress BP Email Assign Templates allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects BP Email Assign Templates: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24639 | WordPress Korea for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.11 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24639</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in GREYS Korea for WooCommerce allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Korea for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24642 | WordPress Setup Default Featured Image plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24642</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theme funda Setup Default Featured Image allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Setup Default Featured Image: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24643 | WordPress WPGuppy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24643</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Amento Tech Pvt ltd WPGuppy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WPGuppy: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24646 | WordPress XML for Avito Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Maxim Glazunov XML for Avito allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XML for Avito: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24656 | WordPress Realtyna Provisioning Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Realtyna Realtyna Provisioning allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Realtyna Provisioning: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24660 | WordPress Simple Membership Custom Messages Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24660</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wp.insider Simple Membership Custom Messages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple Membership Custom Messages: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24661 | WordPress Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24661</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MagePeople Team Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce allows Object Injection. This issue affects Taxi Booking Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24676 | WordPress Custom WP Store Locator plugin  &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24676</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metatagg Inc Custom WP Store Locator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom WP Store Locator: from n/a through 1.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24684 | WordPress Media Downloader Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.7.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24684</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ederson Peka Media Downloader allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Media Downloader: from n/a through 0.4.7.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24697 | WordPress Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24697</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Realwebcare Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Image Gallery – Responsive Photo Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24707 | WordPress Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp;amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.7.24 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24707</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GT3 Photo Gallery Photo Gallery - GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Photo Gallery - GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery: from n/a through 2.7.7.24.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24781 | WordPress WPJobBoard plugin &amp;lt;= 5.10.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24781</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WPJobBoard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WPJobBoard: from n/a through 5.10.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57522 | SourceCodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Users.php. An attacker can inject a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57522</link><description>SourceCodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in Users.php. An attacker can inject a malicious script into the username or name field during user creation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 13:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6790 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver can cause the whole system to become unresponsive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6790</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Arm Ltd Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a non-privileged user process to make valid GPU memory processing operations, including via WebGL or WebGPU, to cause the whole system to become unresponsive.This issue affects Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0; Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: r44p1, from r46p0 through r49p0, from r50p0 through r51p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0015 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0015</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in Arm Ltd Valhall GPU Kernel Driver, Arm Ltd Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver allows a local non-privileged user process to make improper GPU processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.This issue affects Valhall GPU Kernel Driver: from r48p0 through r49p1, from r50p0 through r52p0; Arm 5th Gen GPU Architecture Kernel Driver: from r48p0 through r49p1, from r50p0 through r52p0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 10:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10395 | net: lib: http_server: Buffer Under-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10395</link><description>No proper validation of the length of user input in http_server_get_content_type_from_extension.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 07:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13347 | Essential WP Real Estate &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13347</link><description>The Essential WP Real Estate WordPress plugin through 1.1.3 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25066 | nDPI through 4.12 has a potential stack-based buffer overflow in ndpi_address_cache_restore in lib/ndpi_cache.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25066</link><description>nDPI through 4.12 has a potential stack-based buffer overflow in ndpi_address_cache_restore in lib/ndpi_cache.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 05:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57966 | libarchiveplugin.cpp in KDE ark before 24.12.0 can extract to an absolute path from an archive.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57966</link><description>libarchiveplugin.cpp in KDE ark before 24.12.0 can extract to an absolute path from an archive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 04:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25062 | An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It doesn't sufficiently isolate long text content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25062</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It doesn't sufficiently isolate long text content when the CKEditor 5 rich text editor is used. This allows a potential attacker to craft specialized HTML and JavaScript that may be executed when an administrator attempts to edit a piece of content. This vulnerability is mitigated by the fact that an attacker must have the ability to create long text content (such as through the node or comment forms) and an administrator must edit (not view) the content that contains the malicious content. This problem only exists when using the CKEditor 5 module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25063 | An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It does not sufficiently validate uploaded SVG im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25063</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in Backdrop CMS 1.28.x before 1.28.5 and 1.29.x before 1.29.3. It does not sufficiently validate uploaded SVG images to ensure they do not contain potentially dangerous SVG tags. SVG images can contain clickable links and executable scripting, and using a crafted SVG, it is possible to execute scripting in the browser when an SVG image is viewed. This issue is mitigated by the attacker needing to be able to upload SVG images, and that Backdrop embeds all uploaded SVG images within &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; tags, which prevents scripting from executing. The SVG must be viewed directly by its URL in order to run any embedded scripting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20141 | In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20141</link><description>In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291402; Issue ID: MSV-2073.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20142 | In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20142</link><description>In V5 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291406; Issue ID: MSV-2070.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20147 | In Bluetooth FW, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20147</link><description>In Bluetooth FW, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00389046 (Note: For MT79XX chipsets) / ALPS09136501 (Note: For MT2737, MT3603, MT6XXX, and MT8XXX chipsets); Issue ID: MSV-1797.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20631 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20631</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00397141; Issue ID: MSV-2187.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20632 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20632</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00397139; Issue ID: MSV-2188.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20633 | In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20633</link><description>In wlan AP driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00400889; Issue ID: MSV-2491.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20634 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20634</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01289384; Issue ID: MSV-2436.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20635 | In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20635</link><description>In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09403752; Issue ID: MSV-2434.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20636 | In secmem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20636</link><description>In secmem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09403554; Issue ID: MSV-2431.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20637 | In network HW, there is a possible system hang due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20637</link><description>In network HW, there is a possible system hang due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00399035; Issue ID: MSV-2380.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20638 | In DA, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20638</link><description>In DA, there is a possible read of uninitialized heap data due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291449; Issue ID: MSV-2066.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20639 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20639</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2060.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20640 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20640</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2059.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20641 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20641</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2058.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20642 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20642</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2057.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20643 | In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20643</link><description>In DA, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure, if an attacker has physical access to the device, if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09291146; Issue ID: MSV-2056.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 03:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0974 | MaxD Lightning Module deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0974</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in MaxD Lightning Module 4.43 on OpenCart. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation of the argument li_op/md leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 02:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0973 | CmsEasy index.php backAll_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0973</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9. This vulnerability affects the function backAll_action in the library lib/admin/database_admin.php of the file /index.php?case=database&amp;amp;act=backAll&amp;amp;admin_dir=admin&amp;amp;site=default. The manipulation of the argument select[] leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0972 | Zenvia Movidesk New Ticket cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0972</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. This affects an unknown part of the component New Ticket Handler. The manipulation of the argument subject leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0971 | Zenvia Movidesk Profile Editing EditProfile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0971</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Account/EditProfile of the component Profile Editing. The manipulation of the argument username leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0970 | Zenvia Movidesk Login redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0970</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Zenvia Movidesk up to 25.01.22. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Account/Login. The manipulation of the argument ReturnUrl leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 25.01.22.245a473c54 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 23:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0967 | code-projects Chat System add_chatroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/add_chatroom.php. The manipulation of the argument chatname/chatpass leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 15:41:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0131 | NVIDIA GPU kernel driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a potential user-mode attacker could read  a buffer with an in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0131</link><description>NVIDIA GPU kernel driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where a potential user-mode attacker could read  a buffer with an incorrect length. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 01:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>