<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:08:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1355 | needyamin Library Card System Add Picture signup.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1355</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /signup.php of the component Add Picture. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1354 | Asus RT-N12E sysinfo.asp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1354</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Asus RT-N12E 2.0.0.19. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file sysinfo.asp. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 15:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1353 | Kong Insomnia profapi.dll untrusted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1353</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kong Insomnia up to 10.3.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing in the library profapi.dll. The manipulation leads to untrusted search path. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 15:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1352 | GNU elfutils eu-readelf libdw_alloc.c __libdw_thread_tail memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1352</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU elfutils 0.192 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function __libdw_thread_tail in the library libdw_alloc.c of the component eu-readelf. The manipulation of the argument w leads to memory corruption. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 2636426a091bd6c6f7f02e49ab20d4cdc6bfc753. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1341 | PMWeb Setting weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1341</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PMWeb 7.2.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to change the configuration settings. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1340 | TOTOLINK X18 cstecgi.cgi setPasswordCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1340</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK X18 9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329. Affected is the function setPasswordCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation as part of String leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1339 | TOTOLINK X18 cstecgi.cgi setL2tpdConfig os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X18 9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setL2tpdConfig of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument enable leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 12:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1338 | NUUO Camera handle_config.php print_file command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in NUUO Camera up to 20250203. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function print_file of the file /handle_config.php. The manipulation of the argument log leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 11:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1337 | Eastnets PaymentSafe BIC Search cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1337</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Eastnets PaymentSafe 2.5.26.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component BIC Search. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 10:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1336 | CmsEasy image_admin.php deleteimg_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1336</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function deleteimg_action in the library lib/admin/image_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument imgname leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1335 | CmsEasy file_admin.php deleteimg_action path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1335</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CmsEasy 7.7.7.9. Affected is the function deleteimg_action in the library lib/admin/file_admin.php. The manipulation of the argument imgname leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 04:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57971 | DataSourceResource.java in the SpagoBI API support in Knowage Server in KNOWAGE before 8.1.30 does not ensure that java:comp/env/jdbc/ occur...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57971</link><description>DataSourceResource.java in the SpagoBI API support in Knowage Server in KNOWAGE before 8.1.30 does not ensure that java:comp/env/jdbc/ occurs at the beginning of a JNDI Name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 03:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57970 | libarchive through 3.7.7 has a heap-based buffer over-read in header_gnu_longlink in archive_read_support_format_tar.c via a TAR archive bec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57970</link><description>libarchive through 3.7.7 has a heap-based buffer over-read in header_gnu_longlink in archive_read_support_format_tar.c via a TAR archive because it mishandles truncation in the middle of a GNU long linkname.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1332 | FastCMS Template Menu menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1332</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FastCMS up to 0.1.5 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /fastcms.html#/template/menu of the component Template Menu. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26793 | The Web GUI configuration panel of Hirsch (formerly Identiv and Viscount) Enterphone MESH through 2024 ships with default credentials (usern...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26793</link><description>The Web GUI configuration panel of Hirsch (formerly Identiv and Viscount) Enterphone MESH through 2024 ships with default credentials (username freedom, password viscount). The administrator is not prompted to change these credentials on initial configuration, and changing the credentials requires many steps. Attackers can use the credentials over the Internet via mesh.webadmin.MESHAdminServlet to gain access to dozens of Canadian and U.S. apartment buildings and obtain building residents' PII. NOTE: the Supplier's perspective is that the "vulnerable systems are not following manufacturers' recommendations to change the default password."</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13834 | Responsive Plus – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery via remote_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13834</link><description>The Responsive Plus – Starter Templates, Advanced Features and Customizer Settings for Responsive Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 via the 'remote_request' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0822 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read via fileID Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0822</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the fileID Parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 12:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10581 | DirectoryPress Frontend &amp;lt;= 2.7.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Listing Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10581</link><description>The DirectoryPress Frontend plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the dpfl_listingStatusChange() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update listing statuses via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13439 | Team – Team Members Showcase Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13439</link><description>The Team – Team Members Showcase Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the response() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13488 | LTL Freight Quotes – Estes Edition &amp;lt;= 3.3.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13488</link><description>The LTL Freight Quotes – Estes Edition plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'dropship_edit_id' and 'edit_id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13500 | WP Project Manager &amp;lt;= 2.6.17 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13500</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.17 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 11:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12562 | s2Member Pro &amp;lt;= 241216 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12562</link><description>The s2Member Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 241216 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 's2member_pro_remote_op' vulnerable parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13752 | WP Project Manager  &amp;lt;= 2.6.17 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13752</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check in the '/pm/v2/settings/notice' endpoint all versions up to, and including, 2.6.17. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to cause a persistent denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1005 | ElementsKit Elementor addons &amp;lt;= 3.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Accordion Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1005</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Accordion widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13525 | Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13525</link><description>The Customer Email Verification for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.4 via Shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including emails as well as hashed passwords of any user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13563 | Front End Users &amp;lt;= 3.2.30 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via forgot-password Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13563</link><description>The Front End Users plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's forgot-password shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.30 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0935 | Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 8.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Plugin Settings Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0935</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings change due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 8.3.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to change plugin settings related to things such as IP-blocking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22208 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.3 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22208</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.3 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'filter_email' parameter in the GDPR Erase Data Request search feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22209 | Extension - joomsky.com - SQL injection in JS jobs component version 1.1.5 - 1.4.3 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22209</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in the JS Jobs plugin versions 1.1.5-1.4.3 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the 'searchpaymentstatus' parameter in the Employer Payment History search feature.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13513 | Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) &amp;lt;= 2.4.2.3 - Sensitive Information Exposure to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13513</link><description>The Oliver POS – A WooCommerce Point of Sale (POS) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2.3 via the logging functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including the plugin's clientToken, which in turn can be used to change user account information including emails and account type. This allows attackers to then change account passwords resulting in a complete site takeover. Version 2.4.2.3 disabled logging but left sites with existing log files vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 07:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13208 | WP Google Map &amp;lt; 1.9.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13208</link><description>The Maps Plugin using Google Maps for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13306 | WP Google Map &amp;lt; 1.9.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13306</link><description>The Maps Plugin using Google Maps for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.9.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 06:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1302 | Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1302</link><description>Versions of the package jsonpath-plus before 10.3.0 are vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can execute aribitrary code on the system by exploiting the unsafe default usage of eval='safe' mode.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is caused by an incomplete fix for [CVE-2024-21534](https://security.snyk.io/vuln/SNYK-JS-JSONPATHPLUS-7945884).</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 05:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0995 | Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0995</link><description>Use after free in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0996 | Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the content...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0996</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Browser UI in Google Chrome on Android prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to spoof the contents of the Omnibox (URL bar) via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0997 | Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0997</link><description>Use after free in Navigation in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0998 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0998</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 133.0.6943.98 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5461 | Command or parameter injection via unique embedded switch SNMP commands.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5461</link><description>Implementation of the Simple Network 
Management Protocol (SNMP) operating on the Brocade 6547 (FC5022) 
embedded switch blade, makes internal script calls to system.sh from 
within the SNMP binary. An authenticated attacker could perform command 
or parameter injection on SNMP operations that are only enabled on the 
Brocade 6547 (FC5022) embedded switch. This injection could allow the 
authenticated attacker to issue commands as Root.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5462 | Brocade Fabric OS may capture SNMP Passwords in clear text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5462</link><description>If Brocade Fabric OS before Fabric OS 9.2.0 configuration settings are not set to encrypt SNMP passwords, then the SNMP privsecret / authsecret fields can be exposed in plaintext. The plaintext passwords can be exposed in a configupload capture or a supportsave capture if encryption of passwords is not enabled. An attacker can use these passwords to fetch values of the supported OIDs via SNMPv3 queries. There are also a limited number of MIB objects that can be modified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26819 | Monero through 0.18.3.4 before ec74ff4 does not have response limits on HTTP server connections.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26819</link><description>Monero through 0.18.3.4 before ec74ff4 does not have response limits on HTTP server connections.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:49:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4282 | Weak TLS Ciphers on Brocade SANnav OVA SSH port 22</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4282</link><description>Brocade SANnav OVA before SANnav 2.3.1b enables SHA1 deprecated setting for SSH for port 22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10405 | Weak TLS Ciphers on Brocade SANnav port 443 &amp;amp; 18082</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10405</link><description>Brocade SANnav before SANnav 2.3.1b 
enables weak TLS ciphers on ports 443 and 18082. In case of a successful
 exploit, an attacker can read Brocade SANnav data stream that includes 
monitored Brocade Fabric OS switches performance data, port status, 
zoning information, WWNs, IP Addresses, but no customer data, no 
personal data and no secrets or passwords, as it travels across the 
network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21401 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21401</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28693 | Unprotected alternative channel of return branch target prediction in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28693</link><description>Unprotected alternative channel of return branch target prediction in some Intel(R) Processors may allow an authorized user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-26083 | Generation of weak initialization vector in an Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software library before version 2021.5 may allow an unauthenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26083</link><description>Generation of weak initialization vector in an Intel(R) IPP Cryptography software library before version 2021.5 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31144 | Xapi: Metadata injection attack against backup/restore functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31144</link><description>For a brief summary of Xapi terminology, see:

   https://xapi-project.github.io/xen-api/overview.html#object-model-overview 

Xapi contains functionality to backup and restore metadata about Virtual
Machines and Storage Repositories (SRs).

The metadata itself is stored in a Virtual Disk Image (VDI) inside an
SR.  This is used for two purposes; a general backup of metadata
(e.g. to recover from a host failure if the filer is still good), and
Portable SRs (e.g. using an external hard drive to move VMs to another
host).

Metadata is only restored as an explicit administrator action, but
occurs in cases where the host has no information about the SR, and must
locate the metadata VDI in order to retrieve the metadata.

The metadata VDI is located by searching (in UUID alphanumeric order)
each VDI, mounting it, and seeing if there is a suitable metadata file
present.  The first matching VDI is deemed to be the metadata VDI, and
is restored from.

In the general case, the content of VDIs are controlled by the VM owner,
and should not be trusted by the host administrator.

A malicious guest can manipulate its disk to appear to be a metadata
backup.

A guest cannot choose the UUIDs of its VDIs, but a guest with one disk
has a 50% chance of sorting ahead of the legitimate metadata backup.  A
guest with two disks has a 75% chance, etc.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0592 | SICK Lector8xx and InspectorP8xx vulnerable for code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0592</link><description>The vulnerability may allow a remote low priviledged attacker to run arbitrary shell commands by manipulating the firmware file and uploading it to the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0593 | SICK Lector8xx and InspectorP8xx vulnerable for code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0593</link><description>The vulnerability may allow a remote low priviledged attacker to run arbitrary shell commands by using lower-level functions to interact with the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:29:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25288 | @octokit/plugin-paginate-rest has a Regular Expression in iterator that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25288</link><description>@octokit/plugin-paginate-rest is the Octokit plugin to paginate REST API endpoint responses. For versions starting in 1.0.0 and prior to 11.4.1 of the npm package `@octokit/plugin-paginate-rest`, when calling `octokit.paginate.iterator()`, a specially crafted `octokit` instance—particularly with a malicious `link` parameter in the `headers` section of the `request`—can trigger a ReDoS attack. Version 11.4.1 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25289 | @octokit/request-error has a Regular Expression in index that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25289</link><description>@octokit/request-error is an error class for Octokit request errors. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 6.1.7, a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) vulnerability exists in the processing of HTTP request headers. By sending an authorization header containing an excessively long sequence of spaces followed by a newline and "@", an attacker can exploit inefficient regular expression processing, leading to excessive resource consumption. This can significantly degrade server performance or cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, impacting availability. Version 6.1.7 contains a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25290 | @octokit/request has a Regular Expression in fetchWrapper that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25290</link><description>@octokit/request sends parameterized requests to GitHub’s APIs with sensible defaults in browsers and Node. Starting in version 1.0.0 and prior to version 9.2.1, the regular expression `/&lt;([^&gt;]+)&gt;; rel="deprecation"/` used to match the `link` header in HTTP responses is vulnerable to a ReDoS (Regular Expression Denial of Service) attack. This vulnerability arises due to the unbounded nature of the regex's matching behavior, which can lead to catastrophic backtracking when processing specially crafted input. An attacker could exploit this flaw by sending a malicious `link` header, resulting in excessive CPU usage and potentially causing the server to become unresponsive, impacting service availability. Version 9.2.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25285 | @octokit/endpoint has a Regular Expression in parse that Leads to ReDoS Vulnerability Due to Catastrophic Backtracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25285</link><description>@octokit/endpoint turns REST API endpoints into generic request options. Starting in version 4.1.0 and prior to version 10.1.3, by crafting specific `options` parameters, the `endpoint.parse(options)` call can be triggered, leading to a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) attack. This causes the program to hang and results in high CPU utilization. The issue occurs in the `parse` function within the `parse.ts` file of the npm package `@octokit/endpoint`. Version 10.1.3 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25304 | Vega allows Cross-site Scripting via the vlSelectionTuples function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25304</link><description>Vega is a visualization grammar, a declarative format for creating, saving, and sharing interactive visualization designs. Prior to version 5.26.0 of vega and 5.4.2 of vega-selections, the `vlSelectionTuples` function can be used to call JavaScript functions, leading to cross-site scripting.`vlSelectionTuples` calls multiple functions that can be controlled by an attacker, including one call with an attacker-controlled argument. This can be used to call `Function()` with arbitrary JavaScript and the resulting function can be called with `vlSelectionTuples` or using a type coercion to call `toString` or `valueOf`. Version 5.26.0 of vega and 5.4.2 of vega-selections fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25296 | Label Studio allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) via GET request to `/projects/upload-example` endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25296</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. Prior to version 1.16.0, Label Studio's `/projects/upload-example` endpoint allows injection of arbitrary HTML through a `GET` request with an appropriately crafted `label_config` query parameter. By crafting a specially formatted XML label config with inline task data containing malicious HTML/JavaScript, an attacker can achieve Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). While the application has a Content Security Policy (CSP), it is only set in report-only mode, making it ineffective at preventing script execution. The vulnerability exists because the upload-example endpoint renders user-provided HTML content without proper sanitization on a GET request. This allows attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims' browsers by getting them to visit a maliciously crafted URL. This is considered vulnerable because it enables attackers to execute JavaScript in victims' contexts, potentially allowing theft of sensitive data, session hijacking, or other malicious actions. Version 1.16.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25297 | Label Studio allows Server-Side Request Forgery in the S3 Storage Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25297</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. Prior to version 1.16.0, Label Studio's S3 storage integration feature contains a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in its endpoint configuration. When creating an S3 storage connection, the application allows users to specify a custom S3 endpoint URL via the s3_endpoint parameter. This endpoint URL is passed directly to the boto3 AWS SDK without proper validation or restrictions on the protocol or destination. The vulnerability allows an attacker to make the application send HTTP requests to arbitrary internal services by specifying them as the S3 endpoint. When the storage sync operation is triggered, the application attempts to make S3 API calls to the specified endpoint, effectively making HTTP requests to the target service and returning the response in error messages. This SSRF vulnerability enables attackers to bypass network segmentation and access internal services that should not be accessible from the external network. The vulnerability is particularly severe because error messages from failed requests contain the full response body, allowing data exfiltration from internal services. Version 1.16.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0503 | Leaked User IDs and Metadata of Deleted DMs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0503</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.6 fail to filter out DMs from the deleted channels endpoint which allows an attacker to infer user IDs and other metadata from deleted DMs if someone had manually marked DMs as deleted in the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26507 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26507</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26508 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26508</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26506 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, HP LaserJet Managed Printers – Potential Remote Code Execution and Potential Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26506</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro, HP LaserJet Enterprise, and HP LaserJet Managed Printers may potentially be vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Elevation of Privilege when processing a PostScript print job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25206 | Incorrect input validation could allow an authenticated user to read sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25206</link><description>eLabFTW is an open source electronic lab notebook for research labs. Prior to version 5.1.15, an incorrect input validation could allow an authenticated user to read sensitive information, including login token or other content stored in the database. This could lead to privilege escalation if cookies are enabled (default setting). Users must upgrade to eLabFTW version 5.1.15 to receive a fix. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25295 | Label Studio has a Path Traversal Vulnerability via image Field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25295</link><description>Label Studio is an open source data labeling tool. A path traversal vulnerability in Label Studio SDK versions prior to 1.0.10 allows unauthorized file access outside the intended directory structure. The flaw exists in the VOC, COCO and YOLO export functionalities. These functions invoke a `download` function on the `label-studio-sdk` python package, which fails to validate file paths when processing image references during task exports. By creating tasks with path traversal sequences in the image field, an attacker can force the application to read files from arbitrary server filesystem locations when exporting projects in any of the mentioned formats. This is authentication-required vulnerability allowing arbitrary file reads from the server filesystem. It may lead to potential exposure of sensitive information like configuration files, credentials, and confidential data. Label Studio versions before 1.16.0 specified SDK versions prior to 1.0.10 as dependencies, and the issue was confirmed in Label Studio version 1.13.2.dev0; therefore, Label Studio users should upgrade to 1.16.0 or newer to mitigate it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8893 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GoodWe Technologies Co., Ltd. GW1500‑XS allows anyone in physical proximity to the device to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8893</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GoodWe Technologies Co., Ltd. GW1500‑XS allows anyone in physical proximity to the device to fully access the web interface of the inverter via Wi‑Fi.This issue affects GW1500‑XS: 1.1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25204 | `gh attestation verify` returns incorrect exit code during verification if no attestations are present</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25204</link><description>`gh` is GitHub’s official command line tool. Starting in version 2.49.0 and prior to version 2.67.0, under certain conditions, a bug in GitHub's Artifact Attestation cli tool `gh attestation verify` causes it to return a zero exit status when no attestations are present. This behavior is incorrect: When no attestations are present, `gh attestation verify` should return a non-zero exit status code, thereby signaling verification failure. An attacker can abuse this flaw to, for example, deploy malicious artifacts in any system that uses `gh attestation verify`'s exit codes to gatekeep deployments. Users are advised to update `gh` to patched version `v2.67.0` as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25991 | SQL Injection vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25991</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25992 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inquire_inout_item.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25992</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the inquire_inout_item.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25993 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameter "itemid."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25993</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameter "itemid."</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25997 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in FeMiner wms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the databak.php componen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25997</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in FeMiner wms v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the databak.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3220 | Default mimetype known files writeable on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3220</link><description>There is a defect in the CPython standard library module “mimetypes” where on Windows the default list of known file locations are writable meaning other users can create invalid files to cause MemoryError to be raised on Python runtime startup or have file extensions be interpreted as the incorrect file type.

This defect is caused by the default locations of Linux and macOS platforms (such as “/etc/mime.types”) also being used on Windows, where they are user-writable locations (“C:\etc\mime.types”).

To work-around this issue a user can call mimetypes.init() with an empty list (“[]”) on Windows platforms to avoid using the default list of known file locations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57790 | IXON B.V. IXrouter IX2400 (Industrial Edge Gateway) v3.0 was discovered to contain hardcoded root credentials stored in the non-volatile fla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57790</link><description>IXON B.V. IXrouter IX2400 (Industrial Edge Gateway) v3.0 was discovered to contain hardcoded root credentials stored in the non-volatile flash memory. This vulnerability allows physically proximate attackers to gain root access via UART or SSH.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25990 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25990</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.7.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /install/index.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25994 | SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameters date1, date2,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25994</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in FeMiner wms wms 1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the parameters date1, date2, id.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26157 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /bpms/index.php in Source Code and Project Beauty Parlour Management System V1.1, which allows re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26157</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /bpms/index.php in Source Code and Project Beauty Parlour Management System V1.1, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the name POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26158 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the manage-employee.php page of Kashipara Online Attendance Management S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26158</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the manage-employee.php page of Kashipara Online Attendance Management System V1.0. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary scripts via the department parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56463 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56463</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows a privileged user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25988 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.8 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the custom Link title paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25988</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in hooskcms v.1.8 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the custom Link title parameter and the Title parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26156 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /shopping/track-orders.php in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal v2.1, which allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26156</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /shopping/track-orders.php in PHPGurukul Online Shopping Portal v2.1, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via orderid POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 16:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57778 | An issue in Orbe ONetView Roeador Onet-1200 Orbe 1680210096 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the servers response from st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57778</link><description>An issue in Orbe ONetView Roeador Onet-1200 Orbe 1680210096 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the servers response from status code 500 to status code 200.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57725 | An issue in the Arcadyan Livebox Fibra PRV3399B_B_LT allows a remote or local attacker to modify the GPON link value without authentication,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57725</link><description>An issue in the Arcadyan Livebox Fibra PRV3399B_B_LT allows a remote or local attacker to modify the GPON link value without authentication, causing an internet service disruption via the /firstconnection.cgi endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56973 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Alvaria, Inc Unified IP Unified Director before v.7.2SP2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56973</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in Alvaria, Inc Unified IP Unified Director before v.7.2SP2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the source and filename parameters to the ProcessUploadFromURL.jsp component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:32:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25745 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetQuick...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25745</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the Password parameter in the SetQuickVPNSettings module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56477 | IBM Power Hardware Management Console directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56477</link><description>IBM Power Hardware Management Console V10.3.1050.0 could allow an authenticated user to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25740 | D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PSK parameter in the SetQuickVPNSe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25740</link><description>D-Link DIR-853 A1 FW1.20B07 was discovered to contain a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability via the PSK parameter in the SetQuickVPNSettings module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52895 | IBM i denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52895</link><description>IBM i 7.4 and 7.5 is vulnerable to a database access denial of service caused by a bypass of a database capabilities restriction check. A privileged bad actor can remove or otherwise impact database infrastructure files resulting in incorrect behavior of software products that rely upon the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56180 | Apache EventMesh: raft Hessian Deserialization Vulnerability allowing remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56180</link><description>CWE-502 Deserialization of Untrusted Data at the eventmesh-meta-raft plugin module in Apache EventMesh master branch without release version on windows\linux\mac os e.g. platforms allows attackers to send controlled message and remote code execute via hessian deserialization rpc protocol. Users can use the code under the master branch in project repo or version 1.11.0 to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12651 | Sensitive Data Exposure in PTT Inc.&amp;#x27;s HGS Mobile App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12651</link><description>Exposed Dangerous Method or Function vulnerability in PTT Inc. HGS Mobile App allows Manipulating User-Controlled Variables.This issue affects HGS Mobile App: before 6.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0178 | WatchGaurd Firebox Host Header Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0178</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows an attacker to manipulate the value of the HTTP Host header in requests sent to the Web UI. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to redirect users to malicious websites, poison the web cache, or inject malicious JavaScript into responses sent by the Web UI.
This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 up to and including 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1071 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in spamBlocker Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1071</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the spamBlocker module. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.5.12+701324, from 12.6 through 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1239 | WatchGuard Firebox Stored Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Blocked Sites List</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WatchGuard Fireware OS allows Stored XSS via the Blocked Sites list. This vulnerability requires an authenticated administrator session to a locally managed Firebox.This issue affects Fireware OS: from 12.0 through 12.5.12+701324, from 12.6 through 12.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13152 | SQLi in BSS Software&amp;#x27;s Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13152</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled SQL Primary Key vulnerability in BSS Software Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Mobuy Online Machinery Monitoring Panel: before 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52500 | WordPress Monetag Official Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52500</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in monetagwp Monetag Official Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Monetag Official Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0867 | Privilege Escalation in MEAC300-FNADE4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0867</link><description>The standard user uses the run as function to start the MEAC applications with administrative privileges. To ensure that the system can startup on its own, the credentials of the administrator were stored. Consequently, the EPC2 user can execute any command with administrative privileges. This allows a privilege escalation to the administrative level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22698 | WordPress Accessibility Suite by Ability, Inc plugin &amp;lt;= 4.16 - Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22698</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ability, Inc Accessibility Suite by Online ADA allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Accessibility Suite by Online ADA: from n/a through 4.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22702 | WordPress Photography theme &amp;lt;= 7.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22702</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in EPC Photography. This issue affects Photography: from n/a through 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22705 | WordPress Disqus Popular Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - CSRF to Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22705</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in godthor Disqus Popular Posts allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Disqus Popular Posts: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23428 | WordPress QMean plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound QMean – WordPress Did You Mean allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects QMean – WordPress Did You Mean: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23431 | WordPress Envato Affiliater plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23431</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Envato Affiliater allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Envato Affiliater: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23474 | WordPress Live Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23474</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mike Martel Live Dashboard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Live Dashboard: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23492 | WordPress 淘宝客插件 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23492</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CantonBolo WordPress 淘宝客插件 allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress 淘宝客插件: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23523 | WordPress HSS Embed Streaming Video plugin &amp;lt;= 3.23 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23523</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hoststreamsell HSS Embed Streaming Video allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects HSS Embed Streaming Video: from n/a through 3.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23525 | WordPress Kv Compose Email From Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23525</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in kvvaradha Kv Compose Email From Dashboard allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Kv Compose Email From Dashboard: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23534 | WordPress WPLingo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23534</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mark Winiarski WPLingo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WPLingo: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23568 | WordPress WP Login Attempt Log plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23568</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fredsted WP Login Attempt Log allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Login Attempt Log: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23571 | WordPress Internal Links Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.51 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Internal Links Generator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Internal Links Generator: from n/a through 3.51.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23598 | WordPress Recip.ly plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in craig.edmunds@gmail.com Recip.ly allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Recip.ly: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23646 | WordPress Library Instruction Recorder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23646</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matt Brooks Library Instruction Recorder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Library Instruction Recorder: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23647 | WordPress WP-Clap plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23647</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ariagle WP-Clap allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP-Clap: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23648 | WordPress AdsMiddle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23648</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wjharil AdsMiddle allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AdsMiddle: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23650 | WordPress Tidy.ro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23650</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in razvypp Tidy.ro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tidy.ro: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23651 | WordPress Scroll Top plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23651</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Scroll Top allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Scroll Top: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23652 | WordPress Add custom content after post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23652</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Add custom content after post allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Add custom content after post: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23653 | WordPress Form To Online Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23653</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Form To Online Booking allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Form To Online Booking: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23655 | WordPress Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23655</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 – Paystack Add-on: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23657 | WordPress WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress-to-candidate for Salesforce CRM: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23658 | WordPress Advanced Angular Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23658</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tauhidul Alam Advanced Angular Contact Form allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Advanced Angular Contact Form: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23742 | WordPress Podamibe Twilio Private Call plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Podamibe Nepal Podamibe Twilio Private Call allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Podamibe Twilio Private Call: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23748 | WordPress Singsys -Awesome Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Singsys -Awesome Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Singsys -Awesome Gallery: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23750 | WordPress Custom Widget Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23750</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in devbunchuk Custom Widget Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Widget Creator: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23751 | WordPress Data Dash plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23751</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 Data Dash allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Data Dash: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23766 | WordPress OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23766</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ashamil OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects OPSI Israel Domestic Shipments: from n/a through 2.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23771 | WordPress Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23771</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Murali Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Push Notification for Post and BuddyPress: from n/a through 2.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23786 | WordPress Email to Download Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23786</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DuoGeek Email to Download allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Email to Download: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23787 | WordPress Easy Bet Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23787</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Easy Bet allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Bet: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23788 | WordPress Easy Filter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23788</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Easy Filter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Filter: from n/a through 1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23789 | WordPress URL Shortener WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23789</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in tahminajannat URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce: from n/a through 9.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23790 | WordPress Easy Code Placement Plugin &amp;lt;= 18.11 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23790</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wassereimer Easy Code Placement allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Code Placement: from n/a through 18.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23851 | WordPress Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23851</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Coronavirus (COVID-19) Outbreak Data Widgets: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23853 | WordPress NoFollow Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23853</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in michelem NoFollow Free allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects NoFollow Free: from n/a through 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23857 | WordPress Essential WP Real Estate Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23857</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Essential WP Real Estate allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Essential WP Real Estate: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23905 | WordPress Admin Options Pages plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23905</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Johannes van Poelgeest Admin Options Pages allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Admin Options Pages: from n/a through 0.9.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24554 | WordPress AWcode Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in awcode AWcode Toolkit allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AWcode Toolkit: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24558 | WordPress CRM Perks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CRM Perks CRM Perks allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CRM Perks: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24564 | WordPress Contact Form With Shortcode plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in aviplugins.com Contact Form With Shortcode allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Contact Form With Shortcode: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24565 | WordPress WP2LEADS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Saleswonder Team Tobias WP2LEADS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP2LEADS: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24566 | WordPress Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tomáš Groulík Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Intro Tour Tutorial DeepPresentation: from n/a through 6.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24567 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24567</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24592 | WordPress SysBasics Customize My Account for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.22 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SysBasics Customize My Account for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Customize My Account for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.8.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24607 | WordPress IdeaPush plugin &amp;lt;= 8.71 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24607</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Northern Beaches Websites IdeaPush allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects IdeaPush: from n/a through 8.71.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24614 | WordPress Post Timeline Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24614</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in agileLogix Post Timeline allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Post Timeline: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24615 | WordPress Analytics Cat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24615</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fatcatapps Analytics Cat allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Analytics Cat: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24616 | WordPress Uix Page Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24616</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UIUX Lab Uix Page Builder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Uix Page Builder: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24617 | WordPress AcyMailing Plugin &amp;lt; 9.11.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24617</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AcyMailing Newsletter Team AcyMailing SMTP Newsletter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AcyMailing SMTP Newsletter: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24641 | WordPress Better WishList API plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24641</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rickonline_nl Better WishList API allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Better WishList API: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24688 | WordPress WP Mailster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.20.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24688</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in brandtoss WP Mailster allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.20.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24692 | WordPress Bulk Menu Edit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24692</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Michael Revellin-Clerc Bulk Menu Edit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Bulk Menu Edit: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24699 | WordPress WP Coder Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6 -  CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24699</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Wow-Company WP Coder allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). This issue affects WP Coder: from n/a through 3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24700 | WordPress WP Event Aggregator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xylus Themes WP Event Aggregator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Event Aggregator: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:59:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26524 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26524</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoints which could lead to the OTP bombing/ flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26523 | Insufficient Authorization Vulnerability in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26523</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to insufficient authorization controls on certain API endpoints handling addition and deletion operations. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an authenticated remote attacker to modify information belonging to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26522 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability  in RupeeWeb trading platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26522</link><description>This vulnerability exists in RupeeWeb trading platform due to improper implementation of OTP validation mechanism in certain API endpoints. A remote attacker with valid credentials could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API responses.  

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) for other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13791 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Path Traversal to Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Read via downloadResponseFile Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13791</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the downloadResponseFile() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0821 | Bit Assist &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0821</link><description>Bit Assist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 11:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52577 | Apache Ignite: Possible RCE when deserializing incoming messages by the server node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52577</link><description>In Apache Ignite versions from 2.6.0 and before 2.17.0, configured Class Serialization Filters are ignored for some Ignite endpoints. The vulnerability could be exploited if an attacker manually crafts an Ignite message containing a vulnerable object whose class is present in the Ignite server classpath and sends it to Ignite server endpoints. Deserialization of such a message by the Ignite server may result in the execution of arbitrary code on the Apache Ignite server side.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 10:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13735 | HurryTimer &amp;lt;= 2.11.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Campaign Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13735</link><description>The HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping of a campaign name. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26791 | DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26791</link><description>DOMPurify before 3.2.4 has an incorrect template literal regular expression, sometimes leading to mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 08:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26789 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26789</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint AgentX before 1.5.0. A vulnerability caused by limited access controls allowed li-admin users to access sensitive information about AgentX Manager in a Logpoint deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1298 | Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1298</link><description>Logic vulnerability in the mobile application (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to the risk of account takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26788 | StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26788</link><description>StrongKey FIDO Server before 4.15.1 treats a non-discoverable (namedcredential) flow as a discoverable transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22630 | WordPress Widget Options Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Arbitrary Code Execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in MarketingFire Widget Options allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Widget Options: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 07:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9601 | Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;align&amp;#x27; and &amp;#x27;UniqueID&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9601</link><description>The Qubely – Advanced Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’  and 'UniqueID' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57969 | app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57969</link><description>app/Model/Attribute.php in MISP before 2.4.198 ignores an ACL during a GUI attribute search.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13493 | Sensly Online Presence &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13493</link><description>The Sensly Online Presence WordPress plugin through 0.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7052 | Forminator &amp;lt; 1.38.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7052</link><description>The Forminator Forms  WordPress plugin before 1.38.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 06:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13641 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13641</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via the 'attachment' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/attachment directory which can contain file attachments for order refunds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13692 | Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13692</link><description>The Return Refund and Exchange For WooCommerce – Return Management System, RMA Exchange, Wallet And Cancel Order Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via several functions due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to overwrite linked refund image attachments, overwrite refund request message, overwrite order messages, and read order messages of other users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 05:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2240 | Docker implementation in Brocade SANnav is missing Audit Rules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2240</link><description>Docker daemon in Brocade SANnav before SANnav 2.3.1b runs without auditing. The vulnerability could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute various attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23406 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, whic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23406</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability caused by improper checking of TCP MSS option values exists in Cente middleware TCP/IP Network Series, which may lead to processing a specially crafted packet to cause the affected product crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 04:35:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1053 | Brocade SANnav encryption key is logged in the debug logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1053</link><description>Under certain error conditions at time of SANnav installation or upgrade, the encryption key can be written into and obtained from a Brocade SANnav supportsave.  An attacker with privileged access to the Brocade SANnav database could use the encryption key to obtain passwords used by Brocade SANnav.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26519 | musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26519</link><description>musl libc 0.9.13 through 1.2.5 before 1.2.6 has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability when an attacker can trigger iconv conversion of untrusted EUC-KR text to UTF-8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10404 | Clear text password seen in switch-asset-collectors-mw in Brocade SANnav supportsave</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10404</link><description>CalInvocationHandler in Brocade 
SANnav before 2.3.1b logs sensitive information in clear text. The 
vulnerability could allow an authenticated, local attacker to view 
Brocade Fabric OS switch sensitive information in clear text. An 
attacker with administrative privileges could retrieve sensitive 
information including passwords; SNMP responses that contain AuthSecret 
and PrivSecret after collecting a “supportsave” or getting access to an 
already collected “supportsave”. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-29952</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55904 | IBM DevOps Deploy / IBM UrbanCode Deploy command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55904</link><description>IBM DevOps Deploy 8.0 through 8.0.1.4, 8.1 through 8.1.0.0 / IBM UrbanCode Deploy 7.0 through 7.0.5.25, 7.1 through 7.1.2.21, 7.2 through 7.2.3.14, and 7.3 through 7.3.2.9 could allow a remote privileged authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the system by sending specially crafted input containing special elements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 03:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>