<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-31913 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31913</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.2 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31914 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31914</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.2 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51111 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Pnetlab 5.3.11 allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into a web page, which are execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51111</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Pnetlab 5.3.11 allows an attacker to inject malicious scripts into a web page, which are executed in the context of the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51112 | Open Redirect vulnerability in Pnetlab 5.3.11 allows an attacker to manipulate URLs to redirect users to arbitrary external websites via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51112</link><description>Open Redirect vulnerability in Pnetlab 5.3.11 allows an attacker to manipulate URLs to redirect users to arbitrary external websites via a crafted script</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21612 | Cross-site Scripting in TabberTransclude in Extension:TabberNeue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21612</link><description>TabberNeue is a MediaWiki extension that allows the wiki to create tabs. Prior to 2.7.2, TabberTransclude.php doesn't escape the user-supplied page name when outputting, so an XSS payload as the page name can be used here. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21611 | tgstation-server&amp;#x27;s role authorization incorrectly OR&amp;#x27;d with user&amp;#x27;s enabled status</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21611</link><description>tgstation-server is a production scale tool for BYOND server management. Prior to 6.12.3, roles used to authorize API methods were incorrectly OR'd instead of AND'ed with the role used to determine if a user was enabled. This allows enabled users access to most, but not all, authorized actions regardless of their permissions. Notably, the WriteUsers right is unaffected so users may not use this bug to permanently elevate their account permissions. The fix is release in tgstation-server-v6.12.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:51:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21604 | LangChain4j-AIDeepin Using MD5 to Hash files may cause file upload conflicts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21604</link><description>LangChain4j-AIDeepin is a Retrieval enhancement generation (RAG) project. Prior to 3.5.0, LangChain4j-AIDeepin uses MD5 to hash files, which may cause file upload conflicts. This issue is fixed in 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8474 | OpenVPN Connect before version 3.5.0 can contain the configuration profile's clear-text private key which is logged in the application log, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8474</link><description>OpenVPN Connect before version 3.5.0 can contain the configuration profile's clear-text private key which is logged in the application log, which an unauthorized actor can use to decrypt the VPN traffic</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5594 | OpenVPN before 2.6.11 does not santize PUSH_REPLY messages properly which attackers can use to inject unexpected arbitrary data into third-p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5594</link><description>OpenVPN before 2.6.11 does not santize PUSH_REPLY messages properly which attackers can use to inject unexpected arbitrary data into third-party executables or plug-ins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12970 | OS Command Injection in TUBITAK BILGEM&amp;#x27;s Pardus OS My Computer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12970</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in TUBITAK BILGEM Pardus OS My Computer allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Pardus OS My Computer: before 0.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21464 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21464</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IPA statistics, when there are no active clients registered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23366 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive Autonomy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23366</link><description>Information Disclosure while invoking the mailbox write API when message received from user is larger than mailbox size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33041 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33041</link><description>Memory corruption when input parameter validation for number of fences is missing for fence frame IOCTL calls,</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33055 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33055</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls to unmap the DMA buffers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33059 | Use After Free in Computer Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33059</link><description>Memory corruption while processing frame command IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33061 | Buffer Over-read in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33061</link><description>Information disclosure while processing IOCTL call made for releasing a trusted VM process release or opening a channel without initializing the process.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33067 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33067</link><description>Information disclosure while invoking callback function of sound model driver from ADSP for every valid opcode received from sound model driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43063 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive Autonomy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43063</link><description>information disclosure while invoking the mailbox read API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43064 | Permissions, Privileges, and Access Controls issue in Automotive OS Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43064</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption when a driver, an application or a SMMU client tries to access the global registers through SMMU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45541 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45541</link><description>Memory corruption when IOCTL call is invoked from user-space to read board data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45542 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45542</link><description>Memory corruption when IOCTL call is invoked from user-space to write board data to WLAN driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45546 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45546</link><description>Memory corruption while processing FIPS encryption or decryption IOCTL call invoked from user-space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45547 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45547</link><description>Memory corruption while processing IOCTL call invoked from user-space to verify non extension FIPS encryption and decryption functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45548 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45548</link><description>Memory corruption while processing FIPS encryption or decryption validation functionality IOCTL call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45550 | Improper Validation of Array Index in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45550</link><description>Memory corruption occurs when invoking any IOCTL-calling application that executes all MCDM driver IOCTL calls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45553 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45553</link><description>Memory corruption can occur when process-specific maps are added to the global list. If a map is removed from the global list while another thread is using it for a process-specific task, issues may arise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45555 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Automotive OS Platform QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45555</link><description>Memory corruption can occur if an already verified IFS2 image is overwritten, bypassing boot verification. This allows unauthorized programs to be injected into security-sensitive images, enabling the booting of a tampered IFS2 system image.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45558 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Cmn</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45558</link><description>Transient DOS can occur when the driver parses the per STA profile IE and tries to access the EXTN element ID without checking the IE length.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45559 | Buffer Over-read in Automotive OS Platform QNX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45559</link><description>Transient DOS can occur when GVM sends a specific message type to the Vdev-FastRPC backend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11356 | Tourmaster &amp;lt; 5.3.4 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS via Room Booking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11356</link><description>The tourmaster WordPress plugin before 5.3.4 does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputting them in the page, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 06:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11849 | Pods – Custom Content Types and Fields &amp;lt; 3.2.8.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11849</link><description>The Pods  WordPress plugin before 3.2.8.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 06:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12302 | Icegram Engage &amp;lt; 3.1.32 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12302</link><description>The Icegram Engage  WordPress plugin before 3.1.32 does not sanitise and escape some of its Campaign settings, which could allow authors and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 06:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12311 | Email Subscribers &amp;lt; 5.7.44 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12311</link><description>The Email Subscribers by Icegram Express  WordPress plugin before 5.7.44 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 06:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20105 | In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20105</link><description>In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09062027; Issue ID: MSV-1743.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20140 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20140</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09270402; Issue ID: MSV-2020.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20143 | In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20143</link><description>In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09167056; Issue ID: MSV-2069.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20144 | In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20144</link><description>In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09167056; Issue ID: MSV-2041.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20145 | In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20145</link><description>In V6 DA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege, if an attacker has physical access to the device, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09290940; Issue ID: MSV-2040.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20146 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20146</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00389496 / ALPS09137491; Issue ID: MSV-1835.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20148 | In wlan STA FW, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20148</link><description>In wlan STA FW, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote (proximal/adjacent) code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00389045 / ALPS09136494; Issue ID: MSV-1796.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20149 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20149</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01231341 / MOLY01263331 / MOLY01233835; Issue ID: MSV-2165.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20150 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a logic error. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20150</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a logic error. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01412526; Issue ID: MSV-2018.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20151 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20151</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01399339; Issue ID: MSV-1928.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20152 | In wlan STA driver, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to local denial of service i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20152</link><description>In wlan STA driver, there is a possible reachable assertion due to improper exception handling. This could lead to local denial of service if a malicious actor has already obtained the System privilege. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00389047 / ALPS09136505; Issue ID: MSV-1798.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20153 | In wlan STA, there is a possible way to trick a client to connect to an AP with spoofed SSID. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20153</link><description>In wlan STA, there is a possible way to trick a client to connect to an AP with spoofed SSID. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08990446 / ALPS09057442; Issue ID: MSV-1598.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20154 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20154</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution, if a UE has connected to a rogue base station controlled by the attacker, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00720348; Issue ID: MSV-2392.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 03:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13145 | zhenfeng13 My-Blog uploadController. java upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13145</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in zhenfeng13 My-Blog 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function upload of the file src/main/java/com/site/blog/my/core/controller/admin/uploadController. java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13144 | zhenfeng13 My-Blog BlogController.java uploadFileByEditomd unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13144</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in zhenfeng13 My-Blog 1.0. Affected is the function uploadFileByEditomd of the file src/main/java/com/site/blog/my/core/controller/admin/BlogController.java. The manipulation of the argument editormd-image-file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 01:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13143 | ZeroWdd studentmanager PermissionController. java submitAddPermission cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13143</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function submitAddPermission of the file src/main/java/com/zero/system/controller/PermissionController. java. The manipulation of the argument url leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 23:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13142 | ZeroWdd studentmanager RoleController. java submitAddRole cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function submitAddRole of the file src/main/java/com/zero/system/controller/RoleController. java. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 23:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0233 | Codezips Project Management System course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0233</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Project Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /pages/forms/course.php. The manipulation of the argument course_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 22:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0232 | Codezips Blood Bank Management System successadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0232</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Blood Bank Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /successadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument psw leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 22:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0231 | Codezips Gym Management System submit_payments.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0231</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/admin/submit_payments.php. The manipulation of the argument m_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0230 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0230</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/print.php. The manipulation of the argument pid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0229 | code-projects Travel Management System enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0229</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Travel Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /enquiry.php. The manipulation of the argument pid/t1/t2/t3/t4/t5/t6/t7 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 19:35:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0228 | code-projects Local Storage Todo App index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0228</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Local Storage Todo App 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /js-todo-app/index.html. The manipulation of the argument Add leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 18:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0227 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System downLoad.html information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0227</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System 3.2.210802(62532). This affects an unknown part of the file /Logs/Annals/downLoad.html. The manipulation of the argument path leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0226 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System downLoad.html download information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0226</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System 3.2.210802(62532). Affected by this issue is the function download of the file /collect/PortV4/downLoad.html. The manipulation of the argument path leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 17:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0225 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System exampleDownload.html path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0225</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives System 3.2.210802(62532). Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /setting/ClassFy/exampleDownload.html. The manipulation of the argument name leads to path traversal: '/../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 17:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0224 | Provision-ISR SH-4050A-2 server.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0224</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Provision-ISR SH-4050A-2, SH-4100A-2L(MM), SH-8100A-2L(MM), SH-16200A-2(1U), SH-16200A-5(1U) and NVR5-8200PX up to 20241220. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /server.js. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0223 | IObit Protected Folder IOCTL IURegistryFilter.sys 0x8001E010 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0223</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Protected Folder up to 13.6.0.5. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function 0x8001E000/0x8001E00C/0x8001E004/0x8001E010 in the library IURegistryFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 16:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0222 | IObit Protected Folder IOCTL IUProcessFilter.sys 0x8001E004 null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0222</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IObit Protected Folder up to 13.6.0.5 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function 0x8001E000/0x8001E004 in the library IUProcessFilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 15:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0221 | IOBit Protected Folder IOCTL pffilter.sys 0x22200c null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0221</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in IOBit Protected Folder up to 1.3.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function 0x22200c in the library pffilter.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13141 | osuuu LightPicture SVG File Upload upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13141</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in osuuu LightPicture up to 1.2.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/upload of the component SVG File Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 14:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0220 | Trimble SPS851 Ethernet Configuration Menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0220</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Trimble SPS851 488.01. This affects an unknown part of the component Ethernet Configuration Menu. The manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 12:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13140 | Emlog Pro Cover Upload article.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13140</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/article.php?action=upload_cover of the component Cover Upload Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 11:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13139 | wangl1989 mysiteforme FileController doContent server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13139</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function doContent of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteform/admin/controller/system/FileController. The manipulation of the argument content leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 11:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13138 | wangl1989 mysiteforme LocalUploadServiceImpl upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function upload of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteform/admin/service/ipl/LocalUploadServiceImpl. The manipulation of the argument test leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13137 | wangl1989 mysiteforme SiteController RestResponse cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13137</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function RestResponse of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteforme/admin/controller/system/SiteController. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 10:07:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13136 | wangl1989 mysiteforme ShiroConfig.java rememberMeManager deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13136</link><description>A vulnerability was found in wangl1989 mysiteforme 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function rememberMeManager of the file src/main/java/com/mysiteforme/admin/config/ShiroConfig.java. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 09:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13135 | Emlog Pro Subpage twitter.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13135</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Emlog Pro 2.4.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/twitter.php of the component Subpage Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 08:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13134 | ZeroWdd studentmanager TeacherController. java editTeacher unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13134</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. Affected is the function addTeacher/editTeacher of the file src/main/Java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/TeacherController. java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 08:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0219 | Trimble SPS851 Receiver Status Identity Tab cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0219</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Trimble SPS851 488.01. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Receiver Status Identity Tab. The manipulation of the argument System Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 05:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13133 | ZeroWdd studentmanager StudentController. java editStudent unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13133</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ZeroWdd studentmanager 1.0. This issue affects the function addStudent/editStudent of the file src/main/Java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/StudentController. java. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 05:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13132 | Emlog Pro Subpage article.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13132</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Emlog Pro up to 2.4.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/article.php of the component Subpage Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13131 | Dahua IPC-HFW1200S Web Interface webCapsConfig information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13131</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Dahua IPC-HFW1200S, IPC-HFW2300R-Z, IPC-HFW5220E-Z and IPC-HDW1200S up to 20241222. This affects an unknown part of the file /web_caps/webCapsConfig of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 03:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13130 | Dahua IPC-HFW1200S Web Interface Sha1Account1 path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13130</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Dahua IPC-HFW1200S, IPC-HFW2300R-Z, IPC-HFW5220E-Z and IPC-HDW1200S up to 20241222. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ../mtd/Config/Sha1Account1 of the component Web Interface. The manipulation leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 01:12:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0214 | TMD Custom Header Menu index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0214</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TMD Custom Header Menu 4.0.0.1 on OpenCart. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument headermenu_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0213 | Campcodes Project Management System update_forms.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0213</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Project Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forms/update_forms.php?action=change_pic2&amp;amp;id=4. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 16:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0212 | Campcodes Student Grading System view_students.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0212</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Student Grading System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /view_students.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0211 | Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System index.php file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument page leads to file inclusion. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41763 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41763</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3  uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41765 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41765</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41766 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41766</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3  could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service using a complex regular expression.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41767 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41767</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 is vulnerable to SQL injection. A remote attacker could send specially crafted SQL statements, which could allow the attacker to view, add, modify, or delete information in the back-end database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41768 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing unhandled SLL exception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41768</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Publishing 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to cause an unhandled SSL exception which could leave the connection in an unexpected or insecure state.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0210 | Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes School Faculty Scheduling System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10957 | UpdraftPlus: WP Backup &amp;amp; Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.24.11 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10957</link><description>The UpdraftPlus: WP Backup &amp; Migration Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.24.11 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'recursive_unserialized_replace' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must perform a search and replace action to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0208 | code-projects Online Shoe Store summary.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0208</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /summary.php. The manipulation of the argument tid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0207 | code-projects Online Shoe Store login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0207</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /function/login.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0206 | code-projects Online Shoe Store index.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0206</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12195 | WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts &amp;lt;= 2.6.16 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12195</link><description>The WP Project Manager – Task, team, and project management plugin featuring kanban board and gantt charts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'project_id' parameter of the /wp-json/pm/v2/projects/2/task-lists REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.16 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, who have been granted access to a project, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12279 | WP Social AutoConnect &amp;lt;= 4.6.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12279</link><description>The WP Social AutoConnect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.6.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12475 | WP Multi Store Locator &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12475</link><description>The WP Multi Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12221 | Turnkey bbPress by WeaverTheme &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via _wpnonce Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12221</link><description>The Turnkey bbPress by WeaverTheme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘_wpnonce’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 09:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0205 | code-projects Online Shoe Store details2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0205</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /details2.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 09:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11930 | Taskbuilder – WordPress Project &amp;amp; Task Management plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wppm_tasks Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11930</link><description>The Taskbuilder – WordPress Project &amp; Task Management plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wppm_tasks shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 08:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12583 | Dynamics 365 Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution and Arbitrary File Read via Twig Server-Side Template Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12583</link><description>The Dynamics 365 Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution and Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.23 via Twig Server-Side Template Injection. This is due to missing input validation and sanitization on the render function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 08:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0204 | code-projects Online Shoe Store details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0204</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shoe Store 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /details.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10932 | Backup Migration &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via &amp;#x27;recursive_unserialize_replace&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10932</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'recursive_unserialize_replace' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must create a staging site in order to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11974 | Media Library Assistant &amp;lt;= 3.23 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via smc_settings_tab, unattachfixit-action, and woofixit-action Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11974</link><description>The Media Library Assistant plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘smc_settings_tab', 'unattachfixit-action', and 'woofixit-action’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12047 | WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp;amp; Speed Optimization &amp;lt;= 6.30.03 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via custom_server Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12047</link><description>The WP Compress – Instant Performance &amp; Speed Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘custom_server’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.30.03 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12545 | Scratch &amp;amp; Win – Giveaways and Contests &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via reset_installation Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12545</link><description>The Scratch &amp; Win – Giveaways and Contests. Boost subscribers, traffic, repeat visits,  referrals, sales and more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This is due to missing nonce validation on the reset_installation() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the plugin’s installation via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12701 | WP Smart Import : Import any XML File to WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12701</link><description>The WP Smart Import : Import any XML File to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ page’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0203 | code-projects Student Management System DbFunction.php showSubject1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0203</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function showSubject1 of the file /config/DbFunction.php. The manipulation of the argument sid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 07:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0202 | TCS BaNCS REPORTS_SHOW_FILE.jsp file inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0202</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TCS BaNCS 10. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /REPORTS/REPORTS_SHOW_FILE.jsp. The manipulation of the argument FilePath leads to file inclusion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 05:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0201 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System update_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0201</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/update_account.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0200 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System search_num.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0200</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/search_num.php. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22383 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity input validation issue exists in the Commerce B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22383</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity input validation issue exists in the Commerce B2B application, affecting the Contact Us functionality. This allows visitors to send e-mail messages that could contain unfiltered HTML markup in specific scenarios.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22384 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue concerning business logic exists in the C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22384</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue concerning business logic exists in the Commerce B2B application, which allows storefront visitors to purchase discontinued products in specific scenarios where requests are altered before reaching the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22385 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. For newly created accounts, the Commerce B2B application does not...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22385</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. For newly created accounts, the Commerce B2B application does not require email confirmation. This medium-severity issue allows the mass creation of accounts. This could affect database storage; also, non-requested storefront accounts can be created on behalf of visitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22386 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity session issue exists in the Commerce B2B applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22386</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity session issue exists in the Commerce B2B application, affecting the longevity of active sessions in the storefront. This allows session tokens tied to logged-out sessions to still be active and usable.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22387 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue exists in requests for resources where th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22387</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely Configured Commerce before 5.2.2408. A medium-severity issue exists in requests for resources where the session token is submitted as a URL parameter. This exposes information about the authenticated session, which can be leveraged for session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22388 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.22.0. A high-severity Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22388</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.22.0. A high-severity Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the CMS, allowing malicious actors to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript code, potentially compromising user data, escalating privileges, or executing unauthorized actions. The issue exists in multiple areas, including content editing, link management, and file uploads.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22389 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS, where the applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22389</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS, where the application does not properly validate uploaded files. This allows the upload of potentially malicious file types, including .docm .html. When accessed by application users, these files can be used to execute malicious actions or compromise users' systems.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22390 | An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS due to insufficie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22390</link><description>An issue was discovered in Optimizely EPiServer.CMS.Core before 12.32.0. A medium-severity vulnerability exists in the CMS due to insufficient enforcement of password complexity requirements. The application permits users to set passwords with a minimum length of 6 characters, lacking adequate complexity to resist modern attack techniques such as password spraying or offline password cracking.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 02:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>