<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:39:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-22922 | An issue in Projectworlds Vistor Management Systemin PHP v.1.0 allows a remtoe attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22922</link><description>An issue in Projectworlds Vistor Management Systemin PHP v.1.0 allows a remtoe attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted script to the login page in the POST/index.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23055 | An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software allows for remote code execution via improper validation of input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23055</link><description>An issue in Plone Docker Official Image 5.2.13 (5221) open-source software allows for remote code execution via improper validation of input by the HOST headers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0886 | Poikosoft EZ CD Audio Converter Activation denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0886</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Poikosoft EZ CD Audio Converter 8.0.7. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Activation Handler. The manipulation of the argument Key leads to denial of service. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252037 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0885 | SpyCamLizard HTTP GET Request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0885</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SpyCamLizard 1.230. Affected is an unknown function of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252036.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52046 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability (XSS) in webmin v.2.105 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52046</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability (XSS) in webmin v.2.105 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the "Execute cron job as" tab Input field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52251 | An issue discovered in provectus kafka-ui 0.4.0 through 0.7.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the q parameter of /api/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52251</link><description>An issue discovered in provectus kafka-ui 0.4.0 through 0.7.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the q parameter of /api/clusters/local/topics/{topic}/messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0884 | SourceCodester Online Tours &amp;amp; Travels Management System payment.php exec sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0884</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Tours &amp; Travels Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function exec of the file payment.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252035.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22635 | WebCalendar v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /WebCalendarvqsmnseug2/e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22635</link><description>WebCalendar v1.3.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /WebCalendarvqsmnseug2/edit_entry.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22636 | PluXml Blog v5.8.9 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Static Pages feature. This vulnerability is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22636</link><description>PluXml Blog v5.8.9 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in the Static Pages feature. This vulnerability is exploited via injecting a crafted payload into the Content field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22637 | Form Tools v3.1.1 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /form_builder/preview.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22637</link><description>Form Tools v3.1.1 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /form_builder/preview.php?form_id=2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22638 | liveSite v2019.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulenrabiity via the component /livesite/edit_designer_region.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22638</link><description>liveSite v2019.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulenrabiity via the component /livesite/edit_designer_region.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22639 | iGalerie v3.0.22 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Titre (Title) field in the editing i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22639</link><description>iGalerie v3.0.22 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the Titre (Title) field in the editing interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24399 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in LeptonCMS v7.0.0 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24399</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in LeptonCMS v7.0.0 allows authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:28:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52355 | Libtiff: tiffrasterscanlinesize64 produce too-big size and could cause oom</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52355</link><description>An out-of-memory flaw was found in libtiff that could be triggered by passing a crafted tiff file to the TIFFRasterScanlineSize64() API. This flaw allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted input with a size smaller than 379 KB.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52356 | Libtiff: segment fault in libtiff  in tiffreadrgbatileext() leading to denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52356</link><description>A segment fault (SEGV) flaw was found in libtiff that could be triggered by passing a crafted tiff file to the TIFFReadRGBATileExt() API. This flaw allows a remote attacker to cause a heap-buffer overflow, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41474 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.4.153 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41474</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Ivanti Avalanche 6.3.4.153 allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information via the javax.faces.resource component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23656 | Dex 2.37.0 is discarding TLSconfig and always serves deprecated TLS 1.0/1.1 and insecure ciphers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23656</link><description>Dex is an identity service that uses OpenID Connect to drive authentication for other apps. Dex 2.37.0 serves HTTPS with insecure TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1. `cmd/dex/serve.go` line 425 seemingly sets TLS 1.2 as minimum version, but the whole `tlsConfig` is ignored after `TLS cert reloader` was introduced in v2.37.0. Configured cipher suites are not respected either. This issue is fixed in Dex 2.38.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23655 | Attacker can prevent users from accessing received emails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23655</link><description>Tuta is an encrypted email service. Starting in version 3.118.12 and prior to version 3.119.10, an attacker is able to send a manipulated email so that the user can no longer use the app to get access to received emails. By sending a manipulated email, an attacker could put the app into an unusable state. In this case, a user can no longer access received e-mails. Since the vulnerability affects not only the app, but also the web application, a user in this case has no way to access received emails. This issue was tested with iOS and the web app, but it is possible all clients are affected. Version 3.119.10 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23817 | Dolibarr Application Home Page HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23817</link><description>Dolibarr is an enterprise resource planning (ERP) and customer relationship management (CRM) software package. Version 18.0.4 has a HTML Injection vulnerability in the Home page of the Dolibarr Application. This vulnerability allows an attacker to inject arbitrary HTML tags and manipulate the rendered content in the application's response. Specifically, I was able to successfully inject a new HTML tag into the returned document and, as a result, was able to comment out some part of the Dolibarr App Home page HTML code. This behavior can be exploited to perform various attacks like Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). To remediate the issue, validate and sanitize all user-supplied input, especially within HTML attributes, to prevent HTML injection attacks; and implement proper output encoding when rendering user-provided data to ensure it is treated as plain text rather than executable HTML.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21630 | Zulip non-admins can invite new users to streams they would not otherwise be able to add existing users to</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21630</link><description>Zulip is an open-source team collaboration tool. A vulnerability in version 8.0 is similar to CVE-2023-32677, but applies to multi-use invitations, not single-use invitation links as in the prior CVE. Specifically, it applies when the installation has configured non-admins to be able to invite users and create multi-use invitations, and has also configured only admins to be able to invite users to streams. As in CVE-2023-32677, this does not let users invite new users to arbitrary streams, only to streams that the inviter can already see. Version 8.1 fixes this issue. As a workaround, administrators can limit sending of invitations down to users who also have the permission to add users to streams.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0882 | qwdigital LinkWechat Universal Download Interface resource path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in qwdigital LinkWechat 5.1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /linkwechat-api/common/download/resource of the component Universal Download Interface. The manipulation of the argument name with the input /profile/../../../../../etc/passwd leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252033 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0883 | SourceCodester Online Tours &amp;amp; Travels Management System pay.php prepare sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0883</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Tours &amp; Travels Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function prepare of the file admin/pay.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252034 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7227 | Command Injection vulnerability in SystemK NVR 504/508/516</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7227</link><description>SystemK NVR 504/508/516 versions 2.3.5SK.30084998 and prior are vulnerable to a command injection vulnerability in the dynamic domain name system (DDNS) settings that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6267 | Quarkus: json payload getting processed prior to security checks when rest resources  are used with annotations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6267</link><description>A flaw was found in the json payload. If annotation based security is used to secure a REST resource, the JSON body that the resource may consume is being processed (deserialized) prior to the security constraints being evaluated and applied. This does not happen with configuration based security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0880 | Qidianbang qdbcrm Password Reset cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0880</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Qidianbang qdbcrm 1.1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/edit?id=2 of the component Password Reset. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252032. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22749 | GPAC v2.3 was detected to contain a buffer overflow via the function gf_isom_new_generic_sample_description function in the isomedia/isom_wr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22749</link><description>GPAC v2.3 was detected to contain a buffer overflow via the function gf_isom_new_generic_sample_description function in the isomedia/isom_write.c:4577</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:10:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40547 | Shim: rce in http boot support may lead to secure boot bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40547</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability was found in Shim. The Shim boot support trusts attacker-controlled values when parsing an HTTP response. This flaw allows an attacker to craft a specific malicious HTTP request, leading to a completely controlled out-of-bounds write primitive and complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52076 | Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in Atril&amp;#x27;s EPUB ebook parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52076</link><description>Atril Document Viewer is the default document reader of the MATE desktop environment for Linux. A path traversal and arbitrary file write vulnerability exists in versions of Atril prior to 1.26.2. This vulnerability is capable of writing arbitrary files anywhere on the filesystem to which the user opening a crafted document has access. The only limitation is that this vulnerability cannot be exploited to overwrite existing files, but that doesn't stop an attacker from achieving Remote Command Execution on the target system. Version 1.26.2 of Atril contains a patch for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3181 | Insecure Permissions in Splashtop Software Updater</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3181</link><description>The C:\Program Files (x86)\Splashtop\Splashtop Software Updater\uninst.exe process creates a folder at C:\Windows\Temp~nsu.tmp and copies itself to it as Au_.exe. The C:\Windows\Temp~nsu.tmp\Au_.exe file is automatically launched as SYSTEM when the system reboots or when a standard user runs an MSI repair using Splashtop Streamer’s Windows Installer. Since the C:\Windows\Temp~nsu.tmp folder inherits permissions from C:\Windows\Temp and Au_.exe is susceptible to DLL hijacking, standard users can write a malicious DLL to it and elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0822 | Ovirt: authentication bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0822</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability was found in overt-engine. This flaw allows the creation of users in the system without authentication due to a flaw in the CreateUserSession command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22529 | TOTOLINK X2000R_V2 V2.0.0-B20230727.10434 has a command injection vulnerability in the sub_449040 (handle function of formUploadFile) of /bi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22529</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R_V2 V2.0.0-B20230727.10434 has a command injection vulnerability in the sub_449040 (handle function of formUploadFile) of /bin/boa.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22432 | Networker 19.9 and all prior versions contains a Plain-text Password stored in temporary config file during backup duration in NMDA MySQL Da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22432</link><description>Networker 19.9 and all prior versions contains a Plain-text Password stored in temporary config file during backup duration in NMDA MySQL Database backups. User has low privilege access to Networker Client system could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disclosure of configured MySQL Database user credentials. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application Database with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0879 | Authentication bypass in vector-admin domain restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0879</link><description>Authentication bypass in vector-admin allows a user to register to a vector-admin server while “domain restriction” is active, even when not owning an authorized email address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22729 | NETIS SYSTEMS MW5360 V1.0.1.3031 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the password parameter on the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22729</link><description>NETIS SYSTEMS MW5360 V1.0.1.3031 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the password parameter on the login page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23855 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cups Easy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23855</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Cups Easy (Purchase &amp; Inventory), version 1.0, whereby user-controlled inputs are not sufficiently encoded, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via/cupseasylive/taxcodemodify.php, in multiple parameters. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 14:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6282 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in IceHrm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6282</link><description>IceHrm 23.0.0.OS does not sufficiently encode user-controlled input, which creates a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /icehrm/app/fileupload_page.php, in multiple parameters. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted JavaScript payload and partially hijacking the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:44:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33757 | A lack of SSL certificate validation in Splicecom iPCS (iOS App) v1.3.4, iPCS2 (iOS App) v2.8 and before, and iPCS (Android App) v1.8.5 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33757</link><description>A lack of SSL certificate validation in Splicecom iPCS (iOS App) v1.3.4, iPCS2 (iOS App) v2.8 and before, and iPCS (Android App) v1.8.5 and before allows attackers to eavesdrop on communications via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33758 | Splicecom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the CLIENT_NAME and DE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33758</link><description>Splicecom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the CLIENT_NAME and DEVICE_GUID fields in the login component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33759 | SpliceCom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before does not restrict excessive authentication attempts, allowing attackers to bypass authenticatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33759</link><description>SpliceCom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before does not restrict excessive authentication attempts, allowing attackers to bypass authentication via a brute force attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:46:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33760 | SpliceCom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before was discovered to utilize a default SSL certificate. This issue can allow attackers to eavesdro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33760</link><description>SpliceCom Maximiser Soft PBX v1.5 and before was discovered to utilize a default SSL certificate. This issue can allow attackers to eavesdrop on communications via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:46:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22099 | NULL pointer deference in rfcomm_check_security in Linux kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22099</link><description>NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Linux Linux kernel kernel on Linux, x86, ARM (net, bluetooth modules) allows Overflow Buffers. This vulnerability is associated with program files /net/bluetooth/rfcomm/core.C.

This issue affects Linux kernel: v2.6.12-rc2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23307 | Integer overflow in raid5_cache_count in Linux kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23307</link><description>Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability in Linux Linux kernel kernel on Linux, x86, ARM (md, raid, raid5 modules) allows Forced Integer Overflow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 07:02:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50785 | Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus before 7270 allows admin users to view names of arbitrary directories via path traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50785</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus before 7270 allows admin users to view names of arbitrary directories via path traversal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 05:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23985 | EzServer 6.4.017 allows a denial of service (daemon crash) via a long string, such as one for the RNTO command.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23985</link><description>EzServer 6.4.017 allows a denial of service (daemon crash) via a long string, such as one for the RNTO command.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 05:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0625 | The WPFront Notification Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wpfront-notification-bar-options[cus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0625</link><description>The WPFront Notification Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wpfront-notification-bar-options[custom_class]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0617 | The Category Discount Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0617</link><description>The Category Discount Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the wpcd_save_discount() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.12. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify product category discounts that could lead to loss of revenue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0624 | The Paid Memberships Pro – Content Restriction, User Registration, &amp; Paid Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0624</link><description>The Paid Memberships Pro – Content Restriction, User Registration, &amp; Paid Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.12.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the pmpro_update_level_order() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the order of levels via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0688 | The "WebSub (FKA. PubSubHubbub)" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin settings in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0688</link><description>The "WebSub (FKA. PubSubHubbub)" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via plugin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22751 | D-Link DIR-882 DIR882A1_FW130B06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the sub_477AA0 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22751</link><description>D-Link DIR-882 DIR882A1_FW130B06 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the sub_477AA0 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 21:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24676 | An issue found in Processwire 3.0.210 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and install a reverse shell via the download_zip_url parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24676</link><description>An issue found in Processwire 3.0.210 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and install a reverse shell via the download_zip_url parameter when installing a new module.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-43584 | DOM-based Cross Site Scripting (XSS vulnerability in 'Tail Event Logs' functionality in Nagios Nagios Cross-Platform Agent (NCPA) before 2.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-43584</link><description>DOM-based Cross Site Scripting (XSS vulnerability in 'Tail Event Logs' functionality in Nagios Nagios Cross-Platform Agent (NCPA) before 2.4.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the name element when filtering for a log.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 20:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23644 | trillium-http and trillium-client vulnerable to HTTP Request/Response Splitting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23644</link><description>Trillium is a composable toolkit for building internet applications with async rust. In `trillium-http` prior to 0.3.12 and `trillium-client` prior to 0.5.4, insufficient validation of outbound header values may lead to request splitting or response splitting attacks in scenarios where attackers have sufficient control over headers. This only affects use cases where attackers have control of request headers, and can insert "\r\n" sequences. Specifically, if untrusted and unvalidated input is inserted into header names or values.

Outbound `trillium_http::HeaderValue` and `trillium_http::HeaderName` can be constructed infallibly and were not checked for illegal bytes when sending requests from the client or responses from the server. Thus, if an attacker has sufficient control over header values (or names) in a request or response that they could inject `\r\n` sequences, they could get the client and server out of sync, and then pivot to gain control over other parts of requests or responses. (i.e. exfiltrating data from other requests, SSRF, etc.)

In `trillium-http` versions 0.3.12 and later, if a header name is invalid in server response headers, the specific header and any associated values are omitted from network transmission. Additionally, if a header value is invalid in server response headers, the individual header value is omitted from network transmission. Other headers values with the same header name will still be sent. In `trillium-client` versions 0.5.4 and later, if any header name or header value is invalid in the client request headers, awaiting the client Conn returns an `Error::MalformedHeader` prior to any network access. As a workaround, Trillium services and client applications should sanitize or validate untrusted input that is included in header values and header names. Carriage return, newline, and null characters are not allowed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23646 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle SQL Injection in Admin download files as zip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23646</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend user interface for Pimcore. The application allows users to create zip files from available files on the site. In the 1.x branch prior to version 1.3.2, parameter `selectedIds` is susceptible to SQL Injection. Any backend user with very basic permissions can execute arbitrary SQL statements and thus alter any data or escalate their privileges to at least admin level. Version 1.3.2 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42146 | An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. DTLS servers allow remote attackers to reuse the same epoch nu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42146</link><description>An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. DTLS servers allow remote attackers to reuse the same epoch number within two times the TCP maximum segment lifetime, which is prohibited in RFC6347. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive application (data of connected clients).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 19:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42145 | An assertion failure discovered in in check_certificate_request() in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows attackers to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42145</link><description>An assertion failure discovered in in check_certificate_request() in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows attackers to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42147 | Buffer over-read vulnerability in the dtls_sha256_update function in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42147</link><description>Buffer over-read vulnerability in the dtls_sha256_update function in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted data packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23648 | Pimcore Admin Classic Bundle host header injection in the password reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23648</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a backend user interface for Pimcore. The password reset functionality sends to the the user requesting a password change an email containing an URL to reset its password. The URL sent contains a unique token, valid during 24 hours, allowing the user to reset its password. This token is highly sensitive ; as an attacker able to retrieve it would be able to resets the user's password. Prior to version 1.2.3, the reset-password URL is crafted using the "Host" HTTP header of the request sent to request a password reset. This way, an external attacker could send password requests for users, but specify a "Host" header of a website that they control. If the user receiving the mail clicks on the link, the attacker would retrieve the reset token of the victim and perform account takeover. Version 1.2.3 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23649 | Any authenticated user may obtain private message details from other users on the same instance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23649</link><description>Lemmy is a link aggregator and forum for the fediverse. Starting in version 0.17.0 and prior to version 0.19.1, users can report private messages, even when they're neither sender nor recipient of the message. The API response to creating a private message report contains the private message itself, which means any user can just iterate over message ids to (loudly) obtain all private messages of an instance. A user with instance admin privileges can also abuse this if the private message is removed from the response, as they're able to see the resulting reports.

Creating a private message report by POSTing to `/api/v3/private_message/report` does not validate whether the reporter is the recipient of the message. lemmy-ui does not allow the sender to report the message; the API method should likely be restricted to accessible to recipients only. The API response when creating a report contains the `private_message_report_view` with all the details of the report, including the private message that has been reported:

Any authenticated user can obtain arbitrary (untargeted) private message contents. Privileges required depend on the instance configuration; when registrations are enabled without application system, the privileges required are practically none. When registration applications are required, privileges required could be considered low, but this assessment heavily varies by instance.

Version 0.19.1 contains a patch for this issue. A workaround is available. If an update to a fixed Lemmy version is not immediately possible, the API route can be blocked in the reverse proxy. This will prevent anyone from reporting private messages, but it will also prevent exploitation before the update has been applied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42144 | Buffer over-read vulnerability in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows attackers obtain sensitive information via crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42144</link><description>Buffer over-read vulnerability in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97 allows attackers obtain sensitive information via crafted input to dtls_ccm_decrypt_message().</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42143 | An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. An infinite loop bug exists during the handling of a ClientHel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42143</link><description>An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. An infinite loop bug exists during the handling of a ClientHello handshake message. This bug allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service by sending a malformed ClientHello handshake message with an odd length of cipher suites, which triggers an infinite loop (consuming all resources) and a buffer over-read that can disclose sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23897 | Jenkins 2.441 and earlier, LTS 2.426.2 and earlier does not disable a feature of its CLI command parser that replaces an '@' character follo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23897</link><description>Jenkins 2.441 and earlier, LTS 2.426.2 and earlier does not disable a feature of its CLI command parser that replaces an '@' character followed by a file path in an argument with the file's contents, allowing unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23898 | Jenkins 2.217 through 2.441 (both inclusive), LTS 2.222.1 through 2.426.2 (both inclusive) does not perform origin validation of requests ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23898</link><description>Jenkins 2.217 through 2.441 (both inclusive), LTS 2.222.1 through 2.426.2 (both inclusive) does not perform origin validation of requests made through the CLI WebSocket endpoint, resulting in a cross-site WebSocket hijacking (CSWSH) vulnerability, allowing attackers to execute CLI commands on the Jenkins controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23899 | Jenkins Git server Plugin 99.va_0826a_b_cdfa_d and earlier does not disable a feature of its command parser that replaces an '@' character f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23899</link><description>Jenkins Git server Plugin 99.va_0826a_b_cdfa_d and earlier does not disable a feature of its command parser that replaces an '@' character followed by a file path in an argument with the file's contents, allowing attackers with Overall/Read permission to read content from arbitrary files on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23900 | Jenkins Matrix Project Plugin 822.v01b_8c85d16d2 and earlier does not sanitize user-defined axis names of multi-configuration projects, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23900</link><description>Jenkins Matrix Project Plugin 822.v01b_8c85d16d2 and earlier does not sanitize user-defined axis names of multi-configuration projects, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to create or replace any config.xml files on the Jenkins controller file system with content not controllable by the attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23901 | Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier unconditionally discovers projects that are shared with the configured o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23901</link><description>Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier unconditionally discovers projects that are shared with the configured owner group, allowing attackers to configure and share a project, resulting in a crafted Pipeline being built by Jenkins during the next scan of the group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23902 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier allows attackers to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23902</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier allows attackers to connect to an attacker-specified URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23903 | Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23903</link><description>Jenkins GitLab Branch Source Plugin 684.vea_fa_7c1e2fe3 and earlier uses a non-constant time comparison function when checking whether the provided and expected webhook token are equal, potentially allowing attackers to use statistical methods to obtain a valid webhook token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23904 | Jenkins Log Command Plugin 1.0.2 and earlier does not disable a feature of its command parser that replaces an '@' character followed by a f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23904</link><description>Jenkins Log Command Plugin 1.0.2 and earlier does not disable a feature of its command parser that replaces an '@' character followed by a file path in an argument with the file's contents, allowing unauthenticated attackers to read content from arbitrary files on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23905 | Jenkins Red Hat Dependency Analytics Plugin 0.7.1 and earlier programmatically disables Content-Security-Policy protection for user-generate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23905</link><description>Jenkins Red Hat Dependency Analytics Plugin 0.7.1 and earlier programmatically disables Content-Security-Policy protection for user-generated content in workspaces, archived artifacts, etc. that Jenkins offers for download.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 18:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52040 | An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_41284C function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52040</link><description>An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_41284C function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52038 | An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_415C80 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52038</link><description>An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_415C80 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52039 | An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_415AA4 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52039</link><description>An issue discovered in TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 allows attackers to run arbitrary commands via the sub_415AA4 function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22720 | Kanboard 1.2.34 is vulnerable to Html Injection in the group management feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22720</link><description>Kanboard 1.2.34 is vulnerable to Html Injection in the group management feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51890 | An infinite loop issue discovered in Mathtex 1.05 and before allows a remote attackers to consume CPU resources via crafted string in the ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51890</link><description>An infinite loop issue discovered in Mathtex 1.05 and before allows a remote attackers to consume CPU resources via crafted string in the application URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51888 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the nomath() function in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51888</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the nomath() function in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted string in the application URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51889 | Stack Overflow vulnerability in the validate() function in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51889</link><description>Stack Overflow vulnerability in the validate() function in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted string in the application URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51886 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the main() function in Mathtex 1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service when u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51886</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the main() function in Mathtex 1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service when using \convertpath.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51887 | Command Injection vulnerability in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted string in applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51887</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted string in application URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:25:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51885 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the length of the LaTeX st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51885</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Mathtex v.1.05 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the length of the LaTeX string component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23641 | Sending a GET or HEAD request with a body crashes SvelteKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23641</link><description>SvelteKit is a web development kit. In SvelteKit 2, sending a GET request with a body eg `{}` to a built and previewed/hosted sveltekit app throws `Request with GET/HEAD method cannot have body.` and crashes the preview/hosting. After this happens, one must manually restart the app. `TRACE` requests will also cause the app to crash. Prerendered pages and SvelteKit 1 apps are not affected. `@sveltejs/adapter-node` versions 2.1.2, 3.0.3, and 4.0.1 and `@sveltejs/kit` version 2.4.3 contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22229 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a vulnerability whereby log messages can be spoofed by an authenticated attacker. An attacker cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22229</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a vulnerability whereby log messages can be spoofed by an authenticated attacker. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to forge log entries, create false alarms, and inject malicious content into logs that compromise logs integrity. A malicious attacker could also prevent the product from logging information while malicious actions are performed or implicate an arbitrary user for malicious activities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22725 | Orthanc versions before 1.12.2 are affected by a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The vulnerability was present in the se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22725</link><description>Orthanc versions before 1.12.2 are affected by a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The vulnerability was present in the server's error reporting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 16:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22651 | There is a command injection vulnerability in the ssdpcgi_main function of cgibin binary in D-Link DIR-815 router firmware v1.04.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22651</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in the ssdpcgi_main function of cgibin binary in D-Link DIR-815 router firmware v1.04.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:48:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44281 | Dell Pair Installer version prior to 1.2.1 contains an elevation of privilege vulnerability. A low privilege user with local access to the s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44281</link><description>Dell Pair Installer version prior to 1.2.1 contains an elevation of privilege vulnerability. A low privilege user with local access to the system could potentially exploit this vulnerability to delete arbitrary files and result in Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22141 | WordPress Profile Builder Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.0 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22141</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Profile Builder Pro.This issue affects Profile Builder Pro: from n/a through 3.10.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6697 | The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the map id parameter in al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6697</link><description>The WP Go Maps (formerly WP Google Maps) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the map id parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.0.28 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50943 | Apache Airflow: Potential pickle deserialization vulnerability in XComs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50943</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.1, have a vulnerability that allows a potential attacker to poison the XCom data by bypassing the protection of "enable_xcom_pickling=False" configuration setting resulting in poisoned data after XCom deserialization. This vulnerability is considered low since it requires a DAG author to exploit it. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.1 or later, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50944 | Apache Airflow: Bypass permission verification to read code of other dags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50944</link><description>Apache Airflow, versions before 2.8.1, have a vulnerability that allows an authenticated user to access the source code of a DAG to which they don't have access. This vulnerability is considered low since it requires an authenticated user to exploit it. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.8.1, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51702 | Apache Airflow CNCF Kubernetes provider, Apache Airflow: Kubernetes configuration file saved without encryption in the Metadata and logged as plain text in the Triggerer service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51702</link><description>Since version 5.2.0, when using deferrable mode with the path of a Kubernetes configuration file for authentication, the Airflow worker serializes this configuration file as a dictionary and sends it to the triggerer by storing it in metadata without any encryption. Additionally, if used with an Airflow version between 2.3.0 and 2.6.0, the configuration dictionary will be logged as plain text in the triggerer service without masking. This allows anyone with access to the metadata or triggerer log to obtain the configuration file and use it to access the Kubernetes cluster.

This behavior was changed in version 7.0.0, which stopped serializing the file contents and started providing the file path instead to read the contents into the trigger. Users are recommended to upgrade to version 7.0.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22154 | WordPress SalesKing Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.15 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22154</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in SNP Digital SalesKing.This issue affects SalesKing: from n/a through 1.6.15.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22294 | WordPress Download IP2Location Country Blocker Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33.3 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22294</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in IP2Location IP2Location Country Blocker.This issue affects IP2Location Country Blocker: from n/a through 2.33.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22301 | WordPress Albo Pretorio Online Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.6 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22301</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Ignazio Scimone Albo Pretorio On line.This issue affects Albo Pretorio On line: from n/a through 4.6.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22308 | WordPress Simple Membership Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 is vulnerable to Open Redirection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22308</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in smp7, wp.Insider Simple Membership.This issue affects Simple Membership: from n/a through 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52221 | WordPress Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp;amp; Order Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52221</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager.This issue affects Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22135 | WordPress Order Export &amp;amp; Order Import for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22135</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WebToffee Order Export &amp; Order Import for WooCommerce.This issue affects Order Export &amp; Order Import for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22152 | WordPress Product Import Export for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.7 is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22152</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WebToffee Product Import Export for WooCommerce.This issue affects Product Import Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22284 | WordPress Asgaros Forum Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22284</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Thomas Belser Asgaros Forum.This issue affects Asgaros Forum: from n/a through 2.7.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:50:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22309 | WordPress ChatBot Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22309</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in QuantumCloud ChatBot with AI.This issue affects ChatBot with AI: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22134 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.70 is vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22134</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Renzo Johnson Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp: from n/a through 0.5.70.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 11:43:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0854 | URL redirection to untrusted site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in file access component in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0854</link><description>URL redirection to untrusted site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in file access component in Synology DiskStation Manager (DSM) before 7.2.1-69057-2 allows remote authenticated users to conduct phishing attacks via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 10:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43988 | An issue in nature fitness saijo mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43988</link><description>An issue in nature fitness saijo mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43989 | An issue in mokumoku chohu mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43989</link><description>An issue in mokumoku chohu mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43990 | An issue in cherub-hair mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43990</link><description>An issue in cherub-hair mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43991 | An issue in PRIMA CLINIC mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43991</link><description>An issue in PRIMA CLINIC mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43992 | An issue in STOCKMAN GROUP mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43992</link><description>An issue in STOCKMAN GROUP mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43993 | An issue in smaregi_app_market mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43993</link><description>An issue in smaregi_app_market mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43994 | An issue in Cleaning_makotoya mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43994</link><description>An issue in Cleaning_makotoya mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43995 | An issue in picot.golf mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43995</link><description>An issue in picot.golf mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43996 | An issue in Q co ltd mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access tok...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43996</link><description>An issue in Q co ltd mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43997 | An issue in Yoruichi hobby base mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43997</link><description>An issue in Yoruichi hobby base mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43998 | An issue in Books-futaba mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43998</link><description>An issue in Books-futaba mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43999 | An issue in COLORFUL_laundry mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43999</link><description>An issue in COLORFUL_laundry mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44000 | An issue in Otakara lapis totuka mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44000</link><description>An issue in Otakara lapis totuka mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44001 | An issue in Ailand clinic mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44001</link><description>An issue in Ailand clinic mini-app on Line v13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted malicious notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0665 | The WP Customer Area plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0665</link><description>The WP Customer Area plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 07:38:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51711 | An issue was discovered in Regify Regipay Client for Windows version 4.5.1.0 allows DLL hijacking: a user can trigger the execution of arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51711</link><description>An issue was discovered in Regify Regipay Client for Windows version 4.5.1.0 allows DLL hijacking: a user can trigger the execution of arbitrary code every time the product is executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:53:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43317 | An issue in Coign CRM Portal v.06.06 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the userPermissionsList parameter in Session Storag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43317</link><description>An issue in Coign CRM Portal v.06.06 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the userPermissionsList parameter in Session Storage component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22366 | Active debug code exists in Yamaha wireless LAN access point devices. If a logged-in user who knows how to use the debug function accesses t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22366</link><description>Active debug code exists in Yamaha wireless LAN access point devices. If a logged-in user who knows how to use the debug function accesses the device's management page, this function can be enabled by performing specific operations. As a result, an arbitrary OS command may be executed and/or configuration settings of the device may be altered. Affected products and versions are as follows: WLX222 firmware Rev.24.00.03 and earlier, WLX413 firmware Rev.22.00.05 and earlier, WLX212 firmware Rev.21.00.12 and earlier, WLX313 firmware Rev.18.00.12 and earlier, and WLX202 firmware Rev.16.00.18 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 04:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22372 | OS command injection vulnerability in ELECOM wireless LAN routers allows a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22372</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability in ELECOM wireless LAN routers allows a network-adjacent attacker with an administrative privilege to execute arbitrary OS commands by sending a specially crafted request to the product. Affected products and versions are as follows: WRC-X1800GS-B v1.17 and earlier, WRC-X1800GSA-B v1.17 and earlier, WRC-X1800GSH-B v1.17 and earlier, WRC-X6000XS-G v1.09, and WRC-X6000XST-G v1.12 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 04:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31037 | NVIDIA Bluefield 2 and Bluefield 3 DPU BMC contains a vulnerability in ipmitool, where a root user may cause code injection by a network cal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31037</link><description>NVIDIA Bluefield 2 and Bluefield 3 DPU BMC contains a vulnerability in ipmitool, where a root user may cause code injection by a network call. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution on the OS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 02:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21765 | Electronic Delivery Check System (Doboku) Ver.18.1.0 and earlier, Electronic Delivery Check System (Dentsu) Ver.12.1.0 and earlier, Electron...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21765</link><description>Electronic Delivery Check System (Doboku) Ver.18.1.0 and earlier, Electronic Delivery Check System (Dentsu) Ver.12.1.0 and earlier, Electronic Delivery Check System (Kikai) Ver.10.1.0 and earlier, and Electronic delivery item Inspection Support SystemVer.4.0.31 and earlier improperly restrict XML external entity references (XXE). By processing a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary files on the system may be read by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21796 | Electronic Deliverables Creation Support Tool (Construction Edition) prior to Ver1.0.4 and Electronic Deliverables Creation Support Tool (De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21796</link><description>Electronic Deliverables Creation Support Tool (Construction Edition) prior to Ver1.0.4 and Electronic Deliverables Creation Support Tool (Design &amp; Survey Edition) prior to Ver1.0.4 improperly restrict XML external entity references (XXE). By processing a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary files on the system may be read by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22380 | Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) Mar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22380</link><description>Electronic Delivery Check System (Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries The Agriculture and Rural Development Project Version) March, Heisei 31 era edition Ver.14.0.001.002 and earlier improperly restricts XML external entity references (XXE). By processing a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary files on the system may be read by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4964 | Ubuntu's pipewire-pulse in snap grants microphone access even when the snap interface for audio-record is not set.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4964</link><description>Ubuntu's pipewire-pulse in snap grants microphone access even when the snap interface for audio-record is not set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 01:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0804 | Insufficient policy enforcement in iOS Security UI in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin da...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0804</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in iOS Security UI in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to leak cross-origin data via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0805 | Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0805</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Downloads in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to perform domain spoofing via a crafted domain name. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0806 | Use after free in Passwords in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0806</link><description>Use after free in Passwords in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0807 | Use after free in Web Audio in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0807</link><description>Use after free in Web Audio in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0808 | Integer underflow in WebUI in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0808</link><description>Integer underflow in WebUI in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a malicious file. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0809 | Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0809</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Autofill in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to bypass Autofill restrictions via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0810 | Insufficient policy enforcement in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0810</link><description>Insufficient policy enforcement in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to leak cross-origin data via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0811 | Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0811</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Extensions API in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to leak cross-origin data via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Low)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0812 | Inappropriate implementation in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit objec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0812</link><description>Inappropriate implementation in Accessibility in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0813 | Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious exten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0813</link><description>Use after free in Reading Mode in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed an attacker who convinced a user to install a malicious extension to potentially exploit heap corruption via specific UI interaction. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0814 | Incorrect security UI in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof security UI via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0814</link><description>Incorrect security UI in Payments in Google Chrome prior to 121.0.6167.85 allowed a remote attacker to potentially spoof security UI via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23638 | SQUID-2023:11 Denial of Service in Cache Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23638</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. Due to an expired pointer reference bug, Squid prior to version 6.6 is vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against Cache Manager error responses. This problem allows a trusted client to perform Denial of Service when generating error pages for Client Manager reports. Squid older than 5.0.5 have not been tested and should be assumed to be vulnerable. All Squid-5.x up to and including 5.9 are vulnerable. All Squid-6.x up to and including 6.5 are vulnerable. This bug is fixed by Squid version 6.6. In addition, patches addressing this problem for the stable releases can be found in Squid's patch archives. As a workaround, prevent access to Cache Manager using Squid's main access control: `http_access deny manager`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23453 | Android Spoon application version 7.11.1 to 8.6.0 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a local attacker to retrieve the hard-coded A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23453</link><description>Android Spoon application version 7.11.1 to 8.6.0 uses hard-coded credentials, which may allow a local attacker to retrieve the hard-coded API key when the application binary is reverse-engineered. This API key may be used for unexpected access of the associated service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23633 |  Label Studio XSS Vulnerability on Data Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23633</link><description>Label Studio, an open source data labeling tool had a remote import feature allowed users to import data from a remote web source, that was downloaded and could be viewed on the website. Prior to version 1.10.1, this feature could had been abused to download a HTML file that executed malicious JavaScript code in the context of the Label Studio website. Executing arbitrary JavaScript could result in an attacker performing malicious actions on Label Studio users if they visit the crafted avatar image. For an example, an attacker can craft a JavaScript payload that adds a new Django Super Administrator user if a Django administrator visits the image.

`data_import/uploader.py` lines 125C5 through 146 showed that if a URL passed the server side request forgery verification checks, the contents of the file would be downloaded using the filename in the URL. The downloaded file path could then be retrieved by sending a request to `/api/projects/{project_id}/file-uploads?ids=[{download_id}]` where `{project_id}` was the ID of the project and `{download_id}` was the ID of the downloaded file. Once the downloaded file path was retrieved by the previous API endpoint, `data_import/api.py`lines 595C1 through 616C62 demonstrated that the `Content-Type` of the response was determined by the file extension, since `mimetypes.guess_type` guesses the `Content-Type` based on the file extension. Since the `Content-Type` was determined by the file extension of the downloaded file, an attacker could import in a `.html` file that would execute JavaScript when visited.

Version 1.10.1 contains a patch for this issue. Other remediation strategies are also available. For all user provided files that are downloaded by Label Studio, set the `Content-Security-Policy: sandbox;` response header when viewed on the site. The `sandbox` directive restricts a page's actions to prevent popups, execution of plugins and scripts and enforces a `same-origin` policy. Alternatively, restrict the allowed file extensions that may be downloaded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:22:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47115 | Label Studio XSS Vulnerability on Avatar Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47115</link><description>Label Studio is an a popular open source data labeling tool. Versions prior to 1.9.2 have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be exploited when an authenticated user uploads a crafted image file for their avatar that gets rendered as a HTML file on the website. Executing arbitrary JavaScript could result in an attacker performing malicious actions on Label Studio users if they visit the crafted avatar image. For an example, an attacker can craft a JavaScript payload that adds a new Django Super Administrator user if a Django administrator visits the image.

The file `users/functions.py` lines 18-49 show that the only verification check is that the file is an image by extracting the dimensions from the file. Label Studio serves avatar images using Django's built-in `serve` view, which is not secure for production use according to Django's documentation. The issue with the Django `serve` view is that it determines the `Content-Type` of the response by the file extension in the URL path. Therefore, an attacker can upload an image that contains malicious HTML code and name the file with a `.html` extension to be rendered as a HTML page. The only file extension validation is performed on the client-side, which can be easily bypassed.

Version 1.9.2 fixes this issue. Other remediation strategies include validating the file extension on the server side, not in client-side code; removing the use of Django's `serve` view and implement a secure controller for viewing uploaded avatar images; saving file content in the database rather than on the filesystem to mitigate against other file related vulnerabilities; and avoiding trusting user controlled inputs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35835 | An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. The device provides a WiFi access point for initial configuration. The WiFi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35835</link><description>An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. The device provides a WiFi access point for initial configuration. The WiFi network provided has no network authentication (such as an encryption key) and persists permanently, including after enrollment and setup is complete. The WiFi network serves a web-based configuration utility, as well as an unauthenticated ModBus protocol interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35836 | An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. An attacker within RF range can obtain a cleartext copy of the network conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35836</link><description>An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. An attacker within RF range can obtain a cleartext copy of the network configuration of the device, including the Wi-Fi PSK, during device setup and reconfiguration. Upon success, the attacker is able to further infiltrate the target's Wi-Fi networks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35837 | An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. Authentication for web interface is completed via an unauthenticated WiFi A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35837</link><description>An issue was discovered in SolaX Pocket WiFi 3 through 3.001.02. Authentication for web interface is completed via an unauthenticated WiFi AP. The administrative password for the web interface has a default password, equal to the registration ID of the device. This same registration ID is used as the WiFi SSID name. No routine is in place to force a change to this password on first use or bring its default state to the attention of the user. Once authenticated, an attacker can reconfigure the device or upload new firmware, both of which can lead to Denial of Service, code execution, or Escalation of Privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42142 | An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. DTLS servers mishandle the early use of a large epoch number. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42142</link><description>An issue was discovered in Contiki-NG tinyDTLS through master branch 53a0d97. DTLS servers mishandle the early use of a large epoch number. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service and false-positive packet drops.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31654 | Redis raft master-1b8bd86 to master-7b46079 was discovered to contain an ODR violation via the component hiredisAllocFns at /opt/fs/redisraf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31654</link><description>Redis raft master-1b8bd86 to master-7b46079 was discovered to contain an ODR violation via the component hiredisAllocFns at /opt/fs/redisraft/deps/hiredis/alloc.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51201 | Cleartext Transmission issue in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51201</link><description>Cleartext Transmission issue in ROS2 (Robot Operating System 2) Foxy Fitzroy, with ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to access sensitive information via a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7237 | Lantronix XPort Weak Encoding for Password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7237</link><description>Lantronix XPort sends weakly encoded credentials within web request headers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 22:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51208 | An Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to run arbitrary code an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51208</link><description>An Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to run arbitrary code and cause other impacts via upload of crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 21:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36177 | An issue was discovered in badaix Snapcast version 0.27.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36177</link><description>An issue was discovered in badaix Snapcast version 0.27.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain sensitive information via crafted request in JSON-RPC-API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51199 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to run arbitrary code or cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51199</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows attackers to run arbitrary code or cause a denial of service via improper handling of arrays or strings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51200 | An issue in the default configurations of ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows unauthenticated attackers to authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51200</link><description>An issue in the default configurations of ROS2 Foxy Fitzroy ROS_VERSION=2 and ROS_PYTHON_VERSION=3 allows unauthenticated attackers to authenticate using default credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 21:08:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52324 | An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow a remote attacker to create arbitrary files on affected in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52324</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow a remote attacker to create arbitrary files on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, this vulnerability could be exploited when the attacker has any valid set of credentials. Also, this vulnerability could be potentially used in combination with another vulnerability to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52325 | A local file inclusion vulnerability in one of Trend Micro Apex Central's widgets could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52325</link><description>A local file inclusion vulnerability in one of Trend Micro Apex Central's widgets could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: this vulnerability must be used in conjunction with another one to exploit an affected system. In addition, an attacker must first obtain a valid set of credentials on target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52326 | Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52326</link><description>Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution on affected servers.&#13;
&#13;
Please note this vulnerability is similar, but not identical to CVE-2023-52327.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52327 | Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52327</link><description>Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution on affected servers.&#13;
&#13;
Please note this vulnerability is similar, but not identical to CVE-2023-52328.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52328 | Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52328</link><description>Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution on affected servers.&#13;
&#13;
Please note this vulnerability is similar, but not identical to CVE-2023-52329.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52329 | Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52329</link><description>Certain dashboard widgets on Trend Micro Apex Central (on-premise) are vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks that may allow an attacker to achieve remote code execution on affected servers.&#13;
&#13;
Please note this vulnerability is similar, but not identical to CVE-2023-52326.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52330 | A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected install...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52330</link><description>A cross-site scripting vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Trend Micro Apex Central.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: user interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52331 | A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow an attacker to interact with i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52331</link><description>A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central could allow an attacker to interact with internal or local services directly.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52337 | An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 and Trend Micro Cloud One - Endpoint and Workload Security Agent ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52337</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 and Trend Micro Cloud One - Endpoint and Workload Security Agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52338 | A link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 and Trend Micro Cloud One - Endpoint and Workload Security Agent could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52338</link><description>A link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 and Trend Micro Cloud One - Endpoint and Workload Security Agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41176 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41176</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authenticated victim that visits a malicious link provided by an attacker.&#13;
&#13;
Please note, this vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-41177.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41177 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41177</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authenticated victim that visits a malicious link provided by an attacker.&#13;
&#13;
Please note, this vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-41178.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41178 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41178</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Trend Micro Mobile Security (Enterprise) could allow an exploit against an authenticated victim that visits a malicious link provided by an attacker.&#13;
&#13;
Please note, this vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-41176.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47192 | An agent link vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected insta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47192</link><description>An agent link vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47193 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47193</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47194.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47194 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47194</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47195.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47195 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47195</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47196.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47196 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47196</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47197.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47197 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47197</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47198.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47198 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47198</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47199.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47199 | An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47199</link><description>An origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47193.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47200 | A plug-in manager origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47200</link><description>A plug-in manager origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47201.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47201 | A plug-in manager origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47201</link><description>A plug-in manager origin validation vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One security agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to, CVE-2023-47200.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47202 | A local file inclusion vulnerability on the Trend Micro Apex One management server could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47202</link><description>A local file inclusion vulnerability on the Trend Micro Apex One management server could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52090 | A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected instal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52090</link><description>A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52091 | An anti-spyware engine link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52091</link><description>An anti-spyware engine link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52092 | A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected instal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52092</link><description>A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52093 | An exposed dangerous function vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affecte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52093</link><description>An exposed dangerous function vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One agent could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52094 | An updater link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One agent could allow a local attacker to abuse the updater to delete an arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52094</link><description>An updater link following vulnerability in the Trend Micro Apex One agent could allow a local attacker to abuse the updater to delete an arbitrary folder, leading for a local privilege escalation on affected installations.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38624 | A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38624</link><description>A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow an attacker to interact with internal or local services directly.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This is a similar, but not identical vulnerability as CVE-2023-38625 through CVE-2023-38627.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38625 | A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38625</link><description>A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow an attacker to interact with internal or local services directly.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This is a similar, but not identical vulnerability as CVE-2023-38624.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38626 | A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38626</link><description>A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow an attacker to interact with internal or local services directly.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This is a similar, but not identical vulnerability as CVE-2023-38625.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38627 | A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38627</link><description>A post-authenticated server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex Central 2019 (lower than build 6481) could allow an attacker to interact with internal or local services directly.&#13;
&#13;
Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.&#13;
&#13;
This is a similar, but not identical vulnerability as CVE-2023-38626.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46892 | The radio frequency communication protocol being used by Meross MSH30Q 4.5.23 is vulnerable to replay attacks, allowing attackers to record ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46892</link><description>The radio frequency communication protocol being used by Meross MSH30Q 4.5.23 is vulnerable to replay attacks, allowing attackers to record and replay previously captured communication to execute unauthorized commands or actions (e.g., thermostat's temperature).</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42144 | Cleartext Transmission during initial setup in Shelly TRV 20220811-15234 v.2.1.8 allows a local attacker to obtain the Wi-Fi password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42144</link><description>Cleartext Transmission during initial setup in Shelly TRV 20220811-15234 v.2.1.8 allows a local attacker to obtain the Wi-Fi password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:15:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46889 | Meross MSH30Q 4.5.23 is vulnerable to Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information. During the device setup phase, the MSH30Q creates an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46889</link><description>Meross MSH30Q 4.5.23 is vulnerable to Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information. During the device setup phase, the MSH30Q creates an unprotected Wi-Fi access point. In this phase, MSH30Q needs to connect to the Internet through a Wi-Fi router. This is why MSH30Q asks for the Wi-Fi network name (SSID) and the Wi-Fi network password. When the user enters the password, the transmission of the Wi-Fi password and name between the MSH30Q and mobile application is observed in the Wi-Fi network. Although the Wi-Fi password is encrypted, a part of the decryption algorithm is public so we complemented the missing parts to decrypt it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42143 | Missing Integrity Check in Shelly TRV 20220811-152343/v2.1.8@5afc928c allows malicious users to create a backdoor by redirecting the device ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42143</link><description>Missing Integrity Check in Shelly TRV 20220811-152343/v2.1.8@5afc928c allows malicious users to create a backdoor by redirecting the device to an attacker-controlled machine which serves the manipulated firmware file. The device is updated with the manipulated firmware.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 20:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6926 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in Crestron AM-300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6926</link><description>There is an OS command injection vulnerability in Crestron AM-300 firmware version 1.4499.00018 which may enable a user of a limited-access SSH session to escalate their privileges to root-level access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 19:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7238 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in Orthanc Osimis DICOM Web Viewer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7238</link><description>A XSS payload can be uploaded as a DICOM study and when a user tries to view the infected study inside the Osimis WebViewer the XSS vulnerability gets triggered. If exploited, the attacker will be able to execute arbitrary JavaScript code inside the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 19:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51210 | SQL injection vulnerability in Webkul Bundle Product 6.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id_product parameters ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51210</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in Webkul Bundle Product 6.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the id_product parameters in the UpdateProductQuantity function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22497 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin/login password parameter in JFinalcms 5.0.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22497</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in /admin/login password parameter in JFinalcms 5.0.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45889 | A Universal Cross Site Scripting (UXSS) vulnerability in ClassLink OneClick Extension through 10.8 allows remote attackers to inject JavaScr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45889</link><description>A Universal Cross Site Scripting (UXSS) vulnerability in ClassLink OneClick Extension through 10.8 allows remote attackers to inject JavaScript into any webpage. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-48612.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22204 | Whoogle Search Limited File Write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22204</link><description>Whoogle Search is a self-hosted metasearch engine. Versions 0.8.3 and prior have a limited file write vulnerability when the configuration options in Whoogle are enabled. The `config` function in `app/routes.py` does not validate the user-controlled `name` variable on line 447 and `config_data` variable on line 437. The `name` variable is insecurely concatenated in `os.path.join`, leading to path manipulation. The POST data from the `config_data` variable is saved with `pickle.dump` which leads to a limited file write. However, the data that is saved is earlier transformed into a dictionary and the `url` key value pair is added before the file is saved on the system. All in all, the issue allows us to save and overwrite files on the system that the application has permissions to, with a dictionary containing arbitrary data and the `url` key value, which is a limited file write. Version 0.8.4 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22205 | Whoogle Search Server Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22205</link><description>Whoogle Search is a self-hosted metasearch engine. In versions 0.8.3 and prior, the `window` endpoint does not sanitize user-supplied input from the `location` variable and passes it to the `send` method which sends a `GET` request on lines 339-343 in `request.py,` which leads to a server-side request forgery. This issue allows for crafting GET requests to internal and external resources on behalf of the server. For example, this issue would allow for accessing resources on the internal network that the server has access to, even though these resources may not be accessible on the internet. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22417 | Whoogle Search Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22417</link><description>Whoogle Search is a self-hosted metasearch engine. In versions 0.8.3 and prior, the `element` method in `app/routes.py` does not validate the user-controlled `src_type` and `element_url` variables and passes them to the `send` method which sends a `GET` request on lines 339-343 in `requests.py`. The returned contents of the URL are then passed to and reflected back to the user in the `send_file` function on line 484, together with the user-controlled `src_type`, which allows the attacker to control the HTTP response content type leading to a cross-site scripting vulnerability. An attacker could craft a special URL to point to a malicious website and send the link to a victim. The fact that the link would contain a trusted domain (e.g. from one of public Whoogle instances) could be used to trick the user into clicking the link.The malicious website could, for example, be a copy of a real website, meant to steal a person’s credentials to the website, or trick that person in another way. Version 0.8.4 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23330 | Tuta loads images from external resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23330</link><description>Tuta is an encrypted email service. In versions prior to 119.10, an attacker can attach an image in a html mail which is loaded from external resource in the default setting, which should prevent loading of external resources. When displaying emails containing external content, they should be loaded by default only after confirmation by the user. However, it could be recognized that certain embedded images (see PoC) are loaded, even though the "Automatic Reloading of Images" function is disabled by default. The reloading is also done unencrypted via HTTP and redirections are followed. This behavior is unexpected for the user, since the user assumes that external content will only be loaded after explicit manual confirmation. The loading of external content in e-mails represents a risk, because this makes the sender aware that the e-mail address is used, when the e-mail was read, which device is used and expose the user's IP address. Version 119.10 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23341 | TuiTse-TsuSin html injection vulnerability in `tuitse_html` function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23341</link><description>TuiTse-TsuSin is a package for organizing the comparative corpus of Taiwanese Chinese characters and Roman characters, and extracting sentences of the Taiwanese Chinese characters and the Roman characters. Prior to version 1.3.2, when using `tuitse_html` without quoting the input, there is a html injection vulnerability. Version 1.3.2 contains a patch for the issue. As a workaround, sanitize Taigi input with HTML quotation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23636 | SOFARPC Remote Command Execution(RCE) Vulnerbility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23636</link><description>SOFARPC is a Java RPC framework. SOFARPC defaults to using the SOFA Hessian protocol to deserialize received data, while the SOFA Hessian protocol uses a blacklist mechanism to restrict deserialization of potentially dangerous classes for security protection. But, prior to version 5.12.0, there is a gadget chain that can bypass the SOFA Hessian blacklist protection mechanism, and this gadget chain only relies on JDK and does not rely on any third-party components. Version 5.12.0 fixed this issue by adding a blacklist. SOFARPC also provides a way to add additional blacklists. Users can add a class like `-Drpc_serialize_blacklist_override=org.apache.xpath.` to avoid this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6573 | HPE OneView may have a missing passphrase during restore.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6573</link><description>HPE OneView may have a missing passphrase during restore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22203 | Whoogle Search Server Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22203</link><description>Whoogle Search is a self-hosted metasearch engine. In versions prior to 0.8.4, the `element` method in `app/routes.py` does not validate the user-controlled `src_type` and `element_url` variables and passes them to the `send` method which sends a GET request on lines 339-343 in `request.py`, which leads to a server-side request forgery. This issue allows for crafting GET requests to internal and external resources on behalf of the server. For example, this issue would allow for accessing resources on the internal network that the server has access to, even though these resources may not be accessible on the internet. This issue is fixed in version 0.8.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50275 | HPE OneView may allow clusterService Authentication Bypass resulting in denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50275</link><description>HPE OneView may allow clusterService Authentication Bypass resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50274 | HPE OneView may allow command injection with local privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50274</link><description>HPE OneView may allow command injection with local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22496 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in JFinalcms 5.0.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the /admin/login username parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22496</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in JFinalcms 5.0.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the /admin/login username parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 16:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22490 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in beetl-bbs 2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the /index keyword parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22490</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in beetl-bbs 2.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the /index keyword parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 16:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49657 | Apache Superset: Stored XSS in Dashboard Title and Chart Title</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49657</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Apache Superset before 3.0.3. An authenticated attacker with create/update permissions on charts or dashboards could store a script or add a specific HTML snippet that would act as a stored XSS.

For 2.X versions, users should change their config to include:

TALISMAN_CONFIG = {
    "content_security_policy": {
        "base-uri": ["'self'"],
        "default-src": ["'self'"],
        "img-src": ["'self'", "blob:", "data:"],
        "worker-src": ["'self'", "blob:"],
        "connect-src": [
            "'self'",
            " https://api.mapbox.com" https://api.mapbox.com" ;,
            " https://events.mapbox.com" https://events.mapbox.com" ;,
        ],
        "object-src": "'none'",
        "style-src": [
            "'self'",
            "'unsafe-inline'",
        ],
        "script-src": ["'self'", "'strict-dynamic'"],
    },
    "content_security_policy_nonce_in": ["script-src"],
    "force_https": False,
    "session_cookie_secure": False,
}</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22663 | TOTOLINK_A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012has a command Injection vulnerability via setOpModeCfg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22663</link><description>TOTOLINK_A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012has a command Injection vulnerability via setOpModeCfg</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 15:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22660 | TOTOLINK_A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012has a stack overflow vulnerability via setLanguageCfg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22660</link><description>TOTOLINK_A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012has a stack overflow vulnerability via setLanguageCfg</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 14:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22662 | TOTOLINK A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setParentalRules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22662</link><description>TOTOLINK A3700R_V9.1.2u.6165_20211012 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setParentalRules</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 14:51:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49783 | No permission checks for editing/deleting records with CSV import form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49783</link><description>Silverstripe Admin provides a basic management interface for the Silverstripe Framework. In versions on the 1.x branch prior to 1.13.19 and on the 2.x branch prior to 2.1.8, users who don't have edit or delete permissions for records exposed in a `ModelAdmin` can still edit or delete records using the CSV import form, provided they have create permissions. The likelihood of a user having create permissions but not having edit or delete permissions is low, but it is possible. Note that this doesn't affect any `ModelAdmin` which has had the import form disabled via the `showImportForm` public property. Versions 1.13.19 and 2.1.8 contain a patch for the issue. Those who have a custom implementation of `BulkLoader` should update their implementations to respect permissions when the return value of `getCheckPermissions()` is true. Those who use any `BulkLoader` in their own project logic, or maintain a module which uses it, should consider passing `true` to `setCheckPermissions()` if the data is provided by users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48714 | Record titles for restricted records can be viewed if exposed by GridFieldAddExistingAutocompleter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48714</link><description>Silverstripe Framework is the framework that forms the base of the Silverstripe content management system. Prior to versions 4.13.39 and 5.1.11, if a user should not be able to see a record, but that record can be added to a `GridField` using the `GridFieldAddExistingAutocompleter` component, the record's title can be accessed by that user. Versions 4.13.39 and 5.1.11 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0741 | An out of bounds write in ANGLE could have allowed an attacker to corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0741</link><description>An out of bounds write in ANGLE could have allowed an attacker to corrupt memory leading to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0742 | It was possible for certain browser prompts and dialogs to be activated or dismissed unintentionally by the user due to an incorrect timesta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0742</link><description>It was possible for certain browser prompts and dialogs to be activated or dismissed unintentionally by the user due to an incorrect timestamp used to prevent input after page load. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0743 | An unchecked return value in TLS handshake code could have caused a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0743</link><description>An unchecked return value in TLS handshake code could have caused a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0744 | In some circumstances, JIT compiled code could have dereferenced a wild pointer value. This could have led to an exploitable crash. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0744</link><description>In some circumstances, JIT compiled code could have dereferenced a wild pointer value. This could have led to an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0745 | The WebAudio `OscillatorNode` object was susceptible to a stack buffer overflow. This could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0745</link><description>The WebAudio `OscillatorNode` object was susceptible to a stack buffer overflow. This could have led to a potentially exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0746 | A Linux user opening the print preview dialog could have caused the browser to crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0746</link><description>A Linux user opening the print preview dialog could have caused the browser to crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0747 | When a parent page loaded a child in an iframe with `unsafe-inline`, the parent Content Security Policy could have overridden the child Cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0747</link><description>When a parent page loaded a child in an iframe with `unsafe-inline`, the parent Content Security Policy could have overridden the child Content Security Policy. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0748 | A compromised content process could have updated the document URI. This could have allowed an attacker to set an arbitrary URI in the addres...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0748</link><description>A compromised content process could have updated the document URI. This could have allowed an attacker to set an arbitrary URI in the address bar or history. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0749 | A phishing site could have repurposed an `about:` dialog to show phishing content with an incorrect origin in the address bar. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0749</link><description>A phishing site could have repurposed an `about:` dialog to show phishing content with an incorrect origin in the address bar. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0750 | A bug in popup notifications delay calculation could have made it possible for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0750</link><description>A bug in popup notifications delay calculation could have made it possible for an attacker to trick a user into granting permissions. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0751 | A malicious devtools extension could have been used to escalate privileges. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0751</link><description>A malicious devtools extension could have been used to escalate privileges. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0752 | A use-after-free crash could have occurred on macOS if a Firefox update were being applied on a very busy system. This could have resulted i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0752</link><description>A use-after-free crash could have occurred on macOS if a Firefox update were being applied on a very busy system. This could have resulted in an exploitable crash. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0753 | In specific HSTS configurations an attacker could have bypassed HSTS on a subdomain. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt;...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0753</link><description>In specific HSTS configurations an attacker could have bypassed HSTS on a subdomain. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0754 | Some WASM source files could have caused a crash when loaded in devtools. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0754</link><description>Some WASM source files could have caused a crash when loaded in devtools. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0755 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 121, Firefox ESR 115.6, and Thunderbird 115.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0755</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 121, Firefox ESR 115.6, and Thunderbird 115.6. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 122, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.7, and Thunderbird &lt; 115.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44401 | Silverstripe GraqhQL&amp;#x27;s view permissions are bypassed for paginated lists of ORM data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44401</link><description>The Silverstripe CMS GraphQL Server serves Silverstripe data as GraphQL representations. In versions 4.0.0 prior to 4.3.7 and 5.0.0 prior to 5.1.3, `canView` permission checks are bypassed for ORM data in paginated GraphQL query results where the total number of records is greater than the number of records per page. Note that this also affects GraphQL queries which have a limit applied, even if the query isn’t paginated per se. This has been fixed in versions 4.3.7 and 5.1.3 by ensuring no new records are pulled in from the database after performing `canView` permission checks for each page of results. This may result in some pages in the query results having less than the maximum number of records per page even when there are more pages of results. This behavior is consistent with how pagination works in other areas of Silverstripe CMS, such as in `GridField`, and is a result of having to perform permission checks in PHP rather than in the database directly. One may disable these permission checks by disabling the `CanViewPermission` plugin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 13:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0703 | The Sticky Buttons – floating buttons builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sticky URLs in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0703</link><description>The Sticky Buttons – floating buttons builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sticky URLs in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 11:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22076 | MyQ Print Server before 8.2 patch 43 allows Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22076</link><description>MyQ Print Server before 8.2 patch 43 allows Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:58:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22705 | An issue was discovered in ksmbd in the Linux kernel before 6.6.10. smb2_get_data_area_len in fs/smb/server/smb2misc.c can cause an smb_strn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22705</link><description>An issue was discovered in ksmbd in the Linux kernel before 6.6.10. smb2_get_data_area_len in fs/smb/server/smb2misc.c can cause an smb_strndup_from_utf16 out-of-bounds access because the relationship between Name data and CreateContexts data is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51042 | In the Linux kernel before 6.4.12, amdgpu_cs_wait_all_fences in drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/amdgpu_cs.c has a fence use-after-free.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51042</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 6.4.12, amdgpu_cs_wait_all_fences in drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/amdgpu_cs.c has a fence use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51043 | In the Linux kernel before 6.4.5, drivers/gpu/drm/drm_atomic.c has a use-after-free during a race condition between a nonblocking atomic com...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51043</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 6.4.5, drivers/gpu/drm/drm_atomic.c has a use-after-free during a race condition between a nonblocking atomic commit and a driver unload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46343 | In the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, there is a NULL pointer dereference in send_acknowledge in net/nfc/nci/spi.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46343</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 6.5.9, there is a NULL pointer dereference in send_acknowledge in net/nfc/nci/spi.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 10:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23180 | Improper input validation vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23180</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code by uploading a specially crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23181 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23181</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23182 | Relative path traversal vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23182</link><description>Relative path traversal vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23183 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23183</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the logged-in user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23348 | Improper input validation vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23348</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code by uploading a specially crafted SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23848 | In the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there is a use-after-free in cec_queue_msg_fh, related to drivers/media/cec/core/cec-adap.c and drivers/m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23848</link><description>In the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there is a use-after-free in cec_queue_msg_fh, related to drivers/media/cec/core/cec-adap.c and drivers/media/cec/core/cec-api.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23849 | In rds_recv_track_latency in net/rds/af_rds.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there is an off-by-one error for an RDS_MSG_RX_DGRAM_TRACE_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23849</link><description>In rds_recv_track_latency in net/rds/af_rds.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there is an off-by-one error for an RDS_MSG_RX_DGRAM_TRACE_MAX comparison, resulting in out-of-bounds access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23850 | In btrfs_get_root_ref in fs/btrfs/disk-io.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there can be an assertion failure and crash because a subvolu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23850</link><description>In btrfs_get_root_ref in fs/btrfs/disk-io.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1, there can be an assertion failure and crash because a subvolume can be read out too soon after its root item is inserted upon subvolume creation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23851 | copy_params in drivers/md/dm-ioctl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1 can attempt to allocate more than INT_MAX bytes, and crash, because o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23851</link><description>copy_params in drivers/md/dm-ioctl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.1 can attempt to allocate more than INT_MAX bytes, and crash, because of a missing param_kernel-&gt;data_size check. This is related to ctl_ioctl.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 08:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0587 | The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'disqus_name' paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0587</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'disqus_name' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.92.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the executed JS file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 06:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22772 | Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-8H Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22772</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-8H 1.02~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 05:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23842 | Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-16H Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23842</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-16H 1.02~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 05:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22771 | Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-4H Improper Input Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22771</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR LGUVR-4H 1.02~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 04:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22770 | Hitron Systems DVR HVR-16781 Improper Input Validation Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22770</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR HVR-16781 1.03~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 04:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22769 | Hitron Systems DVR HVR-8781 Improper Input Validation Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22769</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR HVR-8781 1.03~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 04:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22768 | Hitron Systems DVR HVR-4781 Improper Input Validation Vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22768</link><description>Improper Input Validation in Hitron Systems DVR HVR-4781 1.03~4.02 allows an attacker to cause network attack in case of using defalut admin ID/PW.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 04:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39197 | Kernel: dccp: conntrack out-of-bounds read in nf_conntrack_dccp_packet()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39197</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in Netfilter Connection Tracking (conntrack) in the Linux kernel. This flaw allows a remote user to disclose sensitive information via the DCCP protocol.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 03:08:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40528 | This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17, watchOS 10, macOS Sonoma 14, iOS 17 and iPadOS 17,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40528</link><description>This issue was addressed by removing the vulnerable code. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17, watchOS 10, macOS Sonoma 14, iOS 17 and iPadOS 17, macOS Ventura 13.6.4. An app may be able to bypass Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42881 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.2. Processing a file may lead to unexpected ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42881</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.2. Processing a file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42887 | An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2. An app m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42887</link><description>An access issue was addressed with additional sandbox restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2. An app may be able to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42888 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, watchOS 10.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42888</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, watchOS 10.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2, macOS Monterey 12.7.3, iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2. Processing a maliciously crafted image may result in disclosure of process memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42915 | Multiple issues were addressed by updating to curl version 8.4.0. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2, macOS Mont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42915</link><description>Multiple issues were addressed by updating to curl version 8.4.0. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2, macOS Monterey 12.7.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5. Multiple issues in curl.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42935 | An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4. A local attacker may be a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42935</link><description>An authentication issue was addressed with improved state management. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.4. A local attacker may be able to view the previous logged in user’s desktop from the fast user switching screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42937 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, wat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42937</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, watchOS 10.2, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Sonoma 14.2, macOS Monterey 12.7.3, iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23203 | The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. A shortcut m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23203</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. A shortcut may be able to use sensitive data with certain actions without prompting the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23204 | The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23204</link><description>The issue was addressed with additional permissions checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. A shortcut may be able to use sensitive data with certain actions without prompting the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23206 | An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23206</link><description>An access issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, Safari 17.3. A maliciously crafted webpage may be able to fingerprint the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23207 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23207</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23208 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23208</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23209 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3. Processing web content may lead to arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23209</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23210 | This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23210</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved redaction of sensitive information. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An app may be able to view a user's phone number in system logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23211 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, mac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23211</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of user preferences. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, Safari 17.3. A user's private browsing activity may be visible in Settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23212 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23212</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.3. An app may be able to execute arbitrary code with kernel privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23213 | The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonom...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23213</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, Safari 17.3. Processing web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23214 | Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23214</link><description>Multiple memory corruption issues were addressed with improved memory handling. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23215 | An issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23215</link><description>An issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An app may be able to access user-sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23217 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23217</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of temporary files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An app may be able to bypass certain Privacy preferences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23218 | A timing side-channel issue was addressed with improvements to constant-time computation in cryptographic functions. This issue is fixed in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23218</link><description>A timing side-channel issue was addressed with improvements to constant-time computation in cryptographic functions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An attacker may be able to decrypt legacy RSA PKCS#1 v1.5 ciphertexts without having the private key.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23219 | The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Stolen Device Protection may be unexp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23219</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved authentication. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Stolen Device Protection may be unexpectedly disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23222 | A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iO...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23222</link><description>A type confusion issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, Safari 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, macOS Monterey 12.7.3. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to arbitrary code execution. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23223 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23223</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved handling of files. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3, tvOS 17.3, iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23224 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4. An app may be able to access s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23224</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 01:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>