<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 06:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-11846 | Travel Tour &amp;lt; 5.2.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11846</link><description>The  does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56020 | WordPress SvegliaT Buttons Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56020</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mario Di Pasquale SvegliaT Buttons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SvegliaT Buttons: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56021 | WordPress Category Post Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56021</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ibnuyahya Category Post Shortcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Category Post Shortcode: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56062 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.987 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56062</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.987.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56063 | WordPress Essential Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56063</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Essential Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 6.0.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56803 | Ghostty improperly handles window title sequences which can lead to arbitrary command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56803</link><description>Ghostty is a cross-platform terminal emulator. Ghostty, as allowed by default in 1.0.0, allows attackers to modify the window title via a certain character escape sequence and then insert it back to the command line in the user's terminal, e.g. when the user views a file containing the malicious sequence, which could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands. This attack requires an attacker to send malicious escape sequences followed by convincing the user to physically press the "enter" key. Fixed in Ghostty v1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13085 | PHPGurukul Land Record System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13085</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:39:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13084 | PHPGurukul Land Record System search-property.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13084</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/search-property.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13083 | PHPGurukul Land Record System admin-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13083</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument Admin Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13082 | PHPGurukul Land Record System search-property.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13082</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-property.php. The manipulation of the argument Search By leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13081 | PHPGurukul Land Record System contactus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13081</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument Page Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13080 | PHPGurukul Land Record System aboutus.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13080</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument Page Description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13079 | PHPGurukul Land Record System property-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13079</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/property-details.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 19:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13078 | PHPGurukul Land Record System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13078</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 19:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13077 | PHPGurukul Land Record System add-property.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13077</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/add-property.php. The manipulation of the argument Land Subtype leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 18:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13076 | PHPGurukul Land Record System edit-propertytype.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13076</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit-propertytype.php. The manipulation of the argument Property Type leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13075 | PHPGurukul Land Record System add-propertytype.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13075</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-propertytype.php. The manipulation of the argument Land Property Type leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 17:37:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13074 | PHPGurukul Land Record System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13074</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in PHPGurukul Land Record System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55631 | An engine link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55631</link><description>An engine link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55632 | A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected instal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55632</link><description>A security agent link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55917 | An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55917</link><description>An origin validation error vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55955 | An incorrect permissions assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 agents between versions 20.0.1-9400 and 20.0.1-23340 cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55955</link><description>An incorrect permissions assignment vulnerability in Trend Micro Deep Security 20.0 agents between versions 20.0.1-9400 and 20.0.1-23340 could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52047 | A widget local file inclusion vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected inst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52047</link><description>A widget local file inclusion vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52048 | A LogServer link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52048</link><description>A LogServer link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2024-52049.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52049 | A LogServer link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52049</link><description>A LogServer link following vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations. This vulnerability is similar to, but not identical to CVE-2024-52048.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52050 | A LogServer arbitrary file creation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52050</link><description>A LogServer arbitrary file creation vulnerability in Trend Micro Apex One could allow a local attacker to escalate privileges on affected installations.

Please note: an attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53647 | Trend Micro ID Security, version 3.0 and below contains a vulnerability that could allow an attacker to send an unlimited number of email ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53647</link><description>Trend Micro ID Security, version 3.0 and below contains a vulnerability that could allow an attacker to send an unlimited number of email verification requests without any restriction, potentially leading to abuse or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:17:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56198 | path-sanitizer allows bypassing the existing filters to achieve path-traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56198</link><description>path-sanitizer is a simple lightweight npm package for sanitizing paths to prevent Path Traversal. Prior to 3.1.0, the filters can be bypassed using .=%5c which results in a path traversal. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56802 | Tapir allows DeployKey exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56802</link><description>Tapir is a private Terraform registry. Tapir versions 0.9.0 and 0.9.1 are facing a critical issue with scope-able Deploykeys where attackers can guess the key to get write access to the registry.  User must upgrade to 0.9.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 15:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13072 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System Customer Detail add-customer-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13072</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-customer-services.php of the component Customer Detail Handler. The manipulation of the argument sids[] leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 15:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13070 | CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System Update User Page update_users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13070</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_users.php of the component Update User Page. The manipulation of the argument user_upd leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6602 | Ffmpeg: improper handling of input format in tty demuxer of ffmpeg</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6602</link><description>A flaw was found in FFmpeg's TTY Demuxer. This vulnerability allows possible data exfiltration via improper parsing of non-TTY-compliant input files in HLS playlists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6603 | Ffmpeg: null pointer dereference in ffmpeg hls parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6603</link><description>A flaw was found in FFmpeg's HLS playlist parsing. This vulnerability allows a denial of service via a maliciously crafted HLS playlist that triggers a null pointer dereference during initialization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25133 | Openshift-dedicated: hive: rce through aws/kubernetes client configuration leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25133</link><description>A flaw was found in the Hive ClusterDeployments resource in OpenShift Dedicated. In certain conditions, this issue may allow a developer account on a Hive-enabled cluster to obtain cluster-admin privileges by executing arbitrary commands on the hive/hive-controllers pod.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49686 | WordPress Landing Page Cat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49686</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fatcat Apps Landing Page Cat.This issue affects Landing Page Cat: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49687 | WordPress Smart Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 8.45.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49687</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StoreApps Smart Manager.This issue affects Smart Manager: from n/a through 8.45.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49694 | WordPress My Wp Brand – Hide menu &amp;amp; Hide Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49694</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in imw3 My Wp Brand – Hide menu &amp; Hide Plugin.This issue affects My Wp Brand – Hide menu &amp; Hide Plugin: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49698 | WordPress Great Restaurant Menu WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49698</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PriceListo Best Restaurant Menu by PriceListo.This issue affects Best Restaurant Menu by PriceListo: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51667 | WordPress Paytium plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51667</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in David de Boer Paytium.This issue affects Paytium: from n/a through 4.4.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55995 | WordPress Torod plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Torod Holding LTD Torod allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Torod: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56002 | WordPress Contact Form, Survey &amp;amp; Form Builder – MightyForms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56002</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Porthas Inc. Contact Form, Survey &amp; Form Builder – MightyForms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Contact Form, Survey &amp; Form Builder – MightyForms: from n/a through 1.3.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56070 | WordPress WP SuperBackup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Multiple Subscriber+ Broken Access Control vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56070</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Azzaroco WP SuperBackup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP SuperBackup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56206 | WordPress gap-hub-user-role. plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 - CSRF to Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56206</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Amarjeet Amar allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects gap-hub-user-role: from n/a through 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56207 | WordPress EditionGuard for WooCommerce – eBook Sales with DRM plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56207</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EditionGuard Dev Team EditionGuard for WooCommerce – eBook Sales with DRM allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects EditionGuard for WooCommerce – eBook Sales with DRM: from n/a through 3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56045 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Directory Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56045</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56061 | WordPress RepairBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8119 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56061</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Webful Creations Computer Repair Shop allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Computer Repair Shop: from n/a through 3.8119.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56066 | WordPress Agency Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.23 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56066</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Inspry Agency Toolkit allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Agency Toolkit: from n/a through 1.0.23.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56203 | WordPress Wayne Audio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56203</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in George Holmes II Wayne Audio Player allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Wayne Audio Player: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56204 | WordPress Sinking Dropdowns plugin &amp;lt;= 1.25 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56204</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yonatan Reinberg of Social Ink Sinking Dropdowns allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Sinking Dropdowns: from n/a through 1.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56040 | WordPress VibeBP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9.4.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56040</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in VibeThemes VibeBP allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects VibeBP: from n/a through 1.9.9.4.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56043 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56043</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56044 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Token Generation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56044</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56041 | WordPress VibeBP plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56041</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes VibeBP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects VibeBP: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56042 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.5.3 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56042</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a before 1.9.9.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48775 | WordPress WP CleanFix plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48775</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gfazioli WP Cleanfix allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Cleanfix: from n/a through 5.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50850 | WordPress Woo Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt; 5.8.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50850</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Woo WooCommerce Subscriptions allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Subscriptions: from n/a before 5.8.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55991 | WordPress CRM Plugin – WP-CRM System plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55991</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP-CRM WP-CRM System allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP-CRM System: from n/a through 3.2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56031 | WordPress Smart Shopify Product plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56031</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Yulio Aleman Jimenez Smart Shopify Product allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Smart Shopify Product: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56039 | WordPress VibeBP plugin &amp;lt; 1.9.9.7.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56039</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in VibeThemes VibeBP allows SQL Injection.This issue affects VibeBP: from n/a before 1.9.9.7.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56046 | WordPress WPLMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56046</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in VibeThemes WPLMS allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPLMS: from n/a through 1.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56064 | WordPress WP SuperBackup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56064</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Azzaroco WP SuperBackup allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WP SuperBackup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56067 | WordPress WP SuperBackup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Unauthenticated Backup File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56067</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Azzaroco WP SuperBackup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP SuperBackup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56068 | WordPress WP SuperBackup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Subscriber+ PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56068</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Azzaroco WP SuperBackup.This issue affects WP SuperBackup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56071 | WordPress Simple Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56071</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Mike Leembruggen Simple Dashboard allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Simple Dashboard: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56205 | WordPress AI Magic – SEO Content Generator &amp;amp; Article Writer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56205</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in AI Magic allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects AI Magic: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13061 | 2100 Technology Electronic Official Document Management System - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13061</link><description>The Electronic Official Document Management System from 2100 Technology has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability. Although the product enforces an IP whitelist for the API used to query user tokens, unauthenticated remote attackers can still deceive the server to obtain tokens of arbitrary users, which can then be used to log into the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 11:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13069 | SourceCodester Multi Role Login System add-user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13069</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Multi Role Login System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /endpoint/add-user.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12105 | WhatsUp Gold - SnmpExtendedActiveMonitor path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12105</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.2, an authenticated user can use a specially crafted HTTP request that can lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12106 | WhatsUp Gold -  LDAP configuration interface leading to allowing attacker to configure LDAP settings without authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12106</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.2, an unauthenticated attacker can configure LDAP settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12108 | WhatsUp Gold - Public API signing key rotation issue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12108</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.2, an attacker can gain access to the WhatsUp Gold server via the public API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56209 | WordPress Kleo theme &amp;lt; 5.4.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56209</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SeventhQueen Kleo allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kleo: from n/a before 5.4.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56210 | WordPress UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56210</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DeluxeThemes Userpro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Userpro: from n/a through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56221 | WordPress WPMozo Addons Lite for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56221</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Elicus WPMozo Addons Lite for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPMozo Addons Lite for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56223 | WordPress Gulri Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.8  - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56223</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Gulri Slider allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Gulri Slider: from n/a through 3.5.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56224 | WordPress Ledenbeheer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56224</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ledenbeheer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ledenbeheer: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56226 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1001 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56226</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.7.1001.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56228 | WordPress Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPFactory Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56231 | WordPress SaasPricing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Debuggers Studio SaasPricing allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SaasPricing: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56233 | WordPress Kintpv Wooconnect plugin &amp;lt;= 8.129 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kinhelios Kintpv Wooconnect allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Kintpv Wooconnect: from n/a through 8.129.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56234 | WordPress VW Automobile Lite theme &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56234</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VW THEMES VW Automobile Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects VW Automobile Lite: from n/a through 2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56215 | WordPress Member Directory and Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56215</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stephen Sherrard Member Directory and Contact Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Member Directory and Contact Form: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56217 | WordPress Download Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.03 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56217</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in W3 Eden, Inc. Download Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Download Manager: from n/a through 3.3.03.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56219 | WordPress Widget Options plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56219</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MarketingFire Widget Options allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Widget Options: from n/a through 4.0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56225 | WordPress Premium Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.56 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56225</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.56.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56227 | WordPress Royal Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1001 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56227</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Addons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Royal Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.7.1001.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56235 | WordPress Coupon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56235</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coupon Plugin Coupon allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Coupon: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56256 | WordPress Embed PDF Viewer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56256</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Andy Fragen Embed PDF Viewer allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Embed PDF Viewer: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56265 | WordPress WooCommerce - PDF Vouchers plugin &amp;lt; 4.9.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56265</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPWeb WooCommerce PDF Vouchers allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce PDF Vouchers: from n/a before 4.9.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56218 | WordPress Contact Form 7 - Dynamic Text Extension plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56218</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AuRise Creative, SevenSpark Contact Form 7 Dynamic Text Extension allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Dynamic Text Extension: from n/a through 5.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56220 | WordPress SSL Wireless SMS Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56220</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in SSL Wireless SSL Wireless SMS Notification allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects SSL Wireless SMS Notification: from n/a through 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56222 | WordPress CodeBard Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56222</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Codebard CodeBard Help Desk allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects CodeBard Help Desk: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56229 | WordPress SearchIQ plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6 - Cross-Site Requst Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56229</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Searchiq SearchIQ.This issue affects SearchIQ: from n/a through 4.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56232 | WordPress WP Nice Loader plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.4 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56232</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alexander Volkov WP Nice Loader allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Nice Loader: from n/a through 0.1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56211 | WordPress UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9 - Authenticated Arbitrary User Meta Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56211</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in DeluxeThemes Userpro.This issue affects Userpro: from n/a through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56212 | WordPress UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56212</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in DeluxeThemes Userpro.This issue affects Userpro: from n/a through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56213 | WordPress Eventin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - Contributor+ Limited Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56213</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Themewinter Eventin allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Eventin: from n/a through 4.0.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56214 | WordPress UserPro plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56214</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in DeluxeThemes Userpro allows Path Traversal.This issue affects Userpro: from n/a through 5.1.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56216 | WordPress Themify Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56216</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Themify Themify Builder allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Themify Builder: from n/a through 7.6.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56230 | WordPress Dynamic Product Category Grid, Slider for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56230</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Dynamic Web Lab Dynamic Product Category Grid, Slider for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Dynamic Product Category Grid, Slider for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 10:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13067 | CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System All Users Page all_users.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13067</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/all_users.php of the component All Users Page. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 09:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49422 | Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to reset lockscreen failure count by ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49422</link><description>Protection Mechanism Failure in bootloader prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to reset lockscreen failure count by hardware fault injection. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 08:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11972 | Hunk Companion &amp;lt; 1.9.0 - Unauthenticated Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11972</link><description>The Hunk Companion WordPress plugin before 1.9.0 does not correctly authorize some REST API endpoints, allowing unauthenticated requests to install and activate arbitrary Hunk Companion WordPress plugin before 1.9.0 from the WordPress.org repo, including vulnerable Hunk Companion WordPress plugin before 1.9.0 that have been closed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 06:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45497 | Openshift-api: build process in openshift allows overwriting of node pull credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45497</link><description>A flaw was found in the OpenShift build process, where the docker-build container is configured with a hostPath volume mount that maps the node's /var/lib/kubelet/config.json file into the build pod. This file contains sensitive credentials necessary for pulling images from private repositories. The mount is not read-only, which allows the attacker to overwrite it. By modifying the config.json file, the attacker can cause a denial of service by preventing the node from pulling new images and potentially exfiltrating sensitive secrets. This flaw impacts the availability of services dependent on image pulls and exposes sensitive information to unauthorized parties.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13040 | Quanta Computer QOCA aim - Authorization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13040</link><description>The QOCA aim from Quanta Computer has an Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability. By controlling the user ID parameter, remote attackers with regular privileges could access certain features as any user, modify any user's account information and privileges, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12838 | Changing Information Technology CGFIDO - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12838</link><description>The passwordless login mechanism in CGFIDO from Changing Information Technology has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to send a crafted request to switch to the identity of any user, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12839 | Changing Information Technology CGFIDO - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12839</link><description>The login mechanism via device authentication of CGFIDO from Changing Information Technology has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability. If a user visits a forged website, the agent program deployed on their device will send an authentication signature to the website. An unauthenticated remote attacker who obtains this signature can use it to log into the system with any device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 02:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13058 | Authenticated, non-admin users can create storage pools via the sifi API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13058</link><description>An issue exists in SoftIron HyperCloud
 where authenticated, but non-admin users can create data pools, which could potentially impact the performance and availability of the backend software-defined storage subsystem.

This issue only impacts SoftIron HyperCloud and related software products (such as VM Squared) software versions 2.3.0 to before 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13042 | Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives Management System SubjectController.class.php download information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13042</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tsinghua Unigroup Electronic Archives Management System 3.2.210802(62532). It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function download of the file SubjectController.class.php. The manipulation of the argument path leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11944 | iXsystems TrueNAS CORE tarfile.extractall Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11944</link><description>iXsystems TrueNAS CORE tarfile.extractall Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of iXsystems TrueNAS devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the tarfile.extractall method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25626.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11946 | iXsystems TrueNAS CORE fetch_plugin_packagesites tar Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11946</link><description>iXsystems TrueNAS CORE fetch_plugin_packagesites tar Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to tamper with firmware update files on affected installations of iXsystems TrueNAS devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of firmware updates. The issue results from the use of an insecure protocol to deliver updates. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-25668.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12751 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12751</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25344.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12752 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12752</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-25345.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12753 | Foxit PDF Reader Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12753</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the product installer. By creating a junction, an attacker can abuse the installer process to create an arbitrary file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25408.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13043 | Panda Security Dome Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13043</link><description>Panda Security Dome Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Panda Security Dome. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Hotspot Shield. By creating a junction, an attacker can abuse the application to delete arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-23478.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13044 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13044</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24870.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13045 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13045</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt AR File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of AR files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24848.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13046 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13046</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24867.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13047 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13047</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt CO File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of CO files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24843.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13048 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13048</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24844.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13049 | Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13049</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt XE File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Cobalt. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XE files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24847.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13050 | Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13050</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24976.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13051 | Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13051</link><description>Ashlar-Vellum Graphite VC6 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Ashlar-Vellum Graphite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of VC6 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24977.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56799 | Simofa Allows Unauthenticated Access to API Routes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56799</link><description>Simofa is a tool to help automate static website building and deployment. Prior to version 0.2.7, due to a design mistake in the RouteLoader class, some API routes may be publicly accessible when they should require authentication. This vulnerability has been patched in v0.2.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56800 | Firecrawl has SSRF Vulnerability via malicious scrape target</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56800</link><description>Firecrawl is a web scraper that allows users to extract the content of a webpage for a large language model. Versions prior to 1.1.1 contain a server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability. The scraping engine could be exploited by crafting a malicious site that redirects to a local IP address. This allowed exfiltration of local network resources through the API. The cloud service was patched on December 27th, 2024, and the maintainers have checked that no user data was exposed by this vulnerability. Scraping engines used in the open sourced version of Firecrawl were patched on December 29th, 2024, except for the playwright services which the maintainers have determined to be un-patchable. All users of open-source software (OSS) Firecrawl should upgrade to v1.1.1. As a workaround, OSS Firecrawl users should supply the playwright services with a secure proxy. A proxy can be specified through the `PROXY_SERVER` env in the environment variables. Please refer to the documentation for instructions. Ensure that the proxy server one is using is setup to block all traffic going to link-local IP addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56801 | Tasklists has Blind SQL Injection in /ajax/reorder.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56801</link><description>Tasklists provides plugin tasklists for GLPI. Versions prior to 2.0.4 have a blind SQL injection vulnerability. Version 2.0.4 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 18:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46542 | Veritas / Arctera Data Insight before 7.1.1 allows Application Administrators to conduct SQL injection attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46542</link><description>Veritas / Arctera Data Insight before 7.1.1 allows Application Administrators to conduct SQL injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 17:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12754 | AnyDesk Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12754</link><description>AnyDesk Link Following Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of AnyDesk. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of background images. By creating a junction, an attacker can abuse the service to read arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-23940.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12828 | Webmin CGI Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12828</link><description>Webmin CGI Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Webmin. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the handling of CGI requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22346.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12834 | Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD STP File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12834</link><description>Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD STP File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22414.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12835 | Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD ICS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12835</link><description>Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD ICS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of ICS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22415.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12836 | Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD STP File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12836</link><description>Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD STP File Parsing Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Delta Electronics DRASimuCAD. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of STP files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22450.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56734 | Better Auth has an Open Redirect Vulnerability in Verify Email Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56734</link><description>Better Auth is an authentication library for TypeScript. An open redirect vulnerability has been identified in the verify email endpoint of all versions of Better Auth prior to v1.1.6, potentially allowing attackers to redirect users to malicious websites. This issue affects users relying on email verification links generated by the library. The verify email callback endpoint accepts a `callbackURL` parameter. Unlike other verification methods, email verification only uses JWT to verify and redirect without proper validation of the target domain. The origin checker is bypassed in this scenario because it only checks for `POST` requests. An attacker can manipulate this parameter to redirect users to arbitrary URLs controlled by the attacker. Version 1.1.6 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56733 | Password Pusher Allows Session Token Interception Leading to Potential Hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56733</link><description>Password Pusher is an open source application to communicate sensitive information over the web. A vulnerability has been reported in versions 1.50.3 and prior where an attacker can copy the session cookie before a user logs out, potentially allowing session hijacking. Although the session token is replaced and invalidated upon logout, if an attacker manages to capture the session cookie before this process, they can use the token to gain unauthorized access to the user's session until the token expires or is manually cleared. This vulnerability hinges on the attacker's ability to access the session cookie during an active session, either through a man-in-the-middle attack, by exploiting another vulnerability like XSS, or via direct access to the victim's device. Although there is no direct resolution to this vulnerability, it is recommended to always use the latest version of Password Pusher to best mitigate risk. If self-hosting, ensure Password Pusher is hosted exclusively over SSL connections to encrypt traffic and prevent session cookies from being intercepted in transit. Additionally, implement best practices in local security to safeguard user systems, browsers, and data against unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56517 | LGSL has a reflected XSS at /lgsl_files/lgsl_list.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56517</link><description>LGSL (Live Game Server List) provides online status lists for online video games. Versions up to and including 6.2.1 contain a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability in the `Referer` HTTP header. The vulnerability allows attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript code, which is reflected in the HTML response without proper sanitization. When crafted malicious input is provided in the `Referer` header, it is echoed back into an HTML attribute in the application’s response. Commit 7ecb839df9358d21f64cdbff5b2536af25a77de1 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56516 | free-one-api uses md5 for password storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56516</link><description>free-one-api allows users to access large language model reverse engineering libraries through the standard OpenAI API format. In versions up to and including 1.0.1, MD5 is used to hash passwords before sending them to the backend. MD5 is a cryptographically broken hashing algorithm and is no longer considered secure for password storage or transmission. It is vulnerable to collision attacks and can be easily cracked using modern hardware, exposing user credentials to potential compromise. As of time of publication, a replacement for MD5 has not been committed to the free-one-api GitHub repository.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52294 | khoj has an IDOR in subscription management that allows unauthorized subscription modifications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52294</link><description>Khoj is a self-hostable artificial intelligence app. Prior to version 1.29.10, an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the update_subscription endpoint allows any authenticated user to manipulate other users' Stripe subscriptions by simply modifying the email parameter in the request. The vulnerability exists in the subscription endpoint at `/api/subscription`. The endpoint uses an email parameter as a direct reference to user subscriptions without verifying object ownership. While authentication is required, there is no authorization check to verify if the authenticated user owns the referenced subscription. The issue was fixed in version 1.29.10. Support for arbitrarily presenting an email for update has been deprecated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50701 | TeamPass before 3.1.3.1, when retrieving information about access rights for a folder, does not properly check whether a folder is in a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50701</link><description>TeamPass before 3.1.3.1, when retrieving information about access rights for a folder, does not properly check whether a folder is in a user's allowed folders list that has been defined by an admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50702 | TeamPass before 3.1.3.1 does not properly check whether a mail_me (aka action_mail) operation is on behalf of an administrator or manager.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50702</link><description>TeamPass before 3.1.3.1 does not properly check whether a mail_me (aka action_mail) operation is on behalf of an administrator or manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 15:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50703 | TeamPass before 3.1.3.1 does not properly prevent a user from acting with the privileges of a different user_id.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50703</link><description>TeamPass before 3.1.3.1 does not properly prevent a user from acting with the privileges of a different user_id.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 15:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54181 | IBM WebSphere Automation command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54181</link><description>IBM WebSphere Automation 1.7.5 could allow a remote privileged user, who has authorized access to the swagger UI, to execute arbitrary code. Using specially crafted input, the user could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 13:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10044 | SSRF in POST /worker_generate_stream API endpoint in lm-sys/fastchat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10044</link><description>A Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the POST /worker_generate_stream API endpoint of the Controller API Server in lm-sys/fastchat, as of commit e208d5677c6837d590b81cb03847c0b9de100765. This vulnerability allows attackers to exploit the victim controller API server's credentials to perform unauthorized web actions or access unauthorized web resources by combining it with the POST /register_worker endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12993 | Location information exposure in Infinix Weather app</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12993</link><description>Infinix devices contain a pre-loaded "com.rlk.weathers" application, that exposes an unsecured content provider. An attacker can communicate with the provider and reveal the user’s location without any privileges. 
After multiple attempts to contact the vendor we did not receive any answer. We suppose this issue affects all Infinix Mobile devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47924 | Boa web server – CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47924</link><description>Boa web server – CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 10:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47925 | Tecnick TCExam – Multiple CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47925</link><description>Tecnick TCExam – Multiple CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 10:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47926 | Tecnick TCExam – CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47926</link><description>Tecnick TCExam – CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 10:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47922 | Priority – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47922</link><description>Priority – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47923 | Mashov – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47923</link><description>Mashov – CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47918 | Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47918</link><description>Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47919 | Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47919</link><description>Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-78: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47920 | Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47920</link><description>Tiki Wiki CMS – CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47921 | Smadar SPS – CWE-327: Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47921</link><description>Smadar SPS – CWE-327: Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47917 | Mobotix - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47917</link><description>CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22063 | ZTE ZENIC ONE R58 product has a CSV injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22063</link><description>The ZENIC ONE R58 products by ZTE Corporation have a command injection vulnerability. An authenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability to tamper with messages, inject malicious code, and subsequently launch attacks on related devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13039 | code-projects Simple Chat System add_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13039</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Simple Chat System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /add_user.php. The manipulation of the argument name/email/password/number leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 04:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13038 | CodeAstro Simple Loan Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13038</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Simple Loan Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 04:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13037 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System report.php attendance_report sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13037</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function attendance_report of the file /admin/report.php. The manipulation of the argument course_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 03:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13036 | code-projects Chat System update_room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13036</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_room.php. The manipulation of the argument id/name/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 03:30:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13035 | code-projects Chat System update_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13035</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/update_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13033 | code-projects Chat System chatroom.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13033</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Chat System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/chatroom.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 02:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13034 | code-projects Chat System update_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13034</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/update_user.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 02:23:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13032 | Antabot White-Jotter Article Editor editor server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13032</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Antabot White-Jotter up to 0.2.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/content/editor of the component Article Editor. The manipulation of the argument articleCover leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 02:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13031 | Antabot White-Jotter Article Content Editor editor cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13031</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Antabot White-Jotter up to 0.2.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/content/editor of the component Article Content Editor. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 01:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13030 | D-Link DIR-823G Web Management Interface HNAP1 SetVirtualServerSettings access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13030</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823G 1.0.2B05_20181207. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function SetAutoRebootSettings/SetClientInfo/SetDMZSettings/SetFirewallSettings/SetParentsControlInfo/SetQoSSettings/SetVirtualServerSettings of the file /HNAP1/ of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 01:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>