<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1002 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setIpPortFilterRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ePort leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252271. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 14:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1014 | Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1014</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could interrupt the availability of the administration panel by sending multiple ICMP packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1015 | Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1015</link><description>Remote command execution vulnerability in SE-elektronic GmbH E-DDC3.3 affecting versions 03.07.03 and higher. An attacker could send different commands from the operating system to the system via the web configuration functionality of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1000 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setTracerouteCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setTracerouteCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument command leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252269 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1001 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi main stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. Affected is the function main of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252270 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0998 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setDiagnosisCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function setDiagnosisCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252267. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0999 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0999</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument eTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252268. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0997 | Totolink N200RE cstecgi.cgi setOpModeCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N200RE 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setOpModeCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument pppoeUser leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252266 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29055 | Apache Kylin: Insufficiently protected credentials in config file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29055</link><description>In Apache Kylin version 2.0.0 to 4.0.3, there is a Server Config web interface that displays the content of file 'kylin.properties', that may contain serverside credentials. When the kylin service runs over HTTP (or other plain text protocol), it is possible for network sniffers to hijack the HTTP payload and get access to the content of kylin.properties and potentially the containing credentials.

To avoid this threat, users are recommended to 

  *  Always turn on HTTPS so that network payload is encrypted.

  *  Avoid putting credentials in kylin.properties, or at least not in plain text.
  *  Use network firewalls to protect the serverside such that it is not accessible to external attackers.

  *  Upgrade to version Apache Kylin 4.0.4, which filters out the sensitive content that goes to the Server Config web interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 12:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5378 | Stored XSS in SmodBIP and MegaBIP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5378</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in  MegaBIP and already unsupported SmodBIP software allows for Stored XSS.This issue affects SmodBIP in all versions and MegaBIP in versions up to 4.36.2 (newer versions were not tested; the vendor has not confirmed fixing the vulnerability).</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 11:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46838 | Linux: netback processing of zero-length transmit fragment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46838</link><description>Transmit requests in Xen's virtual network protocol can consist of
multiple parts.  While not really useful, except for the initial part
any of them may be of zero length, i.e. carry no data at all.  Besides a
certain initial portion of the to be transferred data, these parts are
directly translated into what Linux calls SKB fragments.  Such converted
request parts can, when for a particular SKB they are all of length
zero, lead to a de-reference of NULL in core networking code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23790 | Missing file type check in avatar picture upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23790</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the upload functionality for user avatars allows functionality misuse due to missing check of filetypes.
This issue affects OTRS:  from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023 through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23791 | Unnecessary data is written to log if issues during indexing occurs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23791</link><description>Insertion of debug information into log file during building the elastic search index allows reading of sensitive information from articles.This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0212 | Cloudflare WordPress plugin enables information disclosure of Cloudflare API (for low privileged users)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0212</link><description>The Cloudflare Wordpress plugin was found to be vulnerable to improper authentication. The vulnerability enables attackers with a lower privileged account to access data from the Cloudflare API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23792 | Insufficient access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23792</link><description>When adding attachments to ticket comments, 
another user can add attachments as well impersonating the orginal user. The attack requires a 
logged-in other user to know the UUID. While the legitimate user 
completes the comment, the malicious user can add more files to the 
comment.

This issue affects OTRS: from 7.0.X through 7.0.48, from 8.0.X through 8.0.37, from 2023.X through 2023.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24736 | The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24736</link><description>The POP3 service in YahooPOPs (aka YPOPs!) 1.6 allows a remote denial of service (reboot) via a long string to TCP port 110, a related issue to CVE-2004-1558.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 03:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0996 | Tenda i9 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0996</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.9(4122). This affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252261 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0995 | Tenda W6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0995</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252260. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:06:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0993 | Tenda i6 httpd WifiMacFilterGet formWifiMacFilterGet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0993</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formWifiMacFilterGet of the file /goform/WifiMacFilterGet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252258 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0994 | Tenda W6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0994</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W6 1.0.0.9(4122). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252259. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0991 | Tenda i6 httpd setcfm formSetCfm stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0991</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetCfm of the file /goform/setcfm of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument funcpara1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252256. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0992 | Tenda i6 httpd wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0992</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument index leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252257 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0989 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP Service.php del_sn_db path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0989</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is the function del_sn_db of the file /application/index/controller/Service.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252254 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0990 | Tenda i6 httpd setAutoPing formSetAutoPing stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0990</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda i6 1.0.0.9(3857). This affects the function formSetAutoPing of the file /goform/setAutoPing of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument ping1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252255. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0987 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP log neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0987</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected is an unknown function of the file /runtime/log. The manipulation leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252252. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0988 | Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP common.php checklogin improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0988</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Sichuan Yougou Technology KuERP up to 1.0.4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function checklogin of the file /application/index/common.php. The manipulation of the argument App_User_id/App_user_Token leads to improper authentication. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252253 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0986 | Issabel PBX Asterisk-Cli os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0986</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Issabel PBX 4.0.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php?menu=asterisk_cli of the component Asterisk-Cli. The manipulation of the argument Command leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252251. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23782 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23782</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.x series versions prior to Ver.3.1.7, Ver.3.0.x series versions prior to Ver.3.0.29, Ver.2.11.x series versions prior to Ver.2.11.58, Ver.2.10.x series versions prior to Ver.2.10.50, and Ver.2.9.0 and earlier versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a user with a contributor or higher privilege may execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 23:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6200 | Kernel: icmpv6 router advertisement packets, aka linux tcp/ip remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6200</link><description>A race condition was found in the Linux Kernel. Under certain conditions, an unauthenticated attacker from an adjacent network could send an ICMPv6 router advertisement packet, causing arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0841 | Kernel: hugetlbfs: null pointer dereference in hugetlbfs_fill_super function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0841</link><description>A null pointer dereference flaw was found in the hugetlbfs_fill_super function in the Linux kernel hugetlbfs (HugeTLB pages) functionality. This issue may allow a local user to crash the system or potentially escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23740 | An issue in Kap for macOS version 3.6.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilns...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23740</link><description>An issue in Kap for macOS version 3.6.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23739 | An issue in Discord for macOS version 0.0.291 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNode...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23739</link><description>An issue in Discord for macOS version 0.0.291 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23742 | An issue in Loom on macOS version 0.196.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23742</link><description>An issue in Loom on macOS version 0.196.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23741 | An issue in Hyper on macOS version 3.4.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCliln...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23741</link><description>An issue in Hyper on macOS version 3.4.1 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23743 | An issue in Notion for macOS version 3.1.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23743</link><description>An issue in Notion for macOS version 3.1.0 and before, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments components.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 02:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23738 | An issue in Postman version 10.22 and before on macOS allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeCli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23738</link><description>An issue in Postman version 10.22 and before on macOS allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the RunAsNode and enableNodeClilnspectArguments settings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0962 | obgm libcoap Configuration File coap_oscore.c get_split_entry stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in obgm libcoap 4.3.4. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function get_split_entry of the file src/coap_oscore.c of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-252206 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0960 | flink-extended ai-flow workflow_command.py cloudpickle.loads deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in flink-extended ai-flow 0.3.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cloudpickle.loads of the file \ai_flow\cli\commands\workflow_command.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252205 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0959 | StanfordVL GibsonEnv pposgd_fuse.py cloudpickle.load deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in StanfordVL GibsonEnv 0.3.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function cloudpickle.load of the file gibson\utils\pposgd_fuse.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252204.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22861 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the avcodec/osq module.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22861</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows attackers to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the avcodec/osq module.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0958 | CodeAstro Stock Management System Add Category index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Stock Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /index.php of the component Add Category Handler. The manipulation of the argument Category Name/Category Description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252203.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22862 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the JJPEG XL Parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22862</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the JJPEG XL Parser.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22860 | Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the jpegxl_anim_read_packet comp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22860</link><description>Integer overflow vulnerability in FFmpeg before n6.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the jpegxl_anim_read_packet component in the JPEG XL Animation decoder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 06:16:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48202 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS 8.0.1 allows an authenticated low-privileged user to escalate privileges via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48202</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS 8.0.1 allows an authenticated low-privileged user to escalate privileges via a crafted SVG file in the File Manager component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0618 | The Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0618</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin – Fastest Contact Form Builder Plugin for WordPress by Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imported form titles in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48201 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS v.8.0.1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48201</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Sunlight CMS v.8.0.1, allows remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via a crafted script to the Content text editor component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 05:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0697 | The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and inclu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0697</link><description>The Backuply – Backup, Restore, Migrate and Clone plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 via the node_id parameter in the backuply_get_jstree function. This makes it possible for attackers with administrator privileges or higher to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 04:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0824 | The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Anything functionality in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0824</link><description>The Exclusive Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Anything functionality in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 04:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6497 | The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the automatic redirect URL setting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6497</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the automatic redirect URL setting in all versions up to and including 4.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0664 | The Meks Smart Social Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Meks Smart Social Widget in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0664</link><description>The Meks Smart Social Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Meks Smart Social Widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0667 | The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0667</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.21. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'execute' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary methods in the 'BoosterController' class via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52389 | UTF32Encoding.cpp in POCO has a Poco::UTF32Encoding integer overflow and resultant stack buffer overflow because Poco::UTF32Encoding::conver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52389</link><description>UTF32Encoding.cpp in POCO has a Poco::UTF32Encoding integer overflow and resultant stack buffer overflow because Poco::UTF32Encoding::convert() and Poco::UTF32::queryConvert() may return a negative integer if a UTF-32 byte sequence evaluates to a value of 0x80000000 or higher. This is fixed in 1.11.8p2, 1.12.5p2, and 1.13.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6482 | Encryption key derived from static host information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6482</link><description>Use of encryption key derived from static information in Synaptics Fingerprint Driver allows 

an attacker to set up a TLS session with the fingerprint sensor and send restricted commands to the fingerprint sensor. This may 
allow an attacker, who has physical access to the sensor, to enroll a fingerprint into the 
template database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:53:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>