<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-11980 | Billion Electric in-vehicle router - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11980</link><description>Certain modes of in-vehicle routers from Billion Electric have a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to directly access the specific functionality to obtain partial device information, modify the WiFi SSID, and restart the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10704 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt; 1.8.31 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10704</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.31 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10980 | Element Pack Elementor Addons &amp;lt; 5.10.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10980</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) WordPress plugin before 5.10.3 does not validate and escape some of its Cookie Consent block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53701 | Multiple FCNT Android devices provide the original security features such as "privacy mode" where arbitrary applications can be set not to b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53701</link><description>Multiple FCNT Android devices provide the original security features such as "privacy mode" where arbitrary applications can be set not to be displayed, etc.
Under certain conditions, and when an attacker can directly operate the device which its screen is unlocked by a user, the provided security features' setting pages may be exposed and/or the settings may be altered, without authentication. For example, specific applications in the device configured to be hidden may be displayed and/or activated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39162 | pyspider through 0.3.10 allows /update XSS. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39162</link><description>pyspider through 0.3.10 allows /update XSS. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48651 | In ProFTPD through 1.3.8b before cec01cc, supplemental group inheritance grants unintended access to GID 0 because of the lack of supplement...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48651</link><description>In ProFTPD through 1.3.8b before cec01cc, supplemental group inheritance grants unintended access to GID 0 because of the lack of supplemental groups from mod_sql.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 05:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45495 | MSA FieldServer Gateway 5.0.0 through 6.5.2 allows cross-origin WebSocket hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45495</link><description>MSA FieldServer Gateway 5.0.0 through 6.5.2 allows cross-origin WebSocket hijacking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35451 | LinkStack 2.7.9 through 4.7.7 allows resources\views\components\favicon.blade.php link SSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35451</link><description>LinkStack 2.7.9 through 4.7.7 allows resources\views\components\favicon.blade.php link SSRF.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54124 | In Click Studios Passwordstate before build 9920, there is a potential permission escalation on the edit folder screen.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54124</link><description>In Click Studios Passwordstate before build 9920, there is a potential permission escalation on the edit folder screen.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54123 | Backdrop CMS before 1.28.4 and 1.29.x before 1.29.2 allows XSS via an SVG document, if the SVG tag is allowed for a text format.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54123</link><description>Backdrop CMS before 1.28.4 and 1.29.x before 1.29.2 allows XSS via an SVG document, if the SVG tag is allowed for a text format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 04:17:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11978 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Arbitrary File Reading through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11978</link><description>DreamMaker from Interinfo has a Path Traversal vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11979 | Interinfo DreamMaker - Unrestricted File Upload through Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11979</link><description>DreamMaker from Interinfo has a Path Traversal vulnerability and does not restrict the types of uploaded files. This allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files to any directory, leading to arbitrary code execution by uploading webshells.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 02:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8300 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8300</link><description>Dead Code vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 Version 10.97.2, 10.97.2 CFR1, 10.97.2 CRF2 and 10.97.3 and Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 Version 10.97.2, 10.97.2 CFR1, 10.97.2 CRF2 and 10.97.3 allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by tampering with a specially crafted DLL. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9852 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64 and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9852</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by storing a specially crafted DLL in a specific folder. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8299 | Malicious Code Execution Vulnerability in GENESIS64 and MC Works64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8299</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element vulnerability in ICONICS GENESIS64 all versions, Mitsubishi Electric GENESIS64 all versions and Mitsubishi Electric MC Works64 all versions allows a local authenticated attacker to execute a malicious code by storing a specially crafted DLL in a specific folder. This could lead to disclose, tamper with, destroy, or delete information in the affected products, or cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11970 | code-projects Concert Ticket Ordering System tour(cor).php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Concert Ticket Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tour(cor).php. The manipulation of the argument mai leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11971 | Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress Avatar upload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Guizhou Xiaoma Technology jpress 5.1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /commons/attachment/upload of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument files leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11967 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system reset-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/reset-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11968 | code-projects Farmacia pagamento.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file pagamento.php. The manipulation of the argument notaFiscal leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11966 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11964 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/index.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11965 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management system reset-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management system 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /user/reset-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52338 | Apache Arrow R package: Arbitrary code execution when loading a malicious data file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52338</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in IPC and Parquet readers in the Apache Arrow R package versions 4.0.0 through 16.1.0 allows arbitrary code execution. An application is vulnerable if it 
reads Arrow IPC, Feather or Parquet data from untrusted sources (for 
example, user-supplied input files). This vulnerability only affects the arrow R package, not other Apache Arrow 
implementations or bindings unless those bindings are specifically used via the R package (for example, an R application that embeds a Python interpreter and uses PyArrow to read files from untrusted sources is still vulnerable if the arrow R package is an affected version). It is recommended that users of the arrow R package upgrade to 17.0.0 or later. Similarly, it
 is recommended that downstream libraries upgrade their dependency 
requirements to arrow 17.0.0 or later. If using an affected
version of the package, untrusted data can read into a Table and its internal to_data_frame() method can be used as a workaround (e.g., read_parquet(..., as_data_frame = FALSE)$to_data_frame()).


This issue affects the Apache Arrow R package: from 4.0.0 through 16.1.0.


Users are recommended to upgrade to version 17.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 16:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11969 | Incorrect default permissions in Cradlepoint NetCloud Exchange</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11969</link><description>The NetCloud Exchange client for Windows, version 1.110.50, contains an insecure file and folder permissions vulnerability. A normal (non-admin) user could exploit the weakness in file and folder permissions to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and maintain persistence on the compromised machine. It has been identified that full control permissions exist on the ‘Everyone’ group (i.e. any user who has local access to the operating system regardless of their privileges).</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11962 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11962</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11963 | code-projects Responsive Hotel Site room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Responsive Hotel Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/room.php. The manipulation of the argument troom leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52922 | can: bcm: Fix UAF in bcm_proc_show()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52922</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: bcm: Fix UAF in bcm_proc_show()

BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in bcm_proc_show+0x969/0xa80
Read of size 8 at addr ffff888155846230 by task cat/7862

CPU: 1 PID: 7862 Comm: cat Not tainted 6.5.0-rc1-00153-gc8746099c197 #230
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0xd5/0x150
 print_report+0xc1/0x5e0
 kasan_report+0xba/0xf0
 bcm_proc_show+0x969/0xa80
 seq_read_iter+0x4f6/0x1260
 seq_read+0x165/0x210
 proc_reg_read+0x227/0x300
 vfs_read+0x1d5/0x8d0
 ksys_read+0x11e/0x240
 do_syscall_64+0x35/0xb0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Allocated by task 7846:
 kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
 kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x9e/0xa0
 bcm_sendmsg+0x264b/0x44e0
 sock_sendmsg+0xda/0x180
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x735/0x920
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x11d/0x1b0
 __sys_sendmsg+0xfa/0x1d0
 do_syscall_64+0x35/0xb0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0xcd

Freed by task 7846:
 kasan_save_stack+0x1e/0x40
 kasan_set_track+0x21/0x30
 kasan_save_free_info+0x27/0x40
 ____kasan_slab_free+0x161/0x1c0
 slab_free_freelist_hook+0x119/0x220
 __kmem_cache_free+0xb4/0x2e0
 rcu_core+0x809/0x1bd0

bcm_op is freed before procfs entry be removed in bcm_release(),
this lead to bcm_proc_show() may read the freed bcm_op.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:17:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11961 | Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms WmOmNoticeHController.java preHandle information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11961</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Guangzhou Huayi Intelligent Technology Jeewms 3.7. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function preHandle of the file src/main/java/com/zzjee/wm/controller/WmOmNoticeHController.java. The manipulation of the argument request leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11959 | D-Link DIR-605L formResetStatistic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formResetStatistic of the file /goform/formResetStatistic. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11960 | D-Link DIR-605L formSetPortTr buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetPortTr of the file /goform/formSetPortTr. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7747 | Wallet for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Incorrect Conversion between Numeric Types</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7747</link><description>The Wallet for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to incorrect conversion between numeric types in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.6. This is due to a numerical logic flaw when transferring funds to another user. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create funds during a transfer and distribute these funds to any number of other users or their own account, rendering products free. Attackers could also request to withdraw funds if the Wallet Withdrawal extension is used and the request is approved by an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53731 | WordPress Fintelligence Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53731</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fintelligence Fintelligence Calculator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fintelligence Calculator: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11402 | WordPress Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11402</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP-speedup Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Block Editor Bootstrap Blocks: from n/a through 6.6.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53732 | WordPress Footer Flyout Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53732</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP WOX Footer Flyout Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Footer Flyout Widget: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53733 | WordPress Fence URL plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53733</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rohit Harsh Fence URL allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fence URL: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53734 | WordPress Idealien Category Enhancements plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53734</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Idealien Studios Idealien Category Enhancements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Idealien Category Enhancements: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53736 | WordPress Custom Shortcode Sidebars plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53736</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jason Grim Custom Shortcode Sidebars allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Shortcode Sidebars: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:24:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53737 | WordPress WP Mailster plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.16.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Mailster allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Mailster: from n/a through 1.8.16.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52474 | WordPress Express Payments plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52474</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in LLC «TriIncom» Express Payments Module allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Express Payments Module: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:55:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11620 | WordPress Rank Math SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.231 - Arbitrary .htaccess Overwrite to Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11620</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Rank Math SEO allows Code Injection.This issue affects Rank Math SEO: from n/a through 1.0.231.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52475 | WordPress Wawp plugin &amp;lt; 3.0.18 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52475</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Automation Web Platform Wawp allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Wawp: from n/a before 3.0.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52481 | WordPress Jobify theme &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52481</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Astoundify Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52490 | WordPress Pathomation plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52490</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Pathomation allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Pathomation: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52495 | WordPress Distance Based Shipping Calculator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.21 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52495</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eniture Technology Distance Based Shipping Calculator allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Distance Based Shipping Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52496 | WordPress Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52496</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in AbsolutePlugins Absolute Addons For Elementor allows Local Code Inclusion.This issue affects Absolute Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52497 | WordPress Shopready plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52497</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in quomodosoft Shopready allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Shopready: from n/a through 3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52498 | WordPress SP Blog Designer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52498</link><description>Path Traversal: '.../...//' vulnerability in Softpulse Infotech SP Blog Designer allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects SP Blog Designer: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52499 | WordPress Pricing table addon for elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52499</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Kardi Pricing table addon for elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Pricing table addon for elementor: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52501 | WordPress Office Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52501</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in webbytemplate Office Locator.This issue affects Office Locator: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8308 | Siempelkamp: SQL injection due to improper handling of HTTP request input data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8308</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can insert a SQL injection in the web application due to improper handling of HTTP request input data which allows to exfiltrate all data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 10:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10670 | Primary Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10670</link><description>The Primary Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 via the [prim_elementor_template] shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10780 | Restaurant &amp;amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10780</link><description>The Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9 via the 'narestaurant_elementor_template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10798 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.7.1003 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10798</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1003 via the 'wpr-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created via Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11082 | Tumult Hype Animations &amp;lt;= 1.9.15 - Authenticated (Author+) Arbitrary File Upload via hypeanimations_panel Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11082</link><description>The Tumult Hype Animations plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the hypeanimations_panel() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.15. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11103 | Contest Gallery &amp;lt;= 24.0.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Password Reset to Privilege Escalation/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11103</link><description>The Contest Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 24.0.7. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11599 | Domain Restriction Bypass on Registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11599</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.0.x &lt;= 10.0.1, 10.1.x &lt;= 10.1.1, 9.11.x &lt;= 9.11.3, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.11 fail to properly validate email addresses which allows an unauthenticated user to bypass email domain restrictions via carefully crafted input on email registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22037 | Database password leaked by systemd uyuni-server-attestation service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22037</link><description>The uyuni-server-attestation systemd service needs a database_password environment variable. This file has 640 permission, and cannot be shown users, but the environment is still exposed by systemd to non-privileged users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8672 | Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp;amp; Block Control Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8672</link><description>The Widget Options – The #1 WordPress Widget &amp; Block Control Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.7 via the display logic functionality that extends several page builders. This is due to the plugin allowing users to supply input that will be passed through eval() without any filtering or capability checks. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server. Special note: We suggested the vendor implement an allowlist of functions and limit the ability to execute commands to just administrators, however, they did not take our advice. We are considering this patched, however, we believe it could still be further hardened and there may be residual risk with how the issue is currently patched.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22038 | DoS attacks, information leaks etc. with crafted Git repositories in obs-scm-bridge</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22038</link><description>Various problems in obs-scm-bridge allows attackers that create specially crafted git repositories to leak information of cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49502 | Reflected XSS in Setup Wizard, HTTP Proxy credentials pane in spacewalk-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49502</link><description>A Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in the Setup Wizard, HTTP Proxy credentials pane in spacewalk-web allows attackers to attack users by providing specially crafted URLs to click.
This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.2.7.8.1: before 5.0.15-150600.3.10.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: before 4.3.42-150400.3.52.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49503 | Reflected XSS in Setup Wizard, Organization Credentials in  spacewalk-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49503</link><description>A Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SUSE manager allows attackers to execute Javascript code in the organization credentials sub page.
This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.2.7.8.1: before 5.0.15-150600.3.10.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: before 4.3.42-150400.3.52.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52283 | Missing sanitation of inputs allowed arbitrary users to conduct a stored XSS attack that triggers for users that view a certain project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52283</link><description>Missing sanitation of inputs allowed arbitrary users to conduct a stored XSS attack that triggers for users that view a certain project</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11203 | EmbedPress – Embed PDF, 3D Flipbook, Social Feeds, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, YouTube Videos, Audios, Google Maps in Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;provider_name&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11203</link><description>The EmbedPress – Embed PDF, 3D Flipbook, Social Feeds, Google Docs, Vimeo, Wistia, YouTube Videos, Audios, Google Maps in Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘provider_name parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11333 | HLS Player &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11333</link><description>The HLS Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hls_player' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11366 | SEO Landing Page Generator &amp;lt;= 1.66.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11366</link><description>The SEO Landing Page Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.66.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11431 | Ragic Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11431</link><description>The Ragic Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ragic' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11458 | FAQ Builder AYS &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11458</link><description>The FAQ Builder AYS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ays_faq_tab' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11684 | Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11684</link><description>The Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11685 | Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;add_query_arg&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11685</link><description>The `Kudos Donations – Easy donations and payments with Mollie` plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of `add_query_arg` without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action, such as clicking on a specially crafted link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11761 | LegalWeb Cloud &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11761</link><description>The LegalWeb Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'legalweb-popup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11786 | Login with Vipps and MobilePay &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11786</link><description>The Login with Vipps and MobilePay plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'continue-with-vipps' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11788 | StreamWeasels YouTube Integration &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11788</link><description>The StreamWeasels YouTube Integration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sw-youtube-embed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8066 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8066</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing validation in the 'fsConnector' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, and granted permissions by an Administrator, to upload a new .htaccess file allowing them to subsequently upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9669 | File Manager Pro – Filester &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Local JavaScript File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9669</link><description>The File Manager Pro – Filester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local JavaScript File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the 'fm_locale' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36466 | Unauthenticated Zabbix frontend takeover when SSO is being used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36466</link><description>A bug in the code allows an attacker to sign a forged zbx_session cookie, which then allows them to sign in with admin permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:29:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11925 | WP JobSearch &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11925</link><description>The JobSearch WP Job Board plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.7. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a users identity when verifying an email address through the user_account_activation function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any user, including site administrators if the users email is known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10473 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.5.0 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10473</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Logo Settings when outputing them in pages where the Logo Slider shortcode is embed, which could allow users with a role as low as Author to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10493 | Element Pack Elementor Addons &amp;lt; 5.10.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10493</link><description>The Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid &amp; Carousel, Remote Arrows) WordPress plugin before 5.10.3 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10510 | adBuddy+ (AdBlocker Detection) by NetfunkDesign &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10510</link><description>The adBuddy+ (AdBlocker Detection) by NetfunkDesign WordPress plugin through 1.1.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10896 | Logo Slider &amp;lt; 4.5.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10896</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 4.5.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Logo and Slider settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11918 | Image Alt Text &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Image Alt Text Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11918</link><description>The Image Alt Text plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data| due to a missing capability check on the iat_add_alt_txt_action and iat_update_alt_txt_action AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the alt text on arbitrary images.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 06:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46939 | Game Extension Engine Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46939</link><description>The game extension engine of versions 1.2.7.0 and earlier exposes some components, and attackers can construct parameters to perform path traversal attacks, which can overwrite local specific files</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38309 | There are multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in V-SFT (v6.2.2.0 and earlier), TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier), and TELLUS L...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38309</link><description>There are multiple stack-based buffer overflow vulnerabilities in V-SFT (v6.2.2.0 and earlier), TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier), and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier).
If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38389 | There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38389</link><description>There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in TELLUS (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and TELLUS Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38658 | There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in V-Server (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and V-Server Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38658</link><description>There is an Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in V-Server (v4.0.19.0 and earlier) and V-Server Lite (v4.0.19.0 and earlier). If a user opens a specially crafted file, information may be disclosed and/or arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53008 | Inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') issue exists in HAProxy. If this vulnerability is exploited...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53008</link><description>Inconsistent interpretation of HTTP requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling') issue exists in HAProxy. If this vulnerability is exploited,  a remote attacker may access a path that is restricted by ACL (Access Control List) set on the product. As a result, the attacker may obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9377 | In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9377</link><description>In BnAudioPolicyService::onTransact of IAudioPolicyService.cpp, there is a possible information disclosure due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:43:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9374 | In installPackageLI of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9374</link><description>In installPackageLI of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:54:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11787 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11787</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V10 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24413.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11789 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11789</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V10 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24448.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11790 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11790</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V10 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24449.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11791 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8C File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11791</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8C File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8C files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24450.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11792 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11792</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24502.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11793 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V9C File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11793</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V9C File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V9C files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24503.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11794 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11794</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V10 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V10 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24504.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11795 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11795</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24505.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11796 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V9C File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11796</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V9C File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V9C files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24506.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11797 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11797</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24662.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11798 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT X1 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11798</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT X1 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X1 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24663.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11799 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11799</link><description>Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Tellus Lite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files in the V-Simulator 5 component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24664.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11800 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11800</link><description>Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Tellus Lite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files in the V-Simulator 5 component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24768.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11801 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11801</link><description>Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Tellus Lite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files in the V-Simulator 5 component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24769.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11802 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11802</link><description>Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Tellus Lite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files in the V-Simulator 5 component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24770.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11803 | Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11803</link><description>Fuji Electric Tellus Lite V-Simulator 5 V8 File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Tellus Lite. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of V8 files in the V-Simulator 5 component. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24771.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11933 | Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT X1 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11933</link><description>Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT X1 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Fuji Electric Monitouch V-SFT. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of X1 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24548.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:48:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9352 | In ihevcd_allocate_dynamic_bufs of ihevcd_api.c there is a possible resource exhaustion due to integer overflow. This could lead to remote d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9352</link><description>In ihevcd_allocate_dynamic_bufs of ihevcd_api.c there is a possible resource exhaustion due to integer overflow. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 22:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9353 | In ihevcd_parse_slice_data of ihevcd_parse_slice.c there is a possible heap buffer out of bound read due to a missing bounds check. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9353</link><description>In ihevcd_parse_slice_data of ihevcd_parse_slice.c there is a possible heap buffer out of bound read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 22:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9354 | In VideoFrameScheduler.cpp of VideoFrameScheduler::PLL::fit, there is a possible remote denial of service due to divide by 0. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9354</link><description>In VideoFrameScheduler.cpp of VideoFrameScheduler::PLL::fit, there is a possible remote denial of service due to divide by 0. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 22:44:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9351 | In ih264e_fmt_conv_420p_to_420sp of ih264e_fmt_conv.c there is a possible out of bound read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9351</link><description>In ih264e_fmt_conv_420p_to_420sp of ih264e_fmt_conv.c there is a possible out of bound read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9350 | In ih264d_assign_pic_num of ih264d_utils.c there is a possible out of bound read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to a denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9350</link><description>In ih264d_assign_pic_num of ih264d_utils.c there is a possible out of bound read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to a denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:58:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-9349 | In mv_err_cost of mcomp.c there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to denial of service with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-9349</link><description>In mv_err_cost of mcomp.c there is a possible out of bounds read due to missing bounds check. This could lead to denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13323 | In String16 of String16.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13323</link><description>In String16 of String16.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in an unprivileged process with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13320 | In impeg2d_bit_stream_flush() of libmpeg2dec there is a possible OOB read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to Remote DoS with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13320</link><description>In impeg2d_bit_stream_flush() of libmpeg2dec there is a possible OOB read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to Remote DoS with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13321 | In SensorService::isDataInjectionEnabled of frameworks/native/services/sensorservice/SensorService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13321</link><description>In SensorService::isDataInjectionEnabled of frameworks/native/services/sensorservice/SensorService.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53260 | Course Roster vulnerable to CSV Injection in Autolab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53260</link><description>Autolab is a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments. A user can modify their first and or last name to include a valid excel / spreadsheet formula. When an instructor downloads their course's roster and opens, this name will then be evaluated as a formula. This could lead to leakage of information of students in the course roster by sending the data to a remote endpoint. This issue has been patched in the source code repository and the fix is expected to be released in the next version. Users are advised to manually patch their systems or to wait for the next release. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53858 | Recursive repository cloning can leak authentication tokens to non-GitHub submodule hosts in the gh cli</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53858</link><description>The gh cli is GitHub’s official command line tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in the GitHub CLI that could leak authentication tokens when cloning repositories containing `git` submodules hosted outside of GitHub.com and ghe.com. This vulnerability stems from several `gh` commands used to clone a repository with submodules from a non-GitHub host including `gh repo clone`, `gh repo fork`, and `gh pr checkout`. These GitHub CLI commands invoke git with instructions to retrieve authentication tokens using the `credential.helper` configuration variable for any host encountered. Prior to version `2.63.0`, hosts other than GitHub.com and ghe.com are treated as GitHub Enterprise Server hosts and have tokens sourced from the following environment variables before falling back to host-specific tokens stored within system-specific secured storage: 1. `GITHUB_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN`, 2. `GH_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN` and 3. `GITHUB_TOKEN` when the `CODESPACES` environment variable is set. The result being `git` sending authentication tokens when cloning submodules. In version `2.63.0`, these GitHub CLI commands will limit the hosts for which `gh` acts as a credential helper to source authentication tokens. Additionally, `GITHUB_TOKEN` will only be used for GitHub.com and ghe.com. Users are advised to upgrade. Additionally users are advised to revoke authentication tokens used with the GitHub CLI and to review their personal security log and any relevant audit logs for actions associated with their account or enterprise</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53859 | go-gh `auth.TokenForHost` violates GitHub host security boundary within a codespace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53859</link><description>go-gh is a Go module for interacting with the `gh` utility and the GitHub API from the command line. A security vulnerability has been identified in `go-gh` that could leak authentication tokens intended for GitHub hosts to non-GitHub hosts when within a codespace. `go-gh` sources authentication tokens from different environment variables depending on the host involved: 1. `GITHUB_TOKEN`, `GH_TOKEN` for GitHub.com and ghe.com and 2. `GITHUB_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN`, `GH_ENTERPRISE_TOKEN` for GitHub Enterprise Server. Prior to version `2.11.1`, `auth.TokenForHost` could source a token from the `GITHUB_TOKEN` environment variable for a host other than GitHub.com or ghe.com when within a codespace. In version `2.11.1`, `auth.TokenForHost` will only source a token from the `GITHUB_TOKEN` environment variable for GitHub.com or ghe.com hosts. Successful exploitation could send authentication token to an unintended host. This issue has been addressed in version 2.11.1 and all users are advised to upgrade. Users are also advised to regenerate authentication tokens and to review their personal security log and any relevant audit logs for actions associated with their account or enterprise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53860 | Potential Abuse for Sending Arbitrary Emails in sp-php-email-handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53860</link><description>sp-php-email-handler is a PHP package for handling contact form submissions. Messages sent using this script are vulnerable to abuse, as the script allows anybody to specify arbitrary email recipients and include user-provided content in confirmation emails. This could enable malicious actors to use your server to send spam, phishing emails, or other malicious content, potentially damaging your domain's reputation and leading to blacklisting by email providers. Patched in version 1.0.0 by removing user-provided content from confirmation emails. All pre-release versions (alpha and beta) are vulnerable to this issue and should not be used. There are no workarounds for this issue. Users must upgrade to version 1.0.0 to mitigate the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13319 | In pvmp3_get_main_data_size of pvmp3_get_main_data_size.cpp, there is a possible buffer overread due to a missing bounds check. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13319</link><description>In pvmp3_get_main_data_size of pvmp3_get_main_data_size.cpp, there is a possible buffer overread due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure of global static variables with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 20:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-13316 | In checkPermissions of RecognitionService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-13316</link><description>In checkPermissions of RecognitionService.java, there is a possible permissions bypass due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29001 | Uncontrolled recursion due to insufficient validation of the IPv6 source routing header in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29001</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. The Contiki-NG operating system processes source routing headers (SRH) in its two alternative RPL protocol implementations. The IPv6 implementation uses the results of this processing to determine whether an incoming packet should be forwarded to another host. Because of missing validation of the resulting next-hop address, an uncontrolled recursion may occur in the tcpip_ipv6_output function in the os/net/ipv6/tcpip.c module when receiving a packet with a next-hop address that is a local address. Attackers that have the possibility to send IPv6 packets to the Contiki-NG host can therefore trigger deeply nested recursive calls, which can cause a stack overflow. The vulnerability has not been patched in the current release of Contiki-NG, but is expected to be patched in the next release. The problem can be fixed by applying the patch in Contiki-NG pull request #2264. Users are advised to either apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41125 | Out-of-bounds read in SNMP when decoding a string in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41125</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read of 1 byte can be triggered when sending a packet to a device running the Contiki-NG operating system with SNMP enabled. The SNMP module is disabled in the default Contiki-NG configuration. The vulnerability exists in the os/net/app-layer/snmp/snmp-ber.c module, where the function snmp_ber_decode_string_len_buffer decodes the string length from a received SNMP packet. In one place, one byte is read from the buffer, without checking that the buffer has another byte available, leading to a possible out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG pull request #2936. It will be included in the next release of Contiki-NG. Users are advised to apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. A workaround is to disable the SNMP module in the Contiki-NG build configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41126 | Out-of-bounds read when decoding SNMP messages in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41126</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read of 1 byte can be triggered when sending a packet to a device running the Contiki-NG operating system with SNMP enabled. The SNMP module is disabled in the default Contiki-NG configuration. The vulnerability exists in the os/net/app-layer/snmp/snmp-message.c module, where the snmp_message_decode function fails to check the boundary of the message buffer when reading a byte from it immediately after decoding an object identifier (OID). The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG pull request 2937. It will be included in the next release of Contiki-NG. Users are advised to either apply the patch manually or to wait for the next release. A workaround is to disable the SNMP module in the Contiki-NG build configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47181 | Unaligned memory access in RPL option processing in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47181</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for IoT devices. An unaligned memory access can be triggered in the two RPL implementations of the Contiki-NG operating system. The problem can occur when either one of these RPL implementations is enabled and connected to an RPL instance. If an IPv6 packet containing an odd number of padded bytes before the RPL option, it can cause the rpl_ext_header_hbh_update function to read a 16-bit integer from an odd address. The impact of this unaligned read is architecture-dependent, but can potentially cause the system to crash. The problem has not been patched as of release 4.9, but will be included in the next release. One can apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2962 to patch the system or wait for the next release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53264 | Open Redirect Vulnerability in Loading Page in bunkerweb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53264</link><description>bunkerweb is an Open-source and next-generation Web Application Firewall (WAF). A open redirect vulnerability exists in the loading endpoint, allowing attackers to redirect authenticated users to arbitrary external URLs via the "next" parameter. The loading endpoint accepts and uses an unvalidated "next" parameter for redirects. Ex. visiting: `/loading?next=https://google.com` while authenticated will cause the page will redirect to google.com. This vulnerability could be used in phishing attacks by redirecting users from a legitimate application URL to malicious sites. This issue has been addressed in version 1.5.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53855 | User can view tickets from organizations they&amp;#x27;re not apart of in centurion_erp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53855</link><description>Centurion ERP (Enterprise Rescource Planning) is a simple application developed to provide open source IT management with a large emphasis on the IT Service Management (ITSM) modules. A user who is authenticated and has view permissions for a ticket, can view the tickets of another organization they are not apart of. Users with following permissions are applicable: 1. `view_ticket_change` permission can view change tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 2. `view_ticket_incident` permission can view incident tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 3. `view_ticket_request` permission can view request tickets from organizations they are not apart of. 4. `view_ticket_problem` permission can view problem tickets from organizations they are not apart of. The access to view the tickets from different organizations is only applicable when browsing the API endpoints for the tickets in question. The Centurion UI is not affected. Project Tasks, although a "ticket type" are also **Not** affected. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.3.1 and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may remove the ticket view permissions from users which would alleviate this vulnerability, if this is deemed not-viable, Upgrading is recommended.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7025 | Integer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7025</link><description>Integer overflow in Layout in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9369 | Insufficient data validation in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer proc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9369</link><description>Insufficient data validation in Mojo in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.89 allowed a remote attacker who had compromised the renderer process to perform an out of bounds memory write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:15:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21703 | This Medium severity Security Misconfiguration vulnerability was introduced in version 8.8.1 of Confluence Data Center and Server for Window...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21703</link><description>This Medium severity Security Misconfiguration vulnerability was introduced in version 8.8.1 of Confluence Data Center and Server for Windows installations.



This Security Misconfiguration vulnerability, with a CVSS Score of 6.4 allows an authenticated attacker of the Windows host to read sensitive information about the Confluence Data Center configuration which has high impact to confidentiality, high impact to integrity,  high impact to availability, and no user interaction.



Atlassian recommends that Confluence Data Center and Server customers upgrade to the latest version, if you are unable to do so, upgrade your instance to one of the specified supported fixed versions:

* Confluence Data Center and Server 7.19: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 7.19.18 
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.5: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.5.5
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.7: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.7.2
* Confluence Data Center and Server 8.8: Upgrade to a release greater than or equal to 8.8.0



See the release notes (https://confluence.atlassian.com/conf88/confluence-release-notes-1354501008.html ). You can download the latest version of Confluence Data Center and Server from the download center (https://www.atlassian.com/software/confluence/download-archives ). 

This vulnerability was reported via our Atlassian Bug Bounty Program by Chris Elliot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54003 | Jenkins Simple Queue Plugin 1.4.4 and earlier does not escape the view name, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54003</link><description>Jenkins Simple Queue Plugin 1.4.4 and earlier does not escape the view name, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exploitable by attackers with View/Create permission.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54004 | Jenkins Filesystem List Parameter Plugin 0.0.14 and earlier does not restrict the path used for the File system objects list Parameter, allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54004</link><description>Jenkins Filesystem List Parameter Plugin 0.0.14 and earlier does not restrict the path used for the File system objects list Parameter, allowing attackers with Item/Configure permission to enumerate file names on the Jenkins controller file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51228 | An issue in TOTOLINK-CX-A3002RU V1.0.4-B20171106.1512 and TOTOLINK-CX-N150RT V2.1.6-B20171121.1002 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.6-B20170724.1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51228</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK-CX-A3002RU V1.0.4-B20171106.1512 and TOTOLINK-CX-N150RT V2.1.6-B20171121.1002 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.6-B20170724.1420 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.8-B20171113.1408 and TOTOLINK-CX-N300RT V2.1.8-B20191010.1107 and TOTOLINK-CX-N302RE V2.0.2-B20170511.1523 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /boafrm/formSysCmd component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11860 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System POST Request ajax.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11860</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /rental/ajax.php?action=delete_tenant of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31976 | EnGenius EWS356-FIR 1.1.30 and earlier devices allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via the Controller connectivity para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31976</link><description>EnGenius EWS356-FIR 1.1.30 and earlier devices allow a remote attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands via the Controller connectivity parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37816 | Quectel EC25-EUX EC25EUXGAR08A05M1G was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37816</link><description>Quectel EC25-EUX EC25EUXGAR08A05M1G was discovered to contain a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53920 | In elisp-mode.el in GNU Emacs through 30.0.92, a user who chooses to invoke elisp-completion-at-point (for code completion) on untrusted Ema...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53920</link><description>In elisp-mode.el in GNU Emacs through 30.0.92, a user who chooses to invoke elisp-completion-at-point (for code completion) on untrusted Emacs Lisp source code can trigger unsafe Lisp macro expansion that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. (This unsafe expansion also occurs if a user chooses to enable on-the-fly diagnosis that byte compiles untrusted Emacs Lisp source code.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11862 | Non constant time cryptographic operation in Devolutions.XTS.NET 2024.11.19 and earlier allows an attacker to render half of the encryption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11862</link><description>Non constant time cryptographic operation in Devolutions.XTS.NET 2024.11.19 and earlier allows an attacker to render half of the encryption key obsolete via a timing attacks</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46054 | OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The /upload route is accessible without authentication, allowing any user to up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46054</link><description>OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The /upload route is accessible without authentication, allowing any user to upload files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46055 | OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in review names.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46055</link><description>OpenVidReview 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in review names.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52951 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the Access Request History in Omada Identity before version 15 update 1 allows an authenticated attacker to e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52951</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the Access Request History in Omada Identity before version 15 update 1 allows an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code in the browser of a victim via a specially crafted link or by viewing a manipulated Access Request History</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36464 | Media Types: Office365, SMTP passwords are unencrypted and visible in plaintext when exported</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36464</link><description>When exporting media types, the password is exported in the YAML in plain text. This appears to be a best practices type issue and may have no actual impact. The user would need to have permissions to access the media types and therefore would be expected to have access to these passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53635 | A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/patient-search-report.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Manage...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53635</link><description>A Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/patient-search-report.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the searchdata POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53603 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/password-recovery.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53603</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/password-recovery.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the contactno POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:42:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53604 | A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/check_availability.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53604</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability was found in /covid-tms/check_availability.php in PHPGurukul COVID 19 Testing Management System v1.0, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the mobnumber POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 13:42:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36468 | Stack buffer overflow in zbx_snmp_cache_handle_engineid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36468</link><description>The reported vulnerability is a stack buffer overflow in the zbx_snmp_cache_handle_engineid function within the Zabbix server/proxy code. This issue occurs when copying data from session-&gt;securityEngineID to local_record.engineid without proper bounds checking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42326 | Use after free vulnerability in browser.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42326</link><description>There was discovered a use after free bug in browser.c in the es_browser_get_variant function</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42327 | SQL injection in user.get API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42327</link><description>A non-admin user account on the Zabbix frontend with the default User role, or with any other role that gives API access can exploit this vulnerability. An SQLi exists in the CUser class in the addRelatedObjects function, this function is being called from the CUser.get function which is available for every user who has API access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42328 | JS - Crash on empty HTTP server response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42328</link><description>When the webdriver for the Browser object downloads data from a HTTP server, the data pointer is set to NULL and is allocated only in curl_write_cb when receiving data. If the server's response is an empty document, then wd-&gt;data in the code below will remain NULL and an attempt to read from it will result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42329 | JS - Crash on unexpected HTTP server response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42329</link><description>The webdriver for the Browser object expects an error object to be initialized when the webdriver_session_query function fails. But this function can fail for various reasons without an error description and then the wd-&gt;error will be NULL and trying to read from it will result in a crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42330 | JS - Internal strings in HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42330</link><description>The HttpRequest object allows to get the HTTP headers from the server's response after sending the request. The problem is that the returned strings are created directly from the data returned by the server and are not correctly encoded for JavaScript. This allows to create internal strings that can be used to access hidden properties of objects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42331 | Use after free in browser_push_error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42331</link><description>In the src/libs/zbxembed/browser.c file, the es_browser_ctor method retrieves a heap pointer from the Duktape JavaScript engine. This heap pointer is subsequently utilized by the browser_push_error method in the src/libs/zbxembed/browser_error.c file. A use-after-free bug can occur at this stage if the wd-&gt;browser heap pointer is freed by garbage collection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42332 | New line injection in Zabbix SNMP traps</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42332</link><description>The researcher is showing that due to the way the SNMP trap log is parsed, an attacker can craft an SNMP trap with additional lines of information and have forged data show in the Zabbix UI. This attack requires SNMP auth to be off and/or the attacker to know the community/auth details. The attack requires an SNMP item to be configured as text on the target host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42333 | Heap buffer over-read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42333</link><description>The researcher is showing that it is possible to leak a small amount of Zabbix Server memory using an out of bounds read in src/libs/zbxmedia/email.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 12:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11009 | Internal Linking for SEO traffic &amp;amp; Ranking – Auto internal links (100% automatic) &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via post_id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11009</link><description>The Internal Linking for SEO traffic &amp; Ranking – Auto internal links (100% automatic) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘post_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10521 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via process_bulk_action Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10521</link><description>The WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_bulk_action function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete forms via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11025 | SMA: SQL injection in Sunny Central UP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11025</link><description>An authenticated attacker with low privileges may use a SQL Injection vulnerability in the affected products administration panel to gain read and write access to a specific log file of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 10:37:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52323 | Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52323</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Analytics Plus versions below 6100 are vulnerable to authenticated sensitive data exposure which allows the users to retrieve sensitive tokens associated to the org-admin account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11667 | A directory traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX seri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11667</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of Zyxel ATP series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX series firmware versions V5.00 through V5.38, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions V5.10 through V5.38, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions V5.10 through V5.38 could allow an attacker to download or upload files via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10175 | Pricing Tables For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wdo_pricing_tables Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10175</link><description>The Pricing Tables For WPBakery Page Builder (formerly Visual Composer) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wdo_pricing_tables shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10580 | Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups &amp;lt;= 7.8.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthorized Form Submission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10580</link><description>The Hustle – Email Marketing, Lead Generation, Optins, Popups plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized form submissions due to a missing capability check on the submit_form() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.8.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to submit unpublished forms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10895 | Counter Up – Animated Number Counter &amp;amp; Milestone Showcase &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10895</link><description>The Counter Up – Animated Number Counter &amp; Milestone Showcase plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'lgx-counter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36467 | Authentication privilege escalation via user groups due to missing authorization checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36467</link><description>An authenticated user with API access (e.g.: user with default User role), more specifically a user with access to the user.update API endpoint is enough to be able to add themselves to any group (e.g.: Zabbix Administrators), except to groups that are disabled or having restricted GUI access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11083 | ProfilePress &amp;lt;= 4.15.18 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11083</link><description>The ProfilePress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.18 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11219 | Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp;amp; FSE &amp;lt;= 3.0.6 - Unauthetnicated Path Traversal to Arbitrary Image View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11219</link><description>The Otter Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks, Page Builder for Gutenberg Editor &amp; FSE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.6 via the get_image function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view arbitrary images on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52958 | iota C.ai Conversational Platform - Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52958</link><description>A improper verification of cryptographic signature vulnerability in plugin management in iota C.ai Conversational Platform from 1.0.0 through 2.1.3 allows remote authenticated users to load a malicious DLL via upload plugin function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52959 | iota C.ai Conversational Platform - Improper Control of Generation of Code (&amp;#x27;Code Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52959</link><description>A Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in plugin management in iota C.ai Conversational Platform from 1.0.0 through 2.1.3 allows remote authenticated users to perform arbitrary system commands via a DLL file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 05:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5921 | GlobalProtect App: Insufficient Certificate Validation Leads to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5921</link><description>An insufficient certification validation issue in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app enables attackers to connect the GlobalProtect app to arbitrary servers. This can enable a local non-administrative operating system user or an attacker on the same subnet to install malicious root certificates on the endpoint and subsequently install malicious software signed by the malicious root certificates on that endpoint.

GlobalProtect App for Android is under evaluation. Please subscribe to  our RSS feed https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/rss.xml  to be alerted to new updates to this and other advisories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 03:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11820 | code-projects Crud Operation System add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11820</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Crud Operation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add.php. The manipulation of the argument saddress leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53676 | A directory traversal vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support may allow remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53676</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise Insight Remote Support may allow remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>