<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-42483 | ESP-NOW Replay Attacks Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42483</link><description>ESP-NOW Component provides a connectionless Wi-Fi communication protocol. An replay attacks vulnerability was discovered in the implementation of the ESP-NOW because the caches is not differentiated by message types, it is a single, shared resource for all kinds of messages, whether they are broadcast or unicast, and regardless of whether they are ciphertext or plaintext. This can result an attacker to clear the cache of its legitimate entries, there by creating an opportunity to re-inject previously captured packets. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42484 | ESP-NOW OOB Vulnerability In Group Type Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42484</link><description>ESP-NOW Component provides a connectionless Wi-Fi communication protocol. An Out-of-Bound (OOB) vulnerability was discovered in the implementation of the ESP-NOW group type message because there is no check for the addrs_num field of the group type message. This can result in memory corruption related attacks. Normally there are two fields in the group information that need to be checked, i.e., the addrs_num field and the addrs_list fileld. Since we only checked the addrs_list field, an attacker can send a group type message with an invalid addrs_num field, which will cause the message handled by the firmware to be much larger than the current buffer, thus causing a memory corruption issue that goes beyond the payload length.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45823 | FactoryTalk® Batch View™ Authentication Bypass Vulnerability via shared secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45823</link><description>CVE-2024-45823 IMPACT



An
authentication bypass vulnerability exists in the affected product. The
vulnerability exists due to shared secrets across accounts and could allow a threat
actor to impersonate a user if the threat actor is able to enumerate additional
information required during authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6510 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability in AVG Internet Security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6510</link><description>Local Privilege Escalation in AVG Internet Security v24 on Windows allows a local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM via COM-Hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45824 | FactoryTalk® View Site Edition Remote Code Execution Vulnerability via Lack of Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45824</link><description>CVE-2024-45824 IMPACT



A remote
code vulnerability exists in the affected products. The vulnerability occurs
when chained with Path Traversal, Command Injection, and XSS Vulnerabilities
and allows for full unauthenticated remote code execution. The link in the
mitigations section below contains patches to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28990 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Hardcoded Credentials Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28990</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to contain a hard-coded credential authentication bypass vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability would allow access to the RabbitMQ management console.

We thank Trend Micro Zero Day Initiative (ZDI) for its ongoing partnership in coordinating with SolarWinds on responsible disclosure of this and other potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28991 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28991</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a remote code execution vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability would allow an authenticated user to abuse the service, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40457 | No-IP Dynamic Update Client (DUC) v3.x uses cleartext credentials that may occur on a command line or in a file. NOTE: the vendor's position...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40457</link><description>No-IP Dynamic Update Client (DUC) v3.x uses cleartext credentials that may occur on a command line or in a file. NOTE: the vendor's position is that cleartext in /etc/default/noip-duc is recommended and is the intentional behavior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3305 | Information Disclosure in Utarit Information&amp;#x27;s SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3305</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Utarit Information SoliClub allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects SoliClub: before 4.4.0 for iOS, before 5.2.1 for Android.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3306 | IDOR in Utarit Information&amp;#x27;s SoliClub</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3306</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Utarit Information SoliClub allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SoliClub: before 4.4.0 for iOS, before 5.2.1 for Android.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45850 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45850</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for site column creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45851 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45851</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for list item creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45852 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.3.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded model to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45852</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.3.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded model to run arbitrary code on the server when interacted with.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45853 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45853</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when used for a prediction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45854 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.3.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45854</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.3.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when a ‘describe’ query is run on it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45855 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhous...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45855</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 23.10.2.0 and newer of the MindsDB platform, enabling a maliciously uploaded ‘inhouse’ model to run arbitrary code on the server when using ‘finetune’ on it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45856 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in all versions of the MindsDB platform, enabling the execution of a JavaScript payload wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45856</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in all versions of the MindsDB platform, enabling the execution of a JavaScript payload whenever a user enumerates an ML Engine, database, project, or dataset containing arbitrary JavaScript code within the web UI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:28:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27320 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its classifi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27320</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its classification tasks handle provided CSV files. If a victim user creates a classification task using a maliciously crafted CSV file containing Python code, the code will be passed to an eval function which executes it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27321 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its multilab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27321</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 0.0.8 and newer of the Refuel Autolabel library because of the way its multilabel classification tasks handle provided CSV files. If a user creates a multilabel classification task using a maliciously crafted CSV file containing Python code, the code will be passed to an eval function which executes it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45846 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.3.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Weaviate integration...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45846</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.3.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Weaviate integration is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘SELECT WHERE’ clause containing Python code is run against a database created with the Weaviate engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45847 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.11.4.2 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when one of several integrati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45847</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.11.4.2 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when one of several integrations is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘UPDATE’ query containing Python code is run against a database created with the specified integration engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45848 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.12.4.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the ChromaDB integration...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45848</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.12.4.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the ChromaDB integration is installed on the server. If a specially crafted ‘INSERT’ query containing Python code is run against a database created with the ChromaDB engine, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45849 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45849</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in versions 23.10.5.0 up to 24.7.4.1 of the MindsDB platform, when the Microsoft SharePoint integration is installed on the server. For databases created with the SharePoint engine, an ‘INSERT’ query can be used for list creation. If such a query is specially crafted to contain Python code and is run against the database, the code will be passed to an eval function and executed on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45857 | Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 2.4.0 or newer of the Cleanlab project, enabling a maliciously crafted datalab.pkl f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45857</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data can occur in versions 2.4.0 or newer of the Cleanlab project, enabling a maliciously crafted datalab.pkl file to run arbitrary code on an end user’s system when the data directory is loaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22503 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22503</link><description>Possible 
Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.3.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22518 | Sensitive Information logging in NetIQ Identity Manager Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22518</link><description>A vulnerability identified in OpenText™ 
Identity Manager AzureAD Driver that allows logging of sensitive information into log file. This impacts all versions before 5.1.4.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22532 | Possible NLDAP Denial of Service attack Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22532</link><description>Possible NLDAP Denial of Service attack Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ 
eDirectory before 9.2.4.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22533 | Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22533</link><description>Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.4.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38131 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38131</link><description>Possible Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory 9.2.5.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38132 | Possible External service interaction Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38132</link><description>Possible 
External Service Interaction attack

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory. This impact all version before 9.2.6.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-38133 | Possible Improper authentication Vulnerability in OpenText eDirectory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-38133</link><description>Possible 
External Service Interaction attack

in eDirectory has been discovered in
OpenText™ eDirectory. This impact all version before 9.2.6.0000.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-26322 | Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability in Identity Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-26322</link><description>Possible Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File Vulnerability

in Identity Manager has been discovered in
OpenText™ 
Identity Manager REST Driver. This impact version before 1.1.2.0200.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8749 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Idoit pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8749</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in idoit pro version 28. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a specially crafted query to the ID parameter in /var/www/html/src/classes/modules/api/model/cmdb/isys_api_model_cmdb_objects_by_relation.class.php and retrieve all the information stored in the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8750 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Idoit pro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8750</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in idoit pro version 28. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve session details of an authenticated user due to lack of proper sanitization of the following parameters (id,lang,mNavID,name,pID,treeNode,type,view).</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2010 | Reflected XSS in TE Informatics&amp;#x27; V5 Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2010</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in TE Informatics V5 allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects V5: before 6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8522 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;c_only_fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8522</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'c_only_fields' parameter of the /wp-json/learnpress/v1/courses REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8529 | LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via &amp;#x27;c_fields&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8529</link><description>The LearnPress – WordPress LMS Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'c_fields' parameter of the /wp-json/lp/v1/courses/archive-course REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8622 | amCharts: Charts and Maps &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8622</link><description>The amCharts: Charts and Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'amcharts_javascript' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to the ability to supply arbitrary JavaScript a lack of nonce validation on the preview functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3163 | Easy Property Listings &amp;lt; 3.5.4 - Arbitrary Contact Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3163</link><description>The Easy Property Listings WordPress plugin before 3.5.4 does not have CSRF check when deleting contacts in bulk, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin delete them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5799 | CM Pop-Up Banners for WordPress &amp;lt; 1.7.3 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5799</link><description>The CM Pop-Up Banners for WordPress plugin before 1.7.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its popup fields, which could allow high privilege users such as Contributors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6017 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6017</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6018 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6018</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6019 | Music Request Manager &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6019</link><description>The Music Request Manager WordPress plugin through 1.3 does not sanitise and escape incoming music requests, which could allow unauthenticated users to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks against administrators</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6887 | Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress &amp;lt; 1.12.16 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6887</link><description>The Giveaways and Contests by RafflePress  WordPress plugin before 1.12.16 does not sanitise and escape some of its Giveaways settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7766 | Adicon Server &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7766</link><description>The Adicon Server WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admins to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7816 | Gixaw Chat &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7816</link><description>The Gixaw Chat WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7817 | Misiek Photo Album &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Album Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7817</link><description>The Misiek Photo Album WordPress plugin through 1.4.3 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete arbitrary albums via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7818 | Misiek Photo Album &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7818</link><description>The Misiek Photo Album WordPress plugin through 1.4.3 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7820 | ILC Thickbox &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Settings update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7820</link><description>The ILC Thickbox WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7822 | Quick Code &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7822</link><description>The Quick Code WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7859 | Visual Sound &amp;lt;= 1.03 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7859</link><description>The Visual Sound WordPress plugin through 1.03 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7860 | Simple Headline Rotator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7860</link><description>The Simple Headline Rotator WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7861 | Misiek Paypal &amp;lt;= 1.1.20090324 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7861</link><description>The Misiek Paypal WordPress plugin through 1.1.20090324 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7862 | Blog Introduction &amp;lt;= 0.3.0 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7862</link><description>The blogintroduction-wordpress-plugin WordPress plugin through 0.3.0 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8054 | MM-Breaking News &amp;lt;= 0.7.9 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8054</link><description>The MM-Breaking News WordPress plugin through 0.7.9 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8056 | MM-Breaking News &amp;lt;= 0.7.9 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8056</link><description>The MM-Breaking News WordPress plugin through 0.7.9 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45624 | Exposure of sensitive information due to incompatible policies issue exists in Pgpool-II. If a database user accesses a query cache, table d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45624</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information due to incompatible policies issue exists in Pgpool-II. If a database user accesses a query cache, table data unauthorized for the user may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 04:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8711 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System includes exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8711</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /includes/. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38222 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38222</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8710 | code-projects Inventory Management Products Table Page viewProduct.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8710</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Inventory Management 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /model/viewProduct.php of the component Products Table Page. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8709 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php save_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8709</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is the function delete_user/save_user of the file /admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8708 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System categories.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8708</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file categories.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 02:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29847 | Deserialization of untrusted data in the agent portal of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29847</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in the agent portal of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32840 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32840</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32842 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32842</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32843 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32843</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32845 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32845</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32846 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32846</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32848 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32848</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34779 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34779</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34783 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34783</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34785 | An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34785</link><description>An unspecified SQL injection in Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37397 | An External XML Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the provisioning web service of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37397</link><description>An External XML Entity (XXE) vulnerability in the provisioning web service of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak API secrets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8707 | 云课网络科技有限公司 Yunke Online School System Appadmin.php downfile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 云课网络科技有限公司 Yunke Online School System up to 3.0.6. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function downfile of the file application/admin/controller/Appadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument url leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 01:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8706 | JFinalCMS com.cms.util.TemplateUtils update path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JFinalCMS up to 20240903. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function update of the file /admin/template/update of the component com.cms.util.TemplateUtils. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 23:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28981 | Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp;amp; Analytics - Insufficiently Protected Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28981</link><description>Hitachi Vantara Pentaho Data Integration &amp; Analytics versions before 10.1.0.0 and 9.3.0.8, including 8.3.x, discloses database passwords when searching metadata injectable fields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 23:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7890 | Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7890</link><description>Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges in Citrix Workspace app for Windows</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8705 | Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System UCCGSrv.asmx GetDataKindByType sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shandong Star Measurement and Control Equipment Heating Network Wireless Monitoring System 5.6.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function GetDataKindByType of the file /DataSrvs/UCCGSrv.asmx. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7889 | Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7889</link><description>Local privilege escalation allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM privileges in Citrix Workspace app for Windows</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:22:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8694 | JFinalCMS com.cms.controller.admin.TemplateController update path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8694</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in JFinalCMS up to 20240903. This affects the function update of the file /admin/template/update of the component com.cms.controller.admin.TemplateController. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 21:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8693 | Kaon CG3000 dhcpcd Command cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8693</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Kaon CG3000 1.01.43. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component dhcpcd Command Handler. The manipulation of the argument -h with the input  leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 19:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44541 | evilnapsis Inventio Lite Versions v4 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter in "/?action=processlogin."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44541</link><description>evilnapsis Inventio Lite Versions v4 and before is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the "username" parameter in "/?action=processlogin."</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 19:13:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8692 | TDuckCloud TDuckPro password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8692</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TDuckCloud TDuckPro up to 6.3. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 18:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42760 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /api/mob/instrucao/cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42760</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the /api/mob/instrucao/conta/destinatarios component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 18:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44574 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_conf function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44574</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_conf function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44575 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 does not set the Secure attribute for sensitive cookies in HTTPS sessions, which could cause the user agent to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44575</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 does not set the Secure attribute for sensitive cookies in HTTPS sessions, which could cause the user agent to send those cookies in cleartext over an HTTP session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44577 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the time_date function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44577</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the time_date function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44570 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the getParams function in phpinf.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44570</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a code injection vulnerability via the getParams function in phpinf.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44571 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain incorrect access control in the mService function at phpinf.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44571</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain incorrect access control in the mService function at phpinf.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44572 | RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_mgmt function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44572</link><description>RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sys_mgmt function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44573 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the VLAN configuration of RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44573</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the VLAN configuration of RELY-PCIe v22.2.1 to v23.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20304 | Cisco IOS XR Software Packet Memory Exhaustion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20304</link><description>A vulnerability in the multicast traceroute version 2 (Mtrace2) feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to exhaust the UDP packet memory of an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because the Mtrace2 code does not properly handle packet memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the incoming UDP packet memory. The affected device would not be able to process higher-level UDP-based protocols packets, possibly causing a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Note: This vulnerability can be exploited using IPv4 or IPv6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20317 | Cisco IOS XR Software Layer 2 Services Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20317</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of specific Ethernet frames by Cisco IOS XR Software for various Cisco Network Convergence System (NCS) platforms could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause critical priority packets to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect classification of certain types of Ethernet frames that are received on an interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific types of Ethernet frames to or through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause control plane protocol relationships to fail, resulting in a DoS condition. For more information, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20343 | Cisco IOS XR Software CLI Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20343</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to read any file in the file system of the underlying Linux operating system. The attacker must have valid credentials on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect validation of the arguments that are passed to a specific CLI command. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to an affected device with low-privileged credentials and using the affected command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker access files in read-only mode on the Linux file system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20381 | Cisco Network Services Orchestrator Configuration Update Authorization Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20381</link><description>A vulnerability in the JSON-RPC API feature in ConfD that is used by the web-based management interfaces of Cisco Crosswork Network Services Orchestrator (NSO), Cisco Optical Site Manager, and Cisco RV340 Dual WAN Gigabit VPN Routers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to modify the configuration of an affected application or device.

This vulnerability is due to improper authorization checks on the API. An attacker with privileges sufficient to access the affected application or device could exploit this vulnerability by sending malicious requests to the JSON-RPC API. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to make unauthorized modifications to the configuration of the affected application or device, including creating new user accounts or elevating their own privileges on an affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20390 | Cisco IOS XR Software Dedicated XML Agent TCP Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20390</link><description>A vulnerability in the Dedicated XML Agent feature of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) on XML TCP listen port 38751.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper error validation of ingress XML packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a sustained, crafted stream of XML traffic to a targeted device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause XML TCP port 38751 to become unreachable while the attack traffic persists.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20398 | Cisco IOS XR Software Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20398</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to obtain read/write file system access on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20406 | Cisco IOS XR Software Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20406</link><description>A vulnerability in the segment routing feature for the Intermediate System-to-Intermediate System (IS-IS) protocol of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of ingress IS-IS packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specific IS-IS packets to an affected device after forming an adjacency. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the IS-IS process on all affected devices that are participating in the Flexible Algorithm to crash and restart, resulting in a DoS condition.
Note: The IS-IS protocol is a routing protocol. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must be Layer 2-adjacent to the affected device and must have formed an adjacency. This vulnerability affects segment routing for IS-IS over IPv4 and IPv6 control planes as well as devices that are configured as level 1, level 2, or multi-level routing IS-IS type.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20483 | Cisco IOS XR PON Controller Command Injection Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20483</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in Cisco Routed PON Controller Software, which runs as a docker container on hardware that is supported by Cisco IOS XR Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges on the PON Manager or direct access to the PON Manager MongoDB instance to perform command injection attacks on the PON Controller container and execute arbitrary commands as root.

These vulnerabilities are due to insufficient validation of arguments that are passed to specific configuration commands. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by including crafted input as the argument of an affected configuration command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the PON controller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20489 | Cisco Routed Passive Optical Network Cleartext Password Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20489</link><description>A vulnerability in the storage method of the PON Controller configuration file could allow an authenticated, local attacker with low privileges to obtain the MongoDB credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper storage of the unencrypted database credentials on the device that is running Cisco IOS XR Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by accessing the configuration files on an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to view MongoDB credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8687 | PAN-OS: Cleartext Exposure of GlobalProtect Portal Passcodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8687</link><description>An information exposure vulnerability exists in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software that enables a GlobalProtect end user to learn both the configured GlobalProtect uninstall password and the configured disable or disconnect passcode. After the password or passcode is known, end users can uninstall, disable, or disconnect GlobalProtect even if the GlobalProtect app configuration would not normally permit them to do so.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8688 | PAN-OS: Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability in the Command Line Interface (CLI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8688</link><description>An improper neutralization of matching symbols vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS command line interface (CLI) enables authenticated administrators (including read-only administrators) with access to the CLI to to read arbitrary files on the firewall.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8689 | ActiveMQ Content Pack: Cleartext Exposure of Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8689</link><description>A problem with the ActiveMQ integration for both Cortex XSOAR and Cortex XSIAM can result in the cleartext exposure of the configured ActiveMQ credentials in log bundles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8690 | Cortex XDR Agent: Local Windows Administrator Can Disable the Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8690</link><description>A problem with a detection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a user with Windows administrator privileges to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8691 | PAN-OS: User Impersonation in GlobalProtect Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8691</link><description>A vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated GlobalProtect user to impersonate another GlobalProtect user. Active GlobalProtect users impersonated by an attacker who is exploiting this vulnerability are disconnected from GlobalProtect. Upon exploitation, PAN-OS logs indicate that the impersonated user authenticated to GlobalProtect, which hides the identity of the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8097 | Sensitive information exposure when the org.glassfish.admingui LOGGER is set to FINEST level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8097</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (Logging modules) allows Sensitive credentials posted in plain-text on the server log.This issue affects Payara Server: from 6.0.0 before 6.18.0, from 6.2022.1 before 6.2024.9, from 5.20.0 before 5.67.0, from 5.2020.2 before 5.2022.5, from 4.1.2.191.0 before 4.1.2.191.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8686 | PAN-OS: Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8686</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated administrator to bypass system restrictions and run arbitrary commands as root on the firewall.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39378 | Audition | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39378</link><description>Audition versions 24.4.1, 23.6.6 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41868 | Audition | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41868</link><description>Audition versions 24.4.1, 23.6.6 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44851 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Discussion section of Perfex CRM v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44851</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Discussion section of Perfex CRM v1.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Content parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44466 | COMFAST CF-XR11 V2.7.2 has a command injection vulnerability in function sub_424CB4. Attackers can send POST request messages to /usr/bin/we...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44466</link><description>COMFAST CF-XR11 V2.7.2 has a command injection vulnerability in function sub_424CB4. Attackers can send POST request messages to /usr/bin/webmgnt and inject commands into parameter iface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5760 | The Samsung Universal Print Driver for Windows is potentially vulnerable to escalation of privilege allowing the creation of a reverse shell...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5760</link><description>The Samsung Universal Print Driver for Windows is potentially vulnerable to escalation of privilege allowing the creation of a reverse shell in the tool. This is only applicable for products in the application released or manufactured before 2018.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7312 | REST Interface Link Redirection via Host parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7312</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (REST Management Interface modules) allows Session Hijacking.This issue affects Payara Server: from 6.0.0 before 6.18.0, from 6.2022.1 before 6.2024.9, from 5.2020.2 before 5.2022.5, from 5.20.0 before 5.67.0, from 4.1.2.191.0 before 4.1.2.191.50.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:35:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45009 | mptcp: pm: only decrement add_addr_accepted for MPJ req</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45009</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: only decrement add_addr_accepted for MPJ req

Adding the following warning ...

  WARN_ON_ONCE(msk-&gt;pm.add_addr_accepted == 0)

... before decrementing the add_addr_accepted counter helped to find a
bug when running the "remove single subflow" subtest from the
mptcp_join.sh selftest.

Removing a 'subflow' endpoint will first trigger a RM_ADDR, then the
subflow closure. Before this patch, and upon the reception of the
RM_ADDR, the other peer will then try to decrement this
add_addr_accepted. That's not correct because the attached subflows have
not been created upon the reception of an ADD_ADDR.

A way to solve that is to decrement the counter only if the attached
subflow was an MP_JOIN to a remote id that was not 0, and initiated by
the host receiving the RM_ADDR.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45010 | mptcp: pm: only mark &amp;#x27;subflow&amp;#x27; endp as available</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45010</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: pm: only mark 'subflow' endp as available

Adding the following warning ...

  WARN_ON_ONCE(msk-&gt;pm.local_addr_used == 0)

... before decrementing the local_addr_used counter helped to find a bug
when running the "remove single address" subtest from the mptcp_join.sh
selftests.

Removing a 'signal' endpoint will trigger the removal of all subflows
linked to this endpoint via mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow() with
rm_type == MPTCP_MIB_RMSUBFLOW. This will decrement the local_addr_used
counter, which is wrong in this case because this counter is linked to
'subflow' endpoints, and here it is a 'signal' endpoint that is being
removed.

Now, the counter is decremented, only if the ID is being used outside
of mptcp_pm_nl_rm_addr_or_subflow(), only for 'subflow' endpoints, and
if the ID is not 0 -- local_addr_used is not taking into account these
ones. This marking of the ID as being available, and the decrement is
done no matter if a subflow using this ID is currently available,
because the subflow could have been closed before.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45011 | char: xillybus: Check USB endpoints when probing device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45011</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

char: xillybus: Check USB endpoints when probing device

Ensure, as the driver probes the device, that all endpoints that the
driver may attempt to access exist and are of the correct type.

All XillyUSB devices must have a Bulk IN and Bulk OUT endpoint at
address 1. This is verified in xillyusb_setup_base_eps().

On top of that, a XillyUSB device may have additional Bulk OUT
endpoints. The information about these endpoints' addresses is deduced
from a data structure (the IDT) that the driver fetches from the device
while probing it. These endpoints are checked in setup_channels().

A XillyUSB device never has more than one IN endpoint, as all data
towards the host is multiplexed in this single Bulk IN endpoint. This is
why setup_channels() only checks OUT endpoints.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45012 | nouveau/firmware: use dma non-coherent allocator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45012</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nouveau/firmware: use dma non-coherent allocator

Currently, enabling SG_DEBUG in the kernel will cause nouveau to hit a
BUG() on startup, when the iommu is enabled:

kernel BUG at include/linux/scatterlist.h:187!
invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP NOPTI
CPU: 7 PID: 930 Comm: (udev-worker) Not tainted 6.9.0-rc3Lyude-Test+ #30
Hardware name: MSI MS-7A39/A320M GAMING PRO (MS-7A39), BIOS 1.I0 01/22/2019
RIP: 0010:sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
Code: 69 88 32 01 83 e1 03 f6 c3 03 75 20 a8 01 75 1e 48 09 cb 41 89 54
24 08 49 89 1c 24 41 89 6c 24 0c 5b 5d 41 5c e9 7b b9 88 00 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 0f 0b
0f 0b 48 8b 05 5e 46 9a 01 eb b2 66 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00
RSP: 0018:ffffa776017bf6a0 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffa77600d87000 RCX: 000000000000002b
RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffffa77680d87000
RBP: 000000000000e000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: ffff98f4c46aa508 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: ffff98f4c46aa508
R13: ffff98f4c46aa008 R14: ffffa77600d4a000 R15: ffffa77600d4a018
FS:  00007feeb5aae980(0000) GS:ffff98f5c4dc0000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f22cb9a4520 CR3: 00000001043ba000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
Call Trace:
 
 ? die+0x36/0x90
 ? do_trap+0xdd/0x100
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? do_error_trap+0x65/0x80
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x50/0x70
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
 ? sg_init_one+0x85/0xa0
 nvkm_firmware_ctor+0x14a/0x250 [nouveau]
 nvkm_falcon_fw_ctor+0x42/0x70 [nouveau]
 ga102_gsp_booter_ctor+0xb4/0x1a0 [nouveau]
 r535_gsp_oneinit+0xb3/0x15f0 [nouveau]
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? nvkm_udevice_new+0x95/0x140 [nouveau]
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
 ? ktime_get+0x47/0xb0

Fix this by using the non-coherent allocator instead, I think there
might be a better answer to this, but it involve ripping up some of
APIs using sg lists.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45013 | nvme: move stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45013</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: move stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl()

Commit 4733b65d82bd ("nvme: start keep-alive after admin queue setup")
moves starting keep-alive from nvme_start_ctrl() into
nvme_init_ctrl_finish(), but don't move stopping keep-alive into
nvme_uninit_ctrl(), so keep-alive work can be started and keep pending
after failing to start controller, finally use-after-free is triggered if
nvme host driver is unloaded.

This patch fixes kernel panic when running nvme/004 in case that connection
failure is triggered, by moving stopping keep-alive into nvme_uninit_ctrl().

This way is reasonable because keep-alive is now started in
nvme_init_ctrl_finish().</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45014 | s390/boot: Avoid possible physmem_info segment corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45014</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/boot: Avoid possible physmem_info segment corruption

When physical memory for the kernel image is allocated it does not
consider extra memory required for offsetting the image start to
match it with the lower 20 bits of KASLR virtual base address. That
might lead to kernel access beyond its memory range.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45015 | drm/msm/dpu: move dpu_encoder&amp;#x27;s connector assignment to atomic_enable()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45015</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/msm/dpu: move dpu_encoder's connector assignment to atomic_enable()

For cases where the crtc's connectors_changed was set without enable/active
getting toggled , there is an atomic_enable() call followed by an
atomic_disable() but without an atomic_mode_set().

This results in a NULL ptr access for the dpu_encoder_get_drm_fmt() call in
the atomic_enable() as the dpu_encoder's connector was cleared in the
atomic_disable() but not re-assigned as there was no atomic_mode_set() call.

Fix the NULL ptr access by moving the assignment for atomic_enable() and also
use drm_atomic_get_new_connector_for_encoder() to get the connector from
the atomic_state.

Patchwork: https://patchwork.freedesktop.org/patch/606729/</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45016 | netem: fix return value if duplicate enqueue fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45016</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netem: fix return value if duplicate enqueue fails

There is a bug in netem_enqueue() introduced by
commit 5845f706388a ("net: netem: fix skb length BUG_ON in __skb_to_sgvec")
that can lead to a use-after-free.

This commit made netem_enqueue() always return NET_XMIT_SUCCESS
when a packet is duplicated, which can cause the parent qdisc's q.qlen
to be mistakenly incremented. When this happens qlen_notify() may be
skipped on the parent during destruction, leaving a dangling pointer
for some classful qdiscs like DRR.

There are two ways for the bug happen:

- If the duplicated packet is dropped by rootq-&gt;enqueue() and then
  the original packet is also dropped.
- If rootq-&gt;enqueue() sends the duplicated packet to a different qdisc
  and the original packet is dropped.

In both cases NET_XMIT_SUCCESS is returned even though no packets
are enqueued at the netem qdisc.

The fix is to defer the enqueue of the duplicate packet until after
the original packet has been guaranteed to return NET_XMIT_SUCCESS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45017 | net/mlx5: Fix IPsec RoCE MPV trace call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45017</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5: Fix IPsec RoCE MPV trace call

Prevent the call trace below from happening, by not allowing IPsec
creation over a slave, if master device doesn't support IPsec.

WARNING: CPU: 44 PID: 16136 at kernel/locking/rwsem.c:240 down_read+0x75/0x94
Modules linked in: esp4_offload esp4 act_mirred act_vlan cls_flower sch_ingress mlx5_vdpa vringh vhost_iotlb vdpa mst_pciconf(OE) nfsv3 nfs_acl nfs lockd grace fscache netfs xt_CHECKSUM xt_MASQUERADE xt_conntrack ipt_REJECT nf_reject_ipv4 nft_compat nft_counter nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4 rfkill cuse fuse rpcrdma sunrpc rdma_ucm ib_srpt ib_isert iscsi_target_mod target_core_mod ib_umad ib_iser libiscsi scsi_transport_iscsi rdma_cm ib_ipoib iw_cm ib_cm ipmi_ssif intel_rapl_msr intel_rapl_common amd64_edac edac_mce_amd kvm_amd kvm irqbypass crct10dif_pclmul crc32_pclmul mlx5_ib ghash_clmulni_intel sha1_ssse3 dell_smbios ib_uverbs aesni_intel crypto_simd dcdbas wmi_bmof dell_wmi_descriptor cryptd pcspkr ib_core acpi_ipmi sp5100_tco ccp i2c_piix4 ipmi_si ptdma k10temp ipmi_devintf ipmi_msghandler acpi_power_meter acpi_cpufreq ext4 mbcache jbd2 sd_mod t10_pi sg mgag200 drm_kms_helper syscopyarea sysfillrect mlx5_core sysimgblt fb_sys_fops cec
 ahci libahci mlxfw drm pci_hyperv_intf libata tg3 sha256_ssse3 tls megaraid_sas i2c_algo_bit psample wmi dm_mirror dm_region_hash dm_log dm_mod [last unloaded: mst_pci]
CPU: 44 PID: 16136 Comm: kworker/44:3 Kdump: loaded Tainted: GOE 5.15.0-20240509.el8uek.uek7_u3_update_v6.6_ipsec_bf.x86_64 #2
Hardware name: Dell Inc. PowerEdge R7525/074H08, BIOS 2.0.3 01/15/2021
Workqueue: events xfrm_state_gc_task
RIP: 0010:down_read+0x75/0x94
Code: 00 48 8b 45 08 65 48 8b 14 25 80 fc 01 00 83 e0 02 48 09 d0 48 83 c8 01 48 89 45 08 5d 31 c0 89 c2 89 c6 89 c7 e9 cb 88 3b 00 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 48 8b 45 08 a8 01 74 b2 a8 02 75 ae 48 89 c2 48 83 ca 02 f0
RSP: 0018:ffffb26387773da8 EFLAGS: 00010282
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffa08b658af900 RCX: 0000000000000001
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: ff886bc5e1366f2f RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffffa08b658af940 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: ffffa0a9bfb31540
R13: ffffa0a9bfb37900 R14: 0000000000000000 R15: ffffa0a9bfb37905
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffffa0a9bfb00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 000055a45ed814e8 CR3: 000000109038a000 CR4: 0000000000350ee0
Call Trace:
 
 ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1d6/0x2f9
 ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1d6/0x2f9
 ? mlx5_devcom_for_each_peer_begin+0x29/0x60 [mlx5_core]
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? __warn+0x80/0x113
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? report_bug+0xa4/0x11d
 ? handle_bug+0x35/0x8b
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x14/0x75
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x1b
 ? down_read+0x75/0x94
 ? down_read+0xe/0x94
 mlx5_devcom_for_each_peer_begin+0x29/0x60 [mlx5_core]
 mlx5_ipsec_fs_roce_tx_destroy+0xb1/0x130 [mlx5_core]
 tx_destroy+0x1b/0xc0 [mlx5_core]
 tx_ft_put+0x53/0xc0 [mlx5_core]
 mlx5e_xfrm_free_state+0x45/0x90 [mlx5_core]
 ___xfrm_state_destroy+0x10f/0x1a2
 xfrm_state_gc_task+0x81/0xa9
 process_one_work+0x1f1/0x3c6
 worker_thread+0x53/0x3e4
 ? process_one_work.cold+0x46/0x3c
 kthread+0x127/0x144
 ? set_kthread_struct+0x60/0x52
 ret_from_fork+0x22/0x2d
 
---[ end trace 5ef7896144d398e1 ]---</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45018 | netfilter: flowtable: initialise extack before use</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45018</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: flowtable: initialise extack before use

Fix missing initialisation of extack in flow offload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45019 | net/mlx5e: Take state lock during tx timeout reporter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45019</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/mlx5e: Take state lock during tx timeout reporter

mlx5e_safe_reopen_channels() requires the state lock taken. The
referenced changed in the Fixes tag removed the lock to fix another
issue. This patch adds it back but at a later point (when calling
mlx5e_safe_reopen_channels()) to avoid the deadlock referenced in the
Fixes tag.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45020 | bpf: Fix a kernel verifier crash in stacksafe()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45020</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix a kernel verifier crash in stacksafe()

Daniel Hodges reported a kernel verifier crash when playing with sched-ext.
Further investigation shows that the crash is due to invalid memory access
in stacksafe(). More specifically, it is the following code:

    if (exact != NOT_EXACT &amp;&amp;
        old-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE] !=
        cur-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE])
            return false;

The 'i' iterates old-&gt;allocated_stack.
If cur-&gt;allocated_stack &lt; old-&gt;allocated_stack the out-of-bound
access will happen.

To fix the issue add 'i &gt;= cur-&gt;allocated_stack' check such that if
the condition is true, stacksafe() should fail. Otherwise,
cur-&gt;stack[spi].slot_type[i % BPF_REG_SIZE] memory access is legal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45021 | memcg_write_event_control(): fix a user-triggerable oops</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45021</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

memcg_write_event_control(): fix a user-triggerable oops

we are *not* guaranteed that anything past the terminating NUL
is mapped (let alone initialized with anything sane).</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45022 | mm/vmalloc: fix page mapping if vm_area_alloc_pages() with high order fallback to order 0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45022</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/vmalloc: fix page mapping if vm_area_alloc_pages() with high order fallback to order 0

The __vmap_pages_range_noflush() assumes its argument pages** contains
pages with the same page shift.  However, since commit e9c3cda4d86e ("mm,
vmalloc: fix high order __GFP_NOFAIL allocations"), if gfp_flags includes
__GFP_NOFAIL with high order in vm_area_alloc_pages() and page allocation
failed for high order, the pages** may contain two different page shifts
(high order and order-0).  This could lead __vmap_pages_range_noflush() to
perform incorrect mappings, potentially resulting in memory corruption.

Users might encounter this as follows (vmap_allow_huge = true, 2M is for
PMD_SIZE):

kvmalloc(2M, __GFP_NOFAIL|GFP_X)
    __vmalloc_node_range_noprof(vm_flags=VM_ALLOW_HUGE_VMAP)
        vm_area_alloc_pages(order=9) ---&gt; order-9 allocation failed and fallback to order-0
            vmap_pages_range()
                vmap_pages_range_noflush()
                    __vmap_pages_range_noflush(page_shift = 21) ----&gt; wrong mapping happens

We can remove the fallback code because if a high-order allocation fails,
__vmalloc_node_range_noprof() will retry with order-0.  Therefore, it is
unnecessary to fallback to order-0 here.  Therefore, fix this by removing
the fallback code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45023 | md/raid1: Fix data corruption for degraded array with slow disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45023</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

md/raid1: Fix data corruption for degraded array with slow disk

read_balance() will avoid reading from slow disks as much as possible,
however, if valid data only lands in slow disks, and a new normal disk
is still in recovery, unrecovered data can be read:

raid1_read_request
 read_balance
  raid1_should_read_first
  -&gt; return false
  choose_best_rdev
  -&gt; normal disk is not recovered, return -1
  choose_bb_rdev
  -&gt; missing the checking of recovery, return the normal disk
 -&gt; read unrecovered data

Root cause is that the checking of recovery is missing in
choose_bb_rdev(). Hence add such checking to fix the problem.

Also fix similar problem in choose_slow_rdev().</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45024 | mm/hugetlb: fix hugetlb vs. core-mm PT locking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45024</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/hugetlb: fix hugetlb vs. core-mm PT locking

We recently made GUP's common page table walking code to also walk hugetlb
VMAs without most hugetlb special-casing, preparing for the future of
having less hugetlb-specific page table walking code in the codebase. 
Turns out that we missed one page table locking detail: page table locking
for hugetlb folios that are not mapped using a single PMD/PUD.

Assume we have hugetlb folio that spans multiple PTEs (e.g., 64 KiB
hugetlb folios on arm64 with 4 KiB base page size).  GUP, as it walks the
page tables, will perform a pte_offset_map_lock() to grab the PTE table
lock.

However, hugetlb that concurrently modifies these page tables would
actually grab the mm-&gt;page_table_lock: with USE_SPLIT_PTE_PTLOCKS, the
locks would differ.  Something similar can happen right now with hugetlb
folios that span multiple PMDs when USE_SPLIT_PMD_PTLOCKS.

This issue can be reproduced [1], for example triggering:

[ 3105.936100] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[ 3105.939323] WARNING: CPU: 31 PID: 2732 at mm/gup.c:142 try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3105.944634] Modules linked in: [...]
[ 3105.974841] CPU: 31 PID: 2732 Comm: reproducer Not tainted 6.10.0-64.eln141.aarch64 #1
[ 3105.980406] Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS edk2-20240524-4.fc40 05/24/2024
[ 3105.986185] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[ 3105.991108] pc : try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3105.994013] lr : follow_page_pte+0xd8/0x430
[ 3105.996986] sp : ffff80008eafb8f0
[ 3105.999346] x29: ffff80008eafb900 x28: ffffffe8d481f380 x27: 00f80001207cff43
[ 3106.004414] x26: 0000000000000001 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: ffff80008eafba48
[ 3106.009520] x23: 0000ffff9372f000 x22: ffff7a54459e2000 x21: ffff7a546c1aa978
[ 3106.014529] x20: ffffffe8d481f3c0 x19: 0000000000610041 x18: 0000000000000001
[ 3106.019506] x17: 0000000000000001 x16: ffffffffffffffff x15: 0000000000000000
[ 3106.024494] x14: ffffb85477fdfe08 x13: 0000ffff9372ffff x12: 0000000000000000
[ 3106.029469] x11: 1fffef4a88a96be1 x10: ffff7a54454b5f0c x9 : ffffb854771b12f0
[ 3106.034324] x8 : 0008000000000000 x7 : ffff7a546c1aa980 x6 : 0008000000000080
[ 3106.038902] x5 : 00000000001207cf x4 : 0000ffff9372f000 x3 : ffffffe8d481f000
[ 3106.043420] x2 : 0000000000610041 x1 : 0000000000000001 x0 : 0000000000000000
[ 3106.047957] Call trace:
[ 3106.049522]  try_grab_folio+0x11c/0x188
[ 3106.051996]  follow_pmd_mask.constprop.0.isra.0+0x150/0x2e0
[ 3106.055527]  follow_page_mask+0x1a0/0x2b8
[ 3106.058118]  __get_user_pages+0xf0/0x348
[ 3106.060647]  faultin_page_range+0xb0/0x360
[ 3106.063651]  do_madvise+0x340/0x598

Let's make huge_pte_lockptr() effectively use the same PT locks as any
core-mm page table walker would.  Add ptep_lockptr() to obtain the PTE
page table lock using a pte pointer -- unfortunately we cannot convert
pte_lockptr() because virt_to_page() doesn't work with kmap'ed page tables
we can have with CONFIG_HIGHPTE.

Handle CONFIG_PGTABLE_LEVELS correctly by checking in reverse order, such
that when e.g., CONFIG_PGTABLE_LEVELS==2 with
PGDIR_SIZE==P4D_SIZE==PUD_SIZE==PMD_SIZE will work as expected.  Document
why that works.

There is one ugly case: powerpc 8xx, whereby we have an 8 MiB hugetlb
folio being mapped using two PTE page tables.  While hugetlb wants to take
the PMD table lock, core-mm would grab the PTE table lock of one of both
PTE page tables.  In such corner cases, we have to make sure that both
locks match, which is (fortunately!) currently guaranteed for 8xx as it
does not support SMP and consequently doesn't use split PT locks.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/all/1bbfcc7f-f222-45a5-ac44-c5a1381c596d@redhat.com/</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45025 | fix bitmap corruption on close_range() with CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45025</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fix bitmap corruption on close_range() with CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE

copy_fd_bitmaps(new, old, count) is expected to copy the first
count/BITS_PER_LONG bits from old-&gt;full_fds_bits[] and fill
the rest with zeroes.  What it does is copying enough words
(BITS_TO_LONGS(count/BITS_PER_LONG)), then memsets the rest.
That works fine, *if* all bits past the cutoff point are
clear.  Otherwise we are risking garbage from the last word
we'd copied.

For most of the callers that is true - expand_fdtable() has
count equal to old-&gt;max_fds, so there's no open descriptors
past count, let alone fully occupied words in -&gt;open_fds[],
which is what bits in -&gt;full_fds_bits[] correspond to.

The other caller (dup_fd()) passes sane_fdtable_size(old_fdt, max_fds),
which is the smallest multiple of BITS_PER_LONG that covers all
opened descriptors below max_fds.  In the common case (copying on
fork()) max_fds is ~0U, so all opened descriptors will be below
it and we are fine, by the same reasons why the call in expand_fdtable()
is safe.

Unfortunately, there is a case where max_fds is less than that
and where we might, indeed, end up with junk in -&gt;full_fds_bits[] -
close_range(from, to, CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE) with
	* descriptor table being currently shared
	* 'to' being above the current capacity of descriptor table
	* 'from' being just under some chunk of opened descriptors.
In that case we end up with observably wrong behaviour - e.g. spawn
a child with CLONE_FILES, get all descriptors in range 0..127 open,
then close_range(64, ~0U, CLOSE_RANGE_UNSHARE) and watch dup(0) ending
up with descriptor #128, despite #64 being observably not open.

The minimally invasive fix would be to deal with that in dup_fd().
If this proves to add measurable overhead, we can go that way, but
let's try to fix copy_fd_bitmaps() first.

* new helper: bitmap_copy_and_expand(to, from, bits_to_copy, size).
* make copy_fd_bitmaps() take the bitmap size in words, rather than
bits; it's 'count' argument is always a multiple of BITS_PER_LONG,
so we are not losing any information, and that way we can use the
same helper for all three bitmaps - compiler will see that count
is a multiple of BITS_PER_LONG for the large ones, so it'll generate
plain memcpy()+memset().

Reproducer added to tools/testing/selftests/core/close_range_test.c</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45026 | s390/dasd: fix error recovery leading to data corruption on ESE devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45026</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/dasd: fix error recovery leading to data corruption on ESE devices

Extent Space Efficient (ESE) or thin provisioned volumes need to be
formatted on demand during usual IO processing.

The dasd_ese_needs_format function checks for error codes that signal
the non existence of a proper track format.

The check for incorrect length is to imprecise since other error cases
leading to transport of insufficient data also have this flag set.
This might lead to data corruption in certain error cases for example
during a storage server warmstart.

Fix by removing the check for incorrect length and replacing by
explicitly checking for invalid track format in transport mode.

Also remove the check for file protected since this is not a valid
ESE handling case.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45027 | usb: xhci: Check for xhci-&amp;gt;interrupters being allocated in xhci_mem_clearup()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45027</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: xhci: Check for xhci-&gt;interrupters being allocated in xhci_mem_clearup()

If xhci_mem_init() fails, it calls into xhci_mem_cleanup() to mop
up the damage. If it fails early enough, before xhci-&gt;interrupters
is allocated but after xhci-&gt;max_interrupters has been set, which
happens in most (all?) cases, things get uglier, as xhci_mem_cleanup()
unconditionally derefences xhci-&gt;interrupters. With prejudice.

Gate the interrupt freeing loop with a check on xhci-&gt;interrupters
being non-NULL.

Found while debugging a DMA allocation issue that led the XHCI driver
on this exact path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45028 | mmc: mmc_test: Fix NULL dereference on allocation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45028</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mmc: mmc_test: Fix NULL dereference on allocation failure

If the "test-&gt;highmem = alloc_pages()" allocation fails then calling
__free_pages(test-&gt;highmem) will result in a NULL dereference.  Also
change the error code to -ENOMEM instead of returning success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45029 | i2c: tegra: Do not mark ACPI devices as irq safe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45029</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i2c: tegra: Do not mark ACPI devices as irq safe

On ACPI machines, the tegra i2c module encounters an issue due to a
mutex being called inside a spinlock. This leads to the following bug:

	BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at kernel/locking/mutex.c:585
	...

	Call trace:
	__might_sleep
	__mutex_lock_common
	mutex_lock_nested
	acpi_subsys_runtime_resume
	rpm_resume
	tegra_i2c_xfer

The problem arises because during __pm_runtime_resume(), the spinlock
&amp;amp;dev-&gt;power.lock is acquired before rpm_resume() is called. Later,
rpm_resume() invokes acpi_subsys_runtime_resume(), which relies on
mutexes, triggering the error.

To address this issue, devices on ACPI are now marked as not IRQ-safe,
considering the dependency of acpi_subsys_runtime_resume() on mutexes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45030 | igb: cope with large MAX_SKB_FRAGS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45030</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

igb: cope with large MAX_SKB_FRAGS

Sabrina reports that the igb driver does not cope well with large
MAX_SKB_FRAG values: setting MAX_SKB_FRAG to 45 causes payload
corruption on TX.

An easy reproducer is to run ssh to connect to the machine.  With
MAX_SKB_FRAGS=17 it works, with MAX_SKB_FRAGS=45 it fails.  This has
been reported originally in
https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=2265320

The root cause of the issue is that the driver does not take into
account properly the (possibly large) shared info size when selecting
the ring layout, and will try to fit two packets inside the same 4K
page even when the 1st fraglist will trump over the 2nd head.

Address the issue by checking if 2K buffers are insufficient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46672 | wifi: brcmfmac: cfg80211: Handle SSID based pmksa deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46672</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: brcmfmac: cfg80211: Handle SSID based pmksa deletion

wpa_supplicant 2.11 sends since 1efdba5fdc2c ("Handle PMKSA flush in the
driver for SAE/OWE offload cases") SSID based PMKSA del commands.
brcmfmac is not prepared and tries to dereference the NULL bssid and
pmkid pointers in cfg80211_pmksa. PMKID_V3 operations support SSID based
updates so copy the SSID.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8306 | CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access, loss of confidentiality, integrity and ava...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8306</link><description>CWE-269: Improper Privilege Management vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access, loss of confidentiality, integrity and availability of the workstation when non-admin
authenticated user tries to perform privilege escalation by tampering with the binaries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4465 | Incorrect authorization for Reports configuration in Guardian/CMC before 24.2.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4465</link><description>An access control vulnerability was discovered in the Reports section due to a specific access restriction not being properly enforced for users with limited privileges.



If a logged-in user with reporting privileges learns how to create a specific application request, they might be able to make limited changes to the reporting configuration. This could result in a partial loss of data integrity. In Guardian/CMC instances with a reporting configuration, there could be limited Denial of Service (DoS) impacts, as the reports may not reach their intended destination, and there could also be limited information disclosure impacts. Furthermore, modifying the destination SMTP server for the reports could lead to the compromise of external credentials, as they might be sent to an unauthorized server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43793 | Halo&amp;#x27;s editor has a stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43793</link><description>Halo is an open source website building tool. A security vulnerability has been identified in versions prior to 2.19.0 of the Halo project. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute malicious scripts in the user's browser through specific HTML and JavaScript code, potentially leading to a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.19.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8636 | Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8636</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in Skia in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8637 | Use after free in Media Router in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap cor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8637</link><description>Use after free in Media Router in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8638 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8638</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit object corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8639 | Use after free in Autofill in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corrupt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8639</link><description>Use after free in Autofill in Google Chrome on Android prior to 128.0.6613.137 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27112 | SQL Injection in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27112</link><description>A unauthenticated SQL Injection has been found in the SO Planning tool that occurs when the public view setting is enabled. An attacker could use this vulnerability to gain access to the underlying database. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27113 | Insecure Direct Object Reference to export Database in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27113</link><description>An unauthenticated Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) to the database has been found in the SO Planning tool that occurs when the public view setting is enabled. An attacker could use this vulnerability to gain access to the underlying database by exporting it as a CSV file. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27114 | Remote Code Execution through File Upload in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27114</link><description>A unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability is found in the SO Planning online planning tool. If the public view setting is enabled, a attacker can upload a PHP-file that will be available for execution for a few milliseconds before it is removed, leading to execution of code on the underlying system. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27115 | Remote Code Execution through File Upload in SOPlanning before 1.52.02</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27115</link><description>A unauthenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability is found in the SO Planning online planning tool. With this vulnerability, an attacker can upload executable files that are moved to a publicly accessible folder before verifying any requirements. This leads to the possibility of execution of code on the underlying system when the file is triggered. The vulnerability has been remediated in version 1.52.02.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8642 | Eclipse EDC: Consumer pull transfer token validation checks not applied</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8642</link><description>In Eclipse Dataspace Components, from version 0.5.0 and before version 0.9.0, the ConsumerPullTransferTokenValidationApiController does not check for token validity (expiry, not-before, issuance date), which can allow an attacker to bypass the check for token expiration. The issue requires to have a dataplane configured to support http proxy consumer pull AND include the module "transfer-data-plane". The affected code was marked deprecated from the version 0.6.0 in favour of Dataplane Signaling. In 0.9.0 the vulnerable code has been removed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8646 | Eclipse Glassfish: URL redirection vulnerability to untrusted sites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8646</link><description>In Eclipse Glassfish versions prior to 7.0.10, a URL redirection vulnerability to untrusted sites existed.
This vulnerability is caused by the vulnerability (CVE-2023-41080) in the Apache code included in GlassFish.
This vulnerability only affects applications that are explicitly deployed to the root context ('/').</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6091 | Shell Command Denylist Bypass in significant-gravitas/autogpt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6091</link><description>A vulnerability in significant-gravitas/autogpt version 0.5.1 allows an attacker to bypass the shell commands denylist settings. The issue arises when the denylist is configured to block specific commands, such as 'whoami' and '/bin/whoami'. An attacker can circumvent this restriction by executing commands with a modified path, such as '/bin/./whoami', which is not recognized by the denylist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45790 | User Enumeration vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45790</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to missing restrictions for excessive failed authentication attempts on its API based login. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by conducting a brute force attack against legitimate user passwords, which could lead to gain unauthorized access and compromise other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45788 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45788</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoints which could lead to the OTP bombing/flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45789 | Parameter Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45789</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to improper validation of the ‘mode’ parameter in the API endpoint used during the registration process. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating parameter in the API request body on the vulnerable application.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass certain constraints in the registration process leading to creation of multiple accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45786 | Improper Authorization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45786</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to improper access controls on its certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter through API request URL which could lead to gain unauthorized access to sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45787 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45787</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Reedos aiM-Star version 2.0.1 due to transmission of sensitive information in plain text in certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter through API request URL and intercepting response of the API request leading to exposure of sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5416 | Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.23.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in the URL Parameter in Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5416</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder – More than Just a Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the url parameter of multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.23.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in Elementor Editor pages. This was partially patched in version 3.23.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7609 | Directory Traversal in Vidco Software&amp;#x27;s VOC TESTER</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7609</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Vidco Software VOC TESTER allows Path Traversal.This issue affects VOC TESTER: before 12.34.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 11:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8096 | OCSP stapling bypass with GnuTLS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8096</link><description>When curl is told to use the Certificate Status Request TLS extension, often referred to as OCSP stapling, to verify that the server certificate is valid, it might fail to detect some OCSP problems and instead wrongly consider the response as fine.  If the returned status reports another error than 'revoked' (like for example 'unauthorized') it is not treated as a bad certficate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45327 | An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiSOAR version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.3.0 through 7.3.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45327</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability [CWE-285] in FortiSOAR version 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.3.0 through 7.3.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 through 7.0.3 change password endpoint may allow an authenticated attacker to perform a brute force attack on users and administrators password via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25212 | video carousel slider with lightbox &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25212</link><description>The video carousel slider with lightbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8277 | WooCommerce Photo Reviews Premium &amp;lt;= 1.3.13.2 - Authentication Bypass to Account Takeover and Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8277</link><description>The WooCommerce Photo Reviews Premium plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.13.2. This is due to the plugin not properly validating what user transient is being used in the login() function and not properly verifying the user's identity. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as user that has dismissed an admin notice in the past 30 days, which is often an administrator. Alternatively, a user can log in as any user with any transient that has a valid user_id as the value, though it would be more difficult to exploit this successfully.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7626 | WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Improper Path Validation to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Move and Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7626</link><description>The WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file movement and reading due to insufficient file path validation in the save_edit_profile_details() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php). This can also lead to the reading of arbitrary files that may contain sensitive information like wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8045 | Advanced WordPress Backgrounds &amp;lt;= 1.12.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via imageTag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8045</link><description>The Advanced WordPress Backgrounds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘imageTag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8440 | Essential Addons for Elementor -- Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp;amp; WooCommerce Builders &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Fancy Text Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8440</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Fancy Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3899 | Envira Gallery &amp;lt; 1.8.15 - Author+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3899</link><description>The Gallery Plugin for WordPress  WordPress plugin before 1.8.15 does not sanitise and escape some of its image settings, which could allow users with post-writing privilege such as Author to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7716 | GS Logo Slider Lite &amp;lt; 3.6.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7716</link><description>The Logo Slider  WordPress plugin before 3.6.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 06:14:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21529 | Versions of the package dset before 3.1.4 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the dset function due improper user input sanitization. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21529</link><description>Versions of the package dset before 3.1.4 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the dset function due improper user input sanitization. This vulnerability allows the attacker to inject malicious object property using the built-in Object property __proto__, which is recursively assigned to all the objects in the program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 05:10:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7721 | HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block &amp;lt;= 2.5.34 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7721</link><description>The HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_password' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.34. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to set any options that are not explicitly checked as false to an array, including enabling user registration if it has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7727 | HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block &amp;lt;= 2.5.32 - Missing Authorization in multiple functions via h5vp_ajax_handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7727</link><description>The HTML5 Video Player – mp4 Video Player Plugin and Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on multiple functions called via the 'h5vp_ajax_handler' ajax action in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.32. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call these functions to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1656 | Affected versions of Octopus Server had a weak content security policy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1656</link><description>Affected versions of Octopus Server had a weak content security policy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43690 | Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere(CWE-829) in the Command Centre Server and Workstations may allow an attacker to per...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43690</link><description>Inclusion of Functionality from Untrusted Control Sphere(CWE-829) in the Command Centre Server and Workstations may allow an attacker to perform Remote Code Execution (RCE).

This issue affects: Command Centre Server and Command Centre Workstations 9.10 prior to vEL9.10.1530 (MR2), 9.00 prior to vEL9.00.2168 (MR4), 8.90 prior to vEL8.90.2155 (MR5), 8.80 prior to vEL8.80.1938 (MR6), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23906 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (CWE-79) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic webpage allows an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23906</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (CWE-79) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic webpage allows an attacker to modify Controller configuration during an authenticated Operator's session.

 



This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24972 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (CWE-120) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authorise...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24972</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (CWE-120) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 diagnostic web interface allows an authorised and authenticated operator to reboot the Controller, causing a Denial of Service. Gallagher recommend the diagnostic web page is not enabled (default is off) unless advised by Gallagher Technical support. This interface is intended only for diagnostic purposes.

This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39808 | Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size (CWE-131) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 OSDP message handling, allows an attacker with phy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39808</link><description>Incorrect Calculation of Buffer Size (CWE-131) in the Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 OSDP message handling, allows an attacker with physical access to Controller wiring to instigate a reboot leading to a denial of service. 



This issue affects: Controller 6000 and Controller 7000 9.10 prior to vCR9.10.240816a (distributed in 9.10.1530 (MR2)), 9.00 prior to vCR9.00.240816a (distributed in 9.00.2168 (MR4)), 8.90 prior to vCR8.90.240816a (distributed in 8.90.2155 (MR5)), 8.80 prior to vCR8.80.240816b (distributed in 8.80.1938 (MR6)), all versions of 8.70 and prior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8253 | Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks 2.2.87 - 2.2.90 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8253</link><description>The Post Grid and Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions 2.2.87 to 2.2.90. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting what user meta values can be updated and ensuring a form is active. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update their user meta to become an administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 03:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23716 | In DevmemIntPFNotify of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23716</link><description>In DevmemIntPFNotify of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible use-after-free due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31336 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31336</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40650 | In wifi_item_edit_content of styles.xml , there is a possible FRP bypass due to Missing check for FRP state. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40650</link><description>In wifi_item_edit_content of styles.xml , there is a possible FRP bypass due to Missing check for FRP state. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40652 | In onCreate of SettingsHomepageActivity.java, there is a possible way to access the Settings app while the device is provisioning due to a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40652</link><description>In onCreate of SettingsHomepageActivity.java, there is a possible way to access the Settings app while the device is provisioning due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40654 | In multiple locations, there is a possible permission bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40654</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible permission bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40655 | In bindAndGetCallIdentification of CallScreeningServiceHelper.java, there is a possible way to maintain a while-in-use permission in the bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40655</link><description>In bindAndGetCallIdentification of CallScreeningServiceHelper.java, there is a possible way to maintain a while-in-use permission in the background due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40656 | In handleCreateConferenceComplete of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confused ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40656</link><description>In handleCreateConferenceComplete of ConnectionServiceWrapper.java, there is a possible way to reveal images across users due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40657 | In addPreferencesForType of AccountTypePreferenceLoader.java, there is a possible way to disable apps for other users due to a confused depu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40657</link><description>In addPreferencesForType of AccountTypePreferenceLoader.java, there is a possible way to disable apps for other users due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40658 | In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40658</link><description>In getConfig of SoftVideoDecoderOMXComponent.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40659 | In getRegistration of RemoteProvisioningService.java, there is a possible way to permanently disable the AndroidKeyStore key generation feat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40659</link><description>In getRegistration of RemoteProvisioningService.java, there is a possible way to permanently disable the AndroidKeyStore key generation feature by updating the attestation keys of all installed apps due to improper input validation. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40662 | In scheme of Uri.java, there is a possible way to craft a malformed Uri object due to improper input validation. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40662</link><description>In scheme of Uri.java, there is a possible way to craft a malformed Uri object due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45597 | Pluto&amp;#x27;s http.request allows CR and LF in header values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45597</link><description>Pluto is a superset of Lua 5.4 with a focus on general-purpose programming. Scripts passing user-controlled values to http.request header values are affected. An attacker could use this to send arbitrary requests, potentially leveraging authentication tokens provided in the same headers table.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8322 | Weak authentication in Patch Management of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8322</link><description>Weak authentication in Patch Management of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote authenticated attacker to access restricted functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:22:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8441 | An uncontrolled search path in the agent of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a local authenticated attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8441</link><description>An uncontrolled search path in the agent of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a local authenticated attacker with admin privileges to escalate their privileges to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8191 | SQL injection in the management console of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8191</link><description>SQL injection in the management console of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8320 | Missing authentication in Network Isolation of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8320</link><description>Missing authentication in Network Isolation of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to spoof Network Isolation status of managed devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8321 | Missing authentication in Network Isolation of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8321</link><description>Missing authentication in Network Isolation of Ivanti EPM before 2022 SU6, or the 2024 September update allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to isolate managed devices from the network.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44105 | Cleartext transmission of sensitive information in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44105</link><description>Cleartext transmission of sensitive information in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to obtain OS credentials.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44106 | Insufficient server-side controls in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44106</link><description>Insufficient server-side controls in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44107 | DLL hijacking in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44107</link><description>DLL hijacking in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges and achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44103 | DLL hijacking in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44103</link><description>DLL hijacking in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44104 | An incorrectly implemented authentication scheme that is subjected to a spoofing attack in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Contro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44104</link><description>An incorrectly implemented authentication scheme that is subjected to a spoofing attack in the management console of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8012 | An authentication bypass weakness in the message broker service of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8012</link><description>An authentication bypass weakness in the message broker service of Ivanti Workspace Control version 10.18.0.0 and below allows a local authenticated attacker to escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:51:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8190 | An OS command injection vulnerability in Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance versions 4.6 Patch 518 and before allows a remote authenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8190</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance versions 4.6 Patch 518 and before allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain remote code execution. The attacker must have admin level privileges to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43040 | Renwoxing Enterprise Intelligent Management System before v3.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the parid paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43040</link><description>Renwoxing Enterprise Intelligent Management System before v3.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the parid parameter at /fx/baseinfo/SearchInfo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:17:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8232 | iniNet Solutions SpiderControl SCADA Web Server Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8232</link><description>SpiderControl SCADA Web Server has a vulnerability that could allow an 
attacker to upload specially crafted malicious files without 
authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8655 | Mercury MNVR816 web-static file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mercury MNVR816 up to 2.0.1.0.5. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /web-static/. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8504 | VICIdial Authenticated Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8504</link><description>An attacker with authenticated access to VICIdial as an "agent" can execute arbitrary shell commands as the "root" user. This attack can be chained with CVE-2024-8503 to execute arbitrary shell commands starting from an unauthenticated perspective.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8503 | VICIdial Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8503</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can leverage a time-based SQL injection vulnerability in VICIdial to enumerate database records. By default, VICIdial stores plaintext credentials within the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45409 | The Ruby SAML library vulnerable to a SAML authentication bypass via Incorrect XPath selector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45409</link><description>The Ruby SAML library is for implementing the client side of a SAML authorization. Ruby-SAML in &lt;= 12.2 and 1.13.0 &lt;= 1.16.0 does not properly verify the signature of the SAML Response. An unauthenticated attacker with access to any signed saml document (by the IdP) can thus forge a SAML Response/Assertion with arbitrary contents. This would allow the attacker to log in as arbitrary user within the vulnerable system. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.17.0 and 1.12.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45596 | Directus&amp;#x27;s session is cached for OpenID and OAuth2 if `redirect` is not used</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45596</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. An unauthenticated user can access credentials of last authenticated user via OpenID or OAuth2 where the authentication URL did not include redirect query string. This happens because on that endpoint for both OpenId and Oauth2 Directus is using the respond middleware, which by default will try to cache GET requests that met some conditions. Although, those conditions do not include this scenario, when an unauthenticated request returns user credentials. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.13.3 and 11.1.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34831 | cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gibbon Core v26.0.00 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the imageLink parameter in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34831</link><description>cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Gibbon Core v26.0.00 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the imageLink parameter in the library_manage_catalog_editProcess.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21416 | Windows TCP/IP Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21416</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26186 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26186</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26191 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26191</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30073 | Windows Security Zone Mapping Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30073</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37335 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37335</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37337 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37337</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37338 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37338</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37339 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37339</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37340 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37340</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37341 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37341</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37342 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37342</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37965 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37965</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37966 | Microsoft SQL Server Native Scoring Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37966</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37980 | Microsoft SQL Server Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37980</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38014 | Windows Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38014</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38018 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38018</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38045 | Windows TCP/IP Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38045</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38046 | PowerShell Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38046</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38119 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38119</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38188 | Azure Network Watcher VM Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38188</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38194 | Azure Web Apps Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38194</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38216 | Azure Stack Hub Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38216</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38217 | Windows Mark of the Web Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38217</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38220 | Azure Stack Hub Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38220</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38225 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38225</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38226 | Microsoft Publisher Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38226</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38227 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38227</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38228 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38228</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38230 | Windows Standards-Based Storage Management Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38230</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38231 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38231</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38232 | Windows Networking Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38232</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38233 | Windows Networking Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38233</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38234 | Windows Networking Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38234</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38235 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38235</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38236 | DHCP Server Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38236</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38237 | Kernel Streaming WOW Thunk Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38237</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38238 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38238</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38239 | Windows Kerberos Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38239</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38240 | Windows Remote Access Connection Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38240</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38241 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38241</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38242 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38242</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38243 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38243</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38244 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38244</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38245 | Kernel Streaming Service Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38245</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38246 | Win32k Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38246</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38247 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38247</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38248 | Windows Storage Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38248</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38249 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38249</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38250 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38250</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38252 | Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38252</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38253 | Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38253</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38254 | Windows Authentication Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38254</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38256 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38256</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38257 | Microsoft AllJoyn API Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38257</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38258 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38258</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38259 | Microsoft Management Console Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38259</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38260 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38260</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38263 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38263</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43454 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43454</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43455 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43455</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43457 | Windows Setup and Deployment Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43457</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43458 | Windows Networking Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43458</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43461 | Windows MSHTML Platform Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43461</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43463 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43463</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43464 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43464</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43465 | Microsoft Excel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43465</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43466 | Microsoft SharePoint Server Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43466</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43467 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43467</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43469 | Azure CycleCloud Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43469</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43470 | Azure Network Watcher VM Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43470</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43474 | Microsoft SQL Server Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43474</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43475 | Microsoft Windows Admin Center Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43475</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43476 | Microsoft Dynamics 365 (on-premises) Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43476</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43479 | Microsoft Power Automate Desktop Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43479</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43482 | Microsoft Outlook for iOS Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43482</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43487 | Windows Mark of the Web Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43487</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43491 | Microsoft Windows Update Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43491</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43492 | Microsoft AutoUpdate (MAU) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43492</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43495 | Windows libarchive Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43495</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44872 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in moziloCMS v3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44872</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in moziloCMS v3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44667 | Shenzhen Haichangxing Technology Co., Ltd HCX H822 4G LTE Router M7628NNxISPxUIv2_v1.0.1557.15.35_P0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Contr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44667</link><description>Shenzhen Haichangxing Technology Co., Ltd HCX H822 4G LTE Router M7628NNxISPxUIv2_v1.0.1557.15.35_P0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Unauthenticated factory mode reset and command injection leads to information exposure and root shell access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44871 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/index.php of moziloCMS v3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44871</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /admin/index.php of moziloCMS v3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6841 | Keycloak: amount of attributes per object is not limited and it may lead to dos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6841</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in keycloak where the amount of attributes per object is not limited,an attacker by sending repeated HTTP requests could cause a resource exhaustion when the application send back rows with long attribute values.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44893 | An issue in the component /jeecg-boot/jmreport/dict/list of JimuReport v1.7.8 allows attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted GET reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44893</link><description>An issue in the component /jeecg-boot/jmreport/dict/list of JimuReport v1.7.8 allows attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36103 | Command Injection vulnerability in goform/SetIPTVCfg interface of Tenda AC15 V15.03.05.20 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary commands ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36103</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability in goform/SetIPTVCfg interface of Tenda AC15 V15.03.05.20 allows remote attackers to run arbitrary commands via crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45595 | D-Tale allows Remote Code Execution through the Query input on Chart Builder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45595</link><description>D-Tale is a visualizer for Pandas data structures. Users hosting D-Tale publicly can be vulnerable to remote code execution allowing attackers to run malicious code on the server. Users should upgrade to version 3.14.1 where the "Custom Filter" input is turned off by default.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45590 | body-parser vulnerable to denial of service when url encoding is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45590</link><description>body-parser is Node.js body parsing middleware. body-parser &lt;1.20.3 is vulnerable to denial of service when url encoding is enabled. A malicious actor using a specially crafted payload could flood the server with a large number of requests, resulting in denial of service. This issue is patched in 1.20.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45591 | XWiki Platform document history including authors of any page exposed to unauthorized actors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45591</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform. The REST API exposes the history of any page in XWiki of which the attacker knows the name. The exposed information includes for each modification of the page the time of the modification, the version number, the author of the modification (both username and displayed name) and the version comment. This information is exposed regardless of the rights setup, and even when the wiki is configured to be fully private. On a private wiki, this can be tested by accessing /xwiki/rest/wikis/xwiki/spaces/Main/pages/WebHome/history, if this shows the history of the main page then the installation is vulnerable. This has been patched in XWiki 15.10.9 and XWiki 16.3.0RC1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45592 | auditor-bundle vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting because name of entity does not get escaped</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45592</link><description>auditor-bundle, formerly known as DoctrineAuditBundle, integrates auditor library into any Symfony 3.4+ application. Prior to 6.0.0, there is an unescaped entity property enabling Javascript injection. This is possible because %source_label% in twig macro is not escaped. Therefore script tags can be inserted and are executed. The vulnerability is fixed in 6.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45593 | Nix affected by unsafe NAR unpacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45593</link><description>Nix is a package manager for Linux and other Unix systems. A bug in Nix 2.24 prior to 2.24.6 allows a substituter or malicious user to craft a NAR that, when unpacked by Nix, causes Nix to write to arbitrary file system locations to which the Nix process has access. This will be with root permissions when using the Nix daemon. This issue is fixed in Nix 2.24.6.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:59:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37234 | Loftware Spectrum through 4.6 has unprotected JMX Registry.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37234</link><description>Loftware Spectrum through 4.6 has unprotected JMX Registry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44677 | eladmin v2.7 and before is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Datab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44677</link><description>eladmin v2.7 and before is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the DatabaseController.java component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37232 | Loftware Spectrum through 4.6 exposes Sensitive Information (Logs) to an Unauthorized Actor.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37232</link><description>Loftware Spectrum through 4.6 exposes Sensitive Information (Logs) to an Unauthorized Actor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37233 | Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 allows authenticated XXE attacks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37233</link><description>Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 allows authenticated XXE attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44676 | eladmin v2.7 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via LocalStoreControl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44676</link><description>eladmin v2.7 and before is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via LocalStoreController. java.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45412 | Yeti affected by a Potential Denial of Service due to the One Milion Unicode characters attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45412</link><description>Yeti bridges the gap between CTI and DFIR practitioners by providing a Forensics Intelligence platform and pipeline. Remote user-controlled data tags can reach a Unicode normalization with a compatibility form NFKD. Under Windows, such normalization is costly in resources and may lead to denial of service with attacks such as One Million Unicode payload. This can get worse with the use of special Unicode characters like U+2100 (℀), or U+2105 (℅) which could lead the payload size to be tripled. Versions prior to 2.1.11 are affected by this vulnerability. The patch is included in 2.1.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31960 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. The xclipse amdgpu driver has a reference count bug. This can ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31960</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1480, Exynos 2400. The xclipse amdgpu driver has a reference count bug. This can lead to a use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44815 | An issue in Hathway Skyworth Router CM5100 v.4.1.1.24 allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain sensitive information via SPI flash F...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44815</link><description>An issue in Hathway Skyworth Router CM5100 v.4.1.1.24 allows a physically proximate attacker to obtain sensitive information via SPI flash Firmware W25Q64JV</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45407 | Sunshine has incorrect state management during pairing process may lead to incorrectly authorized client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45407</link><description>Sunshine is a self-hosted game stream host for Moonlight. Clients that experience a MITM attack during the pairing process may inadvertantly allow access to an unintended client rather than failing authentication due to a PIN validation error. The pairing attempt fails due to the incorrect PIN, but the certificate from the forged pairing attempt is incorrectly persisted prior to the completion of the pairing request. This allows access to the certificate belonging to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6876 | Out-of-bounds read in OSCAT-Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6876</link><description>Out-of-Bounds read vulnerability in OSCAT Basic Library allows an local, unprivileged attacker to access limited internal data of the PLC which may lead to a crash of the affected service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25073 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Semiconductor Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, Exynos 9825, Exynos 980, Exy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25073</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Semiconductor Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, Exynos 9825, Exynos 980, Exynos 990, Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 2200, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, Exynos 1330, Exynos 9110, Exynos W920, Exynos W930, Exynos Modem 5123, Exynos Modem 5300. The baseband software does not properly check a pointer specified by the CC (Call Control module), which can lead to Denial of Service (Untrusted Pointer Dereference).</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45044 | Bareos&amp;#x27;s negative command ACLs can be circumvented by abbreviating commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45044</link><description>Bareos is open source software for backup, archiving, and recovery of data for operating systems. When a command ACL is in place and a user executes a command in bconsole using an abbreviation (i.e. "w" for "whoami") the ACL check did not apply to the full form (i.e. "whoami") but to the abbreviated form (i.e. "w"). If the command ACL is configured with negative ACL that should forbid using the "whoami" command, you could still use "w" or "who" as a command successfully. Fixes for the problem are shipped in Bareos versions 23.0.4, 22.1.6 and 21.1.11. If only positive command ACLs are used without any negation, the problem does not occur.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45393 | Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is missing authorization for endpoints related to webhook deliveries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45393</link><description>Computer Vision Annotation Tool (CVAT) is an interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. An attacker with a CVAT account can access webhook delivery information for any webhook registered on the CVAT instance, including that of other users. For each delivery, this contains information about the event that caused the delivery, typically including full details about the object on which an action was performed (such as the task for an "update:task" event), and the user who performed the action. In addition, the attacker can redeliver any past delivery of any webhook, and trigger a ping event for any webhook. Upgrade to CVAT 2.18.0 or any later version.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25074 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Semiconductor Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, Exynos 9825, Exynos 980, Exy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25074</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Semiconductor Mobile Processor, Automotive Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, Exynos 9825, Exynos 980, Exynos 990, Exynos 850, Exynos 1080, Exynos 2100, Exynos 2200, Exynos 1280, Exynos 1380, Exynos 1330, Exynos 9110, Exynos W920, Exynos W930, Exynos Modem 5123, Exynos Modem 5300. The baseband software does not properly check a pointer specified by the SM (Session Management module), which can lead to Denial of Service (Untrusted Pointer Dereference).</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42423 | Citrix Workspace App version 23.9.0.24.4 on Dell ThinOS 2311 contains an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability when Citrix CEB is enabled fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42423</link><description>Citrix Workspace App version 23.9.0.24.4 on Dell ThinOS 2311 contains an Incorrect Authorization vulnerability when Citrix CEB is enabled for WebLogin. A local unauthenticated user with low privileges may potentially exploit this vulnerability to bypass existing controls and perform unauthorized actions leading to information disclosure and tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43800 | serve-static affected by template injection that can lead to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43800</link><description>serve-static serves static files. serve-static passes untrusted user input - even after sanitizing it - to redirect() may execute untrusted code. This issue is patched in serve-static 1.16.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43799 | send vulnerable to template injection that can lead to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43799</link><description>Send is a library for streaming files from the file system as a http response. Send passes untrusted user input to SendStream.redirect() which executes untrusted code. This issue is patched in send 0.19.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45856 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiClientWindows 6.4 all versions, 7.0.0 through 7.0.7, FortiClientMac 6.4 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45856</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiClientWindows 6.4 all versions, 7.0.0 through 7.0.7, FortiClientMac 6.4 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, FortiClientLinux 6.4 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, FortiClientAndroid 6.4 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 7.2.0 and FortiClientiOS 5.6 all versions, 6.0.0 through 6.0.1, 7.0.0 through 7.0.6 SAML SSO feature may allow an unauthenticated attacker to man-in-the-middle the communication between the FortiClient and  both the service provider and the identity provider.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44254 | An authorization bypass through user-controlled key [CWE-639] vulnerability in FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.1 and before 7.2.5 and FortiManager...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44254</link><description>An authorization bypass through user-controlled key [CWE-639] vulnerability in FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.1 and before 7.2.5 and FortiManager version 7.4.1 and before 7.2.5 may allow a remote attacker with low privileges to read sensitive data via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21753 | A improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('path traversal') in Fortinet FortiClientEMS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21753</link><description>A improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('path traversal') in Fortinet FortiClientEMS versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, 6.4.0 through 6.4.9, 6.2.0 through 6.2.9, 6.0.0 through 6.0.8, 1.2.1 through 1.2.5 allows attacker to perform a denial of service, read or write a limited number of files via specially crafted HTTP requests</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23184 | Having a large number of address headers (From, To, Cc, Bcc, etc.) becomes excessively CPU intensive. With 100k header lines CPU usage is al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23184</link><description>Having a large number of address headers (From, To, Cc, Bcc, etc.) becomes excessively CPU intensive. With 100k header lines CPU usage is already 12 seconds, and in a production environment we observed 500k header lines taking 18 minutes to parse. Since this can be triggered by external actors sending emails to a victim, this is a security issue. An external attacker can send specially crafted messages that consume target system resources and cause outage. One can implement restrictions on address headers on MTA component preceding Dovecot. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23185 | Very large headers can cause resource exhaustion when parsing message. The message-parser normally reads reasonably sized chunks of the mess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23185</link><description>Very large headers can cause resource exhaustion when parsing message. The message-parser normally reads reasonably sized chunks of the message. However, when it feeds them to message-header-parser, it starts building up "full_value" buffer out of the smaller chunks. The full_value buffer has no size limit, so large headers can cause large memory usage. It doesn't matter whether it's a single long header line, or a single header split into multiple lines. This bug exists in all Dovecot versions. Incoming mails typically have some size limits set by MTA, so even largest possible header size may still fit into Dovecot's vsz_limit. So attackers probably can't DoS a victim user this way. A user could APPEND larger mails though, allowing them to DoS themselves (although maybe cause some memory issues for the backend in general). One can implement restrictions on headers on MTA component preceding Dovecot. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31489 | AAn improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11,  FortiClientLin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31489</link><description>AAn improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.2, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11,  FortiClientLinux 7.2.0, 7.0.0 through 7.0.11 and FortiClientMac 7.0.0 through 7.0.11, 7.2.0 through 7.2.4 may allow a remote and unauthenticated attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack on the communication channel between the FortiGate and the FortiClient during the ZTNA tunnel creation</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31490 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 4.4.0 through 4.4.4 and 4.2.0 through 4.2.6 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31490</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor in Fortinet FortiSandbox version 4.4.0 through 4.4.4 and 4.2.0 through 4.2.6 and 4.0.0 through 4.0.5 and 3.2.2 through 3.2.4 and 3.1.5 allows attacker to information disclosure via HTTP get requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33508 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-77] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS 7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33508</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-77] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS 7.2.0 through 7.2.4, 7.0.0 through 7.0.12 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute limited and temporary operations on the underlying database via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35282 | A cleartext storage of sensitive information in memory vulnerability [CWE-316] affecting FortiClient VPN iOS 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35282</link><description>A cleartext storage of sensitive information in memory vulnerability [CWE-316] affecting FortiClient VPN iOS 7.2 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.4 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.0 all versions may allow an unauthenticated attacker that has physical access to a jailbroken device to obtain cleartext passwords via keychain dump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36511 | An improperly implemented security check for standard vulnerability [CWE-358] in FortiADC Web Application Firewall (WAF) 7.4.0 through 7.4.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36511</link><description>An improperly implemented security check for standard vulnerability [CWE-358] in FortiADC Web Application Firewall (WAF) 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, 7.2 all versions, 7.1 all versions, 7.0 all versions, 6.2 all versions, 6.1 all versions, 6.0 all versions when cookie security policy is enabled may allow an attacker, under specific conditions, to retrieve the initial encrypted and signed cookie protected by the feature</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43796 | express vulnerable to XSS via response.redirect()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43796</link><description>Express.js minimalist web framework for node. In express &lt; 4.20.0, passing untrusted user input - even after sanitizing it - to response.redirect() may execute untrusted code. This issue is patched in express 4.20.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45323 | An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiEDR Manager API 6.2.0 through 6.2.2, 6.0 all versions may allow in a shared envir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45323</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability [CWE-284] in FortiEDR Manager API 6.2.0 through 6.2.2, 6.0 all versions may allow in a shared environment context an authenticated admin with REST API permissions in his profile and restricted to a specific organization to access backend logs that include information related to other organizations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27257 | IBM OpenPages information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27257</link><description>IBM OpenPages 8.3 and 9.0 potentially exposes information about client-side source code through use of JavaScript source maps to unauthorized users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37230 | Loftware Spectrum (testDeviceConnection) before 5.1 allows SSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37230</link><description>Loftware Spectrum (testDeviceConnection) before 5.1 allows SSRF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37231 | Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 uses a Hard-coded Password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37231</link><description>Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 uses a Hard-coded Password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37229 | Loftware Spectrum before 5.1 allows SSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37229</link><description>Loftware Spectrum before 5.1 allows SSRF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37226 | Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 has Missing Authentication for a Critical Function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37226</link><description>Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF14 has Missing Authentication for a Critical Function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37227 | Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF13 Deserializes Untrusted Data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37227</link><description>Loftware Spectrum before 4.6 HF13 Deserializes Untrusted Data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37728 | Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in Xi'an Daxi Information Technology Co., Ltd OfficeWeb365 v.7.18.23.0 and v8.6.1.0 allows a remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37728</link><description>Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in Xi'an Daxi Information Technology Co., Ltd OfficeWeb365 v.7.18.23.0 and v8.6.1.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the "Pic/Indexes" interface</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8654 | MongoDB Server may access non-initialized region of memory leading to unexpected behaviour</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8654</link><description>MongoDB Server may access non-initialized region of memory leading to unexpected behaviour when zero arguments are called in internal aggregation stage. This issue affected MongoDB Server v6.0 version 6.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44867 | phpok v3.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the component /autoload/file.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44867</link><description>phpok v3.0 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the component /autoload/file.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8443 | Libopensc: heap buffer overflow in openpgp driver when generating key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8443</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability was found in the libopensc OpenPGP driver. A crafted USB device or smart card with malicious responses to the APDUs during the card enrollment process using the `pkcs15-init` tool may lead to out-of-bound rights, possibly resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6282 | Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.0.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via data-jltma-wrapper-link Element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6282</link><description>The Master Addons – Free Widgets, Hover Effects, Toggle, Conditions, Animations for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-jltma-wrapper-link element in all versions up to, and including 2.0.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user-supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user clicks on the injected link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8369 | EventPrime &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Private or Password-Protected Events Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8369</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access to Private or Password-protected events due to missing authorization checks in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view private or password-protected events.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45845 | nix 2.24 through 2.24.5 allows directory traversal via a symlink in a nar file, because of mishandling of a directory containing a symlink a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45845</link><description>nix 2.24 through 2.24.5 allows directory traversal via a symlink in a nar file, because of mishandling of a directory containing a symlink and a directory of the same name, aka GHSA-h4vv-h3jq-v493.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7770 | Bit File Manager – 100% Free &amp;amp; Open Source File Manager and Code Editor for WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.5.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7770</link><description>The Bit File Manager – 100% Free &amp; Open Source File Manager and Code Editor for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, and granted upload permissions by an administrator, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40754 | Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Escarg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40754</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Samsung Open Source Escargot JavaScript engine allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects Escargot: 4.0.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:58:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8645 | Access of Uninitialized Pointer in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8645</link><description>SPRT dissector crash in Wireshark 4.2.0 to 4.0.5 and 4.0.0 to 4.0.15 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:21:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28827 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28827</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 DNP3 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 IEC (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-7 LTE (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-8 IRC (6GK7243-8RX30-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagBase (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagMonitor (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions), SIPLUS TIM 1531 IRC (6AG1543-1MX00-7XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8), TIM 1531 IRC (6GK7543-1MX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8). The web server of the affected devices do not properly handle certain requests, causing a timeout in the watchdog, which could lead to the clean up of pointers. 

This could allow a remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition in the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30755 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30755</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 DNP3 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 IEC (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-7 LTE (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-8 IRC (6GK7243-8RX30-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagBase (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagMonitor (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions), SIPLUS TIM 1531 IRC (6AG1543-1MX00-7XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8), TIM 1531 IRC (6GK7543-1MX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8). The web server of the affected devices do not properly handle the shutdown or reboot request, which could lead to the clean up of certain resources. 

This could allow a remote attacker with elevated privileges to cause a denial of service condition in the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30756 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLU...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30756</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC CP 1242-7 V2 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 DNP3 (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-1 IEC (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-7 LTE (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC CP 1243-8 IRC (6GK7243-8RX30-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V3.5.20), SIMATIC HMI Comfort Panels (incl. SIPLUS variants) (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagBase (All versions), SIMATIC IPC DiagMonitor (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Advanced (All versions), SIPLUS TIM 1531 IRC (6AG1543-1MX00-7XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8), TIM 1531 IRC (6GK7543-1MX00-0XE0) (All versions &lt; V2.4.8). The web server of the affected devices do not properly handle certain errors when using the Expect HTTP request header, resulting in NULL dereference.

This could allow a remote attacker with no privileges to cause a denial of service condition in the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49069 | A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix Runtime V10 (All versions &lt; V10.14.0 only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49069</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Mendix Runtime V10 (All versions &lt; V10.14.0 only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the application), Mendix Runtime V10.12 (All versions &lt; V10.12.2 only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the application), Mendix Runtime V10.6 (All versions &lt; V10.6.12 only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the application), Mendix Runtime V8 (All versions only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the application), Mendix Runtime V9 (All versions &lt; V9.24.26 only if the basic authentication mechanism is used by the application). The authentication mechanism of affected applications contains an observable response discrepancy vulnerability when validating usernames. This could allow unauthenticated remote attackers to distinguish between valid and invalid usernames.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32006 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Client (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application does not expire the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32006</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Client (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application does not expire the user session on reboot without logout. This could allow an attacker to bypass Multi-Factor Authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33698 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Information Server 2022 (All versions), SIMATIC Information Server 2024 (All versions), SIMAT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33698</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Information Server 2022 (All versions), SIMATIC Information Server 2024 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V4.0 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS neo V4.1 (All versions &lt; V4.1 Update 2), SIMATIC PCS neo V5.0 (All versions), SINEC NMS (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V16 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V17 (All versions &lt; V17 Update 8), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V18 (All versions), Totally Integrated Automation Portal (TIA Portal) V19 (All versions). Affected products contain a heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the integrated UMC component. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35783 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Information Server 2020 (All versions), SIMATIC Informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35783</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC BATCH V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Information Server 2020 (All versions), SIMATIC Information Server 2022 (All versions), SIMATIC PCS 7 V9.1 (All versions), SIMATIC Process Historian 2020 (All versions), SIMATIC Process Historian 2022 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V18 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC Runtime Professional V19 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.4 (All versions), SIMATIC WinCC V7.5 (All versions &lt; V7.5 SP2 Update 18), SIMATIC WinCC V8.0 (All versions &lt; V8.0 Update 5). The affected products run their DB server with elevated privileges which could allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands with administrative privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37990 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37990</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The affected applications contain configuration files which can be modified. An attacker with privilege access can modify these files and enable features that are not released for this device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37991 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37991</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The service log files of the affected application can be accessed without proper authentication. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to get access to sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37992 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37992</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The affected devices does not properly handle the error in case of exceeding characters while setting SNMP leading to the restart of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37993 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37993</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The affected applications do not authenticated the creation of Ajax2App instances. This could allow an unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37994 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37994</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The affected application contains a hidden configuration item to enable debug functionality. This could allow an attacker to gain insight into the internal configuration of the deployment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37995 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37995</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC Reader RF610R CMIIT (6GT2811-6BC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R ETSI (6GT2811-6BC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF610R FCC (6GT2811-6BC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CC10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R ETSI (6GT2811-6CC10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF615R FCC (6GT2811-6CC10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ARIB (6GT2811-6AB20-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AB20-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R ETSI (6GT2811-6AB20-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF650R FCC (6GT2811-6AB20-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ARIB (6GT2811-6AA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R CMIIT (6GT2811-6AA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R ETSI (6GT2811-6AA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF680R FCC (6GT2811-6AA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ARIB (6GT2811-6CA10-4AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R CMIIT (6GT2811-6CA10-2AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R ETSI (6GT2811-6CA10-0AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC Reader RF685R FCC (6GT2811-6CA10-1AA0) (All versions &lt; V4.2), SIMATIC RF1140R (6GT2831-6CB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF1170R (6GT2831-6BB00) (All versions &lt; V1.1), SIMATIC RF166C (6GT2002-0EE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF185C (6GT2002-0JE10) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186C (6GT2002-0JE20) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF186CI (6GT2002-0JE50) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188C (6GT2002-0JE40) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF188CI (6GT2002-0JE60) (All versions &lt; V2.2), SIMATIC RF360R (6GT2801-5BA30) (All versions &lt; V2.2). The affected application improperly handles error while a faulty certificate upload leading to crashing of application. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to disclose sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41170 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0015), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41170</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0015), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0004). The affected applications contain a stack based overflow vulnerability while parsing specially crafted SPP files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41171 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V5 (All versions &lt; V5.24), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41171</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4 (All versions), SINUMERIK 828D V5 (All versions &lt; V5.24), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4 (All versions), SINUMERIK ONE (All versions &lt; V6.24). Affected devices do not properly enforce access restrictions to scripts that are regularly executed by the system with elevated privileges. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to escalate their privileges in the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42344 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Client (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application inserts sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42344</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Client (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application inserts sensitive information into a log file which is readable by all legitimate users of the underlying system. This could allow an authenticated attacker to compromise the confidentiality of other users' configuration data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42345 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Server (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application does not properly ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42345</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEMA Remote Connect Server (All versions &lt; V3.2 SP2). The affected application does not properly handle user session establishment and invalidation. This could allow a remote attacker to circumvent the additional multi factor authentication for user session establishment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43647 | A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU CR40 (6ES7288-1CR40-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU CR60 (6ES...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43647</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU CR40 (6ES7288-1CR40-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU CR60 (6ES7288-1CR60-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR20 (6ES7288-1SR20-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR20 (6ES7288-1SR20-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR30 (6ES7288-1SR30-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR30 (6ES7288-1SR30-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR40 (6ES7288-1SR40-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR40 (6ES7288-1SR40-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR60 (6ES7288-1SR60-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU SR60 (6ES7288-1SR60-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST20 (6ES7288-1ST20-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST20 (6ES7288-1ST20-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST30 (6ES7288-1ST30-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST30 (6ES7288-1ST30-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST40 (6ES7288-1ST40-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST40 (6ES7288-1ST40-0AA1) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST60 (6ES7288-1ST60-0AA0) (All versions), SIMATIC S7-200 SMART CPU ST60 (6ES7288-1ST60-0AA1) (All versions). Affected devices do not properly handle TCP packets with an incorrect structure. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause a denial of service condition. To restore normal operations, the network cable of the device needs to be unplugged and re-plugged.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43781 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4 (All versions &lt; V4.95 SP3), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4 (All versions &lt; V4.95 SP3 in conne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43781</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINUMERIK 828D V4 (All versions &lt; V4.95 SP3), SINUMERIK 840D sl V4 (All versions &lt; V4.95 SP3 in connection with using Create MyConfig (CMC) &lt;= V4.8 SP1 HF6), SINUMERIK ONE (All versions &lt; V6.23 in connection with using Create MyConfig (CMC) &lt;= V6.6), SINUMERIK ONE (All versions &lt; V6.15 SP4 in connection with using Create MyConfig (CMC) &lt;= V6.6). Affected systems, that have been provisioned with Create MyConfig (CMC), contain a Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. This could allow a local authenticated user with low privileges to read sensitive information and thus circumvent access restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44087 | A vulnerability has been identified in Automation License Manager V5 (All versions), Automation License Manager V6.0 (All versions), Automat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44087</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Automation License Manager V5 (All versions), Automation License Manager V6.0 (All versions), Automation License Manager V6.2 (All versions &lt; V6.2 Upd3). Affected applications do not properly validate certain fields in incoming network packets on port 4410/tcp. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to cause an integer overflow and crash of the application. This denial of service condition could prevent legitimate users from using subsequent products that rely on the affected application for license verification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45032 | A vulnerability has been identified in Industrial Edge Management Pro (All versions &lt; V1.9.5), Industrial Edge Management Virtual (All versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45032</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Industrial Edge Management Pro (All versions &lt; V1.9.5), Industrial Edge Management Virtual (All versions &lt; V2.3.1-1). Affected components do not properly validate the device tokens. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to impersonate other devices onboarded to the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2919 | Tutor LMS &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;addon_enable_disable&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2919</link><description>The Tutor LMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.7.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'addon_enable_disable' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable or disable addons via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8241 | Nova Blocks by Pixelgrade &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8241</link><description>The Nova Blocks by Pixelgrade plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'align' attribute of the 'wp:separator' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8543 | Slider comparison image before and after &amp;lt;= 0.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8543</link><description>The Slider comparison image before and after plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's [sciba] shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39574 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.1, contain an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39574</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.1, contain an Improper Privilege Management vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:26:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39582 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.0, contain a Use of hard coded Credentials vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39582</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, version 5.0, contain a Use of hard coded Credentials vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:26:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39580 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39580</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39581 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains a File or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. An unauthe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39581</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains a File or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read, modify, and delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39583 | Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability. An unauthent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39583</link><description>Dell PowerScale InsightIQ, versions 5.0 through 5.1, contains a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43387 | Phoenix Contact: Access files due to improper neutralization of special elements in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43387</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can read and write files as root due to improper neutralization of special elements in the variable EMAIL_RELAY_PASSWORD in mGuard devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43388 | Phoenix Contact: SNMP reconfiguration due to improper input validation in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43388</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker with write permissions can reconfigure the SNMP service due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43389 | Phoenix Contact: OSPF reconfiguration due to improper input validation in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43389</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can perform configuration changes of the ospf service through OSPF_INTERFACE.SIMPLE_KEY, OSPF_INTERFACE.DIGEST_KEY environment variables which can lead to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43390 | Phoenix Contact: Firewall reconfiguration due to improper input validation in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43390</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can perform configuration changes of the firewall services, including packet forwarding or NAT through the FW_NAT.IN_IP environment variable which can lead to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43391 | Phoenix Contact: Firewall reconfiguration through the FW_PORTFORWARDING.SRC_IP in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43391</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can perform configuration changes of the firewall services, including packet filter, packet forwarding, network access control or NAT through the FW_PORTFORWARDING.SRC_IP environment variable which can lead to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43392 | Phoenix Contact: Firewall reconfiguration through the FW_environment variables  in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43392</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can perform configuration changes of the firewall services, including packet filter, packet forwarding, network access control or NAT through the FW_INCOMING.FROM_IP FW_INCOMING.IN_IP FW_OUTGOING.FROM_IP FW_OUTGOING.IN_IP  environment variable which can lead to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43393 | Phoenix Contact: Configuration changes of the firewall services can lead to DoS in MGUARD devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43393</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can perform configuration changes of the firewall services, including packet filter, packet forwarding, network access control or NAT through the FW_INCOMING.FROM_IP FW_INCOMING.IN_IP FW_OUTGOING.FROM_IP FW_OUTGOING.IN_IP FW_RULESETS.FROM_IP FW_RULESETS.IN_IP  environment variable which can lead to a DoS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43385 | Phoenix Contact: OS command execution through PROXY_HTTP_PORT in mGuard devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43385</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can trigger the execution of arbitrary OS commands as root due to improper neutralization of special elements in the variable PROXY_HTTP_PORT in mGuard devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43386 | Phoenix Contact: OS command execution through EMAIL_NOTIFICATION.TO in mGuard devices.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43386</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can trigger the execution of arbitrary OS commands as root due to improper neutralization of special elements in the variable EMAIL_NOTIFICATION.TO in mGuard devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:51:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7698 | Phoenix Contact: Access to CSRF tokens of higher privileged users in MGUARD products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7698</link><description>A low privileged remote attacker can get access to CSRF tokens of higher privileged users which can be abused to mount CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7699 | Phoenix Contact: OS command execution in MGUARD products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7699</link><description>An low privileged remote attacker can execute OS commands with root privileges due to improper neutralization of special elements in user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8258 | Insecure Electron Fuses in Logitech Options Plus Allowing Arbitrary Code Execution on macOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8258</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') in Electron Fuses in Logitech Options Plus version 1.60.496306 on macOS allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via insecure Electron Fuses configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42425 | Dell Precision Rack, 14G Intel BIOS versions prior to 2.22.2, contains an Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability. A low...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42425</link><description>Dell Precision Rack, 14G Intel BIOS versions prior to 2.22.2, contains an Access of Memory Location After End of Buffer vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42424 | Dell Precision Rack, 14G Intel BIOS versions prior to 2.22.2, contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A high privileged attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42424</link><description>Dell Precision Rack, 14G Intel BIOS versions prior to 2.22.2, contains an Improper Input Validation vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6596 | Endress+Hauser: Multiple products are vulnerable to code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6596</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can run malicious c# code included in curve files and execute commands in the users context.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7734 | Phoenix Contact: Multiple mGuard devices are vulnerable to a drain of open file descriptors.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7734</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit the behavior of the pathfinder TCP encapsulation service by establishing a high number of TCP connections to the pathfinder TCP encapsulation service. The impact is limited to blocking of valid IPsec VPN peers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42427 | Dell ThinOS versions 2402 and 2405, contains an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42427</link><description>Dell ThinOS versions 2402 and 2405, contains an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with physical access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 07:48:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7618 | Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles &amp;lt;= 6.4.5.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via content Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7618</link><description>The Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘content’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 07:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7655 | Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles &amp;lt;= 6.4.5.0 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7655</link><description>The Community by PeepSo – Social Network, Membership, Registration, User Profiles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 07:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44072 | OS command injection vulnerability exists in BUFFALO wireless LAN routers and wireless LAN repeaters. If a user logs in to the management pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44072</link><description>OS command injection vulnerability exists in BUFFALO wireless LAN routers and wireless LAN repeaters. If a user logs in to the management page and sends a specially crafted request to the affected product from the product's specific management page, an arbitrary OS command may be executed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 07:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7891 | Floating Contact Button &amp;lt; 2.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7891</link><description>The Floating Contact Button WordPress plugin before 2.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 06:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7955 | Starbox &amp;lt; 3.5.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7955</link><description>The Starbox  WordPress plugin before 3.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 06:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6979 | Amin Aliakbari, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found a broken access control which would lead to less-privileged operator- an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6979</link><description>Amin Aliakbari, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found a broken access control which would lead to less-privileged operator- and/or viewer accounts having more privileges than designed. The risk of exploitation is very low as it requires complex steps to execute, including knowing of account passwords and social engineering attacks in tricking the administrator to perform specific configurations on operator- and/or viewer-privileged accounts. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS a version for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7784 | During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7784</link><description>During internal Axis Security Development Model (ASDM) threat-modelling, a flaw was found in the protection for device tampering (commonly known as Secure Boot) in AXIS OS making it vulnerable to a sophisticated attack to bypass this protection. To Axis' knowledge, there are no known exploits of the vulnerability at this time. Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21528 | All versions of the package node-gettext are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the addTranslations() function in gettext.js due to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21528</link><description>All versions of the package node-gettext are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the addTranslations() function in gettext.js due to improper user input sanitization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45284 | Missing authorization check in SAP Student Life Cycle Management (SLcM)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45284</link><description>An authenticated attacker with high privilege can use functions of SLCM transactions to which access should be restricted. This may result in an escalation of privileges causing low impact on integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45285 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45285</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to perform denial of service on any user and also change or delete favourite nodes. By sending a crafted packet in the function module targeting specific parameters, the specific targeted user will no longer have access to any functionality of SAP GUI. There is low impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6173 | 51l3nc3, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that a Guard Tour VAPIX API parameter allowed the use of arbitrary values allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6173</link><description>51l3nc3, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that a Guard Tour VAPIX API parameter allowed the use of arbitrary values allowing for an attacker to block access to the guard tour configuration page in the web interface of the Axis device. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6509 | Marinus Pfund, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, 
has found the VAPIX API alwaysmulti.cgi was vulnerable for file globbing which cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6509</link><description>Marinus Pfund, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, 
has found the VAPIX API alwaysmulti.cgi was vulnerable for file globbing which could lead to resource exhaustion of the Axis device. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0067 | Marinus Pfund, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, 
has found the VAPIX API ledlimit.cgi was vulnerable for path traversal attacks all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0067</link><description>Marinus Pfund, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, 
has found the VAPIX API ledlimit.cgi was vulnerable for path traversal attacks allowing to list folder/file names on the local file system of the Axis device. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45283 | Information disclosure vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS for Java (Destination Service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45283</link><description>SAP NetWeaver AS for Java allows an authorized attacker to obtain sensitive information. The attacker could obtain the username and password when creating an RFC destination. After successful exploitation, an attacker can read the sensitive information but cannot modify or delete the data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 05:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45281 | DLL hijacking vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45281</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform allows a high privilege user to run client desktop applications even if some of the DLLs are not digitally signed or if the signature is broken. The attacker needs to have local access to the vulnerable system to perform DLL related tasks. This could result in a high impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45504 | Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in multiple Alps System Integration products and the OEM products allow a remote unauthentic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45504</link><description>Cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in multiple Alps System Integration products and the OEM products allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to hijack the authentication of the user and to perform unintended operations if the user views a malicious page while logged in.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:50:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44117 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44117</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to perform various actions, such as modifying the URLs of any user's favourite nodes and workbook ID. There is low impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44120 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44120</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal is vulnerable to reflected cross site scripting due to insufficient encoding of user-controlled input. An unauthenticated attacker could craft a malicious URL and trick a user to click it. If the victim clicks on this crafted URL before it times out, then the attacker could read and manipulate user content in the browser.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44121 | Information Disclosure in SAP S/4 HANA (Statutory Reports)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44121</link><description>Under certain conditions Statutory Reports in SAP S/4 HANA allows an attacker with basic privileges to access information which would otherwise be restricted. The vulnerability could expose internal user data that should remain confidential. It does not impact the integrity and availability of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45279 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP (CRM Blueprint Application Builder Panel)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45279</link><description>Due to insufficient input validation, CRM Blueprint Application Builder Panel of SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a URL link which could embed a malicious JavaScript. When a victim clicks on this link, the script will be executed in the victim's browser giving the attacker the ability to access and/or modify information with no effect on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45280 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver AS Java (Logon Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45280</link><description>Due to insufficient encoding of user-controlled inputs, SAP NetWeaver AS Java allows malicious scripts to be executed in the login application. This has a limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application. There is no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41728 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41728</link><description>Due to missing authorization check, SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an attacker logged in as a developer to read objects contained in a package. This causes an impact on confidentiality, as this attacker would otherwise not have access to view these objects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44112 | Missing Authorization check in SAP for Oil &amp;amp; Gas (Transportation and Distribution)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44112</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP for Oil &amp; Gas (Transportation and Distribution), an attacker authenticated as a non-administrative user could call a remote-enabled function which will allow them to delete non-sensitive entries in a user data table. There is no effect on confidentiality or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45286 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Production and Revenue Accounting (Tobin interface)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45286</link><description>Due to lack of proper authorization checks when calling user, a function module in obsolete Tobin interface in SAP Production and Revenue Accounting allows unauthorized access that could lead to disclosure of highly sensitive data. There is no impact on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44113 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in the SAP Business Warehouse (BEx Analyzer)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44113</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP Business Warehouse (BEx Analyzer) allows an authenticated attacker to access information over the network which is otherwise restricted. On successful exploitation the attacker can enumerate information causing a limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44114 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44114</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform allow users with high privileges to execute a program that reveals data over the network. This results in a minimal impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44115 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44115</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to add URLs to any user's workplace favourites. This vulnerability could be utilized to identify usernames and access information about targeted user's workplaces, and nodes. There is low impact on integrity of the application</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44116 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44116</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to add any workbook to any user's workplace favourites. This vulnerability could be utilized to identify usernames and access information about targeted user's workplaces. There is low impact on integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41729 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in the SAP NetWeaver BW (BEx Analyzer)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41729</link><description>Due to missing authorization checks, SAP BEx Analyzer allows an authenticated attacker to access information over the network which is otherwise restricted. On successful exploitation the attacker can enumerate information causing a limited impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:59:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42371 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42371</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to delete the workplace favourites of any user. This vulnerability could be utilized to identify usernames and access information about targeted user's workplaces and nodes. There is low impact on integrity and availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42378 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in eProcurement on S/4HANA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42378</link><description>Due to weak encoding of user-controlled inputs, eProcurement on SAP S/4HANA allows malicious scripts to be executed in the application, potentially leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This has no impact on the availability of the application, but it can have some minor impact on its confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42380 | Multiple vulnerabilities in SAP NetWeaver Application Server for ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42380</link><description>The RFC enabled function module allows a low privileged user to read any user's workplace favourites and user menu along with all the specific data of each node. Usernames can be enumerated by exploiting vulnerability. There is low impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:59:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8268 | Frontend Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Function Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8268</link><description>The Frontend Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized code execution due to insufficient filtering on callable methods/functions via the ajax_request() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to call arbitrary functions that can be leverage for privilege escalation by changing user's passwords.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:37:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8478 | Affiliate Super Assistent &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8478</link><description>The The Affiliate Super Assistent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3. This is due to the software allowing users to supply arbitrary shortcodes in comments when the 'Parse comments' option is enabled. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6342 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED** A command injection vulnerability in the export-cgi program of Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions through V5.21(AA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6342</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED** A command injection vulnerability in the export-cgi program of Zyxel NAS326 firmware versions through V5.21(AAZF.18)C0 and NAS542 firmware versions through V5.21(ABAG.15)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some operating system (OS) commands by sending a crafted HTTP POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 02:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38270 | An insufficient entropy vulnerability caused by the improper use of a randomness function with low entropy for web authentication tokens gen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38270</link><description>An insufficient entropy vulnerability caused by the improper use of a randomness function with low entropy for web authentication tokens generation exists in the Zyxel GS1900-10HP firmware version V2.80(AAZI.0)C0. This vulnerability could allow a LAN-based attacker a slight chance to gain a valid session token if multiple authenticated sessions are alive.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>