<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:39:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-1944 | picklescan ZIP archive manipulation attack leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1944</link><description>picklescan before 0.0.23 is vulnerable to a ZIP archive manipulation attack that causes it to crash when attempting to extract and scan PyTorch model archives. By modifying the filename in the ZIP header while keeping the original filename in the directory listing, an attacker can make PickleScan raise a BadZipFile error. However, PyTorch's more forgiving ZIP implementation still allows the model to be loaded, enabling malicious payloads to bypass detection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2147 | Beijing Zhide Intelligent Internet Technology Modern Farm Digital Integrated Management System file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2147</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Zhide Intelligent Internet Technology Modern Farm Digital Integrated Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to files or directories accessible. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple endpoints are affected. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13918 | Laravel Reflected XSS via Request Parameter in Debug-Mode Error Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13918</link><description>The Laravel framework versions between 11.9.0 and 11.35.1 are susceptible to reflected cross-site scripting due to an improper encoding of request parameters in the debug-mode error page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13919 | Laravel Reflected XSS via Route Parameter in Debug-Mode Error Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13919</link><description>The Laravel framework versions between 11.9.0 and 11.35.1 are susceptible to reflected cross-site scripting due to an improper encoding of route parameters in the debug-mode error page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 10:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24387 | Missing CSRF protection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24387</link><description>A vulnerability in OTRS Application Server allows session hijacking due to missing attributes for sensitive 
cookie settings in HTTPS sessions. A request to an OTRS endpoint from a possible malicious web site, would send the authentication cookie, performing an unwanted read operation.
 

This issue affects:

  *  OTRS 7.0.X
  *  OTRS 8.0.X
  *  OTRS 2023.X
  *  OTRS 2024.X
  *  OTRS 2025.x</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27253 | An improper input validation in GE Vernova UR IED family devices from version 7.0 up to 8.60 allows an attacker to provide input that enstab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27253</link><description>An improper input validation in GE Vernova UR IED family devices from version 7.0 up to 8.60 allows an attacker to provide input that enstablishes a TCP connection through a port forwarding. The lack of the IP address and port validation may allow the attacker to bypass firewall rules or to send malicious traffic in the network</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27254 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Authentication Bypass. 
The software's startup authentication ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27254</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Authentication Bypass. 
The software's startup authentication can be disabled by altering a Windows registry setting that any user can modify.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27255 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Privilege Escalation. The local user database is encrypt...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27255</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in GE Vernova EnerVista UR Setup allows Privilege Escalation. The local user database is encrypted using an hardcoded password retrievable by an attacker analyzing the application code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27256 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in GE Vernova Enervista UR Setup application allows Authentication Bypass due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27256</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in GE Vernova Enervista UR Setup application allows Authentication Bypass due to a missing SSH server authentication. Since the client connection is not authenticated, an attacker may perform a man-in-the-middle attack on the network.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27257 | Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in GE Vernova UR IED family devices allows an authenticated user to install a m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27257</link><description>Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in GE Vernova UR IED family devices allows an authenticated user to install a modified firmware.
The firmware signature verification is enforced only on the client-side dedicated software Enervista UR Setup, allowing the integration check to be bypassed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2150 | HGiga C&amp;amp;Cm@il - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2150</link><description>The C&amp;amp;Cm@il from HGiga has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to send emails containing malicious JavaScript code, which will be executed in the recipient's browser when they view the email.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 07:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11638 | Gtbabel &amp;lt; 6.6.9 - Unauthenticated Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11638</link><description>The Gtbabel WordPress plugin before 6.6.9 does not ensure that the URL to perform code analysis upon belongs to the blog which could allow unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a logged in user (such as admin) cookies by making them open a crafted URL as the request made to analysed the URL contains such cookies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 06:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1926 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) To Post Contents Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1926</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the pagelayer_save_post function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify post contents via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 04:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41724 | Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Command Centre SALTO integration allowed an attacker to spoof the SALTO server. 
...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41724</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Command Centre SALTO integration allowed an attacker to spoof the SALTO server. 




This issue affects all versions of Gallagher Command Centre prior to 9.20.1043.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43107 | Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Milestone Integration Plugin (MIP) permits unauthenticated messages (e.g. alarm e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43107</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation (CWE-295) in the Gallagher Milestone Integration Plugin (MIP) permits unauthenticated messages (e.g. alarm events) to be sent to the Plugin.
This issue effects Gallagher MIPS Plugin v4.0 prior to v4.0.32, all versions of v3.0 and prior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 02:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2133 | ftcms edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2133</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ftcms 2.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php/news/edit. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 23:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2132 | ftcms Search ajax_all_lists sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2132</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ftcms 2.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/index.php/web/ajax_all_lists of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 23:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2131 | dayrui XunRuiCMS Friendly Links cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dayrui XunRuiCMS up to 4.6.3. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Friendly Links Handler. The manipulation of the argument Website Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 22:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2130 | OpenXE Ticket Bearbeiten Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2130</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenXE up to 1.12. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Ticket Bearbeiten Page. The manipulation of the argument Notizen leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26205 | Lua 5.4.7, when the debug library is used, has a out-of-bounds read and segmentation violation in mainpositionTV in ltable.c. NOTE: this is ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26205</link><description>Lua 5.4.7, when the debug library is used, has a out-of-bounds read and segmentation violation in mainpositionTV in ltable.c. NOTE: this is disputed because the documentation states "when using [the debug] library ... its functions violate basic assumptions about Lua code (e.g., that ... Lua programs do not crash)."</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26204 | Lua 5.4.7, when the debug library is used, has a out-of-bounds read and segmentation violation in equalkey in ltable.c. NOTE: this is disput...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26204</link><description>Lua 5.4.7, when the debug library is used, has a out-of-bounds read and segmentation violation in equalkey in ltable.c. NOTE: this is disputed because the documentation states "when using [the debug] library ... its functions violate basic assumptions about Lua code (e.g., that ... Lua programs do not crash)."</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2129 | Mage AI insecure default initialization of resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Mage AI 0.9.75. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to insecure default initialization of resource. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. After 7 months of repeated follow-ups by the researcher, Mage AI has decided to not accept this issue as a valid security vulnerability and has confirmed that they will not be addressing it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 20:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2127 | JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate realties cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2127</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate 3.4.0 on Joomla. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /extensions/realestate/index.php/properties/list/list-with-sidebar/realties. The manipulation of the argument Itemid/jp_yearbuilt leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 17:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2126 | JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate GET Parameter realties sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2126</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoomlaUX JUX Real Estate 3.4.0 on Joomla and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /extensions/realestate/index.php/properties/list/list-with-sidebar/realties of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 17:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2125 | Control iD RH iD PDF Document companyId resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2125</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Control iD RH iD 25.2.25.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /v2/report.svc/comprovante_marcacao/?companyId=1 of the component PDF Document Handler. The manipulation of the argument nsr leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack can be initiated remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2124 | Control iD RH iD API change_password cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2124</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Control iD RH iD 25.2.25.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /v2/customerdb/person.svc/change_password of the component API Handler. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2123 | GeSHi CSS cssgen.php get_var cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2123</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in GeSHi up to 1.0.9.1. Affected by this issue is the function get_var of the file /contrib/cssgen.php of the component CSS Handler. The manipulation of the argument default-styles/keywords-1/keywords-2/keywords-3/keywords-4/comments leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2122 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Connection denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2122</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Connection Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can only be initiated within the local network. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27636 | Apache Camel: Camel Message Header Injection via Improper Filtering</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27636</link><description>Bypass/Injection vulnerability in Apache Camel.

This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.10.0 through &lt;= 4.10.1, from 4.8.0 through &lt;= 4.8.4, from 3.10.0 through &lt;= 3.22.3.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.10.2 for 4.10.x LTS, 4.8.5 for 4.8.x LTS and 3.22.4 for 3.x releases.

The vulnerability arises due to a bug in the default filtering mechanism that only blocks headers starting with "Camel", "camel", or "org.apache.camel.". Attackers can bypass this filter by altering the casing of letters. This allows attackers to inject headers which can be exploited to invoke arbitrary methods from the Bean registry and also supports using Simple Expression Language (or OGNL in some cases) as part of the method parameters passed to the bean. It's important to note that only methods in the same bean declared in the bean URI could be invoked.


Mitigation: You can easily work around this in your Camel applications by removing the headers in your Camel routes. There are many ways of doing this, also globally or per route. This means you could use the removeHeaders EIP, to filter out anything like "cAmel, cAMEL" etc, or in general everything not starting with "Camel", "camel" or "org.apache.camel.".</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2121 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro File Storage access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2121</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. Affected is an unknown function of the component File Storage. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2120 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Configuration File hostapd.conf cleartext storage in a file or on disk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /tmp/hostapd.conf of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage in a file or on disk. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 10:38:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2119 | Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro Device Registration default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2119</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Thinkware Car Dashcam F800 Pro up to 20250226. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Device Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 09:19:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2118 | Quantico Tecnologia PRMV Login Endpoint login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quantico Tecnologia PRMV 6.48. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php of the component Login Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 08:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2117 | Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System reportCenter.do electricDocList sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System 3.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function electricDocList of the file /newsedit/report/reportCenter.do. The manipulation of the argument fvID/catID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 07:40:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2116 | Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System File Protocol imageProxy.do server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Beijing Founder Electronics Founder Enjoys All-Media Acquisition and Editing System 3.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /newsedit/newsedit/xy/imageProxy.do of the component File Protocol Handler. The manipulation of the argument xyImgUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1362 | easy-broken-link-checker &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Bulk Actions via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1362</link><description>The URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 9.0.2 does not have CSRF checks in some bulk actions, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins perform unwanted actions, such as deleting customers via CSRF attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1363 | easy-broken-link-checker &amp;lt;= 9.0.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1363</link><description>The URL Shortener | Conversion Tracking  | AB Testing  | WooCommerce WordPress plugin through 9.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1382 | Contact Us By Lord Linus &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1382</link><description>The Contact Us By Lord Linus WordPress plugin through 2.6 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 06:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2115 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System AcceptZip.ashx ProcessRequest unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2115</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 3.1. Affected is the function ProcessRequest of the file /AcceptZip.ashx. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 05:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2114 | Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System Reset Password Interface OperatorStop.asp improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2114</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Shenzhen Sixun Software Sixun Shanghui Group Business Management System 7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /WebPages/Adm/OperatorStop.asp of the component Reset Password Interface. The manipulation of the argument OperId leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 04:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2113 | AT Software Solutions ATSVD Esqueceu a senha sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2113</link><description>A vulnerability was found in AT Software Solutions ATSVD up to 3.4.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Esqueceu a senha. The manipulation of the argument txtCPF leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.4.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52968 | MariaDB Server 10.4 before 10.4.33, 10.5 before 10.5.24, 10.6 before 10.6.17, 10.7 through 10.11 before 10.11.7, 11.0 before 11.0.5, and 11....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52968</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 before 10.4.33, 10.5 before 10.5.24, 10.6 before 10.6.17, 10.7 through 10.11 before 10.11.7, 11.0 before 11.0.5, and 11.1 before 11.1.4 calls fix_fields_if_needed under mysql_derived_prepare when derived is not yet prepared, leading to a find_field_in_table crash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52969 | MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, and 11.0 through 11.0.* can sometimes crash with an empty bac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52969</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, and 11.0 through 11.0.* can sometimes crash with an empty backtrace log. This may be related to make_aggr_tables_info and optimize_stage2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52970 | MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, 11.0 through 11.0.*, and 11.1 through 11.4.* crashes in Item_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52970</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.4 through 10.5.*, 10.6 through 10.6.*, 10.7 through 10.11.*, 11.0 through 11.0.*, and 11.1 through 11.4.* crashes in Item_direct_view_ref::derived_field_transformer_for_where.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52971 | MariaDB Server 10.10 through 10.11.* and 11.0 through 11.4.* crashes in JOIN::fix_all_splittings_in_plan.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52971</link><description>MariaDB Server 10.10 through 10.11.* and 11.0 through 11.4.* crashes in JOIN::fix_all_splittings_in_plan.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:47:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2112 | user-xiangpeng yaoqishan MediaInfoService.java getMediaLisByFilter sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2112</link><description>A vulnerability was found in user-xiangpeng yaoqishan up to a47fec4a31cbd13698c592dfdc938c8824dd25e4. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getMediaLisByFilter of the file cn/javaex/yaoqishan/service/media_info/MediaInfoService.java. The manipulation of the argument typeId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 21:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27840 | Espressif ESP32 chips allow 29 hidden HCI commands, such as 0xFC02 (Write memory).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27840</link><description>Espressif ESP32 chips allow 29 hidden HCI commands, such as 0xFC02 (Write memory).</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10326 | RomethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Missing Authorization in save_options and reset_widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10326</link><description>The RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_options and reset_widgets functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify plugin settings or reset plugin widgets to their default state (all enabled). NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13924 | Starter Templates by FancyWP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13924</link><description>The Starter Templates by FancyWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 via the 'http_request_host_is_external' filter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 12:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11640 | VikRentCar Car Rental Management System &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11640</link><description>The VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change plugin access privileges via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Successful exploitation allows attackers with subscriber-level privileges and above to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13649 | 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE &amp;lt;= 1.4.6.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13649</link><description>The 140+ Widgets | Xpro Addons For Elementor – FREE plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13675 | SlingBlocks – Gutenberg Blocks by FunnelKit (Formerly WooFunnels) &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13675</link><description>The SlingBlocks – Gutenberg Blocks by FunnelKit (Formerly WooFunnels) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Icon List" Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1664 | Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp;amp; Templates &amp;lt;= 5.3.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1664</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Parallax slider in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 11:20:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13359 | Product Input Fields for WooCommerce  &amp;lt;= 1.12.1 - Unauthenticated Limited File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13359</link><description>The Product Input Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the add_product_input_fields_to_order_item_meta() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.12.1. This may make it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Please note that by default the plugin is only vulnerable to a double extension file upload attack, unless an administrators leaves the accepted file extensions field blank which can make .php file uploads possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1322 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1322</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 via the 'feed' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1323 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1323</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'databeat' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1324 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1324</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'public-form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1325 | WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 16.26.10 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Exeuction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1325</link><description>The WP-Recall – Registration, Profile, Commerce &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution due to a missing capability check on the 'rcl_preview_post' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 16.26.10. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1783 | Gallery Styles &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1783</link><description>The Gallery Styles plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Gallery Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 09:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10321 | All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10321</link><description>The All-in-One Addons for Elementor – WidgetKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 in elements/advanced-tab/template/view.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13816 | Aiomatic - AI Content Writer, Editor, ChatBot &amp;amp; AI Toolkit &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Multiple Administrator Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13816</link><description>The Aiomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp; Editor, GPT-3 &amp; GPT-4, ChatGPT ChatBot &amp; AI Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update and delete posts, list and delete batches, list assistant uploaded files, delete personas, delete forms, delete templates, and clear logs. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13882 | Aiomatic - AI Content Writer, Editor, ChatBot &amp;amp; AI Toolkit &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13882</link><description>The Aiomatic - Automatic AI Content Writer &amp; Editor, GPT-3 &amp; GPT-4, ChatGPT ChatBot &amp; AI Toolkit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'aiomatic_generate_featured_image' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0177 | Javo Core &amp;lt;= 3.0.0.080 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation in ajax_signup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0177</link><description>The Javo Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.0.080. This is due to the plugin allowing users who are registering new accounts to set their own role. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to gain elevated privileges by creating an account with the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1287 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1287</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown, Syntax Highlighter, and Page Scroll widgets in all versions up to, and including, 6.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 08:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11087 | miniOrange Social Login and Register (Discord, Google, Twitter, LinkedIn) Pro Addon &amp;lt;= 200.3.9 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11087</link><description>The miniOrange Social Login and Register (Discord, Google, Twitter, LinkedIn) Pro Addon plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 200.3.9. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 07:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13908 | SMTP by BestWebSoft &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13908</link><description>The SMTP by BestWebSoft plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'save_options' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 07:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13825 | Email Keep &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13825</link><description>The Email Keep WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 06:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13826 | Email Keep &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Email Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13826</link><description>The Email Keep WordPress plugin through 1.1 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 06:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12114 | FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp;amp; Carousel &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Custom+) Arbitrary Post/Page Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12114</link><description>The FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp; Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 via the foogallery_attachment_modal_save AJAX action due to missing validation on a user controlled key (img_id). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with granted access and above, to update arbitrary post and page content. This requires the Gallery Creator Role setting to be a value lower than 'Editor' for there to be any real impact.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12119 | FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp;amp; Carousel &amp;lt;= 2.4.29 - Authenticated (Custom+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Album Title Size</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12119</link><description>The FooGallery – Responsive Photo Gallery, Image Viewer, Justified, Masonry &amp; Carousel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the default_gallery_title_size parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with granted gallery and album creator roles, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13844 | Post SMTP &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via columns Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13844</link><description>The Post SMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to generic SQL Injection via the ‘columns’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 05:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13640 | Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.4.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13640</link><description>The Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.1 via the 'wcdn/invoice' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/wcdn/invoice directory which can contain invoice files if an email attachment setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 04:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12460 | Years Since – Timeless &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12460</link><description>The Years Since – Timeless Texts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'years-since' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13774 | Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer &amp;lt;= 3.1.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Cross-Site Scriping via Wishlist Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13774</link><description>The Wishlist for WooCommerce: Multi Wishlists Per Customer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'save_to_multiple_wishlist' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13835 | Post Meta Data Manager &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authentciated (Admin+) Multisite Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13835</link><description>The Post Meta Data Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to multisite privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying the existence of a multisite installation prior to allowing user meta to be added/modified. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to gain elevated privileges on subsites that would otherwise be inaccessible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13890 | Allow PHP Execute &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) PHP Code Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13890</link><description>The Allow PHP Execute plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to allowing PHP code to be entered by all users for whom unfiltered HTML is allowed. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to inject PHP code into posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13895 | Code Snippets CPT &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13895</link><description>The The Code Snippets CPT plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1481 | Shortcode Cleaner Lite &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1481</link><description>The Shortcode Cleaner Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the download_backup() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to export arbitrary options.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1504 | Post Lockdown &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1504</link><description>The Post Lockdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.2 via the 'pl_autocomplete' AJAX action due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1261 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1261</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Countdown widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: This vulnerability exists due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-3307.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 02:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>