<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:25:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-24337 | CSV Injection vulnerability in '/members/moremember.pl' and '/admin/aqbudgets.pl' endpoints in Koha Library Management System version 23.05....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24337</link><description>CSV Injection vulnerability in '/members/moremember.pl' and '/admin/aqbudgets.pl' endpoints in Koha Library Management System version 23.05.05 and earlier allows attackers to to inject DDE commands into csv exports via the 'Budget' and 'Patrons Member' components.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:25:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1250 | Improper Privilege Management in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1250</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 16.8 before 16.8.2. When a user is assigned a custom role with manage_group_access_tokens permission, they may be able to create group access tokens with Owner privileges, which may lead to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:48:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1459 | Undertow: directory traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1459</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was found in Undertow. This issue may allow a remote attacker to append a specially-crafted sequence to an HTTP request for an application deployed to JBoss EAP, which may permit access to privileged or restricted files and directories.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23833 | OpenRefine JDBC Attack Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23833</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source power tool for working with messy data and improving it. A jdbc attack vulnerability exists in OpenRefine(version&lt;=3.7.7) where an attacker may construct a JDBC query which may read files on the host filesystem. Due to the newer MySQL driver library in the latest version of OpenRefine (8.0.30), there is no associated deserialization utilization point, so original code execution cannot be achieved, but attackers can use this vulnerability to read sensitive files on the target server. This issue has been addressed in version 3.7.8. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25108 | Insufficient authorization allowing elevated access to resources in pixelfed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25108</link><description>Pixelfed is an open source photo sharing platform. When processing requests authorization was improperly and insufficiently checked, allowing attackers to access far more functionality than users intended, including to the administrative and moderator functionality of the Pixelfed server. This vulnerability affects every version of Pixelfed between v0.10.4 and v0.11.9, inclusive. A proof of concept of this vulnerability exists. This vulnerability affects every local user of a Pixelfed server, and can potentially affect the servers' ability to federate. Some user interaction is required to setup the conditions to be able to exercise the vulnerability, but the attacker could conduct this attack time-delayed manner, where user interaction is not actively required. This vulnerability has been addressed in version 0.11.11. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25110 | Azure IoT Platform Device SDK Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25110</link><description>The UAMQP is a general purpose C library for AMQP 1.0. During a call to open_get_offered_capabilities, a memory allocation may fail causing a use-after-free issue and if a client called it during connection communication it may cause a remote code execution. Users are advised to update the submodule with commit `30865c9c`. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:07:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4437 | dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard JSON Mime-Type JsonDeserializer.ts redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4437</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in dbartholomae lambda-middleware frameguard up to 1.0.4. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file packages/json-deserializer/src/JsonDeserializer.ts of the component JSON Mime-Type Handler. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. Upgrading to version 1.1.0 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as f689404d830cbc1edd6a1018d3334ff5f44dc6a6. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-253406 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-22506 | IBM Robotic Process Automation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-22506</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation 21.0.2 contains a vulnerability that could allow user ids may be exposed across tenants.  IBM X-Force ID:  227293.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:19:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34309 | IBM CICS TX information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34309</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  229440.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22221 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains SQL Injection vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22221</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains SQL Injection vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22222 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_udoctor utility. An authenticated malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22222</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_udoctor utility. An authenticated malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22223 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_cbr utility. An authenticated malicious use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22223</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability within its svc_cbr utility. An authenticated malicious user with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands on the application's underlying OS, with the privileges of the vulnerable application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22226 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22226</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain a path traversal vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to gain unauthorized write access to the files stored on the server filesystem, with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 19:08:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22225 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22225</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_supportassist utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22224 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_nas utility. An authenticated attacker could po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22224</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_nas utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22230 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Cross-site scripting vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22230</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Cross-site scripting vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, stealing session information, masquerading as the affected user or carry out any actions that this user could perform, or to generally control the victim's browser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22228 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cifssupport utility. An authenticated attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22228</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cifssupport utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0164 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0164</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contain an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22227 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_dc utility. An authenticated attacker could pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22227</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_dc utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability execute commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:41:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0165 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_acldb_dump utility. An authenticated attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0165</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_acldb_dump utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execution of arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0166 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_tcpdump utility. An authenticated attacker coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0166</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_tcpdump utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0167 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in the svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0167</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in the svc_topstats utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to overwrite arbitrary files on the file system with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0168 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Command Injection Vulnerability in svc_oscheck utility. An authenticated attacker could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0168</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a Command Injection Vulnerability in svc_oscheck utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the ability to inject arbitrary operating system commands. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to execute commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34311 | IBM CICS TX session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34311</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 could allow a user with physical access to the web browser to gain access to the user's session due to insufficiently protected credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  229446.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0169 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0169</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading users to download and execute malicious software crafted by this product's feature to compromise their systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0170 | Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cava utility. An authenticated attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0170</link><description>Dell Unity, versions prior to 5.4, contains an OS Command Injection Vulnerability in its svc_cava utility. An authenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, escaping the restricted shell and execute arbitrary operating system commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 18:26:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34310 | IBM CICS TX information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34310</link><description>IBM CICS TX Standard and Advanced 11.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  229441.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-38714 | IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-38714</link><description>IBM DataStage on Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.6 to 4.5.2 stores sensitive credential information that can be read by a privileged user.  IBM X-Force ID:  235060.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6036 | Web3 – Crypto wallet Login &amp;amp; NFT token gating &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6036</link><description>The Web3 WordPress plugin before 3.0.0 is vulnerable to an authentication bypass due to incorrect authentication checking in the login flow in functions 'handle_auth_request' and 'hadle_login_request'. This makes it possible for non authenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the username.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6081 | Chart.js for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2023.2 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting in New Chart</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6081</link><description>The chartjs WordPress plugin through 2023.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6082 | Chart.js for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2023.2 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6082</link><description>The chartjs WordPress plugin through 2023.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6294 | popup-builder &amp;lt; 4.2.6 - Admin+ SSRF &amp;amp; File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6294</link><description>The Popup Builder WordPress plugin before 4.2.6 does not validate a parameter before making a request to it, which could allow users with the administrator role to perform SSRF attack in Multisite WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6499 | lasTunes &amp;lt;= 3.6.1 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6499</link><description>The lasTunes WordPress plugin through 3.6.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6501 | Splashscreen &amp;lt;= 0.20 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6501</link><description>The Splashscreen WordPress plugin through 0.20 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6591 | Popup Box Pro &amp;lt; 20.9.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6591</link><description>The Popup Box WordPress plugin before 20.9.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7233 | GigPress &amp;lt;= 2.3.29 - Admin+ Stored Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7233</link><description>The GigPress WordPress plugin through 2.3.29 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0248 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.4.0 - Subscriber+ Arbitrary Posts Deletion and Document Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0248</link><description>The EazyDocs WordPress plugin before 2.4.0 re-introduced CVE-2023-6029 (https://wpscan.com/vulnerability/7a0aaf85-8130-4fd7-8f09-f8edc929597e/) in 2.3.8, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber to delete arbitrary posts, as well as add and delete documents/sections. The issue was partially fixed in 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0250 | Analytics Insights for Google Analytics 4 &amp;lt; 6.3 - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0250</link><description>The Analytics Insights for Google Analytics 4 (AIWP) WordPress plugin before 6.3 is vulnerable to Open Redirect due to insufficient validation on the redirect oauth2callback.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to redirect users to potentially malicious sites if they can successfully trick them into performing an action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0420 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.88.15 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0420</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.88.15 does not sanitize and escape the map title when outputting it back in the admin dashboard, allowing Contributors and above roles to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0421 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.88.16 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Private/Draft Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0421</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.88.16 does not ensure that posts to be retrieve via an AJAX action is a public map, allowing unauthenticated users to read arbitrary private and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0566 | Smart Manager &amp;lt; 8.28.0 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0566</link><description>The Smart Manager WordPress plugin before 8.28.0 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25360 | A hidden interface in Motorola CX2L Router firmware v1.0.1 leaks information regarding the SystemWizardStatus component via sending a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25360</link><description>A hidden interface in Motorola CX2L Router firmware v1.0.1 leaks information regarding the SystemWizardStatus component via sending a crafted request to device_web_ip.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:27:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6681 | Jwcrypto: denail of service  via specifically crafted jwe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6681</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JWCrypto. This flaw allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) attack and possible password brute-force and dictionary attacks to be more resource-intensive. This issue can result in a large amount of computational consumption, causing a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 14:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1062 | 389-ds-base: a heap overflow leading to denail-of-servce while writing a value larger than 256 chars (in log_entry_attr)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1062</link><description>A heap overflow flaw was found in 389-ds-base. This issue leads to a denial of service when writing a value larger than 256 chars in log_entry_attr.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 13:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1439 | Inadequate access control vulnerability in Moodle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1439</link><description>Inadequate access control in Moodle LMS. This vulnerability could allow a local user with a student role to create arbitrary events intended for users with higher roles. It could also allow the attacker to add events to the calendar of all users without their prior consent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 10:58:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24875 | WordPress Link Library Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24875</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library.This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.5.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24884 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Connector Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24884</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ARI Soft Contact Form 7 Connector.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Connector: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24887 | WordPress Contest Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 21.2.8.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24887</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Contest Gallery Photos and Files Contest Gallery – Contact Form, Upload Form, Social Share and Voting Plugin for WordPress.This issue affects Photos and Files Contest Gallery – Contact Form, Upload Form, Social Share and Voting Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 21.2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24929 | WordPress WP Contact Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24929</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Ryan Duff, Peter Westwood WP Contact Form.This issue affects WP Contact Form: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24935 | WordPress Basic Log Viewer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24935</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WpSimpleTools Basic Log Viewer.This issue affects Basic Log Viewer: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46615 | WordPress KD Coming Soon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46615</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Kalli Dan. KD Coming Soon.This issue affects KD Coming Soon: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41703 | User ID references at mentions in document comments were not correctly sanitized. Script code could be injected to a users session when work...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41703</link><description>User ID references at mentions in document comments were not correctly sanitized. Script code could be injected to a users session when working with a malicious document. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. User-defined content like comments and mentions are now filtered to avoid potentially malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41704 | Processing of CID references at E-Mail can be abused to inject malicious script code that passes the sanitization engine. Malicious script c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41704</link><description>Processing of CID references at E-Mail can be abused to inject malicious script code that passes the sanitization engine. Malicious script code could be injected to a users sessions when interacting with E-Mails. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID handing has been improved and resulting content is checked for malicious content. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41705 | Processing of user-defined DAV user-agent strings is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41705</link><description>Processing of user-defined DAV user-agent strings is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of DAV user-agents now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41706 | Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Av...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41706</link><description>Processing time of drive search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing of user-defined drive search expressions is not limited No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41707 | Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41707</link><description>Processing of user-defined mail search expressions is not limited. Availability of OX App Suite could be reduced due to high processing load. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. Processing time of mail search expressions now gets monitored, and the related request is terminated if a resource threshold is reached.&#13;
 No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41708 | References to the "app loader" functionality could contain redirects to unexpected locations. Attackers could forge app references that bypa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41708</link><description>References to the "app loader" functionality could contain redirects to unexpected locations. Attackers could forge app references that bypass existing safeguards to inject malicious script code. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. References to apps are now controlled more strict to avoid relative references. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23512 | WordPress ProductX – Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23512</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in wpxpo ProductX – WooCommerce Builder &amp; Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks.This issue affects ProductX – WooCommerce Builder &amp; Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23513 | WordPress PropertyHive Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23513</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PropertyHive.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 08:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24796 | WordPress Event Manager for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24796</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce – WpEvently – WordPress Plugin.This issue affects Event Manager and Tickets Selling Plugin for WooCommerce – WpEvently – WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 4.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24797 | WordPress ERE Recently Viewed Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24797</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in G5Theme ERE Recently Viewed – Essential Real Estate Add-On.This issue affects ERE Recently Viewed – Essential Real Estate Add-On: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24926 | WordPress Brooklyn Theme &amp;lt;= 4.9.7.6 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24926</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in UnitedThemes Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme.This issue affects Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.9.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:20:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25100 | WordPress Coupon Referral Program Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25100</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WP Swings Coupon Referral Program.This issue affects Coupon Referral Program: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47526 | WordPress Chartify Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47526</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Chart Builder Team Chartify – WordPress Chart Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Chartify – WordPress Chart Plugin: from n/a through 2.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50875 | WordPress Sensei LMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.17.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50875</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic Sensei LMS – Online Courses, Quizzes, &amp; Learning allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sensei LMS – Online Courses, Quizzes, &amp; Learning: from n/a through 4.17.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51370 | WordPress WP Chat App Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51370</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NinjaTeam WP Chat App allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Chat App: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51403 | WordPress Restaurant Reservations Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51403</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nicdark Restaurant Reservations allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Restaurant Reservations: from n/a through 1.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24889 | WordPress All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Geek Code Lab All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage allows Stored XSS.This issue affects All 404 Pages Redirect to Homepage: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24927 | WordPress Brooklyn Theme &amp;lt;= 4.9.7.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24927</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UnitedThemes Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Brooklyn | Creative Multi-Purpose Responsive WordPress Theme: from n/a through 4.9.7.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24928 | WordPress Content Cards Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24928</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Arunas Liuiza Content Cards allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Content Cards: from n/a through 0.9.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:19:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24930 | WordPress Buttons Shortcode and Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.16 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24930</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in OTWthemes.Com Buttons Shortcode and Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Buttons Shortcode and Widget: from n/a through 1.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:00:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24931 | WordPress Before After Image Slider WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24931</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in swadeshswain Before After Image Slider WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Before After Image Slider WP: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24932 | WordPress VK Poster Group Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24932</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Djo VK Poster Group allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects VK Poster Group: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24933 | WordPress Honeypot for WP Comment Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24933</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prasidhda Malla Honeypot for WP Comment allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Honeypot for WP Comment: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25744 | In the Linux kernel before 6.6.7, an untrusted VMM can trigger int80 syscall handling at any given point. This is related to arch/x86/coco/t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25744</link><description>In the Linux kernel before 6.6.7, an untrusted VMM can trigger int80 syscall handling at any given point. This is related to arch/x86/coco/tdx/tdx.c and arch/x86/mm/mem_encrypt_amd.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 04:27:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52429 | dm_table_create in drivers/md/dm-table.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to (in alloc_targets) allocate more than INT_MAX byte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52429</link><description>dm_table_create in drivers/md/dm-table.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to (in alloc_targets) allocate more than INT_MAX bytes, and crash, because of a missing check for struct dm_ioctl.target_count.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25739 | create_empty_lvol in drivers/mtd/ubi/vtbl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to allocate zero bytes, and crash, because of a mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25739</link><description>create_empty_lvol in drivers/mtd/ubi/vtbl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 can attempt to allocate zero bytes, and crash, because of a missing check for ubi-&gt;leb_size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25740 | A memory leak flaw was found in the UBI driver in drivers/mtd/ubi/attach.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 for UBI_IOCATT, because kobj-&gt;n...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25740</link><description>A memory leak flaw was found in the UBI driver in drivers/mtd/ubi/attach.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 for UBI_IOCATT, because kobj-&gt;name is not released.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25741 | printer_write in drivers/usb/gadget/function/f_printer.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 does not properly call usb_ep_queue, which might ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25741</link><description>printer_write in drivers/usb/gadget/function/f_printer.c in the Linux kernel through 6.7.4 does not properly call usb_ep_queue, which might allow attackers to cause a denial of service or have unspecified other impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1433 | KDE Plasma Workspace Theme File eventpluginsmanager.cpp enabledPlugins path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1433</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in KDE Plasma Workspace up to 5.93.0. This affects the function EventPluginsManager::enabledPlugins of the file components/calendar/eventpluginsmanager.cpp of the component Theme File Handler. The manipulation of the argument pluginId leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The patch is named 6cdf42916369ebf4ad5bd876c4dfa0170d7b2f01. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253407. NOTE: This requires write access to user's home or the installation of third party global themes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 23:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25728 | ExpressVPN before 12.73.0 on Windows, when split tunneling is used, sends DNS requests according to the Windows configuration (e.g., sends t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25728</link><description>ExpressVPN before 12.73.0 on Windows, when split tunneling is used, sends DNS requests according to the Windows configuration (e.g., sends them to DNS servers operated by the user's ISP instead of to the ExpressVPN DNS servers), which may allow remote attackers to obtain sensitive information about websites visited by VPN users.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25417 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_translation.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25417</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/add_translation.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25418 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25418</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/delete_menu.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25419 | flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25419</link><description>flusity-CMS v2.33 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /core/tools/update_menu.php.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 20:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1151 | Kernel: stack overflow problem in open vswitch kernel module leading to dos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1151</link><description>A vulnerability was reported in the Open vSwitch sub-component in the Linux Kernel. The flaw occurs when a recursive operation of code push recursively calls into the code block. The OVS module does not validate the stack depth, pushing too many frames and causing a stack overflow. As a result, this can lead to a crash or other related issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21875 | DoS attack when broadcasting billboard messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21875</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Badge leading to a denial of service attack.Team Hacker Hotel Badge 2024 on risc-v (billboard modules) allows Flooding.This issue affects Hacker Hotel Badge 2024: from 0.1.0 through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 08:42:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25722 | qanything_kernel/connector/database/mysql/mysql_client.py in qanything.ai QAnything before 1.2.0 allows SQL Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25722</link><description>qanything_kernel/connector/database/mysql/mysql_client.py in qanything.ai QAnything before 1.2.0 allows SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52428 | In Connect2id Nimbus JOSE+JWT before 9.37.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service (resource consumption) via a large JWE p2c header val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52428</link><description>In Connect2id Nimbus JOSE+JWT before 9.37.2, an attacker can cause a denial of service (resource consumption) via a large JWE p2c header value (aka iteration count) for the PasswordBasedDecrypter (PBKDF2) component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25718 | In the Samly package before 1.4.0 for Elixir, Samly.State.Store.get_assertion/3 can return an expired session, which interferes with access ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25718</link><description>In the Samly package before 1.4.0 for Elixir, Samly.State.Store.get_assertion/3 can return an expired session, which interferes with access control because Samly.AuthHandler uses a cached session and does not replace it, even after expiry.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:27:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52427 | In OpenDDS through 3.27, there is a segmentation fault for a DataWriter with a large value of resource_limits.max_samples. NOTE: the vendor'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52427</link><description>In OpenDDS through 3.27, there is a segmentation fault for a DataWriter with a large value of resource_limits.max_samples. NOTE: the vendor's position is that the product is not designed to handle a max_samples value that is too large for the amount of memory on the system.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 04:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1432 | DeepFaceLab main.py apply_xseg deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1432</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function apply_xseg of the file main.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-253391. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 03:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1431 | Netgear R7000 Web Management Interface debuginfo.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1431</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /debuginfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253382 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25714 | In Rhonabwy through 1.1.13, HMAC signature verification uses a strcmp function that is vulnerable to side-channel attacks, because it stops ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25714</link><description>In Rhonabwy through 1.1.13, HMAC signature verification uses a strcmp function that is vulnerable to side-channel attacks, because it stops the comparison when the first difference is spotted in the two signatures. (The fix uses gnutls_memcmp, which has constant-time execution.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25715 | Glewlwyd SSO server 2.x through 2.7.6 allows open redirection via redirect_uri.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25715</link><description>Glewlwyd SSO server 2.x through 2.7.6 allows open redirection via redirect_uri.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25713 | yyjson through 0.8.0 has a double free, leading to remote code execution in some cases, because the pool_free function lacks loop checks. (p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25713</link><description>yyjson through 0.8.0 has a double free, leading to remote code execution in some cases, because the pool_free function lacks loop checks. (pool_free is part of the pool series allocator, along with pool_malloc and pool_realloc.)</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25712 | http-swagger before 1.2.6 allows XSS via PUT requests, because a file that has been uploaded (via httpSwagger.WrapHandler and *webdav.memFil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25712</link><description>http-swagger before 1.2.6 allows XSS via PUT requests, because a file that has been uploaded (via httpSwagger.WrapHandler and *webdav.memFile) can subsequently be accessed via a GET request. NOTE: this is independently fixable with respect to CVE-2022-24863, because (if a solution continued to allow PUT requests) large files could have been blocked without blocking JavaScript, or JavaScript could have been blocked without blocking large files.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 02:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25711 | diffoscope before 256 allows directory traversal via an embedded filename in a GPG file. Contents of any file, such as ../.ssh/id_rsa, may b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25711</link><description>diffoscope before 256 allows directory traversal via an embedded filename in a GPG file. Contents of any file, such as ../.ssh/id_rsa, may be disclosed to an attacker. This occurs because the value of the gpg --use-embedded-filenames option is trusted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1430 | Netgear R7000 Web Management Interface currentsetting.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1430</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Netgear R7000 1.0.11.136_10.2.120 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /currentsetting.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253381 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23724 | Ghost through 5.76.0 allows stored XSS, and resultant privilege escalation in which a contributor can take over any account, via an SVG prof...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23724</link><description>Ghost through 5.76.0 allows stored XSS, and resultant privilege escalation in which a contributor can take over any account, via an SVG profile picture that contains JavaScript code to interact with the API on localhost TCP port 3001. NOTE: The discoverer reports that "The vendor does not view this as a valid vector."</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 01:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22313 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22313</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0 contains hard-coded credentials, such as a password or cryptographic key, which it uses for its own inbound authentication, outbound communication to external components, or encryption of internal data.  IBM X-Force ID:  278749.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22312 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22312</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0 stores user credentials in plain clear text which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  278748.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 15:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50957 | IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50957</link><description>IBM Storage Defender - Resiliency Service 2.0 could allow a privileged user to perform unauthorized actions after obtaining encrypted data from clear text key storage.  IBM X-Force ID:  275783.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22361 | IBM Semeru Runtime information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22361</link><description>IBM Semeru Runtime 8.0.302.0 through 8.0.392.0, 11.0.12.0 through 11.0.21.0, 17.0.1.0 - 17.0.9.0, and 21.0.1.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  281222.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 15:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51404 | WordPress My Agile Privacy Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51404</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MyAgilePrivacy My Agile Privacy – The only GDPR solution for WordPress that you can truly trust allows Stored XSS.This issue affects My Agile Privacy – The only GDPR solution for WordPress that you can truly trust: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:51:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51415 | WordPress GiveWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51415</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GiveWP GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform: from n/a through 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51480 | WordPress Active Products Tables for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51480</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Active Products Tables for WooCommerce. Professional products tables for WooCommerce store : from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51485 | WordPress Pay with Vipps for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51485</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Hosting Pay with Vipps and MobilePay for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pay with Vipps and MobilePay for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.14.13.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51488 | WordPress Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp;amp; more Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51488</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Automattic, Inc. Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Crowdsignal Dashboard – Polls, Surveys &amp; more: from n/a through 3.0.11.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51492 | WordPress If-So Dynamic Content Personalization Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51492</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in If So Plugin If-So Dynamic Content Personalization allows Stored XSS.This issue affects If-So Dynamic Content Personalization: from n/a through 1.6.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:29:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51493 | WordPress Custom Post Carousels with Owl Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51493</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Howard Ehrenberg Custom Post Carousels with Owl allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Custom Post Carousels with Owl: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23514 | WordPress Click To Tweet Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.14 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23514</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ClickToTweet.Com Click To Tweet allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Click To Tweet: from n/a through 2.0.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23516 | WordPress CC BMI Calculator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23516</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Calculators World CC BMI Calculator allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CC BMI Calculator: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:23:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23517 | WordPress Scheduling Plugin – Online Booking for WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.10 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23517</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Start Booking Scheduling Plugin – Online Booking for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Scheduling Plugin – Online Booking for WordPress: from n/a through 3.5.10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24712 | WordPress Heateor Social Login Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.30 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24712</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Team Heateor Heateor Social Login WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Heateor Social Login WordPress: from n/a through 1.1.30.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24713 | WordPress Auto Listings Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24713</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Auto Listings Auto Listings – Car Listings &amp; Car Dealership Plugin for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Auto Listings – Car Listings &amp; Car Dealership Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 2.6.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24717 | WordPress Beds24 Online Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.23 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24717</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mark Kinchin Beds24 Online Booking allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Beds24 Online Booking: from n/a through 2.0.23.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24801 | WordPress OWL Carousel Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24801</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LogicHunt OWL Carousel – WordPress Owl Carousel Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects OWL Carousel – WordPress Owl Carousel Slider: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:56:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24803 | WordPress Ultra Companion Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24803</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPoperation Ultra Companion – Companion plugin for WPoperation Themes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Ultra Companion – Companion plugin for WPoperation Themes: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24804 | WordPress MW WP Form Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.6 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24804</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in websoudan MW WP Form allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MW WP Form: from n/a through 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:56:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24831 | WordPress Premium Addons for Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.16 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24831</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.16.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:49:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1406 | Linksys WRT54GL Web Management Interface SysInfo1.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1406</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54GL 4.30.18. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /SysInfo1.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-253330 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0594 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union-based SQL Injection via the 'q' parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0594</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union-based SQL Injection via the 'q' parameter of the wpas_get_users action in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0595 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0595</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpas_get_users() function hooked via AJAX in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve user data such as emails.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0596 | The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0596</link><description>The Awesome Support – WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the editor_html() function in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to view password protected and draft posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 07:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1405 | Linksys WRT54GL Web Management Interface wlaninfo.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1405</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Linksys WRT54GL 4.30.18. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /wlaninfo.htm of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-253329 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 05:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21490 | This affects versions of the package angular from 1.3.0. A regular expression used to split the value of the ng-srcset directive is vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21490</link><description>This affects versions of the package angular from 1.3.0. A regular expression used to split the value of the ng-srcset directive is vulnerable to super-linear runtime due to backtracking. With a large carefully-crafted input, this can result in catastrophic backtracking and cause a denial of service. &#13;&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This package is EOL and will not receive any updates to address this issue. Users should migrate to [@angular/core](https://www.npmjs.com/package/@angular/core).</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 05:07:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45698 | HCL Sametime is impacted by clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45698</link><description>Sametime is impacted by lack of clickjacking protection in Outlook add-in. The application is not implementing appropriate protections in order to protect users from clickjacking attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28077 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J, versions prior to 6.5, and versions 7.0 and 7.1 contain a debug message revealing unnecessary information vulnerability. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28077</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J, versions prior to 6.5, and versions 7.0 and 7.1 contain a debug message revealing unnecessary information vulnerability. This may lead to disclosing sensitive information to a locally privileged user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45696 | HCL Sametime is impacted by an autocomplete enabled vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45696</link><description>Sametime is impacted by sensitive fields with autocomplete enabled in the Legacy web chat client. By default, this allows user entered data to be stored by the browser.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 03:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>