<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:15:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-32472 | DoS attack by conducting a slowloris-type attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32472</link><description>The multiScan and picoScan are vulnerable to a denial-of-service (DoS) attack. A remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability by conducting a Slowloris-type attack, causing the web page to become unresponsive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4019 | 20120630 Novel-Plus GeneratorController.java genCode missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4019</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 20120630 Novel-Plus up to 0e156c04b4b7ce0563bef6c97af4476fcda8f160. Affected is the function genCode of the file novel-admin/src/main/java/com/java2nb/common/controller/GeneratorController.java. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4018 | 20120630 Novel-Plus CrawlController.java addCrawlSource missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4018</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 20120630 Novel-Plus up to 0e156c04b4b7ce0563bef6c97af4476fcda8f160. This issue affects the function addCrawlSource of the file novel-crawl/src/main/java/com/java2nb/novel/controller/CrawlController.java. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 11:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4017 | 20120630 Novel-Plus LogController.java list improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4017</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in 20120630 Novel-Plus up to 0e156c04b4b7ce0563bef6c97af4476fcda8f160. This vulnerability affects the function list of the file nnovel-admin/src/main/java/com/java2nb/common/controller/LogController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 11:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4016 | 20120630 Novel-Plus LogController.java deleteIndex improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4016</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in 20120630 Novel-Plus up to 0e156c04b4b7ce0563bef6c97af4476fcda8f160. This affects the function deleteIndex of the file novel-admin/src/main/java/com/java2nb/common/controller/LogController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3200 | Com-Server Exposed via Weak TLS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3200</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker could exploit the used, insecure TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 protocols to intercept and manipulate encrypted communications between the Com-Server and connected systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4014 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System manage-art-medium.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4014</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/manage-art-medium.php. The manipulation of the argument artmed leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4015 | 20120630 Novel-Plus SessionController.java list missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4015</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 20120630 Novel-Plus up to 0e156c04b4b7ce0563bef6c97af4476fcda8f160. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function list of the file novel-system/src/main/java/com/java2nb/system/controller/SessionController.java. The manipulation leads to missing authentication. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32470 | Unauthenticated change of IP adress</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32470</link><description>A remote unauthenticated attacker may be able to change the IP adress of the device, and therefore affecting the availability of the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32471 | Reuse of salt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32471</link><description>The device’s passwords have not been adequately salted, making them vulnerable to password extraction attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-39367 | WordPress Kleo theme &amp;lt; 5.4.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-39367</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SeventhQueen Kleo.This issue affects Kleo: from n/a before 5.4.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4013 | PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4013</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4012 | playeduxyz PlayEdu 开源培训系统 User Avatar create server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4012</link><description>A vulnerability was found in playeduxyz PlayEdu 开源培训系统 up to 1.8 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/backend/v1/user/create of the component User Avatar Handler. The manipulation of the argument Avatar leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42598 | Multiple SEIKO EPSON printer drivers for Windows OS are configured with an improper access permission settings when installed or used in a l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42598</link><description>Multiple SEIKO EPSON printer drivers for Windows OS are configured with an improper access permission settings when installed or used in a language other than English. If a user is directed to place a crafted DLL file in a location of an attacker's choosing, the attacker may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege on a Windows system on which the printer driver is installed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4011 | Redmine Custom Query cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4011</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Redmine 6.0.0/6.0.1/6.0.2/6.0.3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Custom Query Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 6.0.4 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4007 | Tenda W12/i24 httpd modules cgidhcpsCfgSet stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4007</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda W12 and i24 3.0.0.4(2887)/3.0.0.5(3644). Affected by this vulnerability is the function cgidhcpsCfgSet of the file /goform/modules of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument json leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 08:01:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22235 | Spring Boot EndpointRequest.to() creates wrong matcher if actuator endpoint is not exposed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22235</link><description>EndpointRequest.to() creates a matcher for null/** if the actuator endpoint, for which the EndpointRequest has been created, is disabled or not exposed.

Your application may be affected by this if all the following conditions are met:

  *  You use Spring Security
  *  EndpointRequest.to() has been used in a Spring Security chain configuration
  *  The endpoint which EndpointRequest references is disabled or not exposed via web
  *  Your application handles requests to /null and this path needs protection


You are not affected if any of the following is true:

  *  You don't use Spring Security
  *  You don't use EndpointRequest.to()
  *  The endpoint which EndpointRequest.to() refers to is enabled and is exposed
  *  Your application does not handle requests to /null or this path does not need protection</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4006 | youyiio BeyongCms Document Management Page Upload.html unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4006</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in youyiio BeyongCms 1.6.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/theme/Upload.html of the component Document Management Page. The manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4005 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System patient-report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4005</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /patient-report.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13688 | Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) &amp;lt; 7.6.10 - Password Protection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13688</link><description>The Admin and Site Enhancements (ASE) WordPress plugin before 7.6.10 uses a hardcoded password in its Password Protection feature, allowing attacker to bypass the protection offered via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 06:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9771 | WP-Recall &amp;lt; 16.26.12 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9771</link><description>The WP-Recall  WordPress plugin before 16.26.12 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 06:23:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0627 | AI Autotagger &amp;lt; 3.30.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0627</link><description>The WordPress Tag, Category, and Taxonomy Manager  WordPress plugin before 3.30.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its Widgets settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 06:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4004 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4004</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /password-recovery.php. The manipulation of the argument contactno leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 06:23:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4003 | RefindPlusRepo RefindPlus RP_ApfsIo.c InternalApfsTranslateBlock null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4003</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RefindPlusRepo RefindPlus 0.14.2.AB. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function InternalApfsTranslateBlock of the file Library/RP_ApfsLib/RP_ApfsIo.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The patch is named 4d35125ca689a255647e9033dd60c257d26df7cb. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 05:55:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4002 | RefindPlusRepo RefindPlus BootLog.c GetDebugLogFile null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4002</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RefindPlusRepo RefindPlus 0.14.2.AB and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function GetDebugLogFile of the file Library/MemLogLib/BootLog.c. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Attacking locally is a requirement. The patch is identified as d2143a1e2deefddd9b105fb7160763c4f8d47ea2. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 05:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4001 | scipopt scip File Descriptor genRandomLOPInstance.c main file descriptor consumption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4001</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in scipopt scip up to 9.2.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function main of the file examples/LOP/src/genRandomLOPInstance.c of the component File Descriptor Handler. The manipulation of the argument File leads to uncontrolled file descriptor consumption. Local access is required to approach this attack. Upgrading to version 9.2.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is d6da63b941216d75fbc1aefea9abf1de6712a2d0. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 04:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4000 | Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System ssoproxy.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4000</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System 8.1 SP2. Affected is an unknown function of the file seeyon\opt\Seeyon\A8\ApacheJetspeed\webapps\seeyon\ssoproxy\jsp\ssoproxy.jsp. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 04:25:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3999 | Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System URL Parameter date.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3999</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Seeyon Zhiyuan OA Web Application System 8.1 SP2. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file seeyon\opt\Seeyon\A8\ApacheJetspeed\webapps\seeyon\common\js\addDate\date.jsp of the component URL Parameter Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3998 | CodeAstro Membership Management System renew.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3998</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in CodeAstro Membership Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file renew.php?id=6. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3706 | 104 Corporation eHRMS - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3706</link><description>The eHRMS from 104 Corporation has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3997 | dazhouda lecms Personal Information Page index.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3997</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in dazhouda lecms 3.0.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?my-profile-ajax-1 of the component Personal Information Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3996 | TOTOLINK N150RT MAC Filtering Page home.htm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3996</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /home.htm of the component MAC Filtering Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:03:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3995 | TOTOLINK N150RT LAN Settings Page fromStaticDHCP cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3995</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/fromStaticDHCP of the component LAN Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3994 | TOTOLINK N150RT IP Port Filtering home.htm cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3994</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /home.htm of the component IP Port Filtering. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3993 | TOTOLINK N150RT formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3993</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWsc. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26692 | Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal'). If e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26692</link><description>Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal'). If exploited, arbitrary code may be executed by a remote unauthenticated attacker with the Windows system privilege where the product is running.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27937 | Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal'). If e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27937</link><description>Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ('Path Traversal'). If exploited, an arbitrary file in the affected product may be obtained by a remote attacker who can log in to the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31144 | Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints. If exploited, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31144</link><description>Quick Agent V3 and Quick Agent V2 contain an issue with improper restriction of communication channel to intended endpoints. If exploited, a remote unauthenticated attacker may attempt to log in to an arbitrary host via Windows system where the product is running.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3992 | TOTOLINK N150RT formWlwds buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3992</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formWlwds. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3991 | TOTOLINK N150RT formWdsEncrypt buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3991</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formWdsEncrypt. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 23:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3990 | TOTOLINK N150RT formVlan buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3990</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formVlan. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 23:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3989 | TOTOLINK N150RT formStaticDHCP buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3989</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formStaticDHCP. The manipulation of the argument Hostname leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 22:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3988 | TOTOLINK N150RT formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3988</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formPortFw. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3987 | TOTOLINK N150RT formWsc command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3987</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N150RT 3.4.0-B20190525. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWsc. The manipulation of the argument localPin leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46689 | Ververica Platform 2.14.0 contain an Reflected XSS vulnerability via a namespaces/default/formats URI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46689</link><description>Ververica Platform 2.14.0 contain an Reflected XSS vulnerability via a namespaces/default/formats URI.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46690 | Ververica Platform 2.14.0 allows low-privileged users to access SQL connectors via a direct namespaces/default/formats request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46690</link><description>Ververica Platform 2.14.0 allows low-privileged users to access SQL connectors via a direct namespaces/default/formats request.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:34:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3986 | Apereo CAS CasConfigurationMetadataServerController.java redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3986</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apereo CAS 5.2.6. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file cas-5.2.6\core\cas-server-core-configuration-metadata-repository\src\main\java\org\apereo\cas\metadata\rest\CasConfigurationMetadataServerController.java. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3985 | Apereo CAS ResponseEntity redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3985</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apereo CAS 5.2.6. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function ResponseEntity of the file cas-5.2.6\webapp-mgmt\cas-management-webapp-support\src\main\java\org\apereo\cas\mgmt\services\web\ManageRegisteredServicesMultiActionController.java. The manipulation of the argument Query leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3984 | Apereo CAS Groovy Code RegisteredServiceSimpleFormController.java saveService code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3984</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apereo CAS 5.2.6 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function saveService of the file cas-5.2.6\webapp-mgmt\cas-management-webapp-support\src\main\java\org\apereo\cas\mgmt\services\web\RegisteredServiceSimpleFormController.java of the component Groovy Code Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 20:22:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3983 | AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System nlog_down.php command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3983</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in AMTT Hotel Broadband Operation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /manager/system/nlog_down.php. The manipulation of the argument ProtocolType leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46687 | quickjs-ng through 0.9.0 has a missing length check in JS_ReadString for a string, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. QuickJS before 2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46687</link><description>quickjs-ng through 0.9.0 has a missing length check in JS_ReadString for a string, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. QuickJS before 2025-04-26 is also affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46688 | quickjs-ng through 0.9.0 has an incorrect size calculation in JS_ReadBigInt for a BigInt, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. QuickJS b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46688</link><description>quickjs-ng through 0.9.0 has an incorrect size calculation in JS_ReadBigInt for a BigInt, leading to a heap-based buffer overflow. QuickJS before 2025-04-26 is also affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2866 | PDF signature forgery with adbe.pkcs7.sha1 SubFilter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2866</link><description>Improper Verification of Cryptographic Signature vulnerability in LibreOffice allows PDF Signature Spoofing by Improper Validation.




In the affected versions of LibreOffice a flaw in the verification code for adbe.pkcs7.sha1 signatures could cause invalid signatures to be accepted as valid




This issue affects LibreOffice: from 24.8 before &lt; 24.8.6, from 25.2 before &lt; 25.2.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3982 | nortikin Sverchok Set Property Mk2 Node getsetprop_mk2.py SvSetPropNodeMK2 prototype pollution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3982</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in nortikin Sverchok 1.3.0. Affected is the function SvSetPropNodeMK2 of the file sverchok/nodes/object_nodes/getsetprop_mk2.py of the component Set Property Mk2 Node. The manipulation leads to improperly controlled modification of object prototype attributes ('prototype pollution'). It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 19:14:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3981 | wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System details improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3981</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /v1/prescription/details/. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3980 | wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System list improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3980</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in wowjoy 浙江湖州华卓信息科技有限公司 Internet Doctor Workstation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /v1/prescription/list. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 18:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3979 | dazhouda lecms Password Change index.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3979</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in dazhouda lecms 3.0.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?my-password-ajax-1 of the component Password Change Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3978 | dazhouda lecms user_set.htm information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in dazhouda lecms 3.0.3. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/view/default/user_set.htm. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3977 | iteachyou Dreamer CMS Attachment download improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3977</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iteachyou Dreamer CMS up to 4.1.3. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/attachment/download of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46657 | Karaz Karazal through 2025-04-14 allows reflected XSS via the lang parameter to the default URI.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46657</link><description>Karaz Karazal through 2025-04-14 allows reflected XSS via the lang parameter to the default URI.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3976 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System new-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3976</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /new-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3975 | ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP subscriber-csv.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3975</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ScriptAndTools eCommerce-website-in-PHP 3.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/subscriber-csv.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 15:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3974 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System edit-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3974</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-phlebotomist.php?pid=11. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3973 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System check_availability.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3973</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /check_availability.php. The manipulation of the argument mobnumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3972 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System bwdates-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3972</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 14:18:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3971 | PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System add-phlebotomist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3971</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul COVID19 Testing Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-phlebotomist.php. The manipulation of the argument empid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3970 | baseweb JSite save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3970</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in baseweb JSite up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sys/office/save. The manipulation of the argument Remarks leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:02:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3969 | codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard Edit Category Page edit-category.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3969</link><description>A vulnerability was found in codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /edit-category.php of the component Edit Category Page. The manipulation of the argument category_image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3968 | codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard api.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3968</link><description>A vulnerability was found in codeprojects News Publishing Site Dashboard 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api.php. The manipulation of the argument cat_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 11:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3886 | CatoNetworks CatoClient up to 5.8 PrivilegedHelperTool Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3886</link><description>An issue in CatoNetworks CatoClient before v.5.8.0 allows attackers to escalate privileges and achieve a race condition (TOCTOU) via the PrivilegedHelperTool component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3967 | itwanger paicoding Article post improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /article/api/post of the component Article Handler. The manipulation of the argument articleId leads to improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3966 | itwanger paicoding Browsing History home information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/home?userId=1&amp;amp;homeSelectType=read of the component Browsing History Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:08:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3965 | itwanger paicoding post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3965</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /article/app/post. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 09:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3964 | withstars Books-Management-System Article del cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3964</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /api/article/del of the component Article Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 09:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52887 | Self-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52887</link><description>Authenticated end-user may set a specially crafted SNX bookmark that can make their browser run a script while accessing their own bookmark list.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52888 | Stored-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52888</link><description>For an authenticated end-user the portal may run a script while attempting to display a directory or some file's properties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:55:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3963 | withstars Books-Management-System Background Interface list authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3963</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/article/list of the component Background Interface. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3962 | withstars Books-Management-System Comment add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3962</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/comment/add of the component Comment Handler. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 07:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3961 | withstars Books-Management-System do cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3961</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/article/add/do. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 06:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3960 | withstars Books-Management-System Background Interface allreaders.html authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3960</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /allreaders.html of the component Background Interface. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 06:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3959 | withstars Books-Management-System reader_delete.html cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3959</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /reader_delete.html. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 04:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3958 | withstars Books-Management-System Book Edit Page book_edit_do.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3958</link><description>A vulnerability was found in withstars Books-Management-System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /book_edit_do.html of the component Book Edit Page. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 04:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3957 | opplus springboot-admin SysLogDao.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3957</link><description>A vulnerability was found in opplus springboot-admin 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file \src\main\resources\mapper\sys\SysLogDao.xml. The manipulation of the argument order leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3956 | 201206030 novel-cloud BookInfoMapper.xml RestResp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3956</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 201206030 novel-cloud 1.4.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function RestResp of the file novel-cloud-master/novel-book/novel-book-service/src/main/resources/mapper/BookInfoMapper.xml. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 03:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46580 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a code-related vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46580</link><description>There is a code-related vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can access system tables to disrupt the normal operation of business SQL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46574 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46574</link><description>There is an information disclosure vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit error messages to obtain the system's sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46575 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46575</link><description>There is an information disclosure vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit error messages to obtain the system's sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46576 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a privilege escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46576</link><description>There is a Permission Management and Access Control vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can manipulate requests to bypass privilege restrictions and delete content.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46577 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has an SQL injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46577</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can inject commands to extract database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46578 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has SQL injection vulnerabilities in multiple interfaces</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46578</link><description>There are SQL injection vulnerabilities in multiple interfaces of the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can exploit these interfaces to inject commands and extract sensitive database information.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46579 | ZTE GoldenDB Database product has a DDE injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46579</link><description>There is a DDE injection vulnerability in the GoldenDB database product. Attackers can inject DDE expressions through the interface, and when users download and open the affected file, the DDE commands can be executed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 02:49:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3955 | codeprojects Patient Record Management System edit_rpatient.php.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3955</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in codeprojects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit_rpatient.php.php. The manipulation of the argument id/lastname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46672 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check the OTAR crypto function returned status, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46672</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check the OTAR crypto function returned status, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46673 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check whether the SA is in an operational state before use, possibly leading to a bypass of the Space D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46673</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 does not check whether the SA is in an operational state before use, possibly leading to a bypass of the Space Data Link Security protocol (SDLS).</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46674 | NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 uses Extended Procedures that are a Work in Progress (not intended for use during flight), potentially leading t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46674</link><description>NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2 uses Extended Procedures that are a Work in Progress (not intended for use during flight), potentially leading to a keystream oracle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46675 | In NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2, the key state is not checked before use, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46675</link><description>In NASA CryptoLib before 1.3.2, the key state is not checked before use, potentially leading to spacecraft hijacking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 01:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3954 | ChurchCRM Referer server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3954</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in ChurchCRM 5.16.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Referer Handler. The manipulation leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46656 | python-markdownify (aka markdownify) before 0.14.1 allows large headline prefixes such as &lt;h9999999&gt; in addition to &lt;h1&gt; through &lt;h6&gt;. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46656</link><description>python-markdownify (aka markdownify) before 0.14.1 allows large headline prefixes such as  in addition to &lt;h1&gt; through &lt;h6&gt;. This causes memory consumption.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 21:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46653 | Formidable (aka node-formidable) 2.1.0 through 3.x before 3.5.3 relies on hexoid to prevent guessing of filenames for untrusted executable c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46653</link><description>Formidable (aka node-formidable) 2.1.0 through 3.x before 3.5.3 relies on hexoid to prevent guessing of filenames for untrusted executable content; however, hexoid is documented as not "cryptographically secure." (Also, there is a scenario in which only the last two characters of a hexoid string need to be guessed, but this is not often relevant.) NOTE: this does not imply that, in a typical use case, attackers will be able to exploit any hexoid behavior to upload and execute their own content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46654 | CodiMD through 2.2.0 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded JavaScript content, but it can be bypassed by uploadi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46654</link><description>CodiMD through 2.2.0 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded JavaScript content, but it can be bypassed by uploading a .html file that references an uploaded .js file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46655 | CodiMD through 2.5.4 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded SVG documents containing JavaScript, but it can be by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46655</link><description>CodiMD through 2.5.4 has a CSP-based protection mechanism against XSS through uploaded SVG documents containing JavaScript, but it can be bypassed in certain cases of different-origin file storage, such as AWS S3. NOTE: it can be considered a user error if AWS is employed for hosting untrusted JavaScript content, but the selected architecture within AWS does not have components that are able to insert Content-Security-Policy headers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 20:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46652 | In IZArc through 4.5, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. When a user performs an extraction from an archive file that bears Ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46652</link><description>In IZArc through 4.5, there is a Mark-of-the-Web Bypass Vulnerability. When a user performs an extraction from an archive file that bears Mark-of-the-Web, Mark-of-the-Web is not propagated to the extracted files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53636 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability via writefile.php of Serosoft Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR-1.0.118 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53636</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability via writefile.php of Serosoft Academia Student Information System (SIS) EagleR-1.0.118 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via ../ in the filePath parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46646 | In Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0, decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c mishandles overlong UTF-8 encoding. NOTE: this issue exists because of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46646</link><description>In Artifex Ghostscript before 10.05.0, decode_utf8 in base/gp_utf8.c mishandles overlong UTF-8 encoding. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-46954.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 14:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13812 | Anps Theme plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13812</link><description>The The Anps Theme plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2101 | Edumall &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Unauthenticated Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2101</link><description>The Edumall theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 via the 'template' parameter of the 'edumall_lazy_load_template' AJAX action. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2851 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus RPC plugins.so buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2851</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. Affected is an unknown function of the file plugins.so of the component RPC Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2850 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus Download Interface improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2850</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Download Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2811 | GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus API redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2811</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GL.iNet GL-A1300 Slate Plus, GL-AR300M16 Shadow, GL-AR300M Shadow, GL-AR750 Creta, GL-AR750S-EXT Slate, GL-AX1800 Flint, GL-AXT1800 Slate AX, GL-B1300 Convexa-B, GL-B3000 Marble, GL-BE3600 Slate 7, GL-E750, GL-E750V2 Mudi, GL-MT300N-V2 Mango, GL-MT1300 Beryl, GL-MT2500 Brume 2, GL-MT3000 Beryl AX, GL-MT6000 Flint 2, GL-SFT1200 Opal, GL-X300B Collie, GL-X750 Spitz, GL-X3000 Spitz AX, GL-XE300 Puli and GL-XE3000 Puli AX 4.x. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component API. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 07:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2907 | Order Delivery Date Pro for WooCommerce &amp;lt; 12.3.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2907</link><description>The Order Delivery Date WordPress plugin before 12.3.1 does not have authorization and CSRF checks when importing settings. Furthermore it also lacks proper checks to only update options relevant to the Order Delivery Date WordPress plugin before 12.3.1. This leads to attackers being able to modify the default_user_role to administrator and users_can_register, allowing them to register as an administrator of the site for complete site takeover.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 06:18:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1458 | Element Pack Elementor Addons (Header Footer, Template Library, Dynamic Grid, Carousel and Remote Arrows) &amp;lt;= 5.10.29 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1458</link><description>The Element Pack Addons for Elementor – Free Templates and Widgets for Your WordPress Websites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets like Dual Button, Creative Button, Image Stack and more in all versions up to, and including, 5.10.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2105 | Jupiter X Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.11 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection via PHAR</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2105</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.11 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'file' parameter of the 'raven_download_file' function. This makes it possible for attackers to inject a PHP Object through a PHAR file. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present. This vulnerability may be exploited by unauthenticated attackers when a form is present on the site with the file download action, and the ability to upload files is also present. Otherwise, this would be considered exploitable by Contributor-level users and above, because they could create the form needed to successfully exploit this.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3491 | Add custom page template &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Code Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3491</link><description>The Add custom page template plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Code Injection leading to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 via the 'acpt_validate_setting' function. This is due to insufficient sanitization of the 'template_name' parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3906 | Integração entre Eduzz e Woocommerce 1.5.0 - 1.7.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3906</link><description>The Integração entre Eduzz e Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wep_opcoes' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to edit the default registration role within the plugin's registration flow to Administrator, which allows any user to create an Administrator account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3914 | Aeropage Sync for Airtable &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3914</link><description>The Aeropage Sync for Airtable plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'aeropage_media_downloader' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3915 | Aeropage Sync for Airtable &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3915</link><description>The Aeropage Sync for Airtable plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'aeropageDeletePost' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 05:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13808 | Xpro Elementor Addons - Pro &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13808</link><description>The Xpro Elementor Addons - Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9 via the custom PHP widget. This is due to their only being client side controls when determining who can access the widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 04:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2801 | Create custom forms for WordPress with a smart form plugin for smart businesses &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2801</link><description>The The Create custom forms for WordPress with a smart form plugin for smart businesses plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 03:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>