<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-49757 | Zitadel User Registration Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49757</link><description>The open-source identity infrastructure software Zitadel allows administrators to disable the user self-registration. Due to a missing security check in versions prior to 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7, disabling the "User Registration allowed" option only hid the registration button on the login page. Users could bypass this restriction by directly accessing the registration URL (/ui/login/loginname) and register a user that way. Versions 2.64.0, 2.63.5, 2.62.7, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49753 | Denied Host Validation Bypass in Zitadel Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49753</link><description>Zitadel is open-source identity infrastructure software. Versions prior to 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 have a flaw in the URL validation mechanism of Zitadel actions allows bypassing restrictions intended to block requests to localhost (127.0.0.1). The isHostBlocked check, designed to prevent such requests, can be circumvented by creating a DNS record that resolves to 127.0.0.1. This enables actions to send requests to localhost despite the intended security measures. This vulnerability potentially allows unauthorized access to unsecured internal endpoints, which may contain sensitive information or functionalities. Versions 2.64.1, 2.63.6, 2.62.8, 2.61.4, 2.60.4, 2.59.5, and 2.58.7 contain a patch. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49380 | Plenti arbitrary file write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49380</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file write vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write vulnerability when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to Remote Code Execution. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49381 | Plenti arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49381</link><description>Plenti, a static site generator, has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in versions prior to 0.7.2. The `/postLocal` endpoint is vulnerable to an arbitrary file write deletion when a plenti user serves their website. This issue may lead to information loss. Version 0.7.2 fixes the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10380 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software ajax_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10380</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax_product.php. The manipulation of the argument drop_services leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49376 | Autolab Has Misconfigured Reset Password Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49376</link><description>Autolab, a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments, has misconfigured reset password permissions in version 3.0.0. For email-based accounts, users with insufficient privileges could reset and theoretically access privileged users' accounts by resetting their passwords. This issue is fixed in version 3.0.1. No known workarounds exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49378 | smartUp Cross-site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49378</link><description>smartUp, a web browser mouse gestures extension, has a universal cross-site scripting issue in the Edge and Firefox versions of smartUp 7.2.622.1170. The vulnerability allows another extension to execute arbitrary code in the context of the user’s tab. As of time of publication, no known patches exist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10381 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in Matrix Door Controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10381</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Matrix Door Controller Cosec Vega FAXQ due to improper implementation of session management at the web-based management interface. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted http request on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow remote attacker to gain unauthorized access and take complete control of the targeted device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9991 | Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information Vulnerability in Philips Lighting Devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9991</link><description>This vulnerability exists in Philips lighting devices due to storage of Wi-Fi credentials in plain text within the device firmware. An attacker with physical access could exploit this by extracting the firmware and analyzing the binary data to obtain the plaintext Wi-Fi credentials stored on the vulnerable device.

Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow an attacker to gain unauthorized access to the Wi-Fi network to which vulnerable device is connected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10378 | ESAFENET CDG CDGRenewApplicationService.java actionViewCDGRenewFile sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10378</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected is the function actionViewCDGRenewFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/CDGRenewApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument CDGRenewFileId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10379 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionViewDecyptFile path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function actionViewDecyptFile of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument decryptFileId with the input ../../../Windows/System32/drivers/etc/hosts leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The affected function has a typo and is missing an R. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10374 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.4.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_loginout Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10374</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_loginout shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10376 | ESAFENET CDG AutoSignService.java actionPassOrNotAutoSign sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10376</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function actionPassOrNotAutoSign of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/service/processsign/AutoSignService.java. The manipulation of the argument UniqueId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10377 | ESAFENET CDG DecryptApplicationService.java actionPassDecryptApplication1 sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10377</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function actionPassDecryptApplication1 of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/client/DecryptApplicationService.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This is a different issue than CVE-2024-10069. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47483 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47483</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0 and 1.1.0.0, contain(s) an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47481 | Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47481</link><description>Dell Data Lakehouse, version(s) 1.0.0.0, 1.1.0., contain(s) an Improper Access Control vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker with adjacent network access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:13:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44098 | In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44098</link><description>In lwis_device_event_states_clear_locked of lwis_event.c, there is a possible privilege escalation due to a double free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44099 | There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44099</link><description>There is a possible Local bypass of user interaction due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44100 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44100</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44101 | there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44101</link><description>there is a possible Null Pointer Dereference (modem crash) due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47012 | In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47012</link><description>In mm_GetMobileIdIndexForNsUpdate of mm_GmmPduCodec.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47013 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47013</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible arbitrary write due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47014 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47014</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47015 | In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47015</link><description>In ProtocolMiscHwConfigChangeAdapter::GetData() of protocolmiscadapter.cpp, there is a possible out-of-bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47016 | there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addition...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47016</link><description>there is a possible privilege escalation due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47017 | In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47017</link><description>In ufshc_scsi_cmd of ufs.c, there is a possible stack variable use after free due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47018 | In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47018</link><description>In pmucal_rae_handle_seq_int of flexpmu_cal_rae.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47019 | In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47019</link><description>In ProtocolEmbmsSaiListAdapter::Init() of protocolembmsadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47020 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47020</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47021 | In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47021</link><description>In sms_ExtractCbLanguage of sms_CellBroadcast.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47022 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47022</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47023 | there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47023</link><description>there is a possible man-in-the-middle attack due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47024 | In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47024</link><description>In vring_size of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47025 | In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47025</link><description>In ppmp_protect_buf of drm_fw.c, there is a possible information disclosure due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47026 | In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47026</link><description>In gsc_gsa_rescue of gsc_gsa.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47027 | In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47027</link><description>In sm_mem_compat_get_vmm_obj of lib/sm/shared_mem.c, there is a possible arbitrary physical memory access due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47028 | In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47028</link><description>In ffu_flash_pack of ffu.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47029 | In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47029</link><description>In TrustySharedMemoryManager::GetSharedMemory of ondevice/trusty/trusty_shared_memory_manager.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47030 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47030</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47031 | N/A</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47031</link><description>N/A</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47033 | In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47033</link><description>In lwis_allocator_free of lwis_allocator.c, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47034 | there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47034</link><description>there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47035 | In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47035</link><description>In vring_init of external/headers/include/virtio/virtio_ring.h, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47041 | In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47041</link><description>In valid_address of syscall.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10016 | File Upload Types by WPForms &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10016</link><description>The File Upload Types by WPForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10112 | Simple News &amp;lt;= 2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via news Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10112</link><description>The Simple News plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'news' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10343 | Beek Widget Extention &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10343</link><description>The Beek Widget Extention plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 0.9.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8666 | Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8666</link><description>The Shoutcast Icecast HTML5 Radio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'html5radio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:46:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45785 | MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45785</link><description>MUSASI version 3 contains an issue with use of client-side authentication. If this vulnerability is exploited, other users' credential and sensitive information may be retrieved.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47158 | N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47158</link><description>N-LINE 2.0.6 and prior versions contain a code injection vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, arbitrary code may be executed on the instructor's browser, or the instructor may be directed to a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10150 | Bamazoo – Button Generator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via dgs Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10150</link><description>The Bamazoo – Button Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's dgs shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10341 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10341</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10342 | League of Legends Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10342</link><description>The League of Legends Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9598 | AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages &amp;lt;= 1.0.99.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9598</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.99.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'proxy' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send the logged in user's cookies to their own server via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9628 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Unauthorized Access to Telegram Bot API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9628</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data and loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'Wps_Telegram_Chat_Admin::checkСonnection' function in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to have full access to the Telegram Bot API endpoint and communicate with it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9630 | WPS Telegram Chat &amp;lt;= 4.5.4 - Missing Authorization to Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9630</link><description>The WPS Telegram Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass due to a missing capability check when accessing messages in versions up to, and including, 4.5.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view the messages that are sent through the Telegram Bot API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50583 | Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission sett...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50583</link><description>Whale browser Installer before 3.1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute a malicious DLL in the user environment due to improper permission settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10011 | BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 14.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10011</link><description>The BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 14.1.0 via the id parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to perform actions on files outside of the originally intended directory and enables file uploads to directories outside of the web root. Depending on server configuration it may be possible to upload files with double extensions. This vulnerability only affects Windows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10148 | Awesome buttons &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via btn2 Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10148</link><description>The Awesome buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's btn2 shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9235 | Mapster WP Maps &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9235</link><description>The Mapster WP Maps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to an insufficient capability check on the mapster_wp_maps_set_option_from_js() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9302 | App Builder – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Flight &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Privilege Escalation and Account Takeover via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9302</link><description>The App Builder – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Flight plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This is due to the verify_otp_forgot_password() and update_password() functions not having enough controls to prevent a successful brute force attack of the OTP to change a password, or verify that a password reset request came from an authorized user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to generate and brute force an OTP that makes it possible to change any users passwords, including an administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9607 | 10Web Social Post Feed &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9607</link><description>The 10Web Social Post Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.9. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note this is only exploitable when the leave a review notice is present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42420 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42420</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs contain multiple Out-of-bounds Read vulnerabilities, due to improper processing of keyword search input and improper processing of SOAP messages.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43424 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.&#13;
Crafted HTTP requests...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43424</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP request headers, resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45829 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45829</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide the web page to download data, where query parameters in HTTP requests are improperly processed and resulting in an Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability.
Crafted HTTP requests may cause affected products crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45842 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.&#13;
Unintended interna...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45842</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process URI data in HTTP PUT requests resulting in a path Traversal vulnerability.
Unintended internal files may be retrieved when processing crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47005 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficient...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47005</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs provide configuration related APIs. They are expected to be called by administrative users only, but insufficiently restricted.
A non-administrative user may execute some configuration APIs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47406 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47406</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process HTTP authentication requests, resulting in an authentication bypass vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47549 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47549</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, which may allow contamination of unintended data to HTTP response headers.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47801 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47801</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly process query parameters in HTTP requests, resulting in a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability.
Accessing a crafted URL which points to an affected product may cause malicious script executed on the web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48870 | Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48870</link><description>Sharp and Toshiba Tec MFPs improperly validate input data in URI data registration, resulting in a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability.
If crafted input is stored by an administrative user, malicious script may be executed on the web browsers of other victim users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:44:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9109 | UPS Live Rates and Access Points &amp;lt;= 2.3.11 - Missing Authorization to Plugin API key reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9109</link><description>The WooCommerce UPS Shipping – Live Rates and Access Points plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_oauth_data function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete the plugin's API key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9488 | Comments – wpDiscuz &amp;lt;= 7.6.24 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9488</link><description>The Comments – wpDiscuz plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.24. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 05:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9686 | Order Notification for Telegram &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Send Telegram Test Message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9686</link><description>The Order Notification for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized test message sending due to a missing capability check on the 'nktgnfw_send_test_message' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send a test message via the Telegram Bot API to the user configured in the settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10372 | chidiwilliams buzz model_loader.py download_model temp file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10372</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in chidiwilliams buzz 1.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function download_model of the file buzz/model_loader.py. The manipulation leads to insecure temporary file. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 02:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10368 | Codezips Sales Management System addstock.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addstock.php. The manipulation of the argument prodtype leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10369 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustcom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10369</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /addcustcom.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10370 | Codezips Sales Management System addcustind.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10370</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Sales Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /addcustind.php. The manipulation of the argument refno leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10371 | SourceCodester Payroll Management System main login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10371</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Payroll Management System 1.0. This affects the function login of the file main. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10354 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10354</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/print.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10355 | SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10355</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petrol Pump Management Software 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 01:43:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10351 | Tenda RX9 Pro POST Request setMacFilterCfg sub_424CE0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10351</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX9 Pro 22.03.02.20. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sub_424CE0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg of the component POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10353 | SourceCodester Online Exam System admin-dashboard access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10353</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Exam System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin-dashboard. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This affects a different product and is a different issue than CVE-2024-40480.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10350 | code-projects Hospital Management System add-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10350</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-doctor.php. The manipulation of the argument docname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 23:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10348 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System Manage Tenant Details index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10348</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?page=tenants of the component Manage Tenant Details. The manipulation of the argument Last Name/First Name/Middle Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only shows the field "Last Name" to be affected. Other fields might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10349 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System ajax.php delete_tenant sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10349</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function delete_tenant of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_tenant. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49750 | Snowflake Connector for Python has sensitive data in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49750</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Prior to version 3.12.3, when the logging level was set by the user to DEBUG, the Connector could have logged Duo passcodes (when specified via the `passcode` parameter) and Azure SAS tokens. Additionally, the SecretDetector logging formatter, if enabled, contained bugs which caused it to not fully redact JWT tokens and certain private key formats. Snowflake released version 3.12.3 of the Snowflake Connector for Python, which fixes the issue. In addition to upgrading, users should review their logs for any potentially sensitive information that may have been captured.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 22:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41617 | Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The `redirect_if_not_loggedin` function in `...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41617</link><description>Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The `redirect_if_not_loggedin` function in `functions_security.php` fails to terminate script execution after redirecting unauthenticated users. This flaw allows an unauthenticated attacker to upload arbitrary files, potentially leading to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41618 | Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the `transaction_delete_group` function. The vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41618</link><description>Money Manager EX WebApp (web-money-manager-ex) 1.2.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the `transaction_delete_group` function. The vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user input in the `TrDeleteArr` parameter, which is directly incorporated into an SQL query.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49762 | Pterodactyl Panel has plain-text logging of user passwords when two-factor authentication is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49762</link><description>Pterodactyl is a free, open-source game server management panel. When a user disables two-factor authentication via the Panel, a `DELETE` request with their current password in a query parameter will be sent.  While query parameters are encrypted when using TLS, many webservers (including ones officially documented for use with Pterodactyl) will log query parameters in plain-text, storing a user's password in plain text. Prior to version 1.11.8, if a malicious user obtains access to these logs they could potentially authenticate against a user's account; assuming they are able to discover the account's email address or username separately. This problem has been patched in version 1.11.8. There are no workarounds at this time. There is not a direct vulnerability within the software as it relates to logs generated by intermediate components such as web servers or Layer 7 proxies. Updating to `v1.11.8` or adding the linked patch manually are the only ways to avoid this problem. As this vulnerability relates to historical logging of sensitive data, users who have ever disabled 2FA on a Panel (self-hosted or operated by a company) should change their passwords and consider enabling 2FA if it was left disabled. While it's unlikely that their account swill be compromised by this vulnerability, it's not impossible. Panel administrators should consider clearing any access logs that may contain sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49359 | ZimaOS vulnerable to Directory Listing via Parameter Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49359</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v2_1/file` in ZimaOS is vulnerable to a directory traversal attack, allowing authenticated users to list the contents of any directory on the server. By manipulating the path parameter, attackers can access sensitive system directories such as `/etc`, potentially exposing critical configuration files and increasing the risk of further attacks. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49760 | OpenRefine has a path traversal in LoadLanguageCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49760</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. The load-language command expects a `lang` parameter from which it constructs the path of the localization file to load, of the form `translations-$LANG.json`. But when doing so in versions prior to 3.8.3, it does not check that the resulting path is in the expected directory, which means that this command could be exploited to read other JSON files on the file system. Version 3.8.3 addresses this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49357 | ZimaOS (Installed Applications and System Information) has Unauthorized Sensitive Data Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49357</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoints in ZimaOS, such as `http:///v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/app_order.json` and `http:///v1/users/image?path=/var/lib/casaos/1/system.json`, expose sensitive data like installed applications and system information without requiring any authentication or authorization. This sensitive data leak can be exploited by attackers to gain detailed knowledge about the system setup, installed applications, and other critical information. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49358 | ZimaOS vulnerable to Username Enumeration via API Responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49358</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v1/users/login` in ZimaOS returns distinct responses based on whether a username exists or the password is incorrect. This behavior can be exploited for username enumeration, allowing attackers to determine whether a user exists in the system or not. Attackers can leverage this information in further attacks, such as credential stuffing or targeted password brute-forcing. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48423 | An issue in assimp v.5.4.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the CallbackToLogRedirector function within the Assimp libr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48423</link><description>An issue in assimp v.5.4.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the CallbackToLogRedirector function within the Assimp library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48932 | ZimaOS Unauthenticated API Discloses Usernames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48932</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the API endpoint `http:///v1/users/name` allows unauthenticated users to access sensitive information, such as usernames, without any authorization. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to enumerate usernames and leverage them for further attacks, such as brute-force or phishing campaigns. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 21:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48424 | A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability has been identified in the OpenDDLParser::parseStructure function within the Assimp library, specifical...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48424</link><description>A heap-buffer-overflow vulnerability has been identified in the OpenDDLParser::parseStructure function within the Assimp library, specifically during the processing of OpenGEX files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48426 | A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the SortByPTypeProcess::Execute function in the Assimp library during fuzz testing with AddressS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48426</link><description>A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the SortByPTypeProcess::Execute function in the Assimp library during fuzz testing with AddressSanitizer. The crash occurred due to a read access to an invalid memory address (0x1000c9714971).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48931 | ZimaOS Arbitrary File Read via Parameter Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48931</link><description>ZimaOS is a fork of CasaOS, an operating system for Zima devices and x86-64 systems with UEFI. In version 1.2.4 and all prior versions, the ZimaOS API endpoint `http:///v3/file?token=&amp;amp;files=` is vulnerable to arbitrary file reading due to improper input validation. By manipulating the `files` parameter, authenticated users can read sensitive system files, including `/etc/shadow`, which contains password hashes for all users. This vulnerability exposes critical system data and poses a high risk for privilege escalation or system compromise. The vulnerability occurs because the API endpoint does not validate or restrict file paths provided via the `files` parameter. An attacker can exploit this by manipulating the file path to access sensitive files outside the intended directory. As of time of publication, no known patched versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48425 | A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the Assimp::SplitLargeMeshesProcess_Triangle::UpdateNode function within the Assimp library duri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48425</link><description>A segmentation fault (SEGV) was detected in the Assimp::SplitLargeMeshesProcess_Triangle::UpdateNode function within the Assimp library during fuzz testing using AddressSanitizer. The crash occurs due to a read access violation at address 0x000000000460, which points to the zero page, indicating a null or invalid pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47882 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s error page lacks escaping, leading to potential Cross-site Scripting on import of malicious project</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47882</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the built-in "Something went wrong!" error page includes the exception message and exception traceback without escaping HTML tags, enabling injection into the page if an attacker can reliably produce an error with an attacker-influenced message. It appears that the only way to reach this code in OpenRefine itself is for an attacker to somehow convince a victim to import a malicious file, which may be difficult.  However, out-of-tree extensions may add their own calls to `respondWithErrorPage`. Version 3.8.3 has a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47883 | Butterfly has path/URL confusion in resource handling leading to multiple weaknesses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47883</link><description>The OpenRefine fork of the MIT Simile Butterfly server is a modular web application framework. The Butterfly framework uses the `java.net.URL` class to refer to (what are expected to be) local resource files, like images or templates. This works: "opening a connection" to these URLs opens the local file. However, prior to version 1.2.6, if a `file:/` URL is directly given where a relative path (resource name) is expected, this is also accepted in some code paths; the app then fetches the file, from a remote machine if indicated, and uses it as if it was a trusted part of the app's codebase. This leads to multiple weaknesses and potential weaknesses. An attacker that has network access to the application could use it to gain access to files, either on the the server's filesystem (path traversal) or shared by nearby machines (server-side request forgery with e.g. SMB). An attacker that can lead or redirect a user to a crafted URL belonging to the app could cause arbitrary attacker-controlled JavaScript to be loaded in the victim's browser (cross-site scripting). If an app is written in such a way that an attacker can influence the resource name used for a template, that attacker could cause the app to fetch and execute an attacker-controlled template (remote code execution). Version 1.2.6 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:47:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47881 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s SQLite integration allows filesystem access, remote code execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47881</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Starting in version 3.4-beta and prior to version 3.8.3, in the `database` extension, the "enable_load_extension" property can be set for the SQLite integration, enabling an attacker to load (local or remote) extension DLLs and so run arbitrary code on the server. The attacker needs to have network access to the OpenRefine instance. Version 3.8.3 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10327 | A vulnerability in Okta Verify for iOS versions 9.25.1 (beta) and 9.27.0 (including beta) allows push notification responses through the iOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10327</link><description>A vulnerability in Okta Verify for iOS versions 9.25.1 (beta) and 9.27.0 (including beta) allows push notification responses through the iOS ContextExtension feature allowing the authentication to proceed regardless of the user’s selection. When a user long-presses the notification banner and selects an option, both options allow the authentication to succeed. 
The ContextExtension feature is one of several push mechanisms available when using Okta Verify Push on iOS devices. The vulnerable flows include: 
* When a user is presented with a notification on a locked screen, the user presses on the notification directly and selects their reply without unlocking the device; 
* When a user is presented with a notification on the home screen and drags the notification down and selects their reply; 
* When an Apple Watch is used to reply directly to a notification. 

 A pre-condition for this vulnerability is that the user must have enrolled in Okta Verify while the Okta customer was using Okta Classic. This applies irrespective of whether the organization has since upgraded to Okta Identity Engine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45260 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. Users who belong to unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45260</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. Users who belong to unauthorized groups can invoke any interface of the device, thereby gaining complete control over it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45261 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The SID generated for a spe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45261</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The SID generated for a specific user is not tied to that user itself, which allows other users to potentially use it for authentication. Once an attacker bypasses the application's authentication procedures, they can generate a valid SID, escalate privileges, and gain full control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45262 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The params parameter in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45262</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The params parameter in the call method of the /rpc endpoint is vulnerable to arbitrary directory traversal, which enables attackers to execute scripts under any path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45263 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The upload interface allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45263</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. The upload interface allows the uploading of arbitrary files to the device. Once the device executes the files, it can lead to information leakage, enabling complete control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47878 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability (XSS) in GData extension (authorized.vt)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47878</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the `/extension/gdata/authorized` endpoint includes the `state` GET parameter verbatim in a `</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47879 | OpenRefine&amp;#x27;s PreviewExpressionCommand, which is eval, lacks protection against cross-site request forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47879</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, lack of cross-site request forgery protection on the `preview-expression` command means that visiting a malicious website could cause an attacker-controlled expression to be executed. The expression can contain arbitrary Clojure or Python code. The attacker must know a valid project ID of a project that contains at least one row, and the attacker must convince the victim to open a malicious webpage. Version 3.8.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47880 | OpenRefine has a reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability from POST request in ExportRowsCommand</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47880</link><description>OpenRefine is a free, open source tool for working with messy data. Prior to version 3.8.3, the `export-rows` command can be used in such a way that it reflects part of the request verbatim, with a Content-Type header also taken from the request. An attacker could lead a user to a malicious page that submits a form POST that contains  embedded JavaScript code. This code would then be included in the response, along with an attacker-controlled `Content-Type` header, and so potentially executed in the victim's browser as if it was part of OpenRefine. The attacker-provided code can do anything the user can do, including deleting projects, retrieving database passwords, or executing arbitrary Jython or Closure expressions, if those extensions are also present. The attacker must know a valid project ID of a project that contains at least one row. Version 3.8.3 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48208 | pure-ftpd before 1.0.52 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is an out of bounds read in the domlsd() function of the ls.c file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48208</link><description>pure-ftpd before 1.0.52 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. There is an out of bounds read in the domlsd() function of the ls.c file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7763 | WhatsUp Gold getReport Missing Authentication Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7763</link><description>In WhatsUp Gold versions released before 2024.0.0, 

an Authentication Bypass issue exists which allows an attacker to obtain encrypted user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45242 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT A8J-ENH1350EXT devices through 3.9.3.2_c1.9.51 allow (blind) OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45242</link><description>EnGenius ENH1350EXT A8J-ENH1350EXT devices through 3.9.3.2_c1.9.51 allow (blind) OS Command Injection via shell metacharacters to the Ping or Speed Test utility. During the time of initial setup, the device creates an open unsecured network whose admin panel is configured with the default credentials of admin/admin. An unauthorized attacker in proximity to the Wi-Fi network can exploit this window of time to execute arbitrary OS commands with root-level permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45259 | An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. By intercepting an HTTP req...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45259</link><description>An issue was discovered on certain GL-iNet devices, including MT6000, MT3000, MT2500, AXT1800, and AX1800 4.6.2. By intercepting an HTTP request and changing the filename property in the download interface, any file on the device can be deleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47173 | Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface denial of service vulnerability in SaaS and marketplace setups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47173</link><description>Aimeos is an e-commerce framework. All SaaS and marketplace setups using the Aimeos GraphQL API admin interface version from 2024.04 up to 2024.07.1 are affected by a potential denial of service attack. Version 2024.07.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:16:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48427 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48427</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Sourcecodester Packers and Movers Management System v1.0 allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter in /mpms/admin/?page=services/manage_service&amp;id</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46998 | baserCMS has a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Edit Email Form Settings Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46998</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Edit Email Form Settings Feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48144 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Fusion Chat Chat AI Assistant Ask Me Anything v1.2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48144</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Fusion Chat Chat AI Assistant Ask Me Anything v1.2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48145 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Netangular Technologies ChatNet AI Version v1.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48145</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Netangular Technologies ChatNet AI Version v1.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46996 | baserCMS has a Cross-site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Blog posts Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46996</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in the Blog posts feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48140 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica Your AI Copilot powered by ChatGPT4 v6.3.0 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48140</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica Your AI Copilot powered by ChatGPT4 v6.3.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48141 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Zhipu AI CodeGeeX v2.17.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48141</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Zhipu AI CodeGeeX v2.17.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48142 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica ChatGPT AI Assistant v2.4.0 allows attackers to access an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48142</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Butterfly Effect Limited Monica ChatGPT AI Assistant v2.4.0 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48143 | A lack of rate limiting in the OTP validation component of Digitory Multi Channel Integrated POS v1.0 allows attackers to gain access to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48143</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the OTP validation component of Digitory Multi Channel Integrated POS v1.0 allows attackers to gain access to the ordering system and place an excessive amount of food orders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46994 | baserCMS has Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in Blog posts and Contents list Feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46994</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in Blog posts and Contents list Feature. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46995 | baserCMS has Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in HTTP 400 Bad Request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46995</link><description>baserCMS is a website development framework. Versions prior to 5.1.2 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability in HTTP 400 Bad Request. Version 5.1.2 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48139 | A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Blackbox AI v1.3.95 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48139</link><description>A prompt injection vulnerability in the chatbox of Blackbox AI v1.3.95 allows attackers to access and exfiltrate all previous and subsequent chat data between the user and the AI assistant via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48454 | An issue in SourceCodester Purchase Order Management System v1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /admin?page=user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48454</link><description>An issue in SourceCodester Purchase Order Management System v1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the /admin?page=user component</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10337 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10337</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/home.php?con=add. The manipulation of the argument cat/subcat/ t1/t2/text leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10338 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System home.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10338</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/home.php. The manipulation of the argument view/view1 leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48442 | Incorrect access control in Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48442</link><description>Incorrect access control in Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 allows attackers to access the SSH protocol without authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48514 | php-heic-to-jpg &lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to remote code execution. An attacker who can upload heic images is able to execute code on the remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48514</link><description>php-heic-to-jpg &lt;= 1.0.5 is vulnerable to remote code execution. An attacker who can upload heic images is able to execute code on the remote server via the file name. As a result, the CIA is no longer guaranteed. This affects php-heic-to-jpg 1.0.5 and below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10295 | Gateway: apicast basic auth bypass via malformed base64 headerssending non-base64 &amp;#x27;basic&amp;#x27; auth with special characters causes apicast to incorrectly authenticate a request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10295</link><description>A flaw was found in Gateway. Sending a non-base64 'basic' auth with special characters can cause APICast to incorrectly authenticate a request. A malformed basic authentication header containing special characters bypasses authentication and allows unauthorized access to the backend. This issue can occur due to a failure in the base64 decoding process, which causes APICast to skip the rest of the authentication checks and proceed with routing the request upstream.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48440 | Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 was discovered to contain a command ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48440</link><description>Shenzhen Tuoshi Network Communications Co.,Ltd 5G CPE Router NR500-EA RG500UEAABxCOMSLICv3.2.2543.12.18 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the component at_command.asp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48441 | Wuhan Tianyu Information Industry Co., Ltd Tianyu CPE Router CommonCPExCPETS_v3.2.468.11.04_P4 was discovered to contain a command injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48441</link><description>Wuhan Tianyu Information Industry Co., Ltd Tianyu CPE Router CommonCPExCPETS_v3.2.468.11.04_P4 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the component at_command.asp.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10313 | iniNet Solutions SpiderControl SCADA PC HMI Editor Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10313</link><description>iniNet Solutions SpiderControl SCADA PC HMI Editor has a path traversal 
vulnerability. When the software loads a malicious ‘ems' project 
template file constructed by an attacker, it can write files to 
arbitrary directories. This can lead to overwriting system files, 
causing system paralysis, or writing to startup items, resulting in 
remote control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:50:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46478 | HTMLDOC v1.9.18 contains a buffer overflow in parse_pre function,ps-pdf.cxx:5681.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46478</link><description>HTMLDOC v1.9.18 contains a buffer overflow in parse_pre function,ps-pdf.cxx:5681.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38314 | IBM Maximo Application Suite - Monitor Component information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38314</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite - Monitor Component 8.10, 8.11, and 9.0 could disclose information in the form of the hard-coded cryptographic key to an attacker that has compromised environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48547 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of DreamCatcher Life v1.8.7 allows attackers to access sensitive info...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48547</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of DreamCatcher Life v1.8.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48548 | The APK file in Cloud Smart Lock v2.0.1 has a leaked a URL that can call an API for binding physical devices. This vulnerability allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48548</link><description>The APK file in Cloud Smart Lock v2.0.1 has a leaked a URL that can call an API for binding physical devices. This vulnerability allows attackers to arbitrarily construct a request to use the app to bind to unknown devices by finding a valid serial number via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40810 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. An app may be able to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40810</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. An app may be able to cause a coprocessor crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44141 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. A person with physical access to an unlocked Mac may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44141</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sonoma 14.6. A person with physical access to an unlocked Mac may be able to gain root code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44185 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44185</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may lead to an unexpected process crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44205 | A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.8, macOS Monte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44205</link><description>A privacy issue was addressed with improved private data redaction for log entries. This issue is fixed in macOS Ventura 13.6.8, macOS Monterey 12.7.6, iOS 16.7.9 and iPadOS 16.7.9, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. A sandboxed app may be able to access sensitive user data in system logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44206 | An issue in the handling of URL protocols was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, wa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44206</link><description>An issue in the handling of URL protocols was addressed with improved logic. This issue is fixed in tvOS 17.6, visionOS 1.3, Safari 17.6, watchOS 10.6, iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6, macOS Sonoma 14.6. A user may be able to bypass some web content restrictions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48544 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Sylvania Smart Home v3.0.3 allows attackers to access sensitive in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48544</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Sylvania Smart Home v3.0.3 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48545 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of IVY Smart v4.5.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48545</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of IVY Smart v4.5.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10335 | SourceCodester Garbage Collection Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10335</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Garbage Collection Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "username" to be affected. But it must be assumed that the parameter "password" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10336 | SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System Admin Login Page index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10336</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodeHero Clothes Recommendation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/index.php of the component Admin Login Page. The manipulation of the argument t1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48542 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Yamaha Headphones Controller v1.6.7 allows attackers to access sen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48542</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Yamaha Headphones Controller v1.6.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48546 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Wear Sync v1.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48546</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Wear Sync v1.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48539 | Neye3C v4.5.2.0 was discovered to contain a hardcoded encryption key in the firmware update mechanism.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48539</link><description>Neye3C v4.5.2.0 was discovered to contain a hardcoded encryption key in the firmware update mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48540 | Incorrect access control in XIAO HE Smart 4.3.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48540</link><description>Incorrect access control in XIAO HE Smart 4.3.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48541 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Ruochan Smart v4.4.7 allows attackers to access sensitive informat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48541</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Ruochan Smart v4.4.7 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9692 | Improper Access Control in Input in VIMESA VHF/FM Transmitter Blue Plus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9692</link><description>VIMESA VHF/FM Transmitter Blue Plus is suffering from a Denial-of-Service (DoS) vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker can issue an unauthorized HTTP GET request to the unprotected endpoint 'doreboot' and restart the transmitter operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48538 | Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Neye3C v4.5.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48538</link><description>Incorrect access control in the firmware update and download processes of Neye3C v4.5.2.0 allows attackers to access sensitive information by analyzing the code and data within the APK file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45031 | Apache Syncope: Stored XSS in Console and Enduser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45031</link><description>When editing objects in the Syncope Console, incomplete HTML tags could be used to bypass HTML sanitization. This made it possible to inject stored XSS payloads which would trigger for other users during ordinary usage of the application.
XSS payloads could also be injected in Syncope Enduser when editing “Personal Information” or “User Requests”: such payloads would trigger for administrators in Syncope Console, thus enabling session hijacking.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.9, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10180 | Contact Form 7 - Repeatable Fields &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via field_group Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10180</link><description>The Contact Form 7 – Repeatable Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's field_group shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49693 | WordPress Mega Elements – Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kraftplugins Mega Elements allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mega Elements: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49695 | WordPress WP Flow Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spiffy Plugins WP Flow Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Flow Plus: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49696 | WordPress Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.21 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RoboSoft Robo Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Robo Gallery: from n/a through 3.2.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10332 | A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in Janto v4.3r11 from Impronta. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10332</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in Janto v4.3r11 from Impronta. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending the victim a malicious URL using the endpoint “/abonados/public/janto/main.php”.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49702 | WordPress myCred Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCRED myCred Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49681 | WordPress WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49681</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SWIT WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Sessions Time Monitoring Full Automatic: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49691 | WordPress Product Filter by WBW plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49691</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Woobewoo Product Filter by WBW allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Product Filter by WBW: from n/a through 2.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49703 | WordPress WpEvently plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49703</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MagePeople Team Event Manager for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Event Manager for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49682 | WordPress Simple Membership plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49682</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in smp7, wp.Insider Simple Membership allows Phishing.This issue affects Simple Membership: from n/a through 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49683 | WordPress Schema &amp;amp; Structured Data for WP &amp;amp; AMP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49683</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5608 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5608</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions below 8121 are vulnerable to SQL Injection in the technician reports feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8959 | WP Adminify – Best WordPress Custom Dashboard Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8959</link><description>The WP Adminify – Custom WordPress Dashboard, Login and Admin Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10176 | Compact WP Audio Player &amp;lt;= 1.9.13 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via sc_embed_player Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10176</link><description>The Compact WP Audio Player plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 
sc_embed_player shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.13 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10331 | PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System search-vehicle.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10331</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Vehicle Record System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/search-vehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument searchinputdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9214 | Extra Product Options Builder for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.133 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9214</link><description>The Extra Product Options Builder for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'RednaoSerializedFields' parameter during the creation of a signature file in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.133 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9650 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 9.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;tooltip&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9650</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tooltip’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 9.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6826 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6826</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 11.2 before 17.3.6, 17.4 before 17.4.3, and 17.5 before 17.5.1. A denial of service could occur via importing a malicious crafted XML manifest file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 09:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8312 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8312</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 17.3.6, 17.4 before 17.4.3, and 17.5 before 17.5.1. An attacker could inject HTML into the Global Search field on a diff view leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 09:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10050 | Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder &amp;lt;= 1.6.43 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Disclosure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10050</link><description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.43 via the hfe_template shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to view the contents of Draft, Private and Password-protected posts they do not own.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 08:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8717 | PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook, PDF embed, PDF viewer – DearFlip &amp;lt;= 2.3.32 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8717</link><description>The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook, PDF embed, PDF viewer – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pdf_source' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.32 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6049 | Unauthenticated Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6049</link><description>The web server of Lawo AG vsm LTC Time Sync (vTimeSync) is affected by a "..." (triple dot) path traversal vulnerability. By sending a specially crafted HTTP request, an unauthenticated remote attacker could download arbitrary files from the operating system. As a limitation, the exploitation is only possible if the requested file has some file extension, e. g. .exe or .txt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8667 | HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.10.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Publication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8667</link><description>The HurryTimer – An Scarcity and Urgency Countdown Timer for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post publication due to a missing capability check on the activateCampaign() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to publish arbitrary posts like ones they have submitted for review, or a site administrator has in draft.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9531 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Missing Authorization to Forged Vendor Profile Deletion Email Sending</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9531</link><description>The MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'mvx_sent_deactivation_request' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to send a canned email to the site's administrator asking to delete the profile of an arbitrary vendor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9943 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Vendor Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9943</link><description>The MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on several functions in api/class-mvx-rest-controller.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update vendor account details, create vendor accounts, and delete arbitrary users via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 07:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9864 | EventPrime – Modern Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9864</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ticket names in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when front-end users can submit new events with tickets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9865 | EventPrime – Modern Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets &amp;lt;= 4.0.4.7 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Transaction Log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9865</link><description>The EventPrime – Events Calendar, Bookings and Tickets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ep_booking_attendee_fields’ fields in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the transaction log for a booking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40595 | An authentication-bypass issue in the RDP component of One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Sessions (SPS) On Premise before 7.5.1 (and LTS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40595</link><description>An authentication-bypass issue in the RDP component of One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Sessions (SPS) On Premise before 7.5.1 (and LTS before 7.0.5.1) allows man-in-the-middle attackers to obtain access to privileged sessions on target resources by intercepting cleartext RDP protocol information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 05:25:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9374 | Terms descriptions &amp;lt;= 3.4.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9374</link><description>The Terms descriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 04:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50355 | HCL Sametime is impacted by generation of error messages containing sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50355</link><description>HCL Sametime is impacted by the error messages containing sensitive information.  An attacker can use this information to launch another, more focused attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40431 | A lack of input validation in Realtek SD card reader driver before 10.0.26100.21374 through the implementation of the IOCTL_SCSI_PASS_THROUG...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40431</link><description>A lack of input validation in Realtek SD card reader driver before 10.0.26100.21374 through the implementation of the IOCTL_SCSI_PASS_THROUGH control of the SD card reader driver allows an attacker to write to predictable kernel memory locations, even as a low-privileged user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40432 | A lack of input validation in Realtek SD card reader driver before 10.0.26100.21374 through the implementation of the IOCTL_SFFDISK_DEVICE_C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40432</link><description>A lack of input validation in Realtek SD card reader driver before 10.0.26100.21374 through the implementation of the IOCTL_SFFDISK_DEVICE_COMMAND control of the SD card reader driver allows a privileged attacker to crash the OS.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48213 | RockOA v2.6.5 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in webmain/system/beifen/beifenAction.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48213</link><description>RockOA v2.6.5 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in webmain/system/beifen/beifenAction.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10300 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System View Enquiry Page view-enquiry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10300</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/view-enquiry.php of the component View Enquiry Page. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 19:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10301 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System Search search-medicalcard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10301</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/search-medicalcard.php of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 19:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10299 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System Managecard View Detail Page view-card-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10299</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/view-card-detail.php of the component Managecard View Detail Page. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 19:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10298 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System Managecard Edit Card Detail Page edit-card-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10298</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-card-detail.php of the component Managecard Edit Card Detail Page. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48963 | The package Snyk CLI before 1.1294.0 is vulnerable to Code Injection when scanning an untrusted PHP project. The vulnerability can be trigge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48963</link><description>The package Snyk CLI before 1.1294.0 is vulnerable to Code Injection when scanning an untrusted PHP project. The vulnerability can be triggered if Snyk test is run inside the untrusted project due to the improper handling of the current working directory name. Snyk recommends only scanning trusted projects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48964 | The package Snyk CLI before 1.1294.0 is vulnerable to Code Injection when scanning an untrusted Gradle project. The vulnerability can be tri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48964</link><description>The package Snyk CLI before 1.1294.0 is vulnerable to Code Injection when scanning an untrusted Gradle project. The vulnerability can be triggered if Snyk test is run inside the untrusted project due to the improper handling of the current working directory name. Snyk recommends only scanning trusted projects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20473 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20473</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20481 | A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN (RAVPN) service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20481</link><description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN (RAVPN) service of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) of the RAVPN service.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to resource exhaustion. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of VPN authentication requests to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust resources, resulting in a DoS of the RAVPN service on the affected device. Depending on the impact of the attack, a reload of the device may be required to restore the RAVPN service. Services that are not related to VPN are not affected.
&#13; Cisco Talos discussed these attacks in the blog post Large-scale brute-force activity targeting VPNs, SSH services with commonly used login credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20482 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Manageme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20482</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to elevate privileges on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have a valid account on the device that is configured with a custom read-only role.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of role permissions in part of the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a write operation on the affected part of the web-based management interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to modify certain parts of the configuration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20485 | A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20485</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN web server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a specific file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20493 | A vulnerability in the login authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) So...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20493</link><description>A vulnerability in the login authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to deny further VPN user authentications for several minutes, resulting in a temporary denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to ineffective handling of memory resources during the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted packets, which could cause resource exhaustion of the authentication process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deny authentication for Remote Access SSL VPN users for several minutes, resulting in a temporary DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20494 | A vulnerability in the TLS cryptography functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20494</link><description>A vulnerability in the TLS cryptography functionality of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper data validation during the TLS 1.3 handshake. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted TLS 1.3 packet to an affected system through a TLS 1.3-enabled listening socket. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.
&#13; Note: This vulnerability can also impact the integrity of a device by causing VPN HostScan communication failures or file transfer failures when Cisco ASA Software is upgraded using Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20495 | A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20495</link><description>A vulnerability in the Remote Access VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of client key data after the TLS session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted key value to an affected system over the secure TLS session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20526 | A vulnerability in the SSH server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20526</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH server of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition for the SSH server of an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error when an SSH session is established. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSH messages to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust available SSH resources on the affected device so that new SSH connections to the device are denied, resulting in a DoS condition. Existing SSH connections to the device would continue to function normally. The device must be rebooted manually to recover. However, user traffic would not be impacted and could be managed using a remote application such as Cisco Adaptive Security Device Manager (ASDM).</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 18:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20415 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20415</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20424 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Manageme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20424</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system as root.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain HTTP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the web-based management interface of an affected device and then sending a crafted HTTP request to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root permissions on the underlying operating system of the Cisco FMC device or to execute commands on managed Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) devices. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Security Analyst (Read Only).</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20426 | A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) protocol for VPN termination of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Softw...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20426</link><description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) protocol for VPN termination of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IKEv2 traffic to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20431 | A vulnerability in the geolocation access control feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20431</link><description>A vulnerability in the geolocation access control feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass an access control policy.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper assignment of geolocation data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass a geolocation-based access control policy and successfully send traffic to a protected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20471 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20471</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20472 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20472</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct SQL injection attacks on an affected system.

This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not validate user input adequately. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the application as an Administrator and sending crafted SQL queries to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain unauthorized data from the database and make changes to the system. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20474 | A vulnerability in Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) processing of Cisco Secure Client Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20474</link><description>A vulnerability in Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) processing of Cisco Secure Client Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) of Cisco Secure Client.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to an integer underflow condition. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted IKEv2 packet to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause Cisco Secure Client Software to crash, resulting in a DoS condition on the client software.
&#13; Note: Cisco Secure Client Software releases 4.10 and earlier were known as Cisco AnyConnect Secure Mobility Client.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20402 | A vulnerability in the SSL VPN feature for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Softwar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20402</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSL VPN feature for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error in memory management when the device is handling SSL VPN connections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted SSL/TLS packets to the SSL VPN server of the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20403 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20403</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20407 | A vulnerability in the interaction between the TCP Intercept feature and the Snort 3 detection engine on Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20407</link><description>A vulnerability in the interaction between the TCP Intercept feature and the Snort 3 detection engine on Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass configured policies on an affected system. Devices that are configured with Snort 2 are not affected by this vulnerability. 
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error when handling embryonic (half-open) TCP connections. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted traffic pattern through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow unintended traffic to enter the network protected by the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20408 | A vulnerability in the Dynamic Access Policies (DAP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20408</link><description>A vulnerability in the Dynamic Access Policies (DAP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid remote access VPN user credentials on the affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of data in HTTPS POST requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTPS POST request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20409 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20409</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20410 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20410</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20412 | A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 1000, 2100, 3100, and 4200 Series could allow an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20412</link><description>A vulnerability in Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 1000, 2100, 3100, and 4200 Series could allow an unauthenticated, local attacker to access an affected system using static credentials.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the presence of static accounts with hard-coded passwords on an affected system. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by logging in to the CLI of an affected device with these credentials. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access the affected system and retrieve sensitive information, perform limited troubleshooting actions, modify some configuration options, or render the device unable to boot to the operating system, requiring a reimage of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9949 | Denial of Service in Forescout SecureConnector 11.1.02.1019 on Windows allows Unprivileged user to corrupt the configuration file and cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9949</link><description>Denial of Service in Forescout SecureConnector 11.1.02.1019 on Windows allows Unprivileged user to corrupt the configuration file and cause Denial of Service in the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:52:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10297 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System Managecard Edit Image Page changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10297</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/changeimage.php of the component Managecard Edit Image Page. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20364 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20364</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20370 | A vulnerability in the Cisco FXOS CLI feature on specific hardware platforms for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20370</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco FXOS CLI feature on specific hardware platforms for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to elevate their administrative privileges to root. The attacker would need valid administrative credentials on the device to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because certain system configurations and executable files have insecure storage and permissions. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating on the device and then performing a series of steps that includes downloading malicious system files and accessing the Cisco FXOS CLI to configure the attack. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to obtain root access on the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20372 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20372</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20374 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Manageme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20374</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of certain HTTP request parameters that are sent to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by authenticating to the Cisco FMC web-based management interface and sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands as the root user on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need Administrator-level credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20377 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20377</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to the web-based management interface not properly validating user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20379 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Manageme...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20379</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to read arbitrary files from the underlying operating system.
&#13; This vulnerability exists because the web-based management interface does not properly validate user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read arbitrary files on the underlying operating system of the affected device. The attacker would need valid user credentials to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20382 | A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20382</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20384 | A vulnerability in the Network Service Group (NSG) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20384</link><description>A vulnerability in the Network Service Group (NSG) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should be denied to flow through an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to a logic error that occurs when NSG ACLs are populated on an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing a connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20386 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20386</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20387 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco FMC Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to store malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20387</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco FMC Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to store malicious content for use in XSS attacks. This vulnerability is due to improper input sanitization in the web-based management interface of Cisco FMC Software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to click a malicious link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20388 | A vulnerability in the password change feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20388</link><description>A vulnerability in the password change feature of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to determine valid user names on an affected device.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper authentication of password update responses. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by forcing a password reset on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to determine valid user names in the unauthenticated response to a forced password reset.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20260 | Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance and Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual SSL VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20260</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN and management web servers of the Cisco Adaptive Security Virtual Appliance (ASAv) and Cisco Secure Firewall Threat Defense Virtual (FTDv), formerly Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Virtual, platforms could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the virtual devices to run out of system memory, which could cause SSL VPN connection processing to slow down and eventually cease all together.

This vulnerability is due to a lack of proper memory management for new incoming SSL/TLS connections on the virtual platforms. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large number of new incoming SSL/TLS connections to the targeted virtual platform. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to deplete system memory,&amp;nbsp;resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. The memory could be reclaimed slowly if the attack traffic is stopped, but a manual reload may be required to restore operations quickly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20264 | Cisco Firepower Management Center Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20264</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20268 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance Software and Firepower Threat Defense Software SNMP Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20268</link><description>A vulnerability in the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP) feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to cause an unexpected reload of the device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation of SNMP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted SNMP request to an affected device using IPv4 or IPv6. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability affects all versions of SNMP (versions 1, 2c, and 3) and requires a valid SNMP community string or valid SNMPv3 user credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20269 | Cisco Firepower Management Center Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20269</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20273 | Cisco Firepower Management Center Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20273</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20274 | Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center HTML Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20274</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML content into a device-generated document.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied data. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting malicious content to an affected device and using the device to generate a document that contains sensitive information. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to alter the standard layout of the device-generated documents, access arbitrary files from the underlying operating system, and conduct server-side request forgery (SSRF) attacks. To successfully exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with policy-editing permissions, such as Network Admin, Intrusion Admin, or any custom user role with the same capabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20275 | Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center Software Backup Cluster Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20275</link><description>A vulnerability in the cluster backup feature of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user data that is supplied through the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary operating system commands on the affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need valid credentials for a user account with at least the role of Network Administrator. In addition, the attacker would need to persuade a legitimate user to initiate a cluster backup on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20297 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance and Firepower Threat Defense AnyConnect  Access Control List Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20297</link><description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20298 | Cisco Firepower Management Center Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20298</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20299 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance and Firepower Threat Defense AnyConnect  Access Control List Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20299</link><description>A vulnerability in the AnyConnect firewall for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured access control list (ACL) and allow traffic that should have been denied to flow through an affected device. This vulnerability is due to a logic error in populating group ACLs when an AnyConnect client establishes a new session toward an affected device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by establishing an AnyConnect connection to the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass configured ACL rules.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20300 | Cisco Firepower Management Center Software Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20300</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Firepower Management Center (FMC) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface of an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting crafted input into various data fields in an affected interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the interface, or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20329 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance Software Remote Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20329</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH subsystem of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute operating system commands as root.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting crafted input when executing remote CLI commands over SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. An attacker with limited user privileges could use this vulnerability to gain complete control over the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20330 | Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series TCP UDP Snort 2 and Snort 2 Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20330</link><description>A vulnerability in the Snort 2 and Snort 3 TCP and UDP detection engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Appliances could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause memory corruption, which could cause the Snort detection engine to restart unexpectedly.

This vulnerability is due to improper memory management when the Snort detection engine processes specific TCP or UDP packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted TCP or UDP packets through a device that is inspecting traffic using the Snort detection engine. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to restart the Snort detection engine repeatedly, which could cause a denial of service (DoS) condition. The DoS condition impacts only the traffic through the device that is examined by the Snort detection engine. The device can still be managed over the network.
Note: Once a memory block is corrupted, it cannot be cleared until the Cisco Firepower 2100 Series Appliance is manually reloaded. This means that the Snort detection engine could crash repeatedly, causing traffic that is processed by the Snort detection engine to be dropped until the device is manually reloaded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20331 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance and Firepower Threat Defense Software VPN Authentication DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20331</link><description>A vulnerability in the session authentication functionality of the Remote Access SSL VPN feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent users from authenticating.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient entropy in the authentication process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by determining the handle of an authenticating user and using it to terminate their authentication session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to force a user to restart the authentication process, preventing a legitimate user from establishing remote access VPN sessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20339 | Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software for Firepower 2100 Series TLS Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20339</link><description>A vulnerability in the TLS processing feature of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software for Cisco Firepower 2100 Series could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to an issue that occurs when TLS traffic is processed. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending certain TLS traffic over IPv4 through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition and impacting traffic to and through the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20340 | Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20340</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Secure Firewall Management Center (FMC) Software, formerly Firepower Management Center Software, could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to perform an SQL injection attack against an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must have a valid account on the device with the role of Security Approver, Intrusion Admin, Access Admin, or Network Admin.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to the web-based management interface of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to read the contents of databases on the affected device and also obtain limited read access to the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20341 | Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance WebVPN Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20341</link><description>A vulnerability in the VPN web client services feature of Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a browser that is accessing an affected device. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied input to application endpoints. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user to follow a link designed to submit malicious input to the affected application. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary HTML or script code in the browser in the context of the web services page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20342 | Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Rate Filter Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20342</link><description>Multiple Cisco products are affected by a vulnerability in the rate filtering feature of the Snort detection engine that could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured rate limiting filter.

This vulnerability is due to an incorrect connection count comparison. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic through an affected device at a rate that exceeds a configured rate filter. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to successfully bypass the rate filter. This could allow unintended traffic to enter the network protected by the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20351 | Cisco Firepower Threat Defense Software Snort Firewall Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20351</link><description>A vulnerability in the TCP/IP traffic handling function of the Snort Detection Engine of Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software and Cisco FirePOWER Services could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause legitimate network traffic to be dropped, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to the improper handling of TCP/IP network traffic. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a large amount of TCP/IP network traffic through the affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the Cisco FTD device to drop network traffic, resulting in a DoS condition. The affected device must be rebooted to resolve the DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49756 | AshPostgres empty, atomic, non-bulk actions, policy bypass for side-effects vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49756</link><description>AshPostgres is the PostgreSQL data layer for Ash Framework. Starting in version 2.0.0 and prior to version 2.4.10, in certain very specific situations, it was possible for the policies of an update action to be skipped. This occurred only on "empty" update actions (no changing fields), and would allow their hooks (side effects) to be performed when they should not have been. Note that this does not allow reading new data that the user should not have had access to, only triggering a side effect a user should not have been able to trigger.

To be vulnerable, an affected user must have an update action that is on a resource with no attributes containing an "update default" (updated_at timestamp, for example); can be performed atomically; does not have `require_atomic? false`; has at least one authorizer (typically `Ash.Policy.Authorizer`); and has at least one `change` (on the resource's `changes` block or in the action itself). This is where the side-effects would be performed when they should not have been.

This problem has been patched in `2.4.10` of `ash_postgres`. Several workarounds are available. Potentially affected users may determine that none of their actions are vulnerable using a script the maintainers provide in the GitHub Security Advisory, add `require_atomic? false` to any potentially affected update action, replace any usage of `Ash.update` with `Ash.bulk_update` for an affected action, and/or add an update timestamp to their action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10296 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System Report of Medical Card Page card-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10296</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/card-bwdates-reports-details.php of the component Report of Medical Card Page. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50382 | Botan before 3.6.0, when certain LLVM versions are used, has compiler-induced secret-dependent control flow in lib/utils/ghash/ghash.cpp in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50382</link><description>Botan before 3.6.0, when certain LLVM versions are used, has compiler-induced secret-dependent control flow in lib/utils/ghash/ghash.cpp in GHASH in AES-GCM. There is a branch instead of an XOR with carry. This was observed for Clang in LLVM 15 on RISC-V.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50383 | Botan before 3.6.0, when certain GCC versions are used, has a compiler-induced secret-dependent operation in lib/utils/donna128.h in donna12...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50383</link><description>Botan before 3.6.0, when certain GCC versions are used, has a compiler-induced secret-dependent operation in lib/utils/donna128.h in donna128 (used in Chacha-Poly1305 and x25519). An addition can be skipped if a carry is not set. This was observed for GCC 11.3.0 with -O2 on MIPS, and GCC on x86-i386. (Only 32-bit processors can be affected.)</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10293 | ZZCMS functions.php Ebak_SetGotoPak unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10293</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZZCMS 2023. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function Ebak_SetGotoPak of the file 3/Ebbak5.1/upload/class/functions.php. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49751 | Frappe Press possible HTML injection through SaaS Signup inputs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49751</link><description>Press, a Frappe custom app that runs Frappe Cloud, manages infrastructure, subscription, marketplace, and software-as-a-service (SaaS). Prior to commit 5d118a902872d7941f099ad1fb918e2421e79ccd, a user could inject HTML through SaaS signup inputs. The user who injected the unsafe HTML code would only affect themselves and would not affect other users. Commit 5d118a902872d7941f099ad1fb918e2421e79ccd patches this bug.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49652 | WordPress 3D Work In Progress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49652</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in ReneeCussack 3D Work In Progress allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects 3D Work In Progress: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49653 | WordPress Portfolleo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49653</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in James Eggers Portfolleo portfolleo allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Portfolleo: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49658 | WordPress Woocommerce Custom Profile Picture plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49658</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Ecomerciar Woocommerce Custom Profile Picture allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Woocommerce Custom Profile Picture: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49668 | WordPress Verbalize WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49668</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Admin Verbalize WP Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Verbalize WP: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49669 | WordPress INK Official plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49669</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Alexander De Ridder INK Official allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects INK Official: from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10291 | ZZCMS phome.php Ebak_DotranExecutSQL sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10291</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ZZCMS 2023 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function Ebak_DoExecSQL/Ebak_DotranExecutSQL of the file 3/Ebak5.1/upload/phome.php. The manipulation of the argument phome leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10292 | ZZCMS ChangeTable.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10292</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZZCMS 2023 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file 3/Ebak5.1/upload/ChangeTable.php. The manipulation of the argument savefilename leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49671 | WordPress AI Postpix plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49671</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Dogu Pekgoz AI Image Generator for Your Content &amp; Featured Images – AI Postpix allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects AI Image Generator for Your Content &amp; Featured Images – AI Postpix: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49676 | WordPress Custom Icons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49676</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Michael Bourne Custom Icons for Elementor allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Custom Icons for Elementor: from n/a through 0.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30124 | HCL Sametime is impacted by insecure services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30124</link><description>HCL Sametime is impacted by insecure services in-use on the UIM client by default. An unused legacy REST service was enabled by default using the HTTP protocol. An attacker could potentially use this service endpoint maliciously.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49657 | WordPress 3D Work In Progress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49657</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ReneeCussack 3D Work In Progress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects 3D Work In Progress: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49684 | WordPress Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule plugin &amp;lt;= 1.22.21 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49684</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Revmakx Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule allows Object Injection.This issue affects Backup and Staging by WP Time Capsule: from n/a through 1.22.21.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49690 | WordPress Qi Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49690</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Qode Interactive Qi Blocks.This issue affects Qi Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49701 | WordPress Mags theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49701</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Theme Horse Mags.This issue affects Mags: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47575 | A missing authentication for critical function in FortiManager 7.6.0, FortiManager 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, FortiManager 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, Fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47575</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function in FortiManager 7.6.0, FortiManager 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, FortiManager 7.2.0 through 7.2.7, FortiManager 7.0.0 through 7.0.12, FortiManager 6.4.0 through 6.4.14, FortiManager 6.2.0 through 6.2.12, Fortinet FortiManager Cloud 7.4.1 through 7.4.4, FortiManager Cloud 7.2.1 through 7.2.7, FortiManager Cloud 7.0.1 through 7.0.13, FortiManager Cloud 6.4.1 through 6.4.7 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via specially crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49370 | Change-Password via Portal-Profile sets PimcoreBackendUser password without hashing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49370</link><description>Pimcore is an open source data and experience management platform. When a PortalUserObject is connected to a PimcoreUser and "Use Pimcore Backend Password" is set to true, the change password function in Portal Profile sets the new password. Prior to Pimcore portal engine versions 4.1.7 and 3.1.16, the password is then set without hashing so it can be read by everyone. Everyone who combines PortalUser to PimcoreUsers and change passwords via profile settings could be affected. Versions 4.1.7 and 3.1.16 of the Pimcore portal engine fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49675 | WordPress iBryl Switch User plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49675</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Vitalii Bryl iBryl Switch User allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects iBryl Switch User: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10283 | Tenda RX9/RX9 Pro SetNetControlList sub_4337EC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10283</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda RX9 and RX9 Pro 22.03.02.20. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4337EC of the file /goform/SetNetControlList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10290 | ZZCMS inc.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10290</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in ZZCMS 2023. This affects an unknown part of the file 3/qq-connect2.0/API/com/inc.php. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30122 | HCL Sametime is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30122</link><description>HCL Sametime is impacted by misconfigured security related HTTP headers. It was identified that some HTTP headers were missing on web service responses. This will lead to less secure browser default treatment for the policies controlled by these headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5764 | Nexus Repository 3 - Static hard-coded encryption passphrase used by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5764</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Sonatype Nexus Repository has been discovered in the code responsible for encrypting any secrets stored in the Nexus Repository configuration database (SMTP or HTTP proxy credentials, user tokens, tokens, among others). The affected versions relied on a static hard-coded encryption passphrase. While it was possible for an administrator to define an alternate encryption passphrase, it could only be done at first boot and not updated.

This issue affects Nexus Repository: from 3.0.0 through 3.72.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:54:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10282 | Tenda RX9/RX9 Pro SetVirtualServerCfg sub_42EA38 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10282</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda RX9 and RX9 Pro 22.03.02.10/22.03.02.20. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_42EA38 of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47901 | A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47901</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All versions &lt; V7.2.12 only if the IP interface is enabled (which is not the default configuration)). The web server of affected devices does not sanitize the input parameters in specific GET requests that allow for code execution on operating system level. In combination with other vulnerabilities (CVE-2024-47902, CVE-2024-47903, CVE-2024-47904) this could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47902 | A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47902</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All versions &lt; V7.2.12 only if the IP interface is enabled (which is not the default configuration)). The web server of affected devices does not authenticate GET requests that execute specific commands (such as `ping`) on operating system level.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47903 | A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47903</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All versions &lt; V7.2.12 only if the IP interface is enabled (which is not the default configuration)). The web server of affected devices allows to write arbitrary files to the web server's DocumentRoot directory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47904 | A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47904</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in InterMesh 7177 Hybrid 2.0 Subscriber (All versions &lt; V8.2.12), InterMesh 7707 Fire Subscriber (All versions &lt; V7.2.12 only if the IP interface is enabled (which is not the default configuration)). The affected devices contain a SUID binary that could allow an authenticated local attacker to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10250 | Nioland &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via s</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10250</link><description>The Nioland theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘s’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10281 | Tenda RX9/RX9 Pro SetStaticRouteCfg sub_42EEE0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10281</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda RX9 and RX9 Pro 22.03.02.10/22.03.02.20. Affected is the function sub_42EEE0 of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10041 | Pam: libpam: libpam vulnerable to read hashed password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10041</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PAM. The secret information is stored in memory, where the attacker can trigger the victim program to execute by sending characters to its standard input (stdin). As this occurs, the attacker can train the branch predictor to execute an ROP chain speculatively. This flaw could result in leaked passwords, such as those found in /etc/shadow while performing authentications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:53:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10280 | Tenda AC6/AC7/AC8/AC9/AC10/AC10U/AC15/AC18/AC500/AC1206 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10280</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC6, AC7, AC8, AC9, AC10, AC10U, AC15, AC18, AC500 and AC1206 up to 20241022. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:43:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50050 | Llama Stack prior to revision 7a8aa775e5a267cf8660d83140011a0b7f91e005 used pickle as a serialization format for socket communication, poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50050</link><description>Llama Stack prior to revision 7a8aa775e5a267cf8660d83140011a0b7f91e005 used pickle as a serialization format for socket communication, potentially allowing for remote code execution. Socket communication has been changed to use JSON instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:43:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10278 | ESAFENET CDG ReUserOrganiseService.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10278</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/user/ReUserOrganiseService.java. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:04:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10279 | ESAFENET CDG PrintPolicyService.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10279</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/policy/PrintPolicyService.java. The manipulation of the argument policyId leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:04:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10286 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LocalServer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10286</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting LocalServer 1.0.9 that could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details through /testmail/index.php, parameter to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10287 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LocalServer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10287</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting LocalServer 1.0.9 that could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details through /mlss/ForgotPassword, parameter ListName.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10288 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LocalServer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10288</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting LocalServer 1.0.9 that could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details through /mlss/SubscribeToList, parameter ListName.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10289 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in LocalServer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10289</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting LocalServer 1.0.9 that could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details through /mlss/ManageSubscription, parameter MSubListName.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 12:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10277 | ESAFENET CDG UsbKeyAjax.java sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10277</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG 5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /com/esafenet/servlet/ajax/UsbKeyAjax.java. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10276 | Tektronix Sentry Reports Page page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10276</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tektronix Sentry 6.0.9 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /?page=reports of the component Reports Page. The manipulation of the argument z leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8500 | WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.2.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8500</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50310 | IBM CICS Transaction Gateway for Multiplatforms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50310</link><description>IBM CICS Transaction Gateway for Multiplatforms 9.2 and 9.3 transmits or stores authentication credentials, but it uses an insecure method that is susceptible to unauthorized interception and/or retrieval.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 11:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10045 | Transients Manager &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10045</link><description>The Transients Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the process_actions function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete transients via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 07:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43924 | WordPress Responsive Lightbox &amp;amp; Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43924</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dFactory Responsive Lightbox allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Responsive Lightbox: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 07:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9530 | Qi Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.8.0 - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9530</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.0 via private templates. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the contents of templates that are private.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 07:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9583 | RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging &amp;lt;= 4.23.12 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9583</link><description>The RSS Aggregator – RSS Import, News Feeds, Feed to Post, and Autoblogging plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized use of functionality due to a missing capability check on the wprss_ajax_send_premium_support function in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to send premium support requests with an attacker-controlled subject line and email address to support allowing them to impersonate the site owner. License information may also be leaked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 06:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9947 | ProfilePress - Pro &amp;lt;= 4.11.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9947</link><description>The ProfilePress Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.11.1. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being returned by the social login token. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email and the user does not have an already-existing account for the service returning the token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 06:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9829 | Download Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Metadata and Comment Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9829</link><description>The Download Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability checks on the 'dpwap_handle_download_user' and 'dpwap_handle_download_comment' functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to download any comment, and download metadata for any user including user PII and sensitive information including username, email, hashed passwords and application passwords, session token information and more depending on set up and additional plugins installed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 05:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50066 | mm/mremap: fix move_normal_pmd/retract_page_tables race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50066</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/mremap: fix move_normal_pmd/retract_page_tables race

In mremap(), move_page_tables() looks at the type of the PMD entry and the
specified address range to figure out by which method the next chunk of
page table entries should be moved.

At that point, the mmap_lock is held in write mode, but no rmap locks are
held yet.  For PMD entries that point to page tables and are fully covered
by the source address range, move_pgt_entry(NORMAL_PMD, ...) is called,
which first takes rmap locks, then does move_normal_pmd(). 
move_normal_pmd() takes the necessary page table locks at source and
destination, then moves an entire page table from the source to the
destination.

The problem is: The rmap locks, which protect against concurrent page
table removal by retract_page_tables() in the THP code, are only taken
after the PMD entry has been read and it has been decided how to move it. 
So we can race as follows (with two processes that have mappings of the
same tmpfs file that is stored on a tmpfs mount with huge=advise); note
that process A accesses page tables through the MM while process B does it
through the file rmap:

process A                      process B
=========                      =========
mremap
  mremap_to
    move_vma
      move_page_tables
        get_old_pmd
        alloc_new_pmd
                      *** PREEMPT ***
                               madvise(MADV_COLLAPSE)
                                 do_madvise
                                   madvise_walk_vmas
                                     madvise_vma_behavior
                                       madvise_collapse
                                         hpage_collapse_scan_file
                                           collapse_file
                                             retract_page_tables
                                               i_mmap_lock_read(mapping)
                                               pmdp_collapse_flush
                                               i_mmap_unlock_read(mapping)
        move_pgt_entry(NORMAL_PMD, ...)
          take_rmap_locks
          move_normal_pmd
          drop_rmap_locks

When this happens, move_normal_pmd() can end up creating bogus PMD entries
in the line `pmd_populate(mm, new_pmd, pmd_pgtable(pmd))`.  The effect
depends on arch-specific and machine-specific details; on x86, you can end
up with physical page 0 mapped as a page table, which is likely
exploitable for user-&gt;kernel privilege escalation.

Fix the race by letting process B recheck that the PMD still points to a
page table after the rmap locks have been taken.  Otherwise, we bail and
let the caller fall back to the PTE-level copying path, which will then
bail immediately at the pmd_none() check.

Bug reachability: Reaching this bug requires that you can create
shmem/file THP mappings - anonymous THP uses different code that doesn't
zap stuff under rmap locks.  File THP is gated on an experimental config
flag (CONFIG_READ_ONLY_THP_FOR_FS), so on normal distro kernels you need
shmem THP to hit this bug.  As far as I know, getting shmem THP normally
requires that you can mount your own tmpfs with the right mount flags,
which would require creating your own user+mount namespace; though I don't
know if some distros maybe enable shmem THP by default or something like
that.

Bug impact: This issue can likely be used for user-&gt;kernel privilege
escalation when it is reachable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 05:37:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9927 | WooCommerce Order Proposal &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Privilege Escalation via Order Proposal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9927</link><description>The WooCommerce Order Proposal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via order proposal in all versions up to and including 2.0.5. This is due to the improper implementation of allow_payment_without_login function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to log in to WordPress as an arbitrary user account, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31880 | IBM Db2 denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31880</link><description>IBM Db2 for Linux, UNIX and Windows (includes Db2 Connect Server) 10.5, 11.1, and 11.5 is vulnerable to a denial of service, under specific configurations, as the server may crash when using a specially crafted SQL statement by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 02:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>