<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-33472 | An issue was discovered in Scada-LTS v2.7.5.2 build 4551883606 and before, allows remote attackers with low-level authentication to escalate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33472</link><description>An issue was discovered in Scada-LTS v2.7.5.2 build 4551883606 and before, allows remote attackers with low-level authentication to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code, and obtain sensitive information via Event Handlers function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46942 | Lack of authentication in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46942</link><description>Lack of authentication in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via improper authorization in GraphQL endpoints.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46943 | An issue was discovered in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8. The HMAC secret used for generating tokens is hardcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46943</link><description>An issue was discovered in NPM's package @evershop/evershop before version 1.0.0-rc.8. The HMAC secret used for generating tokens is hardcoded as "secret". A weak HMAC secret poses a risk because attackers can use the predictable secret to create valid JSON Web Tokens (JWTs), allowing them access to important information and actions within the application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51804 | An issue in rymcu forest v.0.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via manipulation of the HTTP body URL in the com.ry...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51804</link><description>An issue in rymcu forest v.0.02 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via manipulation of the HTTP body URL in the com.rymcu.forest.web.api.common.UploadController file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51805 | SQL Injection vulnerability in TDuckCLoud tduck-platform v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getFormKey p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51805</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in TDuckCLoud tduck-platform v.4.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the getFormKey parameter in the search function of FormDataMysqlService.java file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 02:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50072 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in OpenKM version 7.1.40 (dbb6e88) With Professional Extension that allows an authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50072</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in OpenKM version 7.1.40 (dbb6e88) With Professional Extension that allows an authenticated user to upload a note on a file which acts as a stored XSS payload. Any user who opens the note of a document file will trigger the XSS.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 01:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0475 | code-projects Dormitory Management System modifyuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0475</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file modifyuser.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250580.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 01:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22137 | WordPress Constant Contact Forms by MailMunch Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22137</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MailMunch Constant Contact Forms by MailMunch allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Constant Contact Forms by MailMunch: from n/a through 2.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22142 | WordPress Profile Builder Pro Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22142</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Profile Builder Pro allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Profile Builder Pro: from n/a through 3.10.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0230 | A session management issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Magic Keyboard Firmware Update 2.0.6. An attacker with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0230</link><description>A session management issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in Magic Keyboard Firmware Update 2.0.6. An attacker with physical access to the accessory may be able to extract its Bluetooth pairing key and monitor Bluetooth traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 23:19:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23301 | Relax-and-Recover (aka ReaR) through 2.7 creates a world-readable initrd when using GRUB_RESCUE=y. This allows local attackers to gain acces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23301</link><description>Relax-and-Recover (aka ReaR) through 2.7 creates a world-readable initrd when using GRUB_RESCUE=y. This allows local attackers to gain access to system secrets otherwise only readable by root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 23:19:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48166 | A directory traversal vulnerability in the SOAP Server integrated in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice V10 before V10R3.26.1 allows a remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48166</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability in the SOAP Server integrated in Atos Unify OpenScape Voice V10 before V10R3.26.1 allows a remote attacker to view the contents of arbitrary files in the local file system. An unauthenticated attacker might obtain sensitive files that allow for the compromise of the underlying system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0474 | code-projects Dormitory Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0474</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250579.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4962 | Apollo Configuration Center users improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4962</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Apollo 2.0.0/2.0.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /users of the component Configuration Center. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. VDB-250430 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The maintainer explains that user data information like user id, name, and email are not sensitive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49647 | Zoom Desktop Client for Windows - Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49647</link><description>Improper access control in Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom SDKs for Windows before version 5.16.10 may allow an authenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0472 | code-projects Dormitory Management System modifyuser.php information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0472</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file modifyuser.php. The manipulation of the argument mname leads to information disclosure. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250577 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0473 | code-projects Dormitory Management System comment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0473</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Dormitory Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file comment.php. The manipulation of the argument com leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250578 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21639 | OOB Access in CefLayeredWindowUpdaterOSR::OnAllocatedSharedMemory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21639</link><description>CEF (Chromium Embedded Framework ) is a simple framework for embedding Chromium-based browsers in other applications. `CefLayeredWindowUpdaterOSR::OnAllocatedSharedMemory` does not check the size of the shared memory, which leads to out-of-bounds read outside the sandbox. This vulnerability was patched in commit 1f55d2e.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49801 | Lif Auth Server vulnerable to uncontrolled data in path expression </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49801</link><description>Lif Auth Server is a server for validating logins, managing information, and account recovery for Lif Accounts. The issue relates to the `get_pfp` and `get_banner` routes on Auth Server. The issue is that there is no check to ensure that the file that Auth Server is receiving through these URLs is correct. This could allow an attacker access to files they shouldn't have access to. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0470 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System inc_service_credits.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0470</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin_route/inc_service_credits.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250575.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0471 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System dec_service_credits.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0471</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin_route/dec_service_credits.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250576.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21654 | rubygems.org MFA Bypass through password reset function could allow account takeover </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21654</link><description>Rubygems.org is the Ruby community's gem hosting service. Rubygems.org users with MFA enabled would normally be protected from account takeover in the case of email account takeover. However, a workaround on the forgotten password form allows an attacker to bypass the MFA requirement and takeover the account. This vulnerability has been patched in commit 0b3272a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42463 | wazuh-logcollector integer underflow local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42463</link><description>Wazuh is a free and open source platform used for threat prevention, detection, and response. This bug introduced a stack overflow hazard that could allow a local privilege escalation. This vulnerability was patched in version 4.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49099 | Discourse secure uploads accessible to guests even when login is required</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49099</link><description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. Under very specific circumstances, secure upload URLs associated with posts can be accessed by guest users even when login is required. This vulnerability has been patched in 3.2.0.beta4 and 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21655 | Insufficient control of custom field value sizes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21655</link><description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. For fields that are client editable, limits on sizes are not imposed. This allows a malicious actor to cause a Discourse instance to use excessive disk space and also often excessive bandwidth. The issue is patched 3.1.4 and 3.2.0.beta4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48297 | Discourse vulnerable to unlimited mentioned users in message serializer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48297</link><description>Discourse is a platform for community discussion. The message serializer uses the full list of expanded chat mentions (@all and @here) which can lead to a very long array of users. This issue was patched in versions 3.1.4 and beta 3.2.0.beta5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49098 | Reaction data for user notifications exposed in Discourse-reactions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49098</link><description>Discourse-reactions is a plugin that allows user to add their reactions to the post. Data about a user's reaction notifications could be exposed. This vulnerability was patched in commit 2c26939.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51698 | Atril&amp;#x27;s CBT comic book parsing vulnerable to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51698</link><description>Atril is a simple multi-page document viewer. Atril is vulnerable to a critical Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability gives the attacker immediate access to the target system when the target user opens a crafted document or clicks on a crafted link/URL using a maliciously crafted CBT document which is a TAR archive. A patch is available at commit ce41df6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0468 | code-projects Fighting Cock Information System new-father.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0468</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Fighting Cock Information System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/action/new-father.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250573 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0469 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System update_personal_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0469</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file update_personal_info.php. The manipulation of the argument sex leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250574 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22206 | @clerk/nextjs auth() and getAuth() methods vulnerable to insecure direct object reference (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22206</link><description>Clerk helps developers build user management. Unauthorized access or privilege escalation due to a logic flaw in auth() in the App Router or getAuth() in the Pages Router. This vulnerability was patched in version 4.29.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0467 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System edit_position_query.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0467</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file edit_position_query.php. The manipulation of the argument pos_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250572.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:18:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10011 | Acritum Femitter Server path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10011</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Acritum Femitter Server 1.04. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250446 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6683 | Qemu: vnc: null pointer dereference in qemu_clipboard_request()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6683</link><description>A flaw was found in the QEMU built-in VNC server while processing ClientCutText messages. The qemu_clipboard_request() function can be reached before vnc_server_cut_text_caps() was called and had the chance to initialize the clipboard peer, leading to a NULL pointer dereference. This could allow a malicious authenticated VNC client to crash QEMU and trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0465 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System download.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0465</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file download.php. The manipulation of the argument download_file leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250570 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0466 | code-projects Employee Profile Management System file_table.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0466</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Employee Profile Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file file_table.php. The manipulation of the argument per_id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250571.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 19:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31025 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31025</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an LDAP user injection. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31031 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31031</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a heap-based buffer overflow by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31024 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31024</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause stack memory corruption by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31029 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31029</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 baseboard management controller (BMC) contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31030 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31030</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability in the host KVM daemon, where an unauthenticated attacker may cause a stack overflow by sending a specially crafted network packet. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to arbitrary code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31032 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31032</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a dynamic variable evaluation by local access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31033 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31033</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 BMC contains a vulnerability where a user may cause a missing authentication issue for a critical function by an adjacent network . A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31034 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31034</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where a local attacker can cause input validation checks to be bypassed by causing an integer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31035 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31035</link><description>NVIDIA DGX A100 SBIOS contains a vulnerability where an attacker may cause an SMI callout vulnerability that could be used to execute arbitrary code at the SMM level. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, and information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0464 | code-projects Online Faculty Clearance HTTP GET Request delete_faculty.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0464</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file delete_faculty.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250569 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0463 | code-projects Online Faculty Clearance HTTP POST Request admin_view_info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0463</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /production/admin_view_info.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250568.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 18:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0462 | code-projects Online Faculty Clearance HTTP POST Request designee_view_status.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0462</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /production/designee_view_status.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250567.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31036 | CVE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31036</link><description>NVIDIA Triton Inference Server for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability where, when it is launched with the non-default command line option --model-control explicit, an attacker may use the model load API to cause a relative path traversal. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46805 | An authentication bypass vulnerability in the web component of Ivanti ICS 9.x, 22.x and Ivanti Policy Secure allows a remote attacker to acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46805</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability in the web component of Ivanti ICS 9.x, 22.x and Ivanti Policy Secure allows a remote attacker to access restricted resources by bypassing control checks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0461 | code-projects Online Faculty Clearance HTTP POST Request deactivate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0461</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Faculty Clearance 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file deactivate.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument haydi leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250566 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21887 | A command injection vulnerability in web components of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x)  allows an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21887</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in web components of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x)  allows an authenticated administrator to send specially crafted requests and execute arbitrary commands on the appliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 17:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28899 | Denial of Service via ECU reset service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28899</link><description>By sending a specific reset UDS request via OBDII port of Skoda vehicles, it is possible to cause vehicle engine shutdown and denial of service of other vehicle components even when the vehicle is moving at a high speed. No safety critical functions affected.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28898 | Head Unit Denial-of-Service via Apple CarPlay service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28898</link><description>The Real-Time Streaming Protocol implementation in the MIB3 infotainment incorrectly handles requests to /logs URI, when the id parameter equals to zero. This issue allows an attacker connected to the in-vehicle Wi-Fi network to cause denial-of-service of the infotainment system, when the certain preconditions are met.

Vulnerability discovered on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51978 | In PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System v1.1, "Update Artist Image" functionality of "imageid" parameter is vulnerable to SQL Injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51978</link><description>In PHPGurukul Art Gallery Management System v1.1, "Update Artist Image" functionality of "imageid" parameter is vulnerable to SQL Injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:26:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28897 | Hard-coded password for UDS services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28897</link><description>The secret value used for access to critical UDS services of the MIB3 infotainment is hardcoded in the firmware.

Vulnerability discovered on Škoda Superb III (3V3) - 2.0 TDI manufactured in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22493 | A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save content parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22493</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save content parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22492 | A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save contact parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22492</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save contact parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22494 | A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save mobile parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22494</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability exists in JFinalcms 5.0.0 via the /gusetbook/save mobile parameter, which allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0459 | Blood Bank &amp;amp; Donor Management request-received-bydonar.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0459</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Blood Bank &amp; Donor Management 5.6 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/request-received-bydonar.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250564.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0460 | code-projects Faculty Management System student-print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0460</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Faculty Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/pages/student-print.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250565 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51949 | Verydows v2.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /protected/controller/backend/role_controller</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51949</link><description>Verydows v2.0 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /protected/controller/backend/role_controller</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49253 | Predefined root password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49253</link><description>Root user password is hardcoded into the device and cannot be changed in the user interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49254 | Command injection in the network test tools</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49254</link><description>Authenticated user can execute arbitrary commands in the context of the root user by providing payload in the "destination" field of the network test tools. This is similar to the vulnerability CVE-2021-28151 mitigated on the user interface level by blacklisting characters with JavaScript, however, it can still be exploited by sending POST requests directly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49255 | Router console accessible without authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49255</link><description>The router console is accessible without authentication at "data" field, and while a user needs to be logged in in order to modify the configuration, the session state is shared. If any other user is currently logged in, the anonymous user can execute commands in the context of the authenticated one. If the logged in user has administrative privileges, it is possible to use webadmin service configuration commands to create a new admin user with a chosen password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49256 | Predictable encryption passphrase used in publicly accessible configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49256</link><description>It is possible to download the configuration backup without authorization and decrypt included passwords using hardcoded static key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49257 | Command execution using the certificate upload utility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49257</link><description>An authenticated user is able to upload an arbitrary CGI-compatible file using the certificate upload utility and execute it with the root user privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49258 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49258</link><description>User browser may be forced to execute JavaScript and pass the authentication cookie to the attacker leveraging the XSS vulnerability located at "/gui/terminal_tool.cgi" in the "data" parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49259 | Bruteforcing authentication cookie for a given user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49259</link><description>The authentication cookies are generated using an algorithm based on the username, hardcoded secret and the up-time, and can be guessed in a reasonable time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49260 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49260</link><description>An XSS attack can be performed by changing the MOTD banner and pointing the victim to the "terminal_tool.cgi" path. It can be used together with the vulnerability CVE-2023-49255.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49261 | Sensitive authentication-related value accessible publicly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49261</link><description>The "tokenKey" value used in user authorization is visible in the HTML source of the login page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49262 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in Cookie authentication field</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49262</link><description>The authentication mechanism can be bypassed by overflowing the value of the Cookie "authentication" field, provided there is an active user session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2030 | Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2030</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 12.2 prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4, and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2 in which an attacker could potentially modify the metadata of signed commits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4812 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4812</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 15.3 before 16.5.6, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.4, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.2. The required CODEOWNERS approval could be bypassed by adding changes to a previously approved merge request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5356 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5356</link><description>Incorrect authorization checks in GitLab CE/EE from all versions starting from 8.13 before 16.5.6, all versions starting from 16.6 before 16.6.4, all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.7.2, allows a user to abuse slack/mattermost integrations to execute slash commands as another user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6955 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6955</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in GitLab Remote Development affecting all versions prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4 and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2. This condition allows an attacker to create a workspace in one group that is associated with an agent from another group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7028 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7028</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.1 prior to 16.1.6, 16.2 prior to 16.2.9, 16.3 prior to 16.3.7, 16.4 prior to 16.4.5, 16.5 prior to 16.5.6, 16.6 prior to 16.6.4, and 16.7 prior to 16.7.2 in which user account password reset emails could be delivered to an unverified email address.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0437 | MongoDB client C Driver may infinitely loop when validating certain BSON input data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0437</link><description>When calling bson_utf8_validate on some inputs a loop with an exit condition that cannot be reached may occur, i.e. an infinite loop. This issue affects All MongoDB C Driver versions prior to versions 1.25.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 13:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51790 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in piwigo v.14.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lang parameter in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51790</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in piwigo v.14.0.0 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the lang parameter in the Admin Tools plug-in component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51806 | File Upload vulnerability in Ujcms v.8.0.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51806</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Ujcms v.8.0.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52026 | TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the telnet_enabled par...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52026</link><description>TOTOlink EX1800T V9.1.0cu.2112_B20220316 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the telnet_enabled parameter of the setTelnetCfg interface</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49568 | Maliciously crafted Git server replies can cause DoS on go-git clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49568</link><description>A denial of service (DoS) vulnerability was discovered in go-git versions prior to v5.11. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform denial of service attacks by providing specially crafted responses from a Git server which triggers resource exhaustion in go-git clients.

Applications using only the in-memory filesystem supported by go-git are not affected by this vulnerability.
This is a go-git implementation issue and does not affect the upstream git cli.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49569 | Maliciously crafted Git server replies can lead to path traversal and RCE on go-git clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49569</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability was discovered in go-git versions prior to v5.11. This vulnerability allows an attacker to create and amend files across the filesystem. In the worse case scenario, remote code execution could be achieved.

Applications are only affected if they are using the  ChrootOS https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/go-git/go-billy/v5/osfs#ChrootOS , which is the default when using "Plain" versions of Open and Clone funcs (e.g. PlainClone). Applications using  BoundOS https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/go-git/go-billy/v5/osfs#BoundOS  or in-memory filesystems are not affected by this issue.
This is a go-git implementation issue and does not affect the upstream git cli.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 10:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30014 | SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30014</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via sub_event_id parameter in sub_event_stat_update.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30015 | SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30015</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via txtsearch parameter in review_search.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30016 | SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30016</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in oretnom23 Judging Management System v1.0, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via sub_event_id parameter in sub_event_details_edit.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48909 | An issue was discovered in Jave2 version 3.3.1, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the FFmpeg function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48909</link><description>An issue was discovered in Jave2 version 3.3.1, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the FFmpeg function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:25:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40362 | An issue was discovered in CentralSquare Click2Gov Building Permit before October 2023. Lack of access control protections allows remote att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40362</link><description>An issue was discovered in CentralSquare Click2Gov Building Permit before October 2023. Lack of access control protections allows remote attackers to arbitrarily delete the contractors from any user's account when the user ID and contractor information is known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31211 | Disabled automation users could still authenticate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31211</link><description>Insufficient authentication flow in Checkmk before 2.2.0p18, 2.1.0p38 and 2.0.0p39 allows attacker to use locked credentials</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6735 | Privilege escalation in mk_tsm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6735</link><description>Privilege escalation in mk_tsm agent plugin in Checkmk before 2.2.0p18, 2.1.0p38 and 2.0.0p39 allows local user to escalate privileges</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6740 | Privilege escalation in jar_signature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6740</link><description>Privilege escalation in jar_signature agent plugin in Checkmk before 2.2.0p18, 2.1.0p38 and 2.0.0p39 allows local user to escalate privileges</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50919 | An issue was discovered on GL.iNet devices before version 4.5.0. There is an NGINX authentication bypass via Lua string pattern matching. Th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50919</link><description>An issue was discovered on GL.iNet devices before version 4.5.0. There is an NGINX authentication bypass via Lua string pattern matching. This affects A1300 4.4.6, AX1800 4.4.6, AXT1800 4.4.6, MT3000 4.4.6, MT2500 4.4.6, MT6000 4.5.0, MT1300 4.3.7, MT300N-V2 4.3.7, AR750S 4.3.7, AR750 4.3.7, AR300M 4.3.7, and B1300 4.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50920 | An issue was discovered on GL.iNet devices before version 4.5.0. They assign the same session ID after each user reboot, allowing attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50920</link><description>An issue was discovered on GL.iNet devices before version 4.5.0. They assign the same session ID after each user reboot, allowing attackers to share session identifiers between different sessions and bypass authentication or access control measures. Attackers can impersonate legitimate users or perform unauthorized actions. This affects A1300 4.4.6, AX1800 4.4.6, AXT1800 4.4.6, MT3000 4.4.6, MT2500 4.4.6, MT6000 4.5.0, MT1300 4.3.7, MT300N-V2 4.3.7, AR750S 4.3.7, AR750 4.3.7, AR300M 4.3.7, and B1300 4.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34061 | CVE-2023-34061 – Gorouter route pruning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34061</link><description>Cloud Foundry routing release versions from v0.163.0 to v0.283.0 are vulnerable to a DOS attack.  An unauthenticated attacker can use this vulnerability to force route pruning and therefore degrade the service availability of the Cloud Foundry deployment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 07:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22027 | Improper input validation vulnerability in WordPress Quiz Maker Plugin prior to 6.5.0.6 allows a remote authenticated attacker to perform a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22027</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in WordPress Quiz Maker Plugin prior to 6.5.0.6 allows a remote authenticated attacker to perform a Denial of Service (DoS) attack against external services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37117 | A heap-use-after-free vulnerability was found in live555 version 2023.05.10 while handling the SETUP.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37117</link><description>A heap-use-after-free vulnerability was found in live555 version 2023.05.10 while handling the SETUP.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23177 | An issue was discovered in the WatchAnalytics extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. XSS can occur via the Special:PageStatistics page parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23177</link><description>An issue was discovered in the WatchAnalytics extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. XSS can occur via the Special:PageStatistics page parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 05:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23178 | An issue was discovered in the Phonos extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. PhonosButton.js allows i18n-based XSS via the phonos-purge-neede...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23178</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Phonos extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. PhonosButton.js allows i18n-based XSS via the phonos-purge-needed-error message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 05:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23179 | An issue was discovered in the GlobalBlocking extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. For a Special:GlobalBlock?uselang=x-xss URI, i18n-based ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23179</link><description>An issue was discovered in the GlobalBlocking extension in MediaWiki before 1.40.2. For a Special:GlobalBlock?uselang=x-xss URI, i18n-based XSS can occur via the parentheses message. This affects subtitle links in buildSubtitleLinks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 05:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4961 | Weitong Mall OrderDao.xml sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4961</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Weitong Mall 1.0.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file platform-shop\src\main\resources\com\platform\dao\OrderDao.xml. The manipulation of the argument sidx/order leads to sql injection. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250243.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 05:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23171 | An issue was discovered in the CampaignEvents extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23171</link><description>An issue was discovered in the CampaignEvents extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. The Special:EventDetails page allows XSS via the x-xss language setting for internationalization (i18n).</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23172 | An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23172</link><description>An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. XSS can occur via message definitions. e.g., in SpecialCheckUserLog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23173 | An issue was discovered in the Cargo extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23173</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Cargo extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. The Special:Drilldown page allows XSS via artist, album, and position parameters because of applied filter values in drilldown/CargoAppliedFilter.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23174 | An issue was discovered in the PageTriage extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23174</link><description>An issue was discovered in the PageTriage extension in MediaWiki before 1.35.14, 1.36.x through 1.39.x before 1.39.6, and 1.40.x before 1.40.2. XSS can occur via the rev-deleted-user, pagetriage-tags-quickfilter-label, pagetriage-triage, pagetriage-filter-date-range-format-placeholder, pagetriage-filter-date-range-to, pagetriage-filter-date-range-from, pagetriage-filter-date-range-heading, pagetriage-filter-set-button, or pagetriage-filter-reset-button message.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48620 | uev (aka libuev) before 2.4.1 has a buffer overflow in epoll_wait if maxevents is a large number.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48620</link><description>uev (aka libuev) before 2.4.1 has a buffer overflow in epoll_wait if maxevents is a large number.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 04:23:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-20021 | In Gentoo Portage before 3.0.47, there is missing PGP validation of executed code: the standalone emerge-webrsync downloads a .gpgsig file b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-20021</link><description>In Gentoo Portage before 3.0.47, there is missing PGP validation of executed code: the standalone emerge-webrsync downloads a .gpgsig file but does not perform signature verification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48619 | An issue was discovered in drivers/input/input.c in the Linux kernel before 5.17.10. An attacker can cause a denial of service (panic) becau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48619</link><description>An issue was discovered in drivers/input/input.c in the Linux kernel before 5.17.10. An attacker can cause a denial of service (panic) because input_set_capability mishandles the situation in which an event code falls outside of a bitmap.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4960 | cloudfavorites favorites-web Nickname cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4960</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in cloudfavorites favorites-web 1.3.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Nickname Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250238 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52339 | In libebml before 1.4.5, an integer overflow in MemIOCallback.cpp can occur when reading or writing. It may result in buffer overflows.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52339</link><description>In libebml before 1.4.5, an integer overflow in MemIOCallback.cpp can occur when reading or writing. It may result in buffer overflows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6040 | An out-of-bounds access vulnerability involving netfilter was reported and fixed as: f1082dd31fe4 (netfilter: nf_tables: Reject tables of unsupported family)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6040</link><description>An out-of-bounds access vulnerability involving netfilter was reported and fixed as: f1082dd31fe4 (netfilter: nf_tables: Reject tables of unsupported family); While creating a new netfilter table, lack of a safeguard against invalid nf_tables family (pf) values within `nf_tables_newtable` function enables an attacker to achieve out-of-bounds access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0454 | Security Vulnerability on Match-on-Chip FPR Architecture</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0454</link><description>ELAN Match-on-Chip FPR solution has design fault about potential risk of valid SID leakage and enumeration with spoof sensor.
This fault leads to that Windows Hello recognition would be bypass with cloning SID to cause broken account identity.
Version which is lower than 3.0.12011.08009(Legacy)/3.3.12011.08103(ESS) would suffer this risk on DELL Inspiron platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 02:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40250 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Hancom HCell on Windows allows Overflow Buffers.This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40250</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in Hancom HCell on Windows allows Overflow Buffers.This issue affects HCell: 12.0.0.893.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36842 | Junos OS: jdhcpd will hang on receiving a specific DHCP packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36842</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Juniper DHCP Daemon (jdhcpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an adjacent, unauthenticated attacker to cause the jdhcpd to consume all the CPU cycles resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).

On Junos OS devices with forward-snooped-client configured, if an attacker sends a specific DHCP packet to a non-configured interface, this will cause an infinite loop. The DHCP process will have to be restarted to recover the service.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21585 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: BGP session flaps on NSR-enabled devices can cause rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21585</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in BGP session processing of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker, using specific timing outside the attacker's control, to flap BGP sessions and cause the routing protocol daemon (rpd) process to crash and restart, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS) condition. Continued BGP session flapping will create a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue only affects routers configured with non-stop routing (NSR) enabled. Graceful Restart (GR) helper mode, enabled by default, is also required for this issue to be exploitable.

When the BGP session flaps on the NSR-enabled router, the device enters GR-helper/LLGR-helper mode due to the peer having negotiated GR/LLGR-restarter capability and the backup BGP requests for replication of the GR/LLGR-helper session, master BGP schedules, and initiates replication of GR/LLGR stale routes to the backup BGP. In this state, if the BGP session with the BGP peer comes up again, unsolicited replication is initiated for the peer without cleaning up the ongoing GR/LLGR-helper mode replication. This parallel two instances of replication for the same peer leads to the assert if the BGP session flaps again.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1, 23.2R2.




Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved



  *  All versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5-EVO;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4-EVO;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1-EVO;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2-EVO, 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21587 | Junos OS: MX Series: Memory leak in bbe-smgd process if BFD liveness detection for DHCP subscribers is enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21587</link><description>An Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the broadband edge subscriber management daemon (bbe-smgd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series allows an attacker directly connected to the vulnerable system who repeatedly flaps DHCP subscriber sessions to cause a slow memory leak, ultimately leading to a Denial of Service (DoS). Memory can only be recovered by manually restarting bbe-smgd.

This issue only occurs if BFD liveness detection for DHCP subscribers is enabled. Systems without BFD liveness detection enabled are not vulnerable to this issue.

Indication of the issue can be observed by periodically executing the 'show system processes extensive' command, which will indicate an increase in memory allocation for bbe-smgd. A small amount of memory is leaked every time a DHCP subscriber logs in, which will become visible over time, ultimately leading to memory starvation.

user@junos&gt; show system processes extensive | match bbe-smgd
13071 root 24 0 415M 201M select 0 0:41 7.28% bbe-smgd{bbe-smgd}
13071 root 20 0 415M 201M select 1 0:04 0.00% bbe-smgd{bbe-smgd}
...
user@junos&gt; show system processes extensive | match bbe-smgd
13071 root 20 0 420M 208M select 0 4:33 0.10% bbe-smgd{bbe-smgd}
13071 root 20 0 420M 208M select 0 0:12 0.00% bbe-smgd{bbe-smgd}
...
This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21589 | Paragon Active Assurance Control Center: Information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21589</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability in the Juniper Networks Paragon Active Assurance Control Center allows an unauthenticated network-based attacker to access reports without authenticating, potentially containing sensitive configuration information.

A feature was introduced in version 3.1.0 of the Paragon Active Assurance Control Center which allows users to selectively share account data. By exploiting this vulnerability, it is possible to access reports without being logged in, resulting in the opportunity for malicious exfiltration of user data.

Note that the Paragon Active Assurance Control Center SaaS offering is not affected by this issue.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Paragon Active Assurance versions 3.1.0, 3.2.0, 3.2.2, 3.3.0, 3.3.1, 3.4.0.

This issue does not affect Juniper Networks Paragon Active Assurance versions earlier than 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21591 | Junos OS: SRX Series and EX Series: Security Vulnerability in J-web allows a preAuth Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21591</link><description>An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in J-Web of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series and EX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS), or Remote Code Execution (RCE) and obtain root privileges on the device.

This issue is caused by use of an insecure function allowing an attacker to overwrite arbitrary memory.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS SRX Series and EX Series:



  *  Junos OS versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  Junos OS 21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  Junos OS 21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  Junos OS 21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  Junos OS 22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  Junos OS 22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  Junos OS 22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S2;
  *  Junos OS 22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21594 | Junos OS: SRX 5000 Series: Repeated execution of a specific CLI command causes a flowd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21594</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the Network Services Daemon (NSD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows authenticated, low privileged, local attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

On an SRX 5000 Series device, when executing a specific command repeatedly, memory is corrupted, which leads to a Flow Processing Daemon (flowd) crash.

The NSD process has to be restarted to restore services.

If this issue occurs, it can be checked with the following command:

user@host&gt; request security policies check
The following log message can also be observed:

Error: policies are out of sync for PFE node&lt;number&gt;.fpc&lt;number&gt;.pic&lt;number&gt;.
This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX 5000 Series



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S6;
  *  21.1 versions earlier than 21.1R3-S5;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S4;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S3;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S3;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S1;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21595 | Junos OS: EX4100, EX4400, EX4600, QFX5000 Series: A high rate of specific ICMP traffic will cause the PFE to hang</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21595</link><description>An Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If an attacker sends high rate of specific ICMP traffic to a device with VXLAN configured, this causes a deadlock of the PFE and results in the device becoming unresponsive. A manual restart will be required to recover the device.

This issue only affects EX4100, EX4400, EX4600, QFX5000 Series devices.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  21.4R3 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S4;
  *  22.1R3 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S3;
  *  22.2R2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S1;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2;
  *  23.1 versions earlier than 23.1R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21596 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A specific BGP UPDATE message will cause a crash in the backup Routing Engine in NSR-enabled devices</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21596</link><description>A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If an attacker sends a specific BGP UPDATE message to the device, this will cause a memory overwrite and therefore an RPD crash and restart in the backup Routing Engine (RE). Continued receipt of these packets will cause a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition in the backup RE.

The primary RE is not impacted by this issue and there is no impact on traffic.

This issue only affects devices with NSR enabled.

This issue requires an attacker to have an established BGP session to a system affected by the issue. This issue affects both eBGP and iBGP implementations.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.1 versions earlier than 23.1R2;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2, 23.2R2.




Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved



  *  All versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5-EVO;
  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4-EVO;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2-EVO;
  *  22.3-EVO versions later than 22.3R1-EVO;
  *  22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2-EVO, 22.4R3-EVO;
  *  23.1-EVO versions earlier than 23.1R2-EVO;
  *  23.2-EVO versions earlier than 23.2R1-S2-EVO, 23.2R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21597 | Junos OS: MX Series: In an AF scenario traffic can bypass configured lo0 firewall filters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21597</link><description>An Exposure of Resource to Wrong Sphere vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to bypass the intended access restrictions.

In an Abstracted Fabric (AF) scenario if routing-instances (RI) are configured, specific valid traffic destined to the device can bypass the configured lo0 firewall filters as it's received in the wrong RI context.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S3;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21599 | Junos OS: MX Series: MPC3E memory leak with PTP configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21599</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series allows an adjacent, unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If an MX Series device receives PTP packets on an MPC3E that doesn't support PTP this causes a memory leak which will result in unpredictable behavior and ultimately in an MPC crash and restart.

To monitor for this issue, please use the following FPC vty level commands:

show heap
shows an increase in "LAN buffer" utilization and

show clksync ptp nbr-upd-info
shows non-zero "Pending PFEs" counter.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series with MPC3E:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S3;
  *  21.1 versions earlier than 21.1R3-S4;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R2-S1, 21.3R3;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R2;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21600 | Junos OS: PTX Series: In an FTI scenario MPLS packets hitting reject next-hop will cause a host path wedge condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21600</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Equivalent Special Elements vulnerability in the Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on PTX Series allows a unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

When MPLS packets are meant to be sent to a flexible tunnel interface (FTI) and if the FTI tunnel is down, these will hit the reject NH, due to which the packets get sent to the CPU and cause a host path wedge condition. This will cause the FPC to hang and requires a manual restart to recover.

Please note that this issue specifically affects PTX1000, PTX3000, PTX5000 with FPC3, PTX10002-60C, and PTX10008/16 with LC110x. Other PTX Series devices and Line Cards (LC) are not affected.

The following log message can be seen when the issue occurs:

Cmerror Op Set: Host Loopback: HOST LOOPBACK WEDGE DETECTED IN PATH ID &lt;id&gt; (URI: /fpc/&lt;fpc&gt;/pfe/&lt;pfe&gt;/cm/&lt;cm&gt;/Host_Loopback/&lt;cm&gt;/HOST_LOOPBACK_MAKE_CMERROR_ID[&lt;id&gt;])
This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S8;
  *  21.1 versions earlier than 21.1R3-S4;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S6;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S3;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R2-S2, 22.1R3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R2-S1, 22.2R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21601 | Junos OS: SRX Series: Due to an error in processing TCP events flowd will crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21601</link><description>A Concurrent Execution using Shared Resource with Improper Synchronization ('Race Condition') vulnerability in the Flow-processing Daemon (flowd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial-of-Service (Dos).

On SRX Series devices when two different threads try to simultaneously process a queue which is used for TCP events flowd will crash. One of these threads can not be triggered externally, so the exploitation of this race condition is outside the attackers direct control.

Continued exploitation of this issue will lead to a sustained DoS.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:



  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S5;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S4;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S1;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S1, 22.4R3.




This issue does not affect Juniper Networks Junos OS versions earlier than 21.2R1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21602 | Junos OS Evolved: ACX7024, ACX7100-32C and ACX7100-48L: Traffic stops when a specific IPv4 UDP packet is received by the RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21602</link><description>A NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX7024, ACX7100-32C and ACX7100-48L allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If a specific IPv4 UDP packet is received and sent to the Routing Engine (RE) packetio crashes and restarts which causes a momentary traffic interruption. Continued receipt of such packets will lead to a sustained DoS.

This issue does not happen with IPv6 packets.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved on ACX7024, ACX7100-32C and ACX7100-48L:



  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-S6-EVO;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R2-S1-EVO, 22.2R3-EVO;
  *  22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R2-EVO.




This issue does not affect Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 21.4R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21603 | Junos OS: MX Series: Gathering statistics in a scaled SCU/DCU configuration will lead to a device crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21603</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the kernel of Juniper Network Junos OS on MX Series allows a network based attacker with low privileges to cause a denial of service.

If a scaled configuration for Source class usage (SCU) / destination class usage (DCU) (more than 10 route classes) is present and the SCU/DCU statistics are gathered by executing specific SNMP requests or CLI commands, a 'vmcore' for the RE kernel will be seen which leads to a device restart. Continued exploitation of this issue will lead to a sustained DoS.

This issue only affects MX Series devices with MPC10, MPC11 or LC9600, and MX304. No other MX Series devices are affected.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S9;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S6;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R2;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21604 | Junos OS Evolved: A high rate of specific traffic will cause a complete system outage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21604</link><description>An Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in the kernel of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

If a high rate of specific valid packets are processed by the routing engine (RE) this will lead to a loss of connectivity of the RE with other components of the chassis and thereby a complete and persistent system outage. Please note that a carefully designed lo0 firewall filter will block or limit these packets which should prevent this issue from occurring.

The following log messages can be seen when this issue occurs:

&lt;host&gt; kernel: nf_conntrack: nf_conntrack: table full, dropping packet
This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S7-EVO;
  *  21.2R1-EVO and later versions;
  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-S2-EVO;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-EVO;
  *  22.3-EVO versions earlier than 22.3R2-EVO;
  *  22.4-EVO versions earlier than 22.4R2-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21606 | Junos OS: SRX Series: When &amp;quot;tcp-encap&amp;quot; is configured and specific packets are received flowd will crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21606</link><description>A Double Free vulnerability in the flow processing daemon (flowd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

In a remote access VPN scenario, if a "tcp-encap-profile" is configured and a sequence of specific packets is received, a flowd crash and restart will be observed.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on SRX Series:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S8;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S6;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21607 | Junos OS: MX Series and EX9200 Series: If the &amp;quot;tcp-reset&amp;quot; option used in an IPv6 filter, matched packets are accepted instead of rejected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21607</link><description>An Unsupported Feature in the UI vulnerability in Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series and EX9200 Series allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause partial impact to the integrity of the device.

If the "tcp-reset" option is added to the "reject" action in an IPv6 filter which matches on "payload-protocol", packets are permitted instead of rejected. This happens because the payload-protocol match criteria is not supported in the kernel filter causing it to accept all packets without taking any other action. As a fix the payload-protocol match will be treated the same as a "next-header" match to avoid this filter bypass.

This issue doesn't affect IPv4 firewall filters.

This issue affects Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series and EX9200 Series:



  *  All versions earlier than 20.4R3-S7;
  *  21.1 versions earlier than 21.1R3-S5;
  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S5;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S4;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S4;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S2;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2-S2, 22.3R3;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R1-S2, 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21611 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: In a jflow scenario continuous route churn will cause a memory leak and eventually an rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21611</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in the Routing Protocol Daemon (rpd) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

In a Juniper Flow Monitoring (jflow) scenario route churn that causes BGP next hops to be updated will cause a slow memory leak and eventually a crash and restart of rpd.

Thread level memory utilization for the areas where the leak occurs can be checked using the below command:

user@host&gt; show task memory detail | match so_in
so_in6 28 32 344450 11022400 344760 11032320
so_in 8 16 1841629 29466064 1841734 29467744
This issue affects:

Junos OS



  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3.




Junos OS Evolved



  *  21.4-EVO versions earlier than 21.4R3-EVO;
  *  22.1-EVO versions earlier than 22.1R3-EVO;
  *  22.2-EVO versions earlier than 22.2R3-EVO.




This issue does not affect:

Juniper Networks Junos OS versions earlier than 21.4R1.

Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 21.4R1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21612 | Junos OS Evolved: Specific TCP traffic causes OFP core and restart of RE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21612</link><description>An Improper Handling of Syntactically Invalid Structure vulnerability in Object Flooding Protocol (OFP) service of Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS Evolved platforms, when specific TCP packets are received on an open OFP port, the OFP crashes leading to a restart of Routine Engine (RE). Continuous receipt of these specific TCP packets will lead to a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved



  *  All versions earlier than 21.2R3-S7-EVO;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5-EVO ;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5-EVO;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4-EVO;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3-EVO ;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-EVO;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-EVO, 22.4R3-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21613 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A link flap causes patroot memory leak which leads to rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21613</link><description>A Missing Release of Memory after Effective Lifetime vulnerability in Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an rpd crash, leading to Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms, when traffic engineering is enabled for OSPF or ISIS, and a link flaps, a patroot memory leak is observed. This memory leak, over time, will lead to an rpd crash and restart.

The memory usage can be monitored using the below command.

user@host&gt; show task memory detail | match patroot
This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  All versions earlier than 21.2R3-S3;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S3;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3.




Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved



  *  All versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5-EVO;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-EVO;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-EVO;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21614 | Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved: A specific query via DREND causes rpd crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21614</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in Routing Protocol Daemon (RPD) of Juniper Networks Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved allows a network-based, unauthenticated attacker to cause rpd to crash, leading to Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS and Junos OS Evolved platforms, when NETCONF and gRPC are enabled, and a specific query is executed via Dynamic Rendering (DREND), rpd will crash and restart. Continuous execution of this specific query will cause a sustained Denial of Service (DoS) condition.

This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R2-S2, 22.2R3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2, 22.3R3.




Juniper Networks Junos OS Evolved



  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R2-S2-EVO, 22.2R3-EVO;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2-EVO, 22.3R3-EVO.




This issue does not affect Juniper Networks:

Junos OS versions earlier than 22.2R1;

Junos OS Evolved versions earlier than 22.2R1-EVO.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21616 | Junos OS: MX Series and SRX Series: Processing of a specific SIP packet causes NAT IP allocation to fail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21616</link><description>An Improper Validation of Syntactic Correctness of Input vulnerability in Packet Forwarding Engine (PFE) of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an unauthenticated, network-based attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS MX Series and SRX Series platforms, when SIP ALG is enabled, and a specific SIP packet is received and processed, NAT IP allocation fails for genuine traffic, which causes Denial of Service (DoS). Continuous receipt of this specific SIP ALG packet will cause a sustained DoS condition.

NAT IP usage can be monitored by running the following command.

user@srx&gt; show security nat resource-usage source-pool &lt;source_pool_name&gt;


Pool name: source_pool_name
..
Address Factor-index Port-range Used Avail Total Usage
X.X.X.X
0 Single Ports 50258 52342 62464 96% &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;
- Alg Ports 0 2048 2048 0%
This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS on MX Series and SRX Series



  *  All versions earlier than 21.2R3-S6;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S5;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S5;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S4;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S3;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R3-S1;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R2-S2, 22.4R3;
  *  23.2 versions earlier than 23.2R1-S1, 23.2R2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21617 | Junos OS: BGP flap on NSR-enabled devices causes memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21617</link><description>An Incomplete Cleanup vulnerability in Nonstop active routing (NSR) component of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows an adjacent, unauthenticated attacker to cause memory leak leading to Denial of Service (DoS).

On all Junos OS platforms, when NSR is enabled, a BGP flap will cause memory leak. A manual reboot of the system will restore the services.

The memory usage can be monitored using the below commands.

user@host&gt; show chassis routing-engine no-forwarding
user@host&gt; show system memory | no-more
This issue affects:

Juniper Networks Junos OS



  *  21.2 versions earlier than 21.2R3-S5;
  *  21.3 versions earlier than 21.3R3-S4;
  *  21.4 versions earlier than 21.4R3-S4;
  *  22.1 versions earlier than 22.1R3-S2;
  *  22.2 versions earlier than 22.2R3-S2;
  *  22.3 versions earlier than 22.3R2-S1, 22.3R3;
  *  22.4 versions earlier than 22.4R1-S2, 22.4R2.




This issue does not affect Junos OS versions earlier than 20.4R3-S7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 01:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0443 | Kernel: blkio memory leakage due to blkcg and some blkgs are not freed after they are made offline.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0443</link><description>A flaw was found in the blkgs destruction path in block/blk-cgroup.c in the Linux kernel, leading to a cgroup blkio memory leakage problem. When a cgroup is being destroyed, cgroup_rstat_flush() is only called at css_release_work_fn(), which is called when the blkcg reference count reaches 0. This circular dependency will prevent blkcg and some blkgs from being freed after they are made offline. This issue may allow an attacker with a local access to cause system instability, such as an out of memory error.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 23:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21982 |  CVE-2024-21982 Information Disclosure Vulnerability in ONTAP 9 </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21982</link><description>ONTAP versions 9.4 and higher are susceptible to a vulnerability 
which when successfully exploited could lead to disclosure of sensitive 
information to unprivileged attackers when the object-store profiler 
command is being run by an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 23:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51350 | A spoofing attack in ujcms v.8.0.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted script ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51350</link><description>A spoofing attack in ujcms v.8.0.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information and execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the X-Forwarded-For function in the header.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 22:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21337 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21337</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46474 | File Upload vulnerability PMB v.7.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via a crafted PHP file uplo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46474</link><description>File Upload vulnerability PMB v.7.4.8 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and escalate privileges via a crafted PHP file uploaded to the start_import.php file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20675 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20675</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0426 | ForU CMS cms_template.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0426</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin/cms_template.php. The manipulation of the argument t_name/t_path leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250445 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:05:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4959 | qkmc-rk redbbs Nickname cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4959</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in qkmc-rk redbbs 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Nickname Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250237 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7226 | meetyoucrop big-whale Admin Module all.api improper ownership management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in meetyoucrop big-whale 1.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /auth/user/all.api of the component Admin Module. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper ownership management. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250232.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50128 | The remote keyless system of the Hozard alarm system (alarmsystemen) v1.0 sends an identical radio frequency signal for each request, which ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50128</link><description>The remote keyless system of the Hozard alarm system (alarmsystemen) v1.0 sends an identical radio frequency signal for each request, which results in an attacker being able to conduct replay attacks to bring the alarm system to a disarmed state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50129 | Missing encryption in the NFC tags of the Flient Smart Door Lock v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via brief physical proximity t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50129</link><description>Missing encryption in the NFC tags of the Flient Smart Door Lock v1.0 allows attackers to create a cloned tag via brief physical proximity to the original tags, which results in an attacker gaining access to the perimeter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50123 | The number of attempts to bring the Hozard Alarm system (alarmsystemen) v1.0 to a disarmed state is not limited. This could allow an attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50123</link><description>The number of attempts to bring the Hozard Alarm system (alarmsystemen) v1.0 to a disarmed state is not limited. This could allow an attacker to perform a brute force on the SMS authentication, to bring the alarm system to a disarmed state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50124 | Flient Smart Door Lock v1.0 is vulnerable to Use of Default Credentials. Due to default credentials on a debug interface, in combination wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50124</link><description>Flient Smart Door Lock v1.0 is vulnerable to Use of Default Credentials. Due to default credentials on a debug interface, in combination with certain design choices, an attacker can unlock the Flient Smart Door Lock by replacing the fingerprint that is stored on the scanner.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50125 | A default engineer password set on the Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 allows an attacker to bring the alarm system to a disarmed st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50125</link><description>A default engineer password set on the Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 allows an attacker to bring the alarm system to a disarmed state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50126 | Missing encryption in the RFID tags of the Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 allow attackers to create a cloned tag via brief physical...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50126</link><description>Missing encryption in the RFID tags of the Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 allow attackers to create a cloned tag via brief physical proximity to one of the original tags, which results in an attacker being able to bring the alarm system to a disarmed state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50127 | Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 is vulnerable to Improper Authentication. Commands sent via the SMS functionality are accepted from ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50127</link><description>Hozard alarm system (Alarmsysteem) v1.0 is vulnerable to Improper Authentication. Commands sent via the SMS functionality are accepted from random phone numbers, which allows an attacker to bring the alarm system to a disarmed state from any given phone number.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0425 | ForU CMS password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0425</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in ForU CMS up to 2020-06-23. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php?act=reset_admin_psw. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250444.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:14:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0227 | Lack of Brute Force Protection in devise-two-factor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0227</link><description>Devise-Two-Factor does not throttle or otherwise restrict login attempts at the server by default. When combined with the Time-based One Time Password algorithm's (TOTP) inherent entropy limitations, it's possible for an attacker to bypass the 2FA mechanism through brute-force attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22198 | Authenticated (user role) arbitrary command execution by modifying `start_cmd` setting (GHSL-2023-268)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22198</link><description>Nginx-UI is a web interface to manage Nginx configurations. It is vulnerable to arbitrary command execution by abusing the configuration settings. The `Home &gt; Preference` page exposes a list of system settings such as `Run Mode`, `Jwt Secret`, `Node Secret` and `Terminal Start Command`. While the UI doesn't allow users to modify the `Terminal Start Command` setting, it is possible to do so by sending a request to the API. This issue may lead to authenticated remote code execution, privilege escalation, and information disclosure. This vulnerability has been patched in version 2.0.0.beta.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0423 | CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System dishes.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0423</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Online Food Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file dishes.php. The manipulation of the argument res_id leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250442 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0424 | CodeAstro Simple Banking System Create a User Page createuser.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0424</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in CodeAstro Simple Banking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file createuser.php of the component Create a User Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250443.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22196 | Authenticated (user role) SQL injection in `OrderAndPaginate` (GHSL-2023-270)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22196</link><description>Nginx-UI is an online statistics for Server Indicators​​ Monitor CPU usage, memory usage, load average, and disk usage in real-time. This issue may lead to information disclosure. By using `DefaultQuery`, the `"desc"` and `"id"` values are used as default values if the query parameters are not set. Thus, the `order` and `sort_by` query parameter are user-controlled and are being appended to the `order` variable without any sanitization. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.0.beta.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0422 | CodeAstro POS and Inventory Management System New Item Creation Page new_item cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0422</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro POS and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /new_item of the component New Item Creation Page. The manipulation of the argument new_item leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250441 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0419 | Jasper httpdx HTTP POST Request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0419</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jasper httpdx up to 1.5.4 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250439.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0417 | DeShang DSShop MemberAuth.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0417</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in DeShang DSShop up to 2.1.5. This affects an unknown part of the file application/home/controller/MemberAuth.php. The manipulation of the argument member_info leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250437 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0418 | iSharer and upRedSun File Sharing Wizard GET Request denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0418</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in iSharer and upRedSun File Sharing Wizard up to 1.5.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250438 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22197 | Authenticated (user role) remote command execution by modifying `nginx` settings (GHSL-2023-269)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22197</link><description>Nginx-ui is online statistics for Server Indicators​​ Monitor CPU usage, memory usage, load average, and disk usage in real-time. The `Home &gt; Preference` page exposes a small list of nginx settings such as `Nginx Access Log Path` and `Nginx Error Log Path`. However, the API also exposes `test_config_cmd`, `reload_cmd` and `restart_cmd`. While the UI doesn't allow users to modify any of these settings, it is possible to do so by sending a request to the API. This issue may lead to authenticated Remote Code Execution, Privilege Escalation, and Information Disclosure. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.0.beta.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22199 | Django Template Engine Vulnerable to XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22199</link><description>This package provides universal methods to use multiple template engines with the Fiber web framework using the Views interface. This vulnerability specifically impacts web applications that render user-supplied data through this template engine, potentially leading to the execution of malicious scripts in users' browsers when visiting affected web pages. The vulnerability has been addressed, the template engine now defaults to having autoescape set to `true`, effectively mitigating the risk of XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:50:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0415 | DeShang DSMall Image URL TaobaoExport.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0415</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in DeShang DSMall up to 6.1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file application/home/controller/TaobaoExport.php of the component Image URL Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250435.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0416 | DeShang DSMall MemberAuth.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0416</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in DeShang DSMall up to 5.0.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file application/home/controller/MemberAuth.php. The manipulation of the argument file_name leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250436.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50671 | In exiftags 1.01, nikon_prop1 in nikon.c has a heap-based buffer overflow (write of size 28) because snprintf can write to an unexpected add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50671</link><description>In exiftags 1.01, nikon_prop1 in nikon.c has a heap-based buffer overflow (write of size 28) because snprintf can write to an unexpected address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0413 | DeShang DSKMS install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0413</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DeShang DSKMS up to 3.1.2. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file public/install.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-250433 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0414 | DeShang DSCMS install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0414</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DeShang DSCMS up to 3.1.2/7.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file public/install.php. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250434 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0411 | DeShang DSMall HTTP GET Request install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0411</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DeShang DSMall up to 6.1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file public/install.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250431.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0412 | DeShang DSShop HTTP GET Request install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0412</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DeShang DSShop up to 3.1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file public/install.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250432.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0429 | Buffer overflow vulnerability on Hex Workshop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0429</link><description>A denial service vulnerability has been found on  Hex Workshop affecting version 6.7, an attacker could send a command line file arguments and control the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) records resulting in a service shutdown.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22942 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the hostName parameter in the setWan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22942</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the hostName parameter in the setWanCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23057 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the tz parameter in the setNtpCfg fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23057</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the tz parameter in the setNtpCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23058 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pass parameter in the setTr069Cf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23058</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the pass parameter in the setTr069Cfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23059 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the username parameter in the setDdn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23059</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the username parameter in the setDdnsCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23061 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the minute parameter in the setSched...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23061</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the minute parameter in the setScheduleCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23060 | TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ip parameter in the setDmzCfg fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23060</link><description>TOTOLINK A3300R V17.0.0cu.557_B20221024 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the ip parameter in the setDmzCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 16:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51987 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 contains a login bypass in the HNAP1 interface, which allows attackers to log in to administrator accounts with empty...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51987</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 contains a login bypass in the HNAP1 interface, which allows attackers to log in to administrator accounts with empty passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51989 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 contains a login bypass in the HNAP1 interface, which allows attackers to log in to administrator accounts with empty...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51989</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 contains a login bypass in the HNAP1 interface, which allows attackers to log in to administrator accounts with empty passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51984 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 was found to contain a command injection in SetStaticRouteSettings function. allows remote attackers to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51984</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.2 was found to contain a command injection in SetStaticRouteSettings function. allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5118 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability in Kofax Capture software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5118</link><description>The application is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the endpoint /sofer/DocumentService.asc/SaveAnnotation, where input data transmitted via the POST method in the parameters author and text are not adequately sanitized and validated. This allows for the injection of malicious JavaScript code. The vulnerability was identified in the function for adding new annotations while editing document content.

Reporters inform that the vulnerability has been removed in software versions above 11.1.x. Previous versions may also be vulnerable, but this has not been confirmed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:35:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6554 | Missing authorisation in TCExam</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6554</link><description>When access to the "admin" folder is not protected by some external authorization mechanisms e.g. Apache Basic Auth, it is possible for any user to download protected information like exam answers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6242 | The EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6242</link><description>The EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4 (for Pro) &amp; 2.2.7 (for Free). This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the evo_eventpost_update_meta function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary post metadata via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6244 | The EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6244</link><description>The EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.4 (Pro) &amp; 2.2.8 (Free). This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the save_virtual_event_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify virtual event settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6938 | The Oxygen Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a custom field in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6938</link><description>The Oxygen Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a custom field in all versions up to, and including, 4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. NOTE: Version 4.8.1 of the Oxygen Builder plugin for WordPress addresses this vulnerability by implementing an optional filter to provide output escaping for dynamic data. Please see https://oxygenbuilder.com/documentation/other/security/#filtering-dynamic-data for more details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20573 | Debug Exception Delivery in Secure Nested Paging</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20573</link><description>A privileged attacker
can prevent delivery of debug exceptions to SEV-SNP guests potentially
resulting in guests not receiving expected debug information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51750 | ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because file downloads can occur.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51750</link><description>ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because file downloads can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51751 | ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because Alt-F4 can be used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51751</link><description>ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because Alt-F4 can be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50159 | In ScaleFusion (Windows Desktop App) agent v10.5.2, Kiosk mode application restrictions can be bypassed allowing arbitrary code to be execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50159</link><description>In ScaleFusion (Windows Desktop App) agent v10.5.2, Kiosk mode application restrictions can be bypassed allowing arbitrary code to be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51748 | ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because Ctrl-O and Ctrl-S can be used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51748</link><description>ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because Ctrl-O and Ctrl-S can be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51749 | ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because a search can be made from a tooltip.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51749</link><description>ScaleFusion 10.5.2 does not properly limit users to the Edge application because a search can be made from a tooltip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 13:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4958 | qkmc-rk redbbs Post cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4958</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in qkmc-rk redbbs 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component Post Handler. The manipulation of the argument title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-250236.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 11:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52027 | TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the NTPSyncWithHost func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52027</link><description>TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the NTPSyncWithHost function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52029 | TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setDiagnosisCfg func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52029</link><description>TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setDiagnosisCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52030 | TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setOpModeCfg functio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52030</link><description>TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setOpModeCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52031 | TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the UploadFirmwareFile f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52031</link><description>TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the UploadFirmwareFile function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52028 | TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setTracerouteCfg fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52028</link><description>TOTOlink A3700R v9.1.2u.5822_B20200513 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setTracerouteCfg function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52032 | TOTOlink EX1200T V4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the "main" function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52032</link><description>TOTOlink EX1200T V4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the "main" function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4246 | The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4246</link><description>The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the give_sendwp_remote_install_handler function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate the SendWP plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4247 | The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4247</link><description>The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the give_sendwp_disconnect function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate the SendWP plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4248 | The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4248</link><description>The GiveWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 2.33.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the give_stripe_disconnect_connect_stripe_account function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate the plugin's stripe integration settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4372 | The LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'esi' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4372</link><description>The LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'esi' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4960 | The WCFM Marketplace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'wcfm_stores' shortcode in versions up to, and in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4960</link><description>The WCFM Marketplace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'wcfm_stores' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4962 | The Video PopUp plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'video_popup' shortcode in versions up to, and includi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4962</link><description>The Video PopUp plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'video_popup' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5504 | The BackWPup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 via the Log File Folder. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5504</link><description>The BackWPup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in versions up to, and including, 4.0.1 via the Log File Folder. This allows authenticated attackers to store backups in arbitrary folders on the server provided they can be written to by the server. Additionally, default settings will place an index.php and a .htaccess file into the chosen directory (unless already present) when the first backup job is run that are intended to prevent directory listing and file access. This means that an attacker could set the backup directory to the root of another site in a shared environment and thus disable that site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5691 | The Chatbot for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in version 2.3.9 due to insuf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5691</link><description>The Chatbot for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in version 2.3.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6220 | The Piotnet Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'piotnetforms...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6220</link><description>The Piotnet Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'piotnetforms_ajax_form_builder' function in versions up to, and including, 1.0.26. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6266 | The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to insufficient path and file validation on the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6266</link><description>The Backup Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to insufficient path and file validation on the BMI_BACKUP case of the handle_downloading function in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download back-up files which can contain sensitive information such as user passwords, PII,  database credentials, and much more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6316 | The MW WP Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the '_single_file_up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6316</link><description>The MW WP Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the '_single_file_upload' function in versions up to, and including, 5.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6369 | The Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a mi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6369</link><description>The Export WP Page to Static HTML/CSS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to disclose sensitive information or perform unauthorized actions, such as saving advanced plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6496 | The Manage Notification E-mails plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6496</link><description>The Manage Notification E-mails plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.5 via the card_famne_export_settings function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6504 | The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unautho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6504</link><description>The User Profile Builder – Beautiful User Registration Forms, User Profiles &amp; User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the wppb_toolbox_usermeta_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to expose sensitive information within user metadata.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6556 | The FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via currency opti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6556</link><description>The FOX – Currency Switcher Professional for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via currency options in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6558 | The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6558</link><description>The Export and Import Users and Customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation on the 'upload_import_file' function in versions up to, and including, 2.4.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with shop manager-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6561 | The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the featured image alt text in all ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6561</link><description>The Featured Image from URL (FIFU) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the featured image alt text in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6567 | The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order_by’ parameter in all versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6567</link><description>The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order_by’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5.7 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6582 | The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6582</link><description>The ElementsKit Elementor addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.3 via the ekit_widgetarea_content function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to obtain contents of posts in draft, private or pending review status that should not be visible to the general public. This applies to posts created with Elementor only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6583 | The Import and export users and customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6583</link><description>The Import and export users and customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.24.2 via the Recurring Import functionality. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator access and above, to read and delete the contents of arbitrary files on the server including wp-config.php, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6598 | The SpeedyCache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the speedycache...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6598</link><description>The SpeedyCache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the speedycache_save_varniship, speedycache_img_update_settings, speedycache_preloading_add_settings, and speedycache_preloading_delete_resource functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update plugin options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6624 | The Import and export users and customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6624</link><description>The Import and export users and customers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.24.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6632 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via DOM in all versions up to and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6632</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via DOM in all versions up to and including 3.9.1.1 (versions up to 2.9.1.1 in Happy Addons for Elementor Pro) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6634 | The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5.7 via the get_content fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6634</link><description>The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Command Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5.7 via the get_content function. This is due to the plugin making use of the call_user_func function with user input. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute any public function with one parameter, which could result in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6636 | The Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type val...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6636</link><description>The Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation on the 'gspb_save_files' function in versions up to, and including, 7.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level capabilities or above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6637 | The CAOS | Host Google Analytics Locally plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6637</link><description>The CAOS | Host Google Analytics Locally plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_settings' function in versions up to, and including, 4.7.14. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6638 | The GTG Product Feed for Shopping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6638</link><description>The GTG Product Feed for Shopping plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_settings' function in versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6645 | The Post Grid Combo – 36+ Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JS parameter in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6645</link><description>The Post Grid Combo – 36+ Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JS parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.64 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6684 | The Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ive' shortcode in versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6684</link><description>The Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ive' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.2.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on 'width' and 'height' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6737 | The Enable Media Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the SHORTPIXEL_DEBUG parameter in all vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6737</link><description>The Enable Media Replace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the SHORTPIXEL_DEBUG parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Exploiting this vulnerability requires the attacker to know the ID of an attachment uploaded by the user they are attacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6742 | The Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6742</link><description>The Gallery Plugin for WordPress – Envira Photo Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an improper capability check on the 'envira_gallery_insert_images' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to modify galleries on other users' posts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6751 | The Hostinger plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings update due to a missing capability check on the function pu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6751</link><description>The Hostinger plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin settings update due to a missing capability check on the function publish_website in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable and disable maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6776 | The 3D FlipBook plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘Ready Function’ field in all versions up to, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6776</link><description>The 3D FlipBook plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘Ready Function’ field in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6781 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom fields in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6781</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom fields in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied values. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6782 | The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6782</link><description>The AMP for WP – Accelerated Mobile Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.92 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6828 | The Contact Form, Survey &amp; Popup Form Plugin for WordPress –  ARForms Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6828</link><description>The Contact Form, Survey &amp; Popup Form Plugin for WordPress –  ARForms Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘ arf_http_referrer_url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6855 | The Paid Memberships Pro – Content Restriction, User Registration, &amp; Paid Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6855</link><description>The Paid Memberships Pro – Content Restriction, User Registration, &amp; Paid Subscriptions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of membership levels created by the plugin due to an incorrectly implemented capability check in the pmpro_rest_api_get_permissions_check function in all versions up to 2.12.5 (inclusive). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change membership levels including prices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6875 | The POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6875</link><description>The POST SMTP Mailer – Email log, Delivery Failure Notifications and Best Mail SMTP for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data and modification of data due to a type juggling issue on the connect-app REST endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset the API key used to authenticate to the mailer and view logs, including password reset emails, allowing site takeover.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6878 | The Slick Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6878</link><description>The Slick Social Share Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'dcssb_ajax_update' function in versions up to, and including, 2.4.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions or above to update the site options arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6882 | The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘environment_mode’ parameter in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6882</link><description>The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘environment_mode’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.3.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6924 | The Photo Gallery by 10Web plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via widgets in versions up to, and including, 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6924</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via widgets in versions up to, and including, 1.8.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with administrator-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. It can also be exploited with a contributor-level permission with a page builder plugin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6934 | The Limit Login Attempts Reloaded plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6934</link><description>The Limit Login Attempts Reloaded plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 2.25.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6979 | The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6979</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ivole_import_upload_csv AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.38.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6988 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's extend_builder_render_js shortco...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6988</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's extend_builder_render_js shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.239 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6990 | The Weaver Xtreme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom post meta in all versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6990</link><description>The Weaver Xtreme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via custom post meta in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied meta (page-head-code). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6994 | The List category posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'catlist' shortcode in all versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6994</link><description>The List category posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'catlist' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.89.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7019 | The LightStart – Maintenance Mode, Coming Soon and Landing Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7019</link><description>The LightStart – Maintenance Mode, Coming Soon and Landing Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the insert_template function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change page designs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7048 | The My Sticky Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6. This is due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7048</link><description>The My Sticky Bar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in mystickymenu-contact-leads.php. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger the export of a CSV file containing contact leads via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Because the CSV file is exported to a public location, it can be downloaded during a very short window of time before it is automatically deleted by the export function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7070 | The Email Encoder – Protect Email Addresses and Phone Numbers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7070</link><description>The Email Encoder – Protect Email Addresses and Phone Numbers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's eeb_mailto shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7071 | The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7071</link><description>The Essential Blocks – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks, Patterns &amp; Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Table of Contents block in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0252 | Remote code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0252</link><description>ManageEngine ADSelfService Plus versions 6401 and below are vulnerable to the remote code execution due to the improper handling in the load balancer component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:25:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37644 | SWFTools 0.9.2 772e55a allows attackers to trigger a large memory-allocation attempt via a crafted document, as demonstrated by pdf2swf. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37644</link><description>SWFTools 0.9.2 772e55a allows attackers to trigger a large memory-allocation attempt via a crafted document, as demonstrated by pdf2swf. This occurs in png_read_chunk in lib/png.c.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 07:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6223 | The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5.7 via the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6223</link><description>The LearnPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.5.7 via the /wp-json/lp/v1/profile/course-tab REST API due to missing validation on the 'userID' user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve the details of another user's course progress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6446 | The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6446</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.40 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6506 | The WP 2FA – Two-factor authentication for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6506</link><description>The WP 2FA – Two-factor authentication for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 via the send_backup_codes_email due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for subscriber-level attackers to email arbitrary users on the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6520 | The WP 2FA – Two-factor authentication for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6520</link><description>The WP 2FA – Two-factor authentication for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the send_backup_codes_email function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to send emails with arbitrary content to registered users via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator or other registered user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. While a nonce check is present, it is only executed if a nonce is set. By omitting a nonce from the request, the check can be bypassed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6699 | The WP Compress – Image Optimizer [All-In-One] plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and includin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6699</link><description>The WP Compress – Image Optimizer [All-In-One] plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 6.10.33 via the css parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6883 | The Easy Social Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6883</link><description>The Easy Social Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX functions in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform unauthorized actions, such as modifying the plugin's Facebook and Instagram access tokens and updating group IDs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21637 | XSS in Authentik via JavaScript-URI as Redirect URI and form_post Response Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21637</link><description>Authentik is an open-source Identity Provider. Authentik is a vulnerable to a reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability via JavaScript-URIs in OpenID Connect flows with `response_mode=form_post`. This relatively user could use the described attacks to perform a privilege escalation. This vulnerability has been patched in versions 2023.10.6 and 2023.8.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21669 | Hyperledger Aries Cloud Agent Python result of presentation verification not checked for LDP-VC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21669</link><description>Hyperledger Aries Cloud Agent Python (ACA-Py) is a foundation for building decentralized identity applications and services running in non-mobile environments. When verifying W3C Format Verifiable Credentials using JSON-LD with Linked Data Proofs (LDP-VCs), the result of verifying the presentation `document.proof` was not factored into the final `verified` value (`true`/`false`) on the presentation record. The flaw enables holders of W3C Format Verifiable Credentials using JSON-LD with Linked Data Proofs (LDPs) to present incorrectly constructed proofs, and allows malicious verifiers to save and replay a presentation from such holders as their own. This vulnerability has been present since version 0.7.0 and fixed in version 0.10.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:49:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6630 | The Contact Form 7 – Dynamic Text Extension plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6630</link><description>The Contact Form 7 – Dynamic Text Extension plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 via the CF7_get_custom_field and CF7_get_current_user shortcodes due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor access or higher to access arbitrary metadata of any post type, referencing the post by id and the meta by key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5448 | The WP Register Profile With Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5448</link><description>The WP Register Profile With Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 3.5.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the update_password_validate function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reset a user's password via a forged request granted they can trick the user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38267 | IBM Security Access Manager Appliance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38267</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Appliance (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to obtain sensitive configuration information.  IBM X-Force ID:  260584.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31001 | IBM Security Access Manager Container information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31001</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.6.1) temporarily stores sensitive information in files that could be accessed by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  254653.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31003 | IBM Security Access Manager Container privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31003</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to obtain root access due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  254658.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51073 | An issue in Buffalo LS210D v.1.78-0.03 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Firmware Update Script at /etc/init.d/upda...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51073</link><description>An issue in Buffalo LS210D v.1.78-0.03 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Firmware Update Script at /etc/init.d/update_notifications.sh.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22194 | cdo-local-uuid vulnerable to insertion of artifact derived from developer&amp;#x27;s Present Working Directory into demonstration code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22194</link><description>cdo-local-uuid project provides a specialized UUID-generating function that can, on user request, cause a program to generate deterministic UUIDs. An information leakage vulnerability is present in `cdo-local-uuid` at version `0.4.0`, and in `case-utils` in unpatched versions (matching the pattern `0.x.0`) at and since `0.5.0`, before `0.15.0`. The vulnerability stems from a Python function, `cdo_local_uuid.local_uuid()`, and its original implementation `case_utils.local_uuid()`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22195 | Jinja vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22195</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. Special placeholders in the template allow writing code similar to Python syntax. It is possible to inject arbitrary HTML attributes into the rendered HTML template, potentially leading to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS). The Jinja `xmlattr` filter can be abused to inject arbitrary HTML attribute keys and values, bypassing the auto escaping mechanism and potentially leading to XSS. It may also be possible to bypass attribute validation checks if they are blacklist-based.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40361 | Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability in Elite CRM v1.2.11 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the language parameter to the /ngs/log...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40361</link><description>Cross Site Scripting Vulnerability in Elite CRM v1.2.11 allows attacker to execute arbitrary code via the language parameter to the /ngs/login endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45169 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45169</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the pmsvcs kernel extension to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267967.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45171 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45171</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the kernel to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267969.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52274 | member/index/register.html in YzmCMS 6.5 through 7.0 allows XSS via the Referer HTTP header.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52274</link><description>member/index/register.html in YzmCMS 6.5 through 7.0 allows XSS via the Referer HTTP header.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45173 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45173</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the NFS kernel extension to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267971.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45175 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45175</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, and VIOS 3.1 could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the TCP/IP kernel extension to cause a denial of service.  IBM X-Force ID:  267973.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 02:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22190 | Untrusted search path under some conditions on Windows allows arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22190</link><description>GitPython is a python library used to interact with Git repositories. There is an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-40590. On Windows, GitPython uses an untrusted search path if it uses a shell to run `git`, as well as when it runs `bash.exe` to interpret hooks. If either of those features are used on Windows, a malicious `git.exe` or `bash.exe` may be run from an untrusted repository. This issue has been patched in version 3.1.41.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21666 | Pimcore Customer Data Framework Improper Access Control allows unprivileged user to access customers duplicates list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21666</link><description>The Customer Management Framework (CMF) for Pimcore adds functionality for customer data management, segmentation, personalization and marketing automation. An authenticated and unauthorized user can access the list of potential duplicate users and see their data. Permissions are enforced when reaching the `/admin/customermanagementframework/duplicates/list` endpoint allowing an authenticated user without the permissions to access the endpoint and query the data available there. Unauthorized user(s) can access PII data from customers. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21667 | Pimcore Customer Data Framework Improper Access Control allows unprivileged user to access GDPR extracts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21667</link><description>pimcore/customer-data-framework is the Customer Management Framework for management of customer data within Pimcore. An authenticated and unauthorized user can access the GDPR data extraction feature and query over the information returned, leading to customer data exposure. Permissions are not enforced when reaching the `/admin/customermanagementframework/gdpr-data/search-data-objects` endpoint allowing an authenticated user without the permissions to access the endpoint and query the data available there. An unauthorized user can access PII data from customers. This vulnerability has been patched in version 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 01:58:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21665 | Pimcore Ecommerce Framework Bundle Improper Access Control allows unprivileged user to access back-office orders list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21665</link><description>ecommerce-framework-bundle is the Pimcore Ecommerce Framework Bundle. An authenticated and unauthorized user can access the back-office orders list and be able to query over the information returned. Access control and permissions are not being enforced. This vulnerability has been patched in version 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:56:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>