<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-47891 | GPU DDK - Exploitable double free on PTL_STREAM_DESC object in the kernel function TLServerCloseStreamKM due to a race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47891</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47898 | GPU DDK - PVRSRVDeviceSyncOpen use-after-free condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47898</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47899 | GPU DDK - PVRSRVDeviceServicesOpen use-after-free condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47899</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46974 | GPU DDK - Arbitrary write of read-only dmabuf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46974</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper read/write operations on imported/exported DMA buffers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 03:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13396 | Frictionless &amp;lt;= 0.0.23 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13396</link><description>The Frictionless plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'frictionless_form' shortcode[s] in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.23 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13397 | WPRadio – WordPress Radio Streaming Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13397</link><description>The WPRadio – WordPress Radio Streaming Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpradio_player' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13399 | Gosign – Posts Slider Block &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13399</link><description>The Gosign – Posts Slider Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'posts-slider-block' block in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13767 | Live2DWebCanvas &amp;lt;= 1.9.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13767</link><description>The Live2DWebCanvas plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the ClearFiles() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-1736 | Ubuntu's configuration of gnome-control-center allowed Remote Desktop Sharing to be enabled by default.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-1736</link><description>Ubuntu's configuration of gnome-control-center allowed Remote Desktop Sharing to be enabled by default.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0092 | An authenticated user who has read access to the juju controller model, may construct a remote request to download an arbitrary file from th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0092</link><description>An authenticated user who has read access to the juju controller model, may construct a remote request to download an arbitrary file from the controller's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11936 | gdbus setgid privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11936</link><description>gdbus setgid privilege escalation</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-28653 | Users can consume unlimited disk space in /var/crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-28653</link><description>Users can consume unlimited disk space in /var/crash</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 02:08:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23920 | ChargePoint Home Flex Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23920</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the onboardee module. The issue results from improper access control. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23921 | ChargePoint Home Flex Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23921</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the wlanapp module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23929 | Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Telematics Directory Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23929</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX devices. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the telematics functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23928 | Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Telematics Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23928</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise the integrity of downloaded information on affected installations of Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the telematics functionality, which operates over HTTPS. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23930 | Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX Media Service Improper Handling of Exceptional Conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23930</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Media service, which listens on TCP port 42000 by default. The issue results from improper handling of error conditions. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23937 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS Debug Interface Format String</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23937</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the debug interface. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it as a format specifier. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23963 | Alpine Halo9 Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23963</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. An attacker must first obtain the ability to pair a malicious Bluetooth device with the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the PBAP_DecodeVCARD function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24336 | SXF Common Library handles input data improperly. If a product using the library reads a crafted file, the product may be crashed.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24336</link><description>SXF Common Library handles input data improperly. If a product using the library reads a crafted file, the product may be crashed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23962 | Alpine Halo9 Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23962</link><description>This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Alpine Halo9 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DLT interface, which listens on TCP port 3490 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6195 | Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6195</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.5 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2. GitLab was vulnerable to Server Side Request Forgery when an attacker uses a malicious URL in the markdown  image value when importing a GitHub repository.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1211 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1211</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 10.6 prior to 16.9.7, starting from 16.10 prior to 16.10.5, and starting from 16.11 prior to 16.11.2 in which cross-site request forgery may have been possible on GitLab instances configured to use JWT as an OmniAuth provider.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23970 | ChargePoint Home Flex Improper Certificate Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23970</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to compromise transport security on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CURLOPT_SSL_VERIFYHOST setting. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:49:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23971 | ChargePoint Home Flex OCPP bswitch Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23971</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OCPP messages. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23969 | ChargePoint Home Flex wlanchnllst Out-Of-Bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23969</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the wlanchnllst function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23968 | ChargePoint Home Flex SrvrToSmSetAutoChnlListMsg Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23968</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of ChargePoint Home Flex charging stations. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SrvrToSmSetAutoChnlListMsg function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23973 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS HTTP GET Request Handling Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23973</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within the handling of HTTP GET requests. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24731 | Silicon Labs Gecko OS http_download Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24731</link><description>This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Silicon Labs Gecko OS. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the http_download command. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24885 | pwn.college has a XSS on dojo pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24885</link><description>pwn.college is an education platform to learn about, and practice, core cybersecurity concepts in a hands-on fashion. Missing access control on rendering custom (unprivileged) dojo pages causes ability for users to create stored XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24886 | pwn.college has Symlink LFI in Dojo repos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24886</link><description>pwn.college is an education platform to learn about, and practice, core cybersecurity concepts in a hands-on fashion. Incorrect symlink checks on user specified dojos allows for users (admin not required) to perform an LFI from the CTFd container. When a user clones or updates repositories, a check is performed to see if the repository had contained any symlinks. A malicious user could craft a repository with symlinks pointed to sensitive files and then retrieve them using the CTFd website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 22:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0882 | code-projects Chat System addnewmember.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Chat System up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/addnewmember.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 21:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0880 | Codezips Gym Management System updateplan.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0880</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dashboard/admin/updateplan.php. The manipulation of the argument planid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0881 | Codezips Gym Management System saveroutine.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0881</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /dashboard/admin/saveroutine.php. The manipulation of the argument rname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11609 | AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11609</link><description>AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of AutomationDirect C-More EA9. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EAP9 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24772.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11610 | AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11610</link><description>AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of AutomationDirect C-More EA9. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EAP9 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24773.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11611 | AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11611</link><description>AutomationDirect C-More EA9 EAP9 File Parsing Memory Corruption Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of AutomationDirect C-More EA9. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EAP9 files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-24774.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0568 | Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0568</link><description>Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25302.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0569 | Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0569</link><description>Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25303.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0570 | Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0570</link><description>Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25304.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0571 | Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0571</link><description>Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25305.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0572 | Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0572</link><description>Sante PACS Server Web Portal DCM File Parsing Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to write files in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-25308.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0573 | Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0573</link><description>Sante PACS Server DCM File Parsing Directory Traversal Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create arbitrary files on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of DCM files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to write files in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-25309.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0574 | Sante PACS Server URL path Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0574</link><description>Sante PACS Server URL path Memory Corruption Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of URLs in the web server module. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a memory corruption condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-25318.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0144 | Zoom Workplace Apps - Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0144</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in some Zoom Workplace Apps may allow an authorized user to conduct a loss of integrity via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0145 | Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows - Untrusted Search Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0145</link><description>Untrusted search path in the installer for some Zoom Workplace Apps for Windows may allow an authorized user to conduct an escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0146 | Zoom Workplace app for macOS - Symlink Following</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0146</link><description>Symlink following in the installer for Zoom Workplace App for macOS before 6.2.10 may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:52:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0147 | Zoom Workplace App for Linux - Type Confusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0147</link><description>Type confusion in the Zoom Workplace App for Linux before 6.2.10 may allow an authorized user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0142 | Zoom Jenkins Marketplace plugin - Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0142</link><description>Cleartext storage of sensitive information in the Zoom Jenkins Marketplace plugin before version 1.4 may allow an authenticated user to conduct a disclosure of information via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0143 | Zoom Workplace Apps for Linux - Out-of-bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0143</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the Zoom Workplace App for Linux before version 6.2.5 may allow an unauthorized user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24802 | Soundness issue with Plonky2 look up tables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24802</link><description>Plonky2 is a SNARK implementation based on techniques from PLONK and FRI. Lookup tables, whose length is not divisible by 26 = floor(num_routed_wires / 3) always include the 0 -&gt; 0 input-output pair. Thus a malicious prover can always prove that f(0) = 0 for any lookup table f (unless its length happens to be divisible by 26). The cause of problem is that the LookupTableGate-s are padded with zeros. A workaround from the user side is to extend the table (by repeating some entries) so that its length becomes divisible by 26. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10026 | Improved Seeding and Hashing In gVisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10026</link><description>A weak hashing algorithm and small sizes of seeds/secrets in Google's gVisor allowed for a remote attacker to calculate a local IP address and a per-boot identifier that could aid in tracking of a device in certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:23:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10603 | Weaknesses in the generation of TCP/UDP source ports and some other header values in Google's gVisor allowed them to be predicted by an exte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10603</link><description>Weaknesses in the generation of TCP/UDP source ports and some other header values in Google's gVisor allowed them to be predicted by an external attacker in some circumstances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10604 | Identifiable Header Values In Fuchsia Leading To Tracking of The User</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10604</link><description>Vulnerabilities in the algorithms used by Fuchsia to populate network protocol header fields, specifically the TCP ISN, TCP timestamp, TCP and UDP source ports, and IPv4/IPv6 fragment ID allow for these values to be guessed under circumstances</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44142 | The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.12. Processing a maliciously crafted image may l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44142</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved bounds checks. This issue is fixed in GarageBand 10.4.12. Processing a maliciously crafted image may lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0680 | New Rock Technologies Cloud Connected Devices has a Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command (&amp;#x27;OS Command Injection&amp;#x27;) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0680</link><description>Affected products contain a vulnerability in the device cloud rpc command handling process that could allow remote attackers to take control over arbitrary devices connected to the cloud.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0681 | New Rock Technologies Cloud Connected Devices  Improper Neutralization of Wildcards or Matching Symbols</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0681</link><description>The Cloud MQTT service of the affected products supports wildcard topic 
subscription which could allow an attacker to obtain sensitive 
information from tapping the service communications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24505 | This vulnerability allows a high-privileged authenticated PAM user to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by uploadi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24505</link><description>This vulnerability allows a high-privileged authenticated PAM user to achieve remote command execution on the affected PAM system by uploading a specially crafted upgrade file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24506 | A specific authentication strategy allows to learn ids of PAM users associated with certain authentication types.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24506</link><description>A specific authentication strategy allows to learn ids of PAM users associated with certain authentication types.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24507 | This vulnerability allows appliance compromise at boot time.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24507</link><description>This vulnerability allows appliance compromise at boot time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24502 | An improper session validation allows an unauthenticated attacker to cause certain request notifications to be executed in the context of an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24502</link><description>An improper session validation allows an unauthenticated attacker to cause certain request notifications to be executed in the context of an incorrect user by spoofing the client IP address.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24503 | A malicious actor can fix the session of a PAM user by tricking the user to click on a specially crafted link to the PAM server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24503</link><description>A malicious actor can fix the session of a PAM user by tricking the user to click on a specially crafted link to the PAM server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24504 | An improper input validation the CSRF filter results in unsanitized user input written to the application logs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24504</link><description>An improper input validation the CSRF filter results in unsanitized user input written to the application logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12248 | Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability in Contec Health CMS8000 Patient Monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12248</link><description>The affected product is vulnerable to an out-of-bounds write, which could allow an attacker to send specially formatted UDP requests in order to write arbitrary data. This could result in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0626 | Hidden Functionality vulnerability in Contec Health CMS8000 Patient Monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0626</link><description>The affected product sends out remote access requests to a hard-coded IP address, bypassing existing device network settings to do so. This could serve as a backdoor and lead to a malicious actor being able to upload and overwrite files on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0683 | Exposure of Private Personal Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Contec Health CMS8000 Patient Monitor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0683</link><description>In its default configuration, the affected product transmits plain-text patient data to a hard-coded public IP address when a patient is hooked up to the monitor. This could lead to a leakage of confidential patient data to any device with that IP address or an attacker in a machine-in-the-middle scenario.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24500 | The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to access information in PAM database.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24500</link><description>The vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to access information in PAM database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24501 | An improper input validation allows an unauthenticated attacker to alter PAM logs by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24501</link><description>An improper input validation allows an unauthenticated attacker to alter PAM logs by sending a specially crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0874 | code-projects Simple Plugins Car Rental Management approve.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0874</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Simple Plugins Car Rental Management 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/approve.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0477 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0477</link><description>An encryption vulnerability exists in all versions prior to V15.00.001 of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre. The vulnerability exists due to a weak encryption methodology and could allow a threat actor to extract passwords belonging to other users of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:54:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29080 | Privilege escalation in InstallShield</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29080</link><description>Potential privilege escalation vulnerability in Revenera InstallShield versions 2022 R2 and 2021 R2 due to adding InstallScript custom action to a Basic MSI or InstallScript MSI project extracting few binaries to a predefined writable folder during installation time. The standard user account has write access to these files and folders, hence replacing them during installation time can lead to a DLL hijacking vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0497 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0497</link><description>A data exposure vulnerability exists in all versions prior to V15.00.001 of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre. The vulnerability exists due to storing credentials in the configuration file of EventLogAttachmentExtractor, ArchiveExtractor, LogCleanUp, or ArchiveLogCleanUp packages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0498 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0498</link><description>A data exposure vulnerability exists in all versions prior to V15.00.001 of Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® AssetCentre. The vulnerability exists due to insecure storage of FactoryTalk® Security user tokens, which could allow a threat actor to steal a token and, impersonate another user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2658 | Local privilege escalation in FlexNet Publisher</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2658</link><description>A misconfiguration in lmadmin.exe of FlexNet Publisher versions prior to 2024 R1 (11.19.6.0) allows the OpenSSL configuration file to load from a non-existent directory. An unauthorized, locally authenticated user with low privileges can potentially create the directory and load a specially crafted openssl.conf file leading to the execution of a malicious DLL (Dynamic-Link Library) with elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:24:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0367 | Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in Splunk Supporting Add-on for Active Directory (SA-ldapsearch)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0367</link><description>In versions 3.1.0 and lower of the Splunk Supporting Add-on for Active Directory, also known as SA-ldapsearch, a vulnerable regular expression pattern could lead to a Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:06:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0873 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System customeredit.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0873</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /customeredit.php. The manipulation of the argument id/address/fullname/phonenumber/email/city/comment leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 17:06:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24099 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A local ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24099</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.3, macOS Ventura 13.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.7.3. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0872 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System addpayment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0872</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /addpayment.php. The manipulation of the argument id/amount/desc/inccat leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24883 | go-ethereum has a DoS via malicious p2p message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24883</link><description>go-ethereum (geth) is a golang execution layer implementation of the Ethereum protocol. A vulnerable node can be forced to shutdown/crash using a specially crafted message. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.14.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24376 | The kubewarden-controller AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup policies can be used to alter PolicyReport resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24376</link><description>kubewarden-controller is a Kubernetes controller that allows you to dynamically register Kubewarden admission policies. By design, AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup can evaluate only namespaced resources. The resources to be evaluated are determined by the rules provided by the user when defining the policy. There might be Kubernetes namespaced resources that should not be validated by AdmissionPolicy and by the AdmissionPolicyGroup policies because of their sensitive nature. For example, PolicyReport are namespaced resources that contain the list of non compliant objects found inside of a namespace. An attacker can use either an AdmissionPolicy or an AdmissionPolicyGroup to prevent the creation and update of PolicyReport objects to hide non-compliant resources. Moreover, the same attacker might use a mutating AdmissionPolicy to alter the contents of the PolicyReport created inside of the namespace. Starting from the 1.21.0 release, the validation rules applied to AdmissionPolicy and AdmissionPolicyGroup have been tightened to prevent them from validating sensitive types of namespaced resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 16:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24784 | kubewarden-controller has an Information leak via AdmissionPolicyGroup Resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24784</link><description>kubewarden-controller is a Kubernetes controller that allows you to dynamically register Kubewarden admission policies. The policy group feature, added to by the 1.17.0 release. By being namespaced, the AdmissionPolicyGroup has a well constrained impact on cluster resources. Hence, it’s considered safe to allow non-admin users to create and manage these resources in the namespaces they own. Kubewarden policies can be allowed to query the Kubernetes API at evaluation time; these types of policies are called “context aware“. Context aware policies can perform list and get operations against a Kubernetes cluster. The queries are done using the ServiceAccount of the Policy Server instance that hosts the policy. That means that access to the cluster is determined by the RBAC rules that apply to that ServiceAccount. The AdmissionPolicyGroup CRD allowed the deployment of context aware policies. This could allow an attacker to obtain information about resources that are out of their reach, by leveraging a higher access to the cluster granted to the ServiceAccount token used to run the policy. The impact of this vulnerability depends on the privileges that have been granted to the ServiceAccount used to run the Policy Server and assumes that users are using the recommended best practices of keeping the Policy Server's ServiceAccount least privileged. By default, the Kubewarden helm chart grants access to the following resources (cluster wide) only: Namespace, Pod, Deployment and Ingress. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22219 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2025-22219)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22219</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges may be able to inject a malicious script that  (can perform stored cross-site scripting) may lead to arbitrary operations as admin user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22220 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs broken access control vulnerability (CVE-2025-22220)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22220</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with non-administrative privileges and network access to Aria Operations for Logs API may be able to perform certain operations in the context of an admin user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22221 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs stored cross-site scripting vulnerability (CVE-2025-22221)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22221</link><description>VMware Aria Operation for Logs contains a stored cross-site scripting vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges to VMware Aria Operations for Logs may be able to inject a malicious script that could be executed in a victim's browser when performing a delete action in the Agent Configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22222 | VMware Aria Operations information disclosure vulnerability (CVE-2025-22222)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22222</link><description>VMware Aria Operations contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious user with non-administrative privileges may exploit this vulnerability to retrieve credentials for an outbound plugin if a valid service credential ID is known.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23216 | Argo CD does not scrub secret values from patch errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23216</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. A vulnerability was discovered in Argo CD that exposed secret values in error messages and the diff view when an invalid Kubernetes Secret resource was synced from a repository. The vulnerability assumes the user has write access to the repository and can exploit it, either intentionally or unintentionally, by committing an invalid Secret to repository and triggering a Sync. Once exploited, any user with read access to Argo CD can view the exposed secret data. The vulnerability is fixed in v2.13.4, v2.12.10, and v2.11.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53615 | A command injection vulnerability in the video thumbnail rendering component of Karl Ward's files.gallery v0.3.0 through 0.11.0 allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53615</link><description>A command injection vulnerability in the video thumbnail rendering component of Karl Ward's files.gallery v0.3.0 through 0.11.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted video file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55415 | DevDojo Voyager through 1.8.0 is vulnerable to path traversal at the /admin/compass.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55415</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through 1.8.0 is vulnerable to path traversal at the /admin/compass.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55416 | DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via /admin/compass. By manipulating an authenticated user to click on a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55416</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to reflected XSS via /admin/compass. By manipulating an authenticated user to click on a link, arbitrary Javascript can be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55417 | DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to bypassing the file type verification when an authenticated user uploads a file via /a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55417</link><description>DevDojo Voyager through version 1.8.0 is vulnerable to bypassing the file type verification when an authenticated user uploads a file via /admin/media/upload. An authenticated user can upload a web shell causing arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0871 | Maybecms Add Article index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0871</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Maybecms 1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /mb/admin/index.php?u=article-edit of the component Add Article. The manipulation of the argument data_info[content] leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23367 | Org.wildfly.core:wildfly-server: wildfly improper rbac permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23367</link><description>A flaw was found in the Wildfly Server Role Based Access Control (RBAC) provider. When authorization to control management operations is secured using the Role Based Access Control provider, a user without the required privileges can suspend or resume the server. A user with a Monitor or Auditor role is supposed to have only read access permissions and should not be able to suspend the server. 
The vulnerability is caused by the Suspend and Resume handlers not performing authorization checks to validate whether the current user has the required permissions to proceed with the action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22218 | VMware Aria Operations for Logs information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22218</link><description>VMware Aria Operations for Logs contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with View Only Admin permissions may be able to read the credentials of a VMware product integrated with VMware Aria Operations for Logs</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10591 | MWB HubSpot for WooCommerce – CRM, Abandoned Cart, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10591</link><description>The MWB HubSpot for WooCommerce – CRM, Abandoned Cart, Email Marketing, Marketing Automation &amp; Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the hubwoo_save_updates() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10847 | Storely &amp;lt;= 16.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10847</link><description>The Storely theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a malicious display name in all versions up to, and including, 16.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11583 | Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Missing Authorization to Icon Font Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11583</link><description>The Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'remove_zipped_font' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete icon fonts that were previously uploaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11600 | Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11600</link><description>The Borderless – Widgets, Elements, Templates and Toolkit for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.9 via the 'write_config' function. This is due to a lack of sanitization on an imported JSON file. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12102 | Typer Core &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12102</link><description>The Typer Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.6 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private or draft posts created by Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12129 | Royal Core &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12129</link><description>The Royal Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'royal_restore_backup' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12177 | Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12177</link><description>The Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12269 | Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP &amp;lt;= 1.0.17 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Database Export</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12269</link><description>The Safe Ai Malware Protection for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the export_db() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.17. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve a complete dump of the site's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12299 | System Dashboard &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via Filename Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12299</link><description>The System Dashboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the Filename parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.15 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick an administrative user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12320 | Team Rosters &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;tab&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12320</link><description>The Team Rosters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘tab’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12444 | WP Dispensary &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12444</link><description>The WP Dispensary plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpd_menu' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12451 | HTML5 chat &amp;lt;= 1.04 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12451</link><description>The HTML5 chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'HTML5CHAT' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.04 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12821 | Media Manager for UserPro &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12821</link><description>The Media Manager for UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the upm_upload_media() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12822 | Media Manager for UserPro &amp;lt;= 3.12.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12822</link><description>The Media Manager for UserPro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the add_capto_img() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12861 | W2S – Migrate WooCommerce to Shopify &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12861</link><description>The W2S – Migrate WooCommerce to Shopify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.1 via the 'viw2s_view_log' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13349 | Stockdio Historical Chart &amp;lt;= 2.8.18 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13349</link><description>The Stockdio Historical Chart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stockdio-historical-chart' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13400 | Kona Gallery Block &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13400</link><description>The Kona Gallery Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Kona: Instagram for Gutenberg" Block, specifically in the "align" attribute, in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13460 | WE – Testimonial Slider &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13460</link><description>The WE – Testimonial Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Testimonial Author Names in all versions up to, and including, 1.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13512 | Wonder FontAwesome &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13512</link><description>The Wonder FontAwesome plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.8. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on one of its functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13549 | All Bootstrap Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.3.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13549</link><description>The All Bootstrap Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the "Accordion" widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13596 | WordPress Survey &amp;amp; Poll – Quiz, Survey and Poll Plugin for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13596</link><description>The WordPress Survey &amp; Poll – Quiz, Survey and Poll Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' attribute of the 'survey' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13646 | Single-user-chat &amp;lt;= 0.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13646</link><description>The Single-user-chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to insufficient validation on the 'single_user_chat_update_login' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'login' on the WordPress site. This may be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13652 | ECPay Ecommerce for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.2411060 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Log Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13652</link><description>The ECPay Ecommerce for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'clear_ecpay_debug_log' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.2411060. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the plugin's log files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13661 | Table Editor &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13661</link><description>The Table Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wptableeditor_vtabs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13664 | WP Post List Table &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13664</link><description>The WP Post List Table plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpb_post_list_table' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13670 | Music Sheet Viewer &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13670</link><description>The Music Sheet Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'pn_msv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13671 | Music Sheet Viewer &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13671</link><description>The Music Sheet Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 4.1 via the read_score_file() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13700 | Embed Swagger UI &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13700</link><description>The Embed Swagger UI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpsgui' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13705 | StageShow &amp;lt;= 9.8.6 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13705</link><description>The StageShow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 9.8.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13707 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13707</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the gky_image_uploader_main_function() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13715 | zStore Manager Basic &amp;lt;= 3.311 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Cache Clearing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13715</link><description>The zStore Manager Basic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the zstore_clear_cache() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.311. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to clear the plugin's cache.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13720 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13720</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the gky_image_uploader_main_function() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13742 | iControlWP – Multiple WordPress Site Manager &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13742</link><description>The iControlWP – Multiple WordPress Site Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.5 via deserialization of untrusted input from the reqpars parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8494 | Elementor Website Builder Pro – More than Just a Page Builder &amp;lt;= 3.25.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8494</link><description>The Elementor Website Builder Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.25.10 via the 'elementor-template' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of Private, Pending, and Draft Templates. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.24.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0869 | Cianet ONU GW24AC Login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0869</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Cianet ONU GW24AC up to 20250127. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument browserLang leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:20:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0870 | Axiomatic Bento4 Ap4DataBuffer.h GetData heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0870</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Axiomatic Bento4 up to 1.6.0-641. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function AP4_DataBuffer::GetData in the library Ap4DataBuffer.h. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 13:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13380 | Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13380</link><description>The Alex Reservations: Smart Restaurant Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'rr_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13466 | Automatically Hierarchic Categories in Menu &amp;lt;= 2.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13466</link><description>The Automatically Hierarchic Categories in Menu plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'autocategorymenu' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43916 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container improper communications restriction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43916</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 7.1, 7.2, 8.0, 8.1, 8.2, 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 10.0, 10.1, 11.0, 11.1, 11.2, 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, 12.1, 12.2, 12.3, 12.4, 12.5, 12.6, and 12.7 Pods do not restrict network egress for Pods that are used for internal infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:30:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0742 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0742</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain files stored by others users by changing the "FILE_ID" of the endpoint "/embedai/files/show/".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0743 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0743</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to leverage the endpoint "/embedai/visits/show/" to obtain information about the visits made by other users. The information provided by this endpoint includes IP address, userAgent and location of the user that visited the web page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0744 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0744</link><description>an Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker change his subscription plan without paying by making a POST request changing the parameters of the "/demos/embedai/pmt_cash_on_delivery/pay" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0745 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0745</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain the backups of the database by requesting the "/embedai/app/uploads/database/" endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0746 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0746</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to craft a malicious URL leveraging the"/embedai/users/show/</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0747 | Stored Cross-Site vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0747</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to inject a malicious JavaScript code into a message that will be executed when a user opens the chat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12409 | Simple:Press Forum &amp;lt;= 6.10.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12409</link><description>The Simple:Press Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 's' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.10.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12524 | Clinked Client Portal &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12524</link><description>The Clinked Client Portal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'clinked-login-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13453 | Contact Form &amp;amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13453</link><description>The The Contact Form &amp; SMTP Plugin for WordPress by PirateForms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13706 | WP Image Uploader &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13706</link><description>The WP Image Uploader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'file' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0739 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0739</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to show subscription's information of others users by changing the "SUSCBRIPTION_ID" param of the endpoint "/demos/embedai/subscriptions/show/".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0740 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0740</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI

 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to obtain chat messages belonging to other users by changing the “CHAT_ID” of the endpoint "/embedai/chats/load_messages?chat_id=".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0741 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in EmbedAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0741</link><description>An Improper Access Control vulnerability has been found in EmbedAI

 2.1 and below. This vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to write messages into other users chat by changing the parameter "chat_id" of the POST request "/embedai/chats/send_message".</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 11:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23007 | A vulnerability in the NetExtender Windows client log export function allows unauthorized access to sensitive Windows system files, potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23007</link><description>A vulnerability in the NetExtender Windows client log export function allows unauthorized access to sensitive Windows system files, potentially leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0860 | VR-Frases (collect &amp;amp; share quotes) &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0860</link><description>The VR-Frases (collect &amp; share quotes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0861 | VR-Frases (collect &amp;amp; share quotes) &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0861</link><description>The VR-Frases (collect &amp; share quotes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via several parameters in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21107 | Dell NetWorker, version(s) prior to 19.11.0.3, all versions of 19.10 &amp; prior versions contain(s) an Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21107</link><description>Dell NetWorker, version(s) prior to 19.11.0.3, all versions of 19.10 &amp; prior versions contain(s) an Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0834 | Wondershare Dr.Fone Privilege Scalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0834</link><description>Privilege escalation vulnerability has been found in Wondershare Dr.Fone version 13.5.21. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to escalate privileges by replacing the binary ‘C:\ProgramData\Wondershare\wsServices\ElevationService.exe’ with a malicious binary. This binary will be executed by SYSTEM automatically.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 09:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13694 | WooCommerce Wishlist &amp;lt;= 1.8.7 - Unauthenticated Wishlist Disclosure via download_pdf_file Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13694</link><description>The WooCommerce Wishlist (High customization, fast setup,Free Elementor Wishlist, most features) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.7 via the download_pdf_file() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from wishlists that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13732 | Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via section_tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13732</link><description>The Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘section_tag’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13758 | CP Contact Form with PayPal &amp;lt;= 1.3.52 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13758</link><description>The CP Contact Form with PayPal plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.52. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the cp_contact_form_paypal_check_init_actions() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add discount codes via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 08:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13470 | Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You &amp;lt;= 3.8.24 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13470</link><description>The Ninja Forms – The Contact Form Builder That Grows With You plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 07:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13457 | Event Tickets &amp;lt;= 5.18.1 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13457</link><description>The Event Tickets and Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 5.18.1 via the tc-order-id parameter due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view order details of orders they did not place, which includes ticket prices, user emails and order date.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13642 | Stratum – Elementor Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.4.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability via Image Hotspot Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13642</link><description>The Stratum – Elementor Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Image Hotspot widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10309 | Tracking Code Manager &amp;lt; 2.4.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10309</link><description>The Tracking Code Manager WordPress plugin before 2.4.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its metabox settings when outputing them in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as Contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12163 | GoodLayers Core &amp;lt; 2.1.3 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12163</link><description>The goodlayers-core WordPress plugin before 2.1.3 allows users with a subscriber role and above to upload SVGs containing malicious payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12400 | Tourmaster &amp;lt; 5.3.5 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12400</link><description>The tourmaster WordPress plugin before 5.3.5 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12638 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12638</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12708 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12708</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12709 | Bulk Me Now &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Message Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12709</link><description>The Bulk Me Now! WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in users perform unwanted actions via CSRF attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12921 | EthereumICO &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ethereum-ico Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12921</link><description>The EthereumICO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ethereum-ico shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 05:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0373 | Buffer overflow in some filesystems via NFS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0373</link><description>On 64-bit systems, the implementation of VOP_VPTOFH() in the cd9660, tarfs and ext2fs filesystems overflows the destination FID buffer by 4 bytes, a stack buffer overflow.

A NFS server that exports a cd9660, tarfs, or ext2fs file system can be made to panic by mounting and accessing the export with an NFS client.  Further exploitation (e.g., bypassing file permission checking or remote kernel code execution) is potentially possible, though this has not been demonstrated.  In particular, release kernels are compiled with stack protection enabled, and some instances of the overflow are caught by this mechanism, causing a panic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0374 | Unprivileged access to system files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0374</link><description>When etcupdate encounters conflicts while merging files, it saves a version containing conflict markers in /var/db/etcupdate/conflicts.  This version does not preserve the mode of the input file, and is world-readable.  This applies to files that would normally have restricted visibility, such as /etc/master.passwd.

An unprivileged local user may be able to read encrypted root and user passwords from the temporary master.passwd file created in /var/db/etcupdate/conflicts.  This is possible only when conflicts within the password file arise during an update, and the unprotected file is deleted when conflicts are resolved.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0662 | Uninitialized kernel memory disclosure via ktrace(2)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0662</link><description>In some cases, the ktrace facility will log the contents of kernel structures to userspace.  In one such case, ktrace dumps a variable-sized sockaddr to userspace.  There, the full sockaddr is copied, even when it is shorter than the full size.  This can result in up to 14 uninitialized bytes of kernel memory being copied out to userspace.

It is possible for an unprivileged userspace program to leak 14 bytes of a kernel heap allocation to userspace.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:57:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23374 | Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC OS, version(s) prior to 4.4.1 and 4.2.3, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23374</link><description>Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC OS, version(s) prior to 4.4.1 and 4.2.3, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 04:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0847 | 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0847</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0848 | Tenda A18 HTTP POST Request SetCmdlineRun stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A18 up to 15.13.07.09. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function SetCmdlineRun of the file /goform/SetCmdlineRun of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument wpapsk_crypto5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0849 | CampCodes School Management Software Staff edit-staff improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0849</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /edit-staff/ of the component Staff Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0846 | 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System AdminLogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0846</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Employee Task Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/AdminLogin.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0844 | needyamin Library Card System Registration Page signup.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0844</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file signup.php of the component Registration Page. The manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/email/borrow/user_address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21396 | Microsoft Account Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21396</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0843 | needyamin Library Card System Admin Panel admindashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file admindashboard.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21415 | Azure AI Face Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21415</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57665 | JFinalCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rc/main/java/com/cms/entity/Content.java. The cause of the vulnerability is that the title p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57665</link><description>JFinalCMS 1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in rc/main/java/com/cms/entity/Content.java. The cause of the vulnerability is that the title parameter is controllable and is concatenated directly into filterSql without filtering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51182 | HTML Injection vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML code via the "erro" p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51182</link><description>HTML Injection vulnerability in Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 allows a remote attacker to inject arbitrary HTML code via the "erro" parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:07:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48761 | The specific component in Celk Saude 3.1.252.1 that processes user input and returns error messages to the client is vulnerable due to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48761</link><description>The specific component in Celk Saude 3.1.252.1 that processes user input and returns error messages to the client is vulnerable due to improper validation or sanitization of the "erro" parameter. This parameter appears as a response when incorrect credentials are entered during login. The lack of proper validation or sanitization makes the component susceptible to injection attacks, potentially allowing attackers to manipulate the input and exploit the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11187 | Many records in the additional section cause CPU exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11187</link><description>It is possible to construct a zone such that some queries to it will generate responses containing numerous records in the Additional section. An attacker sending many such queries can cause either the authoritative server itself or an independent resolver to use disproportionate resources processing the queries. Zones will usually need to have been deliberately crafted to attack this exposure.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.11.0 through 9.11.37, 9.16.0 through 9.16.50, 9.18.0 through 9.18.32, 9.20.0 through 9.20.4, 9.21.0 through 9.21.3, 9.11.3-S1 through 9.11.37-S1, 9.16.8-S1 through 9.16.50-S1, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.32-S1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12705 | DNS-over-HTTPS implementation suffers from multiple issues under heavy query load</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12705</link><description>Clients using DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) can exhaust a DNS resolver's CPU and/or memory by flooding it with crafted valid or invalid HTTP/2 traffic.
This issue affects BIND 9 versions 9.18.0 through 9.18.32, 9.20.0 through 9.20.4, 9.21.0 through 9.21.3, and 9.18.11-S1 through 9.18.32-S1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54851 | Teedy &lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF), due to the lack of CSRF protection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54851</link><description>Teedy &lt;= 1.12 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF), due to the lack of CSRF protection.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54852 | When LDAP connection is activated in Teedy versions between 1.9 to 1.12, the username field of the login form is vulnerable to LDAP injectio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54852</link><description>When LDAP connection is activated in Teedy versions between 1.9 to 1.12, the username field of the login form is vulnerable to LDAP injection. Due to improper sanitization of user input, an unauthenticated attacker is then able to perform various malicious actions, such as creating arbitrary accounts and spraying passwords.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0842 | needyamin Library Card System Login admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in needyamin Library Card System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument email/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23733 | The /WmAdmin/,/invoke/vm.server/login login page in the Integration Server in Software AG webMethods 10.15.0 before Core_Fix7 allows remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23733</link><description>The /WmAdmin/,/invoke/vm.server/login login page in the Integration Server in Software AG webMethods 10.15.0 before Core_Fix7 allows remote attackers to reach the administration panel and discover hostname and version information by sending an arbitrary username and a blank password to the /WmAdmin/#/login/ URI.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57395 | Password Vulnerability in Safety production process management system v1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges, execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57395</link><description>Password Vulnerability in Safety production process management system v1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the password and account number parameters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57509 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57509</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_File::ParseStream and related functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57510 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57510</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 mp42avc v.3bdc891602d19789b8e8626e4a3e613a937b4d35 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_MemoryByteStream::WritePartial.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57513 | A floating-point exception (FPE) vulnerability exists in the AP4_TfraAtom::AP4_TfraAtom function in Bento4.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57513</link><description>A floating-point exception (FPE) vulnerability exists in the AP4_TfraAtom::AP4_TfraAtom function in Bento4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0851 | Path traversal issue in Deep Java Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0851</link><description>A path traversal issue in ZipUtils.unzip and TarUtils.untar in Deep Java Library (DJL) on all platforms allows a bad actor to write files to arbitrary locations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0841 | Aridius XYZ News loadMore deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0841</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Aridius XYZ up to 20240927 on OpenCart and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function loadMore of the component News. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24795 | The Snowflake Connector for Python uses insecure cache files permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24795</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. On Linux systems, when temporary credential caching is enabled, the Snowflake Connector for Python will cache temporary credentials locally in a world-readable file. This vulnerability affects versions 2.3.7 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24788 | Snowflake Connector for .NET has weak temporary files permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24788</link><description>snowflake-connector-net is the Snowflake Connector for .NET. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for .NET in which files downloaded from stages are temporarily placed in a world-readable local directory, making them accessible to unauthorized users on the same machine. This vulnerability affects versions 2.0.12 through 4.2.0 on Linux and macOS. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24793 | Snowflake Connector for Python has an SQL Injection in write_pandas</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24793</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. A function from the snowflake.connector.pandas_tools module is vulnerable to SQL injection. This vulnerability affects versions 2.2.5 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24794 | The Snowflake Connector for Python uses insecure deserialization of the OCSP response cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24794</link><description>The Snowflake Connector for Python provides an interface for developing Python applications that can connect to Snowflake and perform all standard operations. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake Connector for Python. The OCSP response cache uses pickle as the serialization format, potentially leading to local privilege escalation. This vulnerability affects versions 2.7.12 through 3.13.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.13.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24884 | kube-audit-rest&amp;#x27;s example logging configuration could disclose secret values in the audit log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24884</link><description>kube-audit-rest is a simple logger of mutation/creation requests to the k8s api. If the "full-elastic-stack" example vector configuration was used for a real cluster, the previous values of kubernetes secrets would have been disclosed in the audit messages. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.0.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:28:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0840 | GNU Binutils objdump.c disassemble_bytes stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0840</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in GNU Binutils up to 2.43. This affects the function disassemble_bytes of the file binutils/objdump.c. The manipulation of the argument buf leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.44 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is baac6c221e9d69335bf41366a1c7d87d8ab2f893. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20061 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20061</link><description>mySCADA myPRO does not properly neutralize POST requests sent to a specific port with email information. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20014 | mySCADA myPRO Manager OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20014</link><description>mySCADA myPRO does not properly neutralize POST requests sent to a specific port with version information. This vulnerability could be exploited by an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48852 | Information disclosures</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48852</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability observed in FLEXON. Some information may be improperly disclosed through https access.
 

This issue affects FLXEON through &lt;= 9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:05:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10001 | Code Injection Vulnerability in GitHub Enterprise Server Allows Arbitrary Code Execution via Message Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10001</link><description>A Code Injection vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed attackers to inject malicious code into the query selector via the identity property in the message handling function. This enabled the exfiltration of sensitive data by manipulating the DOM, including authentication tokens. To execute the attack, the victim must be logged into GitHub and interact with the attacker controlled malicious webpage containing the hidden iframe. This vulnerability occurs due to an improper sequence of validation, where the origin check occurs after accepting the user-controlled identity property. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server prior to 3.11.16, 3.12.10, 3.13.5, 3.14.2, and 3.15.0. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48849 | Authentication and Authorization Issues</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48849</link><description>Missing Origin Validation in WebSockets vulnerability in FLXEON. Session management was not sufficient to prevent unauthorized HTTPS requests. This issue affects FLXEON: through &lt;= 9.3.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24790 | Snowflake JDBC uses insecure temporary credential cache file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24790</link><description>Snowflake JDBC provides a JDBC type 4 driver that supports core functionality, allowing Java program to connect to Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC Driver. On Linux systems, when temporary credential caching is enabled, the Snowflake JDBC Driver will cache temporary credentials locally in a world-readable file. This vulnerability affects versions 3.6.8 through 3.21.0. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:58:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24789 | Snowflake JDBC allows an untrusted search path on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24789</link><description>Snowflake JDBC provides a JDBC type 4 driver that supports core functionality, allowing Java program to connect to Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC Driver. When the EXTERNALBROWSER authentication method is used on Windows, an attacker with write access to a directory in the %PATH% can escalate their privileges to the user that runs the vulnerable JDBC Driver version. This vulnerability affects versions 3.2.3 through 3.21.0 on Windows. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24882 | regclient may ignore pinned manifest digests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24882</link><description>regclient is a Docker and OCI Registry Client in Go. A malicious registry could return a different digest for a pinned manifest without detection. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24791 | snowflake-connector-nodejs has incorrect validation of temporary credential cache file permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24791</link><description>snowflake-connector-nodejs is a NodeJS driver for Snowflake. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake NodeJS Driver. File permissions checks of the temporary credential cache could be bypassed by an attacker with write access to the local cache directory. This vulnerability affects versions 1.12.0 through 2.0.1 on Linux. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:15:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35907 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35907</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37398 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37398</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37412 | IBM Aspera Faspex improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37412</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 could allow a privileged user to make system changes without proper access controls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37413 | IBM Aspera Faspex information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37413</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.10 could disclose sensitive username information due to an observable response discrepancy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24527 | An issue was discovered in Akamai Enterprise Application Access (EAA) before 2025-01-17. If an admin knows another tenant's 128-bit connecto...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24527</link><description>An issue was discovered in Akamai Enterprise Application Access (EAA) before 2025-01-17. If an admin knows another tenant's 128-bit connector GUID, they can execute debug commands on that connector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24374 | Twig fixes a security issue where escaping was missing when using null coalesce operator (??)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24374</link><description>Twig is a template language for PHP. When using the ?? operator, output escaping was missing for the expression on the left side of the operator. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.19.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24792 | Snowflake PHP PDO Driver has a Signed-to-Unsigned Conversion Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24792</link><description>Snowflake PHP PDO Driver is a driver that uses the PHP Data Objects (PDO) extension to connect to the Snowflake database. Snowflake discovered and remediated a vulnerability in the Snowflake PHP PDO Driver where executing unsupported queries like PUT or GET on stages causes a signed-to-unsigned conversion error that crashes the application using the Driver. This vulnerability affects versions 0.2.0 through 3.0.3. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 15:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57436 | RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to allow unauthorized attackers to view the session ID of the admin in the system monitoring. This issue can all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57436</link><description>RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to allow unauthorized attackers to view the session ID of the admin in the system monitoring. This issue can allow attackers to impersonate Admin users via using a crafted cookie.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57437 | RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderby parameter at /monitor/online/list.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57437</link><description>RuoYi v4.8.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderby parameter at /monitor/online/list.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57438 | Insecure permissions in RuoYi v4.8.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges by assigning themselves higher level roles.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57438</link><description>Insecure permissions in RuoYi v4.8.0 allows authenticated attackers to escalate privileges by assigning themselves higher level roles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57439 | An issue in the reset password interface of ruoyi v4.8.0 allows attackers with Admin privileges to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by duplic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57439</link><description>An issue in the reset password interface of ruoyi v4.8.0 allows attackers with Admin privileges to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) by duplicating the login name of the account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:28:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54461 | Unsanitized Filenames in Flutter package file_selector_android Allow File Overwrites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54461</link><description>The file names constructed within file_selector are missing sanitization checks leaving them vulnerable to malicious document providers. This may result in cases where a user with a malicious document provider installed can select a document file from that provider while using your app and could potentially override internal files in your app cache. Issue patched in 0.5.1+12. It is recommended to update to the latest version of file_selector_android that contains the changes to address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54462 | Unsanitized Filenames in Flutter package image_picker_android Allow File Overwrites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54462</link><description>The file names constructed within image_picker are missing sanitization checks leaving them vulnerable to malicious document providers. This may result in cases where a user with a malicious document provider installed can select an image file from that provider while using your app and could potentially override internal files in your app cache. Issue patched in 0.8.12+18. It is recommended to update to the latest version of image_picker_android that contains the changes to address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13561 | Target Video Easy Publish &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via brid_override_yt Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13561</link><description>The Target Video Easy Publish plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's brid_override_yt shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41140 | Improper Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41140</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 174000 and prior are vulnerable to the incorrect authorization in the update user function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0353 | Divi Torque Lite &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0353</link><description>The Divi Torque Lite – Best Divi Addon, Extensions, Modules &amp; Social Modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 11:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0762 | Use after free in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0762</link><description>Use after free in DevTools in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.159 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted Chrome Extension. (Chromium security severity: Medium)</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:43:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0617 | An attacker with access to an HX 10.0.0  and previous versions, may send specially-crafted data to the HX console.  The malicious detection ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0617</link><description>An attacker with access to an HX 10.0.0  and previous versions, may send specially-crafted data to the HX console.  The malicious detection would then trigger file parsing containing exponential entity expansions in the consumer process thus causing a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-3978 | Improper Preservation of Permissions in github.com/cloudflare/cfrpki/cmd/octorpki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-3978</link><description>When copying files with rsync, octorpki uses the "-a" flag 0, which forces rsync to copy binaries with the suid bit set as root. Since the provided service definition defaults to root ( https://github.com/cloudflare/cfrpki/blob/master/package/octorpki.service ) this could allow for a vector, when combined with another vulnerability that causes octorpki to process a malicious TAL file, for a local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 10:20:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57965 | In axios before 1.7.8, lib/helpers/isURLSameOrigin.js does not use a URL object when determining an origin, and has a potentially unwanted s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57965</link><description>In axios before 1.7.8, lib/helpers/isURLSameOrigin.js does not use a URL object when determining an origin, and has a potentially unwanted setAttribute('href',href) call. NOTE: some parties feel that the code change only addresses a warning message from a SAST tool and does not fix a vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 09:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7695 | Out-of-bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7695</link><description>Multiple switches are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient input validation, which allows data to be written to memory outside the bounds of the buffer. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could result in a denial-of-service attack. 

This vulnerability poses a significant remote threat if the affected products are exposed to publicly accessible networks. Attackers could potentially disrupt operations by shutting down the affected systems. Due to the critical nature of this security risk, we strongly recommend taking immediate action to prevent its potential exploitation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 07:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13696 | Flexible Wishlist for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.2.25 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wishlist_name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13696</link><description>The Flexible Wishlist for WooCommerce – Ecommerce Wishlist &amp; Save for later plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wishlist_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.25 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 07:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12749 | Competition Form &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12749</link><description>The Competition Form WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 06:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0804 | ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp;amp; Link Pages &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0804</link><description>The ClickWhale – Link Manager, Link Shortener and Click Tracker for Affiliate Links &amp; Link Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via link titles in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 03:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0806 | code-projects Job Recruitment _call_job_search_ajax.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0806</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file _call_job_search_ajax.php. The manipulation of the argument job_type leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0798 | MicroWorld eScan Antivirus Quarantine rtscanner os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0798</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWorld eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rtscanner of the component Quarantine Handler. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0800 | SourceCodester Online Courseware Edit Teacher saveeditt.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0800</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Online Courseware 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pcci/admin/saveeditt.php of the component Edit Teacher. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0802 | SourceCodester Best Employee Management System Administrative Endpoint View_user.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0802</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Best Employee Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/View_user.php of the component Administrative Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0803 | Codezips Gym Management System submit_plan_new.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0803</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Codezips Gym Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /dashboard/admin/submit_plan_new.php. The manipulation of the argument planid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23362 | The old versions of EXIF Viewer Classic contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability caused by improper handling of EXIF meta data. When an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23362</link><description>The old versions of EXIF Viewer Classic contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability caused by improper handling of EXIF meta data. When an image is rendered and crafted EXIF meta data is processed, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser. Versions 2.3.2 and 2.4.0 were reported as vulnerable. According to the vendor, the product has been refactored after those old versions and the version 3.0.1 is not vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33838 | IBM Security Verify Governance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33838</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 Identity Manager 

uses a one-way cryptographic hash against an input that should not be reversible, such as a password, but the product does not also use a salt as part of the input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0795 | ESAFENET CDG todolistjump.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0795</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /todolistjump.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0797 | MicroWorld eScan Antivirus Quarantine Microworld default permission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0797</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MicroWorld eScan Antivirus 7.0.32 on Linux. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /var/Microworld/ of the component Quarantine Handler. The manipulation leads to incorrect default permissions. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0793 | ESAFENET CDG todoDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0793</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in ESAFENET CDG V5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /todoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0794 | ESAFENET CDG todoDetail.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0794</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ESAFENET CDG V5 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /todoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument curpage leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35017 | IBM Security Verify Governance information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35017</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 Identity Manager can transmit user credentials in clear text that could be obtained by an attacker using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0792 | ESAFENET CDG sdTodoDetail.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0792</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in ESAFENET CDG V5. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sdTodoDetail.jsp. The manipulation of the argument flowId leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>