<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-34553 | WordPress Stockholm Core plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Reflected  Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Select-Themes Stockholm Core allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Stockholm Core: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34558 | WordPress WOLF plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34558</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in realmag777 WOLF allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WOLF: from n/a through 1.0.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34560 | WordPress gee Search Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34560</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GOMO gee Search Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects gee Search Plus: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34561 | WordPress Real3D Flipbook PDF Viewer Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.71 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34561</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative interactive media 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 3D FlipBook, PDF Viewer, PDF Embedder – Real 3D FlipBook WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 3.71.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34562 | WordPress Move Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34562</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moveaddons Move Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Move Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34563 | WordPress Gold Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34563</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GoldAddons Gold Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gold Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34564 | WordPress Counter Up plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34564</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LogicHunt Inc. Counter Up allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Counter Up: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34565 | WordPress Debug Info plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34565</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Debug Info allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Debug Info: from n/a through 1.3.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34566 | WordPress Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34566</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Johan van der Wijk Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget) allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Content Blocks (Custom Post Widget): from n/a through 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34568 | WordPress LetterPress Newsletter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34568</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themeqx LetterPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects LetterPress: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3507 | Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability in Lunar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3507</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Lunar software that affects versions 6.0.2 through 6.6.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a secondary process injection into the Lunar application and abuse those rights to access sensitive user information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34569 | WordPress Zotpress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34569</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Katie Seaborn Zotpress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Zotpress: from n/a through 7.3.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:50:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34570 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34570</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:40:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34571 | WordPress Himalayas theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34571</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeGrill Himalayas allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Himalayas: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4135 | The WP Latest Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.7. This is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4135</link><description>The WP Latest Posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.7. This is due to the plugin allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a user-supplied value prior to using that value in a call to do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4281 | The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'link-library' shortcode in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4281</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'link-library' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:45:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34572 | WordPress Fancy Elementor Flipbox plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34572</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemePrix Fancy Elementor Flipbox fancy-elementor-flipbox allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fancy Elementor Flipbox: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34573 | WordPress Pootle Pagebuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pootlepress Pootle Pagebuilder – WordPress Page builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pootle Pagebuilder – WordPress Page builder: from n/a through 5.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41651 | WordPress Multi-column Tag Map plugin &amp;lt;= 17.0.26 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41651</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Multi-column Tag Map.This issue affects Multi-column Tag Map: from n/a through 17.0.26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34574 | WordPress Table Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34574</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wpsoul Table Maker allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Table Maker: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4436 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2022-41723 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4436</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2022-41723. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4437 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2021-44716 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4437</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2021-44716. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4438 | Etcd: incomplete fix for cve-2023-39325/cve-2023-44487 in openstack platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4438</link><description>The etcd package distributed with the Red Hat OpenStack platform has an incomplete fix for CVE-2023-39325/CVE-2023-44487, known as Rapid Reset. This issue occurs because the etcd package in the Red Hat OpenStack platform is using http://golang.org/x/net/http2 instead of the one provided by Red Hat Enterprise Linux versions, meaning it should be updated at compile time instead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1076 | SSL Zen &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Unauthenticated Private Keys Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1076</link><description>The SSL Zen  WordPress plugin before 4.6.0 only relies on the use of .htaccess to prevent visitors from accessing the site's generated private keys, which allows an attacker to read them if the site runs on a server who doesn't support .htaccess files, like NGINX.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3494 | The Mesmerize Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mesmerize_contact_form' shortcod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3494</link><description>The Mesmerize Companion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mesmerize_contact_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.148 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22264 | VMware Avi Load Balancer updates address multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22264</link><description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with admin privileges on VMware Avi Load Balancer can create, modify, execute and delete files as a root user on the host system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22266 | VMware Avi Load Balancer updates address multiple vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22266</link><description>VMware Avi Load Balancer contains an information disclosure vulnerability. A malicious actor with access to the system logs can view cloud connection credentials in plaintext.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 04:07:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32674 | Heateor Social Login WordPress prior to 1.1.32 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32674</link><description>Heateor Social Login WordPress prior to 1.1.32 contains a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who accessed the website using the product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4393 | The Social Connect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insuffi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4393</link><description>The Social Connect plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 1.2. This is due to insufficient verification on the OpenID server being supplied during the social login through the plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the email.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4418 | Libvirt: stack use-after-free in virnetclientioeventloop()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4418</link><description>A race condition leading to a stack use-after-free flaw was found in libvirt. Due to a bad assumption in the virNetClientIOEventLoop() method, the `data` pointer to a stack-allocated virNetClientIOEventData structure ended up being used in the virNetClientIOEventFD callback while the data pointer's stack frame was concurrently being "freed" when returning from virNetClientIOEventLoop(). The 'virtproxyd' daemon can be used to trigger requests. If libvirt is configured with fine-grained access control, this issue, in theory, allows a user to escape their otherwise limited access. This flaw allows a local, unprivileged user to access virtproxyd without authenticating. Remote users would need to authenticate before they could access it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4162 | KW Watcher Vulnerability ALlows Malicious Read Access to Memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4162</link><description>A buffer error in Panasonic KW Watcher versions 1.00 through 2.83 may allow attackers malicious read access to memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1929 | Local Root Exploit via Configuration Dictionary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1929</link><description>Local Root Exploit via Configuration Dictionary  in dnf5daemon-server before 5.1.17 allows a malicious user to impact Confidentiality and Integrity via Configuration Dictionary.

There are issues with the D-Bus interface long before Polkit is invoked. The `org.rpm.dnf.v0.SessionManager.open_session` method takes a key/value map of configuration entries. A sub-entry in this map, placed under the "config" key, is another key/value map. The configuration values found in it will be forwarded as configuration overrides to the `libdnf5::Base` configuration. 

Practically all libdnf5 configuration aspects can be influenced here. Already when opening the session via D-Bus, the libdnf5 will be initialized using these override configuration values. There is no sanity checking of the content of this "config" map, which is untrusted data. It is possible to make the library loading a plug-in shared library under control of an unprivileged user, hence achieving root access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1930 | No Limit on Number of Open Sessions / Bad Session Close Behaviour</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1930</link><description>No Limit on Number of Open Sessions / Bad Session Close Behaviour  in dnf5daemon-server before 5.1.17 allows a malicious user to impact Availability via No Limit on Number of Open Sessions.

There is no limit on how many sessions D-Bus clients may create using the `open_session()` D-Bus method. For each session a thread is created in dnf5daemon-server. This spends a couple of hundred megabytes of memory in the process. Further connections will become impossible, likely because no more threads can be spawned by the D-Bus service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2746 | Incomplete fix for CVE-2024-1929</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2746</link><description>Incomplete fix for CVE-2024-1929

The problem with CVE-2024-1929 was that the dnf5 D-Bus daemon accepted arbitrary configuration parameters from unprivileged users, which allowed a
local root exploit by tricking the daemon into loading a user controlled "plugin". All of this happened before Polkit authentication was even started.

The dnf5 library code does not check whether non-root users control the directory in question. 

On one hand, this poses a Denial-of-Service attack vector by making the daemonoperate on a blocking file (e.g. named FIFO special file) or a very large file
that causes an out-of-memory situation (e.g. /dev/zero). On the other hand, this can be used to let the daemon process privileged files like /etc/shadow.
The file in question is parsed as an INI file. Error diagnostics resulting from parsing privileged files could cause information leaks, if these diagnostics
are accessible to unprivileged users. In the case of libdnf5, no such user accessible diagnostics should exist, though.

Also, a local attacker can place a valid repository configuration file in this directory. This configuration file allows to specify
a plethora of additional configuration options. This makes various additional code paths in libdnf5 accessible to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2860 | The PostgreSQL implementation in Brocade SANnav versions before 2.3.0a is vulnerable to an incorrect local authentication flaw. An attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2860</link><description>The PostgreSQL implementation in Brocade SANnav versions before 2.3.0a is vulnerable to an incorrect local authentication flaw. An attacker accessing the VM where the Brocade SANnav is installed can gain access to sensitive data inside the PostgreSQL database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4456 | In affected versions of Octopus Server with certain access levels it was possible to embed a Cross-Site Scripting payload on the audit page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4456</link><description>In affected versions of Octopus Server with certain access levels it was possible to embed a Cross-Site Scripting payload on the audit page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34947 | NETGEAR R7800 net-cgi Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34947</link><description>NETGEAR R7800 net-cgi Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR R7800 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of the soap_block_table file. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write past the end of an allocated data structure. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.
. Was ZDI-CAN-13055.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34948 | Foxit PDF Reader Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34948</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Square annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14272.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34949 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34949</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14273.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34950 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34950</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14396.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34951 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34951</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14395.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34952 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34952</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14729.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34953 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34953</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use of Uninitialized Variable Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of a pointer prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14658.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34954 | Foxit PDF Editor StrikeOut Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34954</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor StrikeOut Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14355.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34955 | Foxit PDF Editor Stamp Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34955</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Stamp Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14356.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34956 | Foxit PDF Editor Underline Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34956</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Underline Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14357.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34957 | Foxit PDF Editor Highlight Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34957</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Highlight Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14358.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34958 | Foxit PDF Editor Text Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34958</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Text Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14359.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34959 | Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34959</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Square Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14360.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34960 | Foxit PDF Editor Circle Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34960</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Circle Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14362.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34961 | Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34961</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Ink Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14363.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34962 | Foxit PDF Editor Caret Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34962</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Caret Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14364.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34963 | Foxit PDF Editor PolyLine Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34963</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor PolyLine Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14365.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34964 | Foxit PDF Editor Polygon Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34964</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Polygon Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14366.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34965 | Foxit PDF Editor Squiggly Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34965</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Squiggly Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14361.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34966 | Foxit PDF Editor FileAttachment Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34966</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor FileAttachment Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14367.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34967 | Foxit PDF Editor Line Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34967</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor Line Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14368.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34968 | Foxit PDF Editor transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34968</link><description>Foxit PDF Editor transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14370.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34969 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34969</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14622.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34970 | Foxit PDF Reader print Method Use of Externally-Controlled Format String Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34970</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader print Method Use of Externally-Controlled Format String Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the print method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it as a format specifier. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14849.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34971 | Foxit PDF Reader JPG2000 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34971</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader JPG2000 File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14812.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34972 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34972</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14975.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34973 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34973</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14968.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34974 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34974</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15167.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34975 | Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34975</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader transitionToState Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the transitionToState method. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-15218.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34976 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34976</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-14659.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34981 | Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34981</link><description>Linux Kernel Bluetooth CMTP Module Double Free Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Linux Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute high-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the CMTP module. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing further free operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-11977.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34982 | NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34982</link><description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. When parsing the strings file, the process does not properly validate the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root.




. Was ZDI-CAN-13709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34983 | NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34983</link><description>NETGEAR Multiple Routers httpd Missing Authentication for Critical Function Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of multiple NETGEAR routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the httpd service, which listens on TCP port 80 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to system configuration information. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-13708.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-34999 | OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-34999</link><description>OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of OpenBSD Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of multicast routing. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-14540.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35000 | OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35000</link><description>OpenBSD Kernel Multicast Routing Uninitialized Memory Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of OpenBSD Kernel. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of multicast routing. The issue results from the lack of proper initialization of memory prior to accessing it. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of the kernel. Was ZDI-CAN-16112.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35001 | BMC Track-It! GetData Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35001</link><description>BMC Track-It! GetData Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the GetData endpoint. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-14527.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-35002 | BMC Track-It! Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-35002</link><description>BMC Track-It! Unrestricted File Upload Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of BMC Track-It!. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of email attachments. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can allow the upload of arbitrary files. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-14122.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-0369 | Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Restore Workspace Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-0369</link><description>Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway Restore Workspace Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Triangle MicroWorks SCADA Data Gateway. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, the existing authentication mechanism can be bypassed.

The specific flaw exists within the Restore Workspace feature. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-17227.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43651 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43651</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18960.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43652 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43652</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18981.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43653 | Bentley View SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43653</link><description>Bentley View SKP File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. Crafted data in an SKP file can trigger a write past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-19084.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43654 | NETGEAR CAX30S SSO Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43654</link><description>NETGEAR CAX30S SSO Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of NETGEAR CAX30S routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of the token parameter provided to the sso.php endpoint. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-18227.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43655 | Bentley View FBX File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43655</link><description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length heap-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18491.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43656 | Bentley View FBX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43656</link><description>Bentley View FBX File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Bentley View. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of FBX files. Crafted data in an FBX file can trigger a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-18492.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27321 | OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27321</link><description>OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard ConditionRefresh Resource Exhaustion Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of OPC Foundation UA .NET Standard. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of OPC UA ConditionRefresh requests. By sending a large number of requests, an attacker can consume all available resources on the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-20505.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35748 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35748</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Server IPv6 Address Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20076.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35749 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35749</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Firmware Upgrade Filename Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20077.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35757 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35757</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set Date-Time NTP Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-20085.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37325 | D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37325</link><description>D-Link DAP-2622 DDP Set SSID List Missing Authentication Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to make unauthorized changes to device configuration on affected installations of D-Link DAP-2622 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the DDP service. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to manipulate wireless authentication settings. Was ZDI-CAN-20104.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40490 | Maxon Cinema 4D SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40490</link><description>Maxon Cinema 4D SKP File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Maxon Cinema 4D. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of SKP files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21438.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23551 | HCL BigFix Compliance is potentially affected by Oracle database credentials stored at endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23551</link><description>Database scanning using username and password stores the credentials in plaintext or encoded format within files at the endpoint. This has been identified as a significant security risk. This will lead to exposure of sensitive information for unauthorized access, potentially leading to severe consequences such as data breaches, unauthorized data manipulation, and compromised system integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40694 | IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40694</link><description>IBM Watson CP4D Data Stores 4.0.0 through 4.8.4 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  264838.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0022 | In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible launch NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity of another us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0022</link><description>In multiple functions of CompanionDeviceManagerService.java, there is a possible launch NotificationAccessConfirmationActivity of another user profile due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0024 | In multiple methods of UserManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0024</link><description>In multiple methods of UserManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0025 | In sendIntentSender of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0025</link><description>In sendIntentSender of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible background activity launch due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0026 | In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible persistent denial of service due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0026</link><description>In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible persistent denial of service due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0027 | In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible way to cause a boot loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to loca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0027</link><description>In multiple functions of SnoozeHelper.java, there is a possible way to cause a boot loop due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0042 | In TBD of TBD, there is a possible confusion of OEM and DRM certificates due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local bypass of D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0042</link><description>In TBD of TBD, there is a possible confusion of OEM and DRM certificates due to improperly used crypto. This could lead to local bypass of DRM content protection with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0043 | In multiple locations, there is a possible notification listener grant to an app running in the work profile due to a logic error in the cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0043</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible notification listener grant to an app running in the work profile due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23704 | In onCreate of WifiDialogActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass the DISALLOW_ADD_WIFI_CONFIG restriction due to a missing permissi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23704</link><description>In onCreate of WifiDialogActivity.java, there is a possible way to bypass the DISALLOW_ADD_WIFI_CONFIG restriction due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23705 | In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23705</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible failure to persist or enforce user restrictions due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23706 | In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of health data permissions due to an improper input validation. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23706</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible bypass of health data permissions due to an improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23707 | In multiple locations, there is a possible permissions bypass due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23707</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible permissions bypass due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23708 | In multiple functions of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to not show a toast message when a clipboard message has b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23708</link><description>In multiple functions of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to not show a toast message when a clipboard message has been accessed. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23709 | In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23709</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23710 | In assertPackageWithSharedUserIdIsPrivileged of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible execution of arbitrary app code as a privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23710</link><description>In assertPackageWithSharedUserIdIsPrivileged of InstallPackageHelper.java, there is a possible execution of arbitrary app code as a privileged app due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23712 | In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way to saturate the content of /data/system/appops_accesses.xml due to reso...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23712</link><description>In multiple functions of AppOpsService.java, there is a possible way to saturate the content of /data/system/appops_accesses.xml due to resource exhaustion. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23713 | In migrateNotificationFilter of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist notifications settings due to improp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23713</link><description>In migrateNotificationFilter of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible failure to persist notifications settings due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34346 | Deno contains a permission escalation via open of privileged files with missing `--deny` flag</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34346</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime with secure defaults. The Deno sandbox may be unexpectedly weakened by allowing file read/write access to privileged files in various locations on Unix and Windows platforms. For example, reading `/proc/self/environ` may provide access equivalent to `--allow-env`, and writing `/proc/self/mem` may provide access equivalent to `--allow-all`. Users who grant read and write access to the entire filesystem may not realize that these access to these files may have additional, unintended consequences. The documentation did not reflect that this practice should be undertaken to increase the strength of the security sandbox. Users who run code with `--allow-read` or `--allow-write` may unexpectedly end up granting additional permissions via file-system operations. Deno 1.43 and above require explicit `--allow-all` access to read or write `/etc`, `/dev` on unix platform (as well as `/proc` and `/sys` on linux platforms), and any path starting with `\\` on Windows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4030 | tempfile.mkdtemp() may be readable and writeable by all users on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4030</link><description>On Windows a directory returned by tempfile.mkdtemp() would not always have permissions set to restrict reading and writing to the temporary directory by other users, instead usually inheriting the correct permissions from the default location. Alternate configurations or users without a profile directory may not have the intended permissions.

If you’re not using Windows or haven’t changed the temporary directory location then you aren’t affected by this vulnerability. On other platforms the returned directory is consistently readable and writable only by the current user.

This issue was caused by Python not supporting Unix permissions on Windows. The fix adds support for Unix “700” for the mkdir function on Windows which is used by mkdtemp() to ensure the newly created directory has the proper permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27273 | IBM AIX privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27273</link><description>IBM AIX's Unix domain (AIX 7.2, 7.3, VIOS 3.1, and VIOS 4.1) datagram socket implementation could potentially expose applications using Unix domain datagram sockets with SO_PEERID operation and may lead to privilege escalation.  IBM X-Force ID:  284903.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4558 | Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4558</link><description>Use after free in ANGLE in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4559 | Heap buffer overflow in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4559</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in WebAudio in Google Chrome prior to 124.0.6367.155 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25511 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_new.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25511</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_new.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25513 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /CorporateCulture/kaizen_down...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25513</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the file_id parameter at /CorporateCulture/kaizen_download.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25514 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /SysManage/wf_template_ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25514</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the template_id parameter at /SysManage/wf_template_child_field_list.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25509 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25509</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sys_file_storage_id parameter at /WorkFlow/wf_file_download.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25510 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_show.a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25510</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /AddressBook/address_public_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34314 | CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fetch_action method...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34314</link><description>CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fetch_action method of /admin/template_admin.php. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34315 | CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fckedit_action meth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34315</link><description>CmsEasy v7.7.7.9 was discovered to contain a local file inclusion vunerability via the file_get_contents function in the fckedit_action method of /admin/template_admin.php. This vulnerability allows attackers to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42757 | Process Explorer before 17.04 allows attackers to make it functionally unavailable (a denial of service for analysis) by renaming an executa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42757</link><description>Process Explorer before 17.04 allows attackers to make it functionally unavailable (a denial of service for analysis) by renaming an executable file to a new extensionless 255-character name and launching it with NtCreateUserProcess. This can occur through an issue in wcscat_s error handling.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34517 | The Cypher component in Neo4j before 5.19.0 mishandles IMMUTABLE privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34517</link><description>The Cypher component in Neo4j before 5.19.0 mishandles IMMUTABLE privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25507 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email_attach_id parameter at /LHMail/AttachDown.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25507</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email_attach_id parameter at /LHMail/AttachDown.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25512 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the attach_id parameter at /Bulletin/AttachDownLoad.as...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25512</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the attach_id parameter at /Bulletin/AttachDownLoad.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34397 | An issue was discovered in GNOME GLib before 2.78.5, and 2.79.x and 2.80.x before 2.80.1. When a GDBus-based client subscribes to signals fr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34397</link><description>An issue was discovered in GNOME GLib before 2.78.5, and 2.79.x and 2.80.x before 2.80.1. When a GDBus-based client subscribes to signals from a trusted system service such as NetworkManager on a shared computer, other users of the same computer can send spoofed D-Bus signals that the GDBus-based client will wrongly interpret as having been sent by the trusted system service. This could lead to the GDBus-based client behaving incorrectly, with an application-dependent impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25508 | RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /bulletin/bulletin_template_show.a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25508</link><description>RuvarOA v6.01 and v12.01 were discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /bulletin/bulletin_template_show.aspx.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29150 | An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29150</link><description>An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.01.10.728. Because of improper privilege management, an authenticated attacker is able to create symlinks to sensitive and protected data in locations that are used for debugging files. Given that the process of gathering debug logs is carried out with root privileges, any file referenced in the symlink is consequently written to the debug archive, thereby granting accessibility to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29149 | An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29149</link><description>An issue was discovered in Alcatel-Lucent ALE NOE deskphones through 86x8_NOE-R300.1.40.12.4180 and SIP deskphones through 86x8_SIP-R200.1.01.10.728. Because of a time-of-check time-of-use vulnerability, an authenticated attacker is able to replace the verified firmware image with malicious firmware during the update process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29209 | A medium severity vulnerability has been identified in the update mechanism of the Phish Alert Button for Outlook, which could allow an atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29209</link><description>A medium severity vulnerability has been identified in the update mechanism of the Phish Alert Button for Outlook, which could allow an attacker to remotely execute arbitrary code on the host machine. The vulnerability arises from the application's failure to securely verify the authenticity and integrity of the update server.

The application periodically checks for updates by querying a specific URL. However, this process does not enforce strict SSL/TLS verification, nor does it validate the digital signature of the received update files. An attacker with the capability to perform DNS spoofing can exploit this weakness. By manipulating DNS responses, the attacker can redirect the application's update requests to a malicious server under their control.

Once the application queries the spoofed update URL, the malicious server can respond with a crafted update package. Since the application fails to properly verify the authenticity of the update file, it will accept and execute the package, leading to arbitrary code execution on the host machine.

Impact:
Successful exploitation of this vulnerability allows an attacker to execute code with elevated privileges, potentially leading to data theft, installation of further malware, or other malicious activities on the host system.

Affected Products:
Phish Alert Button (PAB) for Outlook versions 1.10.0-1.10.11
Second Chance Client versions 2.0.0-2.0.9
PIQ Client versions 1.0.0-1.0.15

Remediation:
Automated updates will be pushed to address this issue. Users of affected versions should verify the latest version is applied and, if not, apply the latest updates provided by KnowBe4, which addresses this vulnerability by implementing proper SSL/TLS checks of the update server. It is also recommended to ensure DNS settings are secure to prevent DNS spoofing attacks.

Workarounds:
Use secure corporate networks or VPN services to secure network communications, which can help mitigate the risk of DNS spoofing.

Credits:
This vulnerability was discovered by Ceri Coburn at Pen Test Partners, who reported it responsibly to the vendor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29210 | A local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been identified in Phish Alert Button for Outlook (PAB), specifically within its config...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29210</link><description>A local privilege escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been identified in Phish Alert Button for Outlook (PAB), specifically within its configuration management functionalities. This vulnerability allows a regular user to modify the application's configuration file to redirect update checks to an arbitrary server, which can then be exploited in conjunction with CVE-2024-29209 to execute arbitrary code with elevated privileges.

The issue stems from improper permission settings on the application's configuration file, which is stored in a common directory accessible to all users. This file includes critical parameters, such as the update server URL. By default, the application does not enforce adequate access controls on this file, allowing non-privileged users to modify it without administrative consent.

An attacker with regular user access can alter the update server URL specified in the configuration file to point to a malicious server. When the application performs its next update check, it will contact the attacker-controlled server. If the system is also vulnerable to CVE-2024-29209, the attacker can deliver a malicious update package that, when executed, grants them elevated privileges.

Impact:
This vulnerability can lead to a regular user executing code with administrative privileges. This can result in unauthorized access to sensitive data, installation of additional malware, and a full takeover of the affected system.

Affected Products:
Phish Alert Button (PAB) for Outlook versions 1.10.0-1.10.11
Second Chance Client versions 2.0.0-2.0.9
PIQ Client versions 1.0.0-1.0.15

Remediation:
KnowBe4 has released a patch that corrects the permission settings on the configuration file to prevent unauthorized modifications. Automated updates will be pushed to address this issue. Users of affected versions should verify the latest version is applied and, if not, apply the latest updates provided by KnowBe4.

Workarounds:
Manually set the correct permissions on the configuration file to restrict write access to administrators only.

Credits:
This vulnerability was discovered by Ceri Coburn at Pen Test Partners, who reported it responsibly to the vendor.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33149 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the myProcessList function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33149</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the myProcessList function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33164 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authUserList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33164</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authUserList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33153 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the commentList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33153</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the commentList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:55:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33148 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the list function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33148</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the list function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27982 | The team has identified a critical vulnerability in the http server of the most recent version of Node, where malformed headers can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27982</link><description>The team has identified a critical vulnerability in the http server of the most recent version of Node, where malformed headers can lead to HTTP request smuggling. Specifically, if a space is placed before a content-length header, it is not interpreted correctly, enabling attackers to smuggle in a second request within the body of the first.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29206 | An Improper Access Control could allow a malicious actor authenticated in the API to enable Android Debug Bridge (ADB) and make unsupported ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29206</link><description>An Improper Access Control could allow a malicious actor authenticated in the API to enable Android Debug Bridge (ADB) and make unsupported changes to the system.

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro (Version 1.2.172 and earlier)

UniFi Access Reader Pro (Version 2.7.238 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom (Version 1.0.66 and earlier)

UniFi Access Intercom Viewer (Version 1.0.5 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.   

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Access G2 Reader Pro Version 1.3.37 or later.

Update UniFi Access Reader Pro Version 2.8.19 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Version 1.1.32 or later.

Update UniFi Access Intercom Viewer Version 1.1.6 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later. 

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29207 | An Improper Certificate Validation could allow a malicious actor with access to an adjacent network to take control of the system. 

 

Affe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29207</link><description>An Improper Certificate Validation could allow a malicious actor with access to an adjacent network to take control of the system. 

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect Application (Version 3.7.9 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29208 | An Unverified Password Change could allow a malicious actor with API access to the device to change the system password without knowing the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29208</link><description>An Unverified Password Change could allow a malicious actor with API access to the device to change the system password without knowing the previous password.

 

Affected Products:

UniFi Connect EV Station (Version 1.1.18 and earlier) 

UniFi Connect EV Station Pro (Version 1.1.18 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display (Version 1.9.324 and earlier)

UniFi Connect Display Cast (Version 1.6.225 and earlier)

 

Mitigation:

Update UniFi Connect Application to Version 3.10.7 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect EV Station Pro to Version 1.2.15 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display to Version 1.11.348 or later.

Update UniFi Connect Display Cast to Version 1.8.255 or later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33147 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authRoleList function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33147</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the authRoleList function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33155 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the getDeptList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33155</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the getDeptList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33161 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the unallocatedList() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33161</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the unallocatedList() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33859 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. HTML code sent through logs wasn't being escaped in the "Interesting Field" Web UI, leadin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33859</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. HTML code sent through logs wasn't being escaped in the "Interesting Field" Web UI, leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33860 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. It allows Local File Inclusion (LFI) when an arbitrary File Path is used within the File S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33860</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. It allows Local File Inclusion (LFI) when an arbitrary File Path is used within the File System Collector. The content of the file specified can be viewed in the incoming logs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33857 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. Due to a lack of input validation on URLs in threat intelligence, an attacker with low-lev...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33857</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. Due to a lack of input validation on URLs in threat intelligence, an attacker with low-level access to the system can trigger Server Side Request Forgery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33858 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. A path injection vulnerability is seen while adding a CSV enrichment source. The source_na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33858</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. A path injection vulnerability is seen while adding a CSV enrichment source. The source_name parameter could be changed to an absolute path; this will write the CSV file to that path inside the /tmp directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33856 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. An attacker can enumerate a valid list of usernames by observing the response time at the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33856</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.4.0. An attacker can enumerate a valid list of usernames by observing the response time at the Forgot Password endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33146 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the export function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33146</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the export function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33144 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findApplyedTasksPage function in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33144</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findApplyedTasksPage function in BpmTaskMapper.xml.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4596 | Kimai Session information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Kimai up to 2.15.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Session Handler. The manipulation of the argument PHPSESSIONID leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. Upgrading to version 2.16.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-263318 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33139 | J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findpage function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33139</link><description>J2EEFAST v2.7.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the sql_filter parameter in the findpage function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33748 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function in MvnRepository MS Basic 2.1.18.3 and earlier.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33748</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the search function in MvnRepository MS Basic 2.1.18.3 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34341 | The Trix Editor Contains an Arbitrary Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34341</link><description>Trix is a rich text editor. The Trix editor, versions prior to 2.1.1, is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution when copying and pasting content from the web or other documents with markup into the editor. The vulnerability stems from improper sanitization of pasted content, allowing an attacker to embed malicious scripts which are executed within the context of the application. Users should upgrade to Trix editor version 2.1.1 or later, which incorporates proper sanitization of input from copied content.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32867 | Suricata&amp;#x27;s defrag contains various issues leading to policy bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32867</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, various problems in handling of fragmentation anomalies can lead to mis-detection of rules and policy. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.5 or 6.0.19.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34523 | AChecker 1.5 allows remote attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files via the download.php path parameter by using Unauthenticated Pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34523</link><description>AChecker 1.5 allows remote attackers to read the contents of arbitrary files via the download.php path parameter by using Unauthenticated Path Traversal. This occurs through readfile in PHP. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32371 | An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a regular user account to escalate their privileges and gain a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32371</link><description>An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a regular user account to escalate their privileges and gain administrative access by changing the type parameter from 1 to 0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32664 | Suricata&amp;#x27;s base64 contains an out of bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32664</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, specially crafted traffic or datasets can cause a limited buffer overflow. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.0.5 and 6.0.19. Workarounds include not use rules with `base64_decode` keyword with `bytes` option with value 1, 2 or 5 and for 7.0.x, setting `app-layer.protocols.smtp.mime.body-md5` to false.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4595 | SEMCMS function.php locate sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SEMCMS up to 4.8 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function locate of the file function.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263317 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:19:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32370 | An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32370</link><description>An issue in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through 5.2.18 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the id parameter in the mliSystemUsers.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32663 | Suricata &amp;#x27;s http2 parser contains an improper compressed header handling can lead to resource starvation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32663</link><description>Suricata is a network Intrusion Detection System, Intrusion Prevention System and Network Security Monitoring engine. Prior to 7.0.5 and 6.0.19, a small amount of HTTP/2 traffic can lead to Suricata using a large amount of memory. The issue has been addressed in Suricata 7.0.5 and 6.0.19. Workarounds include disabling the HTTP/2 parser and reducing `app-layer.protocols.http2.max-table-size` value (default is 65536).</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32369 | SQL Injection vulnerability in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.18 and earlier allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32369</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in HSC Cybersecurity HC Mailinspector 5.2.18 and earlier allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the start and limit parameter in the mliWhiteList.php component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33122 | Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the topic parameter in the list() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33122</link><description>Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the topic parameter in the list() function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33120 | Roothub v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via the customPath parameter in the upload() function. This vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33120</link><description>Roothub v2.5 was discovered to contain an arbitrary file upload vulnerability via the customPath parameter in the upload() function. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted JSP file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33124 | Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the nodeTitle parameter in the parentNode() function..</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33124</link><description>Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the nodeTitle parameter in the parentNode() function..</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34342 | react-pdf&amp;#x27;s PDF.js vulnerable to arbitrary JavaScript execution upon opening a malicious PDF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34342</link><description>react-pdf displays PDFs in React apps. If PDF.js is used to load a malicious PDF, and PDF.js is configured with `isEvalSupported` set to `true` (which is the default value), unrestricted attacker-controlled JavaScript will be executed in the context of the hosting domain. This vulnerability is fixed in 7.7.3 and 8.0.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4594 | DedeCMS sys_safe.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4594</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeCMS 5.7. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/sys_safe.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263316. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34084 | Minder&amp;#x27;s Github Webhook Handler vulnerable to denial of service from un-validated requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34084</link><description>Minder's `HandleGithubWebhook` is susceptible to a denial of service attack from an untrusted HTTP request. The vulnerability exists before the request has been validated, and as such the request is still untrusted at the point of failure. This allows an attacker with the ability to send requests to `HandleGithubWebhook` to crash the Minder controlplane and deny other users from using it. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.0.48.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46012 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability LINKSYS EA7500 3.0.1.207964 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via an HTTP request to the IGD ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46012</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability LINKSYS EA7500 3.0.1.207964 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via an HTTP request to the IGD UPnP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29889 | GLPI contains an SQL injection through the saved searches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29889</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability in the saved searches feature to alter another user account data take control of it. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31456 | GLPI contains an authenticated SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31456</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. Prior to 10.0.15, an authenticated user can exploit a SQL injection vulnerability from map search. This vulnerability is fixed in 10.0.15.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33782 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function OTExtensionWithMatrix::extend in /OT/OTExtensionWithMatrix.cpp. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33782</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function OTExtensionWithMatrix::extend in /OT/OTExtensionWithMatrix.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33783 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::SilentMultiPprfReceiver::expand in /Tools/Sile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33783</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::SilentMultiPprfReceiver::expand in /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33780 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::copyOut at /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33780</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the function osuCrypto::copyOut at /Tools/SilentPprf.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33781 | MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function octetStream::get_bytes in /Tools/octetStream.cpp. This vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33781</link><description>MP-SPDZ v0.3.8 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function octetStream::get_bytes in /Tools/octetStream.cpp. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted message.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4592 | DedeCMS sys_group_edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4592</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/sys_group_edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263314 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4593 | DedeCMS sys_multiserv.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4593</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/dede/sys_multiserv.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263315. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33434 | An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS before 1b451cf62582295b7225caf5a7b506f0bad56f6b and 24c9e109b5be34df7b2bce8368eae669c481ed5e allows a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33434</link><description>An issue in tiagorlampert CHAOS before 1b451cf62582295b7225caf5a7b506f0bad56f6b and 24c9e109b5be34df7b2bce8368eae669c481ed5e allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the unsafe concatenation of the `filename` argument into the `buildStr` string without any sanitization or filtering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28148 | Apache Superset: Incorrect datasource authorization on explore REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28148</link><description>An authenticated user could potentially access metadata for a datasource they are not authorized to view by submitting a targeted REST API request.This issue affects Apache Superset: before 4.0.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.0.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4590 | DedeCMS sys_info.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4590</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/sys_info.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263312. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4591 | DedeCMS sys_group_add.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4591</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/sys_group_add.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263313 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7240 | Broken Access Control leading to SSRF in NetIQ Identity Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7240</link><description>An improper authorization level has been detected in the login panel. It may lead to
unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery and allows to perform open services
enumeration. Server makes query to provided server (Server IP/DNS field) and is
triggering connection to arbitrary address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4536 | Eclipse EDC: OAuth2 Credential Exfiltration Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4536</link><description>In Eclipse Dataspace Components from version 0.2.1 to 0.6.2, in the EDC Connector component ( https://github.com/eclipse-edc/Connector ), an attacker might obtain OAuth2 client secrets from the vault.

In Eclipse Dataspace Components from version 0.2.1 to 0.6.2, we have identified a security vulnerability in the EDC Connector component ( https://github.com/eclipse-edc/Connector ) regarding the OAuth2-protected data sink feature. When using a custom, OAuth2-protected data sink, the OAuth2-specific data address properties are resolved by the provider data plane. Problematically, the consumer-provided clientSecretKey, which indicates the OAuth2 client secret to retrieve from a secrets vault, is resolved in the context of the provider's vault, not the consumer. This secret's value is then sent to the tokenUrl, also consumer-controlled, as part of an OAuth2 client credentials grant. The returned access token is then sent as a bearer token to the data sink URL.

This feature is now disabled entirely, because not all code paths necessary for a successful realization were fully implemented.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31234 | WordPress Tilda Publishing plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31234</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tilda Publishing.This issue affects Tilda Publishing: from n/a through 0.3.23.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4588 | DedeCMS mytag_add.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4588</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/mytag_add.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263310 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4589 | DedeCMS mytag_edit.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4589</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/mytag_edit.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263311. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:21:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4586 | DedeCMS shops_delivery.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4586</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DedeCMS 5.7 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/shops_delivery.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263308. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4587 | DedeCMS tpl.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4587</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /src/dede/tpl.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263309 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4585 | DedeCMS member_type.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4585</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/member_type.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263307. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4537 | IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4537</link><description>IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software affecting version 4.3r10. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to obtain the download URL of another user to obtain the purchased ticket.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4538 | IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4538</link><description>IDOR vulnerability in Janto Ticketing Software affecting version 4.3r10. This vulnerability could allow a remote user to obtain a user's event ticket by creating a specific request with the ticket reference ID, leading to the exposure of sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4584 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x command_port.ini information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4584</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /command_port.ini. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263306 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4601 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4601</link><description>An incorrect authentication vulnerability has been found in Socomec Net Vision affecting version 7.20. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a brute force attack on the application and recover a valid session, because the application uses a five-digit integer value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4600 | Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4600</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Socomec Net Vision, version 7.20. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to trick registered users into performing critical actions, such as adding and updating accounts, due to lack of proper sanitisation of the ‘set_param.cgi’ file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4582 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x NTP Service os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4582</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected is an unknown function of the component NTP Service. The manipulation of the argument ntp_srv leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263304.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4583 | Faraday GM8181/GM828x Request information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Faraday GM8181 and GM828x up to 20240429. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Request Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-263305 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4599 | Denial of service vulnerability in LAN Messenger</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4599</link><description>Remote denial of service vulnerability in LAN Messenger affecting version 3.4.0. This vulnerability allows an attacker to crash the LAN Messenger service by sending a long string directly and continuously over the UDP protocol.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6810 | The ClickCease Click Fraud Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an improper capability check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6810</link><description>The ClickCease Click Fraud Protection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to an improper capability check on the get_settings function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author access and above, to retrieve the plugin's configured API keys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4345 | The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4345</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to insufficient file type validation in the 'process' function in the 'startklarDropZoneUploadProcess' class in versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4346 | The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4346</link><description>The Startklar Elementor Addons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.13. This is due to the plugin not properly validating the path of an uploaded file prior to deleting it. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files, including the wp-config.php file, which can make site takeover and remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23808 | Arkcompiler ets frontend has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23808</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free or cause DOS through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27217 | MSDP has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27217</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31078 | Bluetooth Service has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31078</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause service crash through NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3757 | Arkcompiler runtime has an integer  overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3757</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause service crash through integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3758 | Hmdfs has a heap buffer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3758</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in TCB through heap buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3759 | Hmdfs has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3759</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in TCB through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3628 | EasyEvent &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3628</link><description>The EasyEvent WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4186 | The Build App Online plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.5. This is due to the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4186</link><description>The Build App Online plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including, 3.0.5. This is due to the 'eb_user_email_verification_key' default value is empty, and the not empty check is missing in the 'eb_user_email_verify' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id. This can only be exploited if the 'Email Verification' setting is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:40:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22472 | Long S0 frames received by 500 series Z-Wave devices may cause buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22472</link><description>A buffer Overflow vulnerability in Silicon Labs 500 Series Z-Wave devices may allow Denial of Service, and potential Remote Code execution

This issue affects all versions of Silicon Labs 500 Series SDK prior to v6.85.2

running on Silicon Labs 500 series Z-wave devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20855 | Improper access control vulnerability in multitasking framework prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access unlocked...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20855</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in multitasking framework prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access unlocked screen for a while.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20821 | A vulnerability possible to reconfigure OTP allows local attackers to transit RMA(Return Merchandise Authorization) mode, which disables sec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20821</link><description>A vulnerability possible to reconfigure OTP allows local attackers to transit RMA(Return Merchandise Authorization) mode, which disables security features. This attack needs additional privilege to control TEE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20856 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Secure Folder prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access Secure Folder wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20856</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Secure Folder prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to access Secure Folder without proper authentication in a specific scenario.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20857 | Improper access control vulnerability in startListening of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20857</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in startListening of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information of current application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20858 | Improper access control vulnerability in setCocktailHostCallbacks of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20858</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in setCocktailHostCallbacks of CocktailBarService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to access information of current application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20859 | Improper access control vulnerability in FactoryCamera prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to take pictures without privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20859</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in FactoryCamera prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to take pictures without privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20860 | Improper export of android application components vulnerability in TelephonyUI prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to reb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20860</link><description>Improper export of android application components vulnerability in TelephonyUI prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to reboot the device without proper permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20861 | Use after free vulnerability in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20861</link><description>Use after free vulnerability in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to cause memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20862 | Out-of-bounds write in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20862</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in SveService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20863 | Out of bounds write vulnerability in SNAP in HAL prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20863</link><description>Out of bounds write vulnerability in SNAP in HAL prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20864 | Improper access control vulnerability in DarManagerService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to monitor system resource...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20864</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in DarManagerService prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to monitor system resources.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20865 | Authentication bypass in bootloader prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to flash arbitrary images.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20865</link><description>Authentication bypass in bootloader prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to flash arbitrary images.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20866 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in Setupwizard prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to skip activation step.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20866</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in Setupwizard prior to SMR May-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to skip activation step.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20867 | Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.91.14 allows local attackers to access sensitive informati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20867</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.91.14 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20868 | Improper input validation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.15 allows local attackers to delete files with Samsung Notes privilege under...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20868</link><description>Improper input validation in Samsung Notes prior to version 4.4.15 allows local attackers to delete files with Samsung Notes privilege under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20869 | Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 25.0.0.41 allows local attackers to bypass protection for c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20869</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in Samsung Internet prior to version 25.0.0.41 allows local attackers to bypass protection for cookies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20870 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.71.8 allows local attackers to writ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20870</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Galaxy Store prior to version 4.5.71.8 allows local attackers to write arbitrary files with the privilege of Galaxy Store.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20871 | Improper authorization vulnerability in Samsung Keyboard prior to version One UI 5.1.1 allows physical attackers to partially bypass the fac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20871</link><description>Improper authorization vulnerability in Samsung Keyboard prior to version One UI 5.1.1 allows physical attackers to partially bypass the factory reset protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20872 | Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in TalkbackSE prior to version Android 14 allows local attackers to modify settin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20872</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in TalkbackSE prior to version Android 14 allows local attackers to modify setting value of TalkbackSE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2913 | Race Condition Vulnerability in mintplex-labs/anything-llm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2913</link><description>A race condition vulnerability exists in the mintplex-labs/anything-llm repository, specifically within the user invite acceptance process. Attackers can exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple concurrent requests to accept a single user invite, allowing the creation of multiple user accounts from a single invite link intended for only one user. This bypasses the intended security mechanism that restricts invite acceptance to a single user, leading to unauthorized user creation without detection in the invite tab. The issue is due to the lack of validation for concurrent requests in the backend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29941 | Credential Cloning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29941</link><description>Insecure storage of the ICT MIFARE and DESFire encryption keys in the firmware
binary allows malicious actors to create credentials for any site code and card number that is using the default
ICT encryption.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30973 | An issue in V-SOL G/EPON ONU HG323AC-B with firmware version V2.0.08-210715 allows an attacker to execute arbtirary code and obtain sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30973</link><description>An issue in V-SOL G/EPON ONU HG323AC-B with firmware version V2.0.08-210715 allows an attacker to execute arbtirary code and obtain sensitive information via crafted POST request to /boaform/getASPdata/formFirewall, /boaform/getASPdata/formAcc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33548 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ASUS RT-AC51U with firmware versions up to and including 3.0.0.4.380.8591 allows attackers to ru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33548</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ASUS RT-AC51U with firmware versions up to and including 3.0.0.4.380.8591 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the WPA Pre-Shared Key field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1695 | A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Application Enabling Software Driver for certain HP PC products, which migh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1695</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Application Enabling Software Driver for certain HP PC products, which might allow escalation of privilege. HP is releasing software updates to mitigate this potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34532 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Yvan Dotet PostgreSQL Query Deluxe module (aka query_deluxe) 17.x before 17.0.0.4 allows a remote attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34532</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Yvan Dotet PostgreSQL Query Deluxe module (aka query_deluxe) 17.x before 17.0.0.4 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via the query parameter to models/querydeluxe.py:QueryDeluxe::get_result_from_query.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34533 | A SQL injection vulnerability in ZI PT Solusi Usaha Mudah Analytic Data Query module (aka izi_data) 11.0 through 17.x before 17.0.3 allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34533</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in ZI PT Solusi Usaha Mudah Analytic Data Query module (aka izi_data) 11.0 through 17.x before 17.0.3 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via a query to IZITools::query_check, IZITools::query_fetch, or IZITools::query_execute.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34534 | A SQL injection vulnerability in Cybrosys Techno Solutions Text Commander module (aka text_commander) 16.0 through 16.0.1 allows a remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34534</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in Cybrosys Techno Solutions Text Commander module (aka text_commander) 16.0 through 16.0.1 allows a remote attacker to gain privileges via the data parameter to models/ir_model.py:IrModel::chech_model.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28725 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in YzmCMS 7.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via Ads Management, Carousel Management, and S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28725</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in YzmCMS 7.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via Ads Management, Carousel Management, and System Settings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34413 | WordPress SliceWP Affiliates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34413</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SliceWP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects SliceWP: from n/a through 1.1.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33117 | crmeb_java v1.3.4 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the mergeList method in class com.zbkj.front.pub.ImageM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33117</link><description>crmeb_java v1.3.4 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the mergeList method in class com.zbkj.front.pub.ImageMergeController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4568 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4568</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in the PDF resources leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33118 | LuckyFrameWeb v3.5.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary read vulnerability via the fileDownload method in class com.luckyframe.project.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33118</link><description>LuckyFrameWeb v3.5.2 was discovered to contain an arbitrary read vulnerability via the fileDownload method in class com.luckyframe.project.common.CommonController.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33121 | Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the 's' parameter in the search() function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33121</link><description>Roothub v2.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the 's' parameter in the search() function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33570 | WordPress MetForm plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33570</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpmet Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder.This issue affects Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder: from n/a through 3.8.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33576 | WordPress WPPizza plugin &amp;lt;= 3.18.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33576</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ollybach WPPizza.This issue affects WPPizza: from n/a through 3.18.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33599 | nscd: Stack-based buffer overflow in netgroup cache</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33599</link><description>nscd: Stack-based buffer overflow in netgroup cache

If the Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) fixed size cache is exhausted
by client requests then a subsequent client request for netgroup data
may result in a stack-based buffer overflow.  This flaw was introduced
in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33600 | nscd: Null pointer crashes after notfound response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33600</link><description>nscd: Null pointer crashes after notfound response

If the Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) cache fails to add a not-found
netgroup response to the cache, the client request can result in a null
pointer dereference.  This flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the
cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33601 | nscd: netgroup cache may terminate daemon on memory allocation failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33601</link><description>nscd: netgroup cache may terminate daemon on memory allocation failure

The Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) netgroup cache uses xmalloc or
xrealloc and these functions may terminate the process due to a memory
allocation failure resulting in a denial of service to the clients.  The
flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33602 | nscd: netgroup cache assumes NSS callback uses in-buffer strings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33602</link><description>nscd: netgroup cache assumes NSS callback uses in-buffer strings

The Name Service Cache Daemon's (nscd) netgroup cache can corrupt memory
when the NSS callback does not store all strings in the provided buffer.
The flaw was introduced in glibc 2.15 when the cache was added to nscd.

This vulnerability is only present in the nscd binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33907 | WordPress Print My Blog plugin &amp;lt;= 3.26.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33907</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Michael Nelson Print My Blog.This issue affects Print My Blog: from n/a through 3.26.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33908 | WordPress WidgetKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33908</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themesgrove WidgetKit.This issue affects WidgetKit: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33910 | WordPress Digital Publications by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33910</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Supsystic Digital Publications by Supsystic.This issue affects Digital Publications by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33912 | WordPress Academy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.16 - Broken Access Control on Paid Courses vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33912</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Academy LMS.This issue affects Academy LMS: from n/a through 1.9.16.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34371 | WordPress Login with phone number plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34371</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hamid Alinia – idehweb Login with phone number.This issue affects Login with phone number: from n/a through 1.7.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34372 | WordPress Post Grid Master plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34372</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AddonMaster Post Grid Master.This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34377 | WordPress Video Gallery – Api Gallery, YouTube and Vimeo, Link Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34377</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in A WP Life Video Gallery – Api Gallery, YouTube and Vimeo, Link Gallery.This issue affects Video Gallery – Api Gallery, YouTube and Vimeo, Link Gallery: from n/a through 1.5.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34378 | WordPress LeadConnector plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 - API Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34378</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LeadConnector.This issue affects LeadConnector: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34387 | WordPress WP Post Author plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Rating Value Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34387</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AF themes WP Post Author.This issue affects WP Post Author: from n/a through 3.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34389 | WordPress WP Post Author plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34389</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AF themes WP Post Author.This issue affects WP Post Author: from n/a through 3.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34366 | WordPress AltText.ai plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34366</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AltText.Ai Download Alt Text AI allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Download Alt Text AI: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34369 | WordPress Web Push Notifications – Webpushr plugin &amp;lt;= 4.35.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34369</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Webpushr Web Push Notifications Webpushr allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Webpushr: from n/a through 4.35.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34373 | WordPress The Plus Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34373</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite allows Stored XSS.This issue affects The Plus Addons for Elementor Page Builder Lite: from n/a through 5.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34374 | WordPress ElementsReady Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34374</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in QuomodoSoft ElementsReady Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ElementsReady Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 5.8.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3661 | DHCP routing options can manipulate interface-based VPN traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3661</link><description>By design, the DHCP protocol does not authenticate messages, including for example the classless static route option (121). An attacker with the ability to send DHCP messages can manipulate routes to redirect VPN traffic, allowing the attacker to read, disrupt, or possibly modify network traffic that was expected to be protected by the VPN. Many, if not most VPN systems based on IP routing are susceptible to such attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34375 | WordPress Sheets to WP Table Live Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34375</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPPOOL Sheets To WP Table Live Sync allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Sheets To WP Table Live Sync: from n/a through 3.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34376 | WordPress Edge theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34376</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Theme Freesia Edge allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Edge: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34379 | WordPress Restaurant and Cafe theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34379</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Restaurant and Cafe.This issue affects Restaurant and Cafe: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34380 | WordPress ChatBot Conversational Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34380</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in QuantumCloud Conversational Forms for ChatBot allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Conversational Forms for ChatBot: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34381 | WordPress PropertyHive plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.10 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34381</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PropertyHive allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PropertyHive: from n/a through 2.0.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34390 | WordPress Post Grid Master plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - Auth. Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34390</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AddonMaster Post Grid Master allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Post Grid Master: from n/a through 3.4.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:38:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34367 | WordPress Popup Box plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34367</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Popup Box Team Popup box allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Popup box: from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34368 | WordPress Mooberry Book Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 4.15.12 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34368</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Mooberry Dreams Mooberry Book Manager.This issue affects Mooberry Book Manager: from n/a through 4.15.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34386 | WordPress Auto Affiliate Links plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.3.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34386</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Lucian Apostol Auto Affiliate Links.This issue affects Auto Affiliate Links: from n/a through 6.4.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34412 | WordPress ParcelPanel  plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34412</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Parcel Panel ParcelPanel.This issue affects ParcelPanel: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34382 | WordPress Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.18 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34382</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in RoboSoft Robo Gallery.This issue affects Robo Gallery: from n/a through 3.2.18.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34383 | WordPress SEOPress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34383</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in The SEO Guys at SEOPress SEOPress.This issue affects SEOPress: from n/a through 7.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34388 | WordPress GDPR Compliance plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34388</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Scribit GDPR Compliance.This issue affects GDPR Compliance: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32807 | WordPress Brevo for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.17 - Arbitrary File Download and Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32807</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Brevo for WooCommerce Sendinblue for WooCommerce.This issue affects Sendinblue for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.0.17.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33408 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_classroom.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33408</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_classroom.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33409 | SQL injection vulnerability in index.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33409</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in index.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the name parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33410 | SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_range_grade.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33410</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_range_grade.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33411 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_admin_profile.php in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33411</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_admin_profile.php in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the my_index parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33403 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_events.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33403</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/get_events.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the event_id parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33404 | A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/add_student_first_payment.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33404</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in /model/add_student_first_payment.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the index parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33405 | SQL injection vulnerability in add_friends.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33405</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in add_friends.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the friend_index parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33406 | SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_student_grade_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33406</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_student_grade_subject.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the index parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33407 | SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_record.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33407</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in /model/delete_record.php in campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 allows attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:51:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34089 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34089</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed by the web browser in the context of the vulnerable application. 6.14 P3 (6.14.0.3) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34090 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The login banner in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34090</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. The login banner in the Archer Control Panel (ACP) did not previously escape content appropriately. 6.14 P3 (6.14.0.3) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34091 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34091</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. There is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability. A remote authenticated malicious Archer user could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious HTML or JavaScript code in a trusted application data store. When victim users access the data store through their browsers, the malicious code gets executed in the background of the application and renders content inaccessible. 6.14 P3 (6.14.0.3) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26312 | Archer Platform 6 before 2024.03 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially obta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26312</link><description>Archer Platform 6 before 2024.03 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An authenticated attacker could potentially obtain access to sensitive information via a popup warning message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34092 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. Authentication was mishandled because lock did not terminate an existing sessio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34092</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.04. Authentication was mishandled because lock did not terminate an existing session. 6.14 P3 (6.14.0.3) is also a fixed release.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34093 | An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.03. There is an X-Forwarded-For Header Bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34093</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Platform 6 before 2024.03. There is an X-Forwarded-For Header Bypass vulnerability. An unauthenticated attacker could potentially bypass intended whitelisting when X-Forwarded-For header is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34471 | An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3. A Path Traversal vulnerability (resulting in file deletion) exists in the mliRealtime...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34471</link><description>An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3. A Path Traversal vulnerability (resulting in file deletion) exists in the mliRealtimeEmails.php file. The filename parameter in the export HTML functionality does not properly validate the file location, allowing an attacker to read and delete arbitrary files on the server. This was observed when the mliRealtimeEmails.php file itself was read and subsequently deleted, resulting in a 404 error for the file and disruption of email information loading.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34250 | A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime v2.0.0 which allows a remote attacker to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34250</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime v2.0.0 which allows a remote attacker to cause at least a denial of service via the "wasm_loader_check_br" function in core/iwasm/interpreter/wasm_loader.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34251 | An out-of-bound memory read vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime v2.0.0 which allows a remote attacker to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34251</link><description>An out-of-bound memory read vulnerability was discovered in Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime v2.0.0 which allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the "block_type_get_arity" function in core/iwasm/interpreter/wasm.h.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34246 | wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain an out-of-bound memory read which leads to segmentation fault via the function "main" in wasm3/platfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34246</link><description>wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain an out-of-bound memory read which leads to segmentation fault via the function "main" in wasm3/platforms/app/main.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34249 | wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow which leads to segmentation fault via the function "DeallocateSlot" in wasm3/s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34249</link><description>wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain a heap buffer overflow which leads to segmentation fault via the function "DeallocateSlot" in wasm3/source/m3_compile.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34252 | wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain a global buffer overflow which leads to segmentation fault via the function "PreserveRegisterIfOccupi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34252</link><description>wasm3 v0.5.0 was discovered to contain a global buffer overflow which leads to segmentation fault via the function "PreserveRegisterIfOccupied" in wasm3/source/m3_compile.c.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34470 | An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through v.5.2.18. An Unauthenticated Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the /publi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34470</link><description>An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through v.5.2.18. An Unauthenticated Path Traversal vulnerability exists in the /public/loader.php file. The path parameter does not properly filter whether the file and directory passed are part of the webroot, allowing an attacker to read arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34472 | An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through v.5.2.18. An authenticated blind SQL injection vulnerability exists in the mli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34472</link><description>An issue was discovered in HSC Mailinspector 5.2.17-3 through v.5.2.18. An authenticated blind SQL injection vulnerability exists in the mliRealtimeEmails.php file. The ordemGrid parameter in a POST request to /mailinspector/mliRealtimeEmails.php does not properly sanitize input, allowing an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary SQL commands, leading to the potential disclosure of the entire application database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33294 | An issue in Library System using PHP/MySQli with Source Code V1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the _FAILE variable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33294</link><description>An issue in Library System using PHP/MySQli with Source Code V1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the _FAILE variable in the student_edit_photo.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33110 | D-Link DIR-845L router v1.01KRb03 and before is vulnerable to Permission Bypass via the getcfg.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33110</link><description>D-Link DIR-845L router v1.01KRb03 and before is vulnerable to Permission Bypass via the getcfg.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33111 | D-Link DIR-845L router &lt;=v1.01KRb03 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /htdocs/webinc/js/bsc_sms_inbox.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33111</link><description>D-Link DIR-845L router &lt;=v1.01KRb03 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via /htdocs/webinc/js/bsc_sms_inbox.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33113 | D-LINK DIR-845L &lt;=v1.01KRb03 is vulnerable to Information disclosurey via bsc_sms_inbox.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33113</link><description>D-LINK DIR-845L &lt;=v1.01KRb03 is vulnerable to Information disclosurey via bsc_sms_inbox.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34078 | html-sanitizer allows arbitrary HTML present after sanitization because of unicode normalization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34078</link><description>html-sanitizer is an allowlist-based HTML cleaner. If using `keep_typographic_whitespace=False` (which is the default), the sanitizer normalizes unicode to the NFKC form at the end. Some unicode characters normalize to chevrons; this allows specially crafted HTML to escape sanitization. The problem has been fixed in 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33112 | D-Link DIR-845L router v1.01KRb03 and before is vulnerable to Command injection via the hnap_main()func.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33112</link><description>D-Link DIR-845L router v1.01KRb03 and before is vulnerable to Command injection via the hnap_main()func.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34069 | Werkzeug&amp;#x27;s improper usage of a pathname and improper CSRF protection results in the remote command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34069</link><description>Werkzeug is a comprehensive WSGI web application library. The debugger in affected versions of Werkzeug can allow an attacker to execute code on a developer's machine under some circumstances. This requires the attacker to get the developer to interact with a domain and subdomain they control, and enter the debugger PIN, but if they are successful it allows access to the debugger even if it is only running on localhost. This also requires the attacker to guess a URL in the developer's application that will trigger the debugger. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32982 | Litestar and Starlite affected by Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32982</link><description>Litestar and Starlite is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.8.3, a Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability has been discovered in the static file serving component of LiteStar. This vulnerability allows attackers to exploit path traversal flaws, enabling unauthorized access to sensitive files outside the designated directories. Such access can lead to the disclosure of sensitive information or potentially compromise the server. The vulnerability is located in the file path handling mechanism within the static content serving function, specifically at `litestar/static_files/base.py`. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34064 | Jinja vulnerable to HTML attribute injection when passing user input as keys to xmlattr filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34064</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. The `xmlattr` filter in affected versions of Jinja accepts keys containing non-attribute characters. XML/HTML attributes cannot contain spaces, `/`, `&gt;`, or `=`, as each would then be interpreted as starting a separate attribute. If an application accepts keys (as opposed to only values) as user input, and renders these in pages that other users see as well, an attacker could use this to inject other attributes and perform XSS. The fix for CVE-2024-22195 only addressed spaces but not other characters. Accepting keys as user input is now explicitly considered an unintended use case of the `xmlattr` filter, and code that does so without otherwise validating the input should be flagged as insecure, regardless of Jinja version. Accepting _values_ as user input continues to be safe. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33119 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33119</link><description>Memory corruption while loading a VM from a signed VM image that is not coherent in the processor cache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43521 | Use After Free in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43521</link><description>Memory corruption when multiple listeners are being registered with the same file descriptor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43524 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43524</link><description>Memory corruption when the bandpass filter order received from AHAL is not within the expected range.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43525 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43525</link><description>Memory corruption while copying the sound model data from user to kernel buffer during sound model register.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43526 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43526</link><description>Memory corruption while querying module parameters from Listen Sound model client in kernel from user space.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43527 | Buffer Over-read in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43527</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing dts header atom in Video.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43528 | Buffer Over-read in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43528</link><description>Information disclosure when the ADSP payload size received in HLOS in response to Audio Stream Manager matrix session is less than this expected size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43529 | Reachable Assertion in Data Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43529</link><description>Transient DOS while processing IKEv2 Informational request messages, when a malformed fragment packet is received.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43530 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43530</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while checking for the storage type.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43531 | Access of Uninitialized Pointer in SPS Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43531</link><description>Memory corruption while verifying the serialized header when the key pairs are generated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21471 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21471</link><description>Memory corruption when IOMMU unmap of a GPU buffer fails in Linux.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21474 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in PMIC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21474</link><description>Memory corruption when size of buffer from previous call is used without validation or re-initialization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21475 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21475</link><description>Memory corruption when the payload received from firmware is not as per the expected protocol size.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21476 | Improper Input Validation in Secure Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21476</link><description>Memory corruption when the channel ID passed by user is not validated and further used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21477 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21477</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing a protected 802.11az Fine Time Measurement (FTM) frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21480 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21480</link><description>Memory corruption while playing audio file having large-sized input buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23351 | Improper Access Control in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23351</link><description>Memory corruption as GPU registers beyond the last protected range can be accessed through LPAC submissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23354 | Use After Free in Graphics Linux</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23354</link><description>Memory corruption when the IOCTL call is interrupted by a signal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32972 | go-ethereum denial of service via malicious p2p message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32972</link><description>go-ethereum (geth) is a golang execution layer implementation of the Ethereum protocol. Prior to 1.13.15, a vulnerable node can be made to consume very large amounts of memory when handling specially crafted p2p messages sent from an attacker node. The fix has been included in geth version `1.13.15` and onwards.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33752 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in emlog pro 2.3.0 and pro 2.3.2 at admin/views/plugin.php that could be exploited by a remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33752</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in emlog pro 2.3.0 and pro 2.3.2 at admin/views/plugin.php that could be exploited by a remote attacker to submit a special request to upload a malicious file to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:17:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4549 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4549</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in Delta Electronics DIAEnergie v1.10.1.8610 and prior. When processing an 'ICS Restart!' message, CEBC.exe restarts the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4547 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4547</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability exists in Delta Electronics DIAEnergie v1.10.1.8610 and prior when CEBC.exe processes a 'RecalculateScript' message, which is splitted into 4 fields using the '~' character as the separator. An unauthenticated remote attacker can perform SQLi via the fourth field</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4548 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4548</link><description>An SQLi vulnerability exists in Delta Electronics DIAEnergie v1.10.1.8610 and prior when CEBC.exe processes a 'RecalculateHDMWYC' message, which is split into 4 fields using the '~' character as the separator. An unauthenticated remote attacker can perform SQLi via the fourth field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33788 | Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the PinCode parameter at /API/info form endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33788</link><description>Linksys E5600 v1.1.0.26 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the PinCode parameter at /API/info form endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:15:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33749 | DedeCMS V5.7.114 is vulnerable to deletion of any file via mail_file_manage.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33749</link><description>DedeCMS V5.7.114 is vulnerable to deletion of any file via mail_file_manage.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33829 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/readDeal.php?mudi=updateWebCache.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33829</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/readDeal.php?mudi=updateWebCache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33830 | idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/readDeal.php?mudi=clearWebCache.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33830</link><description>idccms v1.35 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via the component /admin/readDeal.php?mudi=clearWebCache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:55:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3576 | NPort 5100A Series Store XSS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3576</link><description>The NPort 5100A Series prior to version 1.6 is affected by web server XSS vulnerability. The vulnerability is caused by not correctly neutralizing user-controllable input before placing it in output. Malicious users may use the vulnerability to get sensitive information and escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33753 | Section Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811 and earlier versions allow the accounts and passwords of administrators and users to be changed...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33753</link><description>Section Camera V2.5.5.3116-S50-SMA-B20160811 and earlier versions allow the accounts and passwords of administrators and users to be changed without authorization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49675 | CODESYS: Out-of-bounds write through corrupted project files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49675</link><description>An unauthenticated local attacker may trick a user to open corrupted project files to execute arbitrary code or crash the system due to an out-of-bounds write vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49676 | CODESYS: Use after free vulnerability through corrupted project files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49676</link><description>An unauthenticated local attacker may trick a user to open corrupted project files to crash the system due to use after free vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6854 | The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom postmeta output in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6854</link><description>The Breakdance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's custom postmeta output in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied post meta fields. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:20:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23186 | E-Mail containing malicious display-name information could trigger client-side script execution when using specific mobile devices. Attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23186</link><description>E-Mail containing malicious display-name information could trigger client-side script execution when using specific mobile devices. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding displayname information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23187 | Content-ID based embedding of resources in E-Mails could be abused to trigger client-side script code when using the "show more" option. Att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23187</link><description>Content-ID based embedding of resources in E-Mails could be abused to trigger client-side script code when using the "show more" option. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Exploiting the vulnerability requires user interaction. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. CID replacement has been hardened to omit invalid identifiers. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23188 | Maliciously crafted E-Mail attachment names could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. Co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23188</link><description>Maliciously crafted E-Mail attachment names could be used to temporarily execute script code in the context of the users browser session. Common user interaction is required for the vulnerability to trigger. Attackers could perform malicious API requests or extract information from the users account. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. We now use safer methods of handling external content when embedding attachment information to the web interface. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23193 | E-Mails exported as PDF were stored in a cache that did not consider specific session information for the related user account. Users of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23193</link><description>E-Mails exported as PDF were stored in a cache that did not consider specific session information for the related user account. Users of the same service node could access other users E-Mails in case they were exported as PDF for a brief moment until caches were cleared. Successful exploitation requires good timing and modification of multiple request parameters. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. The cache for PDF exports now takes user session information into consideration when performing authorization decisions. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4528 | SourceCodester Prison Management System user-record.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4528</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Admin/user-record.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263131.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0904 | Fancy Product Designer &amp;lt; 6.1.81 - Admin+ Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0904</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer WordPress plugin before 6.1.81 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3752 | Crelly Slider &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3752</link><description>The Crelly Slider WordPress plugin through 1.4.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3755 | MF Gig Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3755</link><description>The MF Gig Calendar WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3756 | MF Gig Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Arbitrary Event Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3756</link><description>The MF Gig Calendar WordPress plugin through 1.2.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in Contributors and above delete arbitrary events via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4526 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_payment_details3.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4526</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/student_payment_details3.php. The manipulation of the argument month leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263129 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4527 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_payment_details2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4527</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/student_payment_details2.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263130 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 06:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4524 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_payment_invoice.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4524</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/student_payment_invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263127.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4525 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System student_payment_details4.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4525</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view/student_payment_details4.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263128.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 05:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4523 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_attendance_history1.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4523</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/teacher_attendance_history1.php. The manipulation of the argument year leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 05:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4521 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_salary_details2.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4521</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/teacher_salary_details2.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263124.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 04:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4522 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_salary_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4522</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/teacher_salary_details.php. The manipulation of the argument index leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263125 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 04:45:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4519 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_salary_details3.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4519</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/teacher_salary_details3.php. The manipulation of the argument month leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263123.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 04:23:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4518 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_salary_invoice.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4518</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view/teacher_salary_invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263122 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 03:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4517 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System teacher_salary_invoice1.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4517</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /view/teacher_salary_invoice1.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263121 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32871 | In DA, there is a possible permission bypass due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no addi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32871</link><description>In DA, there is a possible permission bypass due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08355514; Issue ID: ALPS08355514.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32873 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32873</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08583919; Issue ID: ALPS08304227.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20021 | In atf spm, there is a possible way to remap physical memory to virtual memory due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20021</link><description>In atf spm, there is a possible way to remap physical memory to virtual memory due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08584568; Issue ID: MSV-1249.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20056 | In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20056</link><description>In preloader, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an insecure default value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08528185; Issue ID: ALPS08528185.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20057 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20057</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08587881; Issue ID: ALPS08587881.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20058 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20058</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08580204; Issue ID: ALPS08580204.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20059 | In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20059</link><description>In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541749; Issue ID: ALPS08541749.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20060 | In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20060</link><description>In da, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect status check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541749; Issue ID: ALPS08541754.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20064 | In wlan service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20064</link><description>In wlan service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08572601; Issue ID: MSV-1229.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:55:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4516 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System timetable.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4516</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/timetable.php. The manipulation of the argument grade leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263120.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34538 | Mateso PasswordSafe through 8.13.9.26689 has Weak Cryptography.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34538</link><description>Mateso PasswordSafe through 8.13.9.26689 has Weak Cryptography.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4514 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System timetable_insert_form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4514</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/timetable_insert_form.php. The manipulation of the argument grade leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263118 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4515 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System timetable_grade_wise.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4515</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/timetable_grade_wise.php. The manipulation of the argument grade leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263119.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:35:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4512 | SourceCodester Prison Management System edit-profile.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4512</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Employee/edit-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname/txtdob/txtaddress/txtqualification/cmddept/cmdemployeetype/txtappointment leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263116.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4513 | Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System timetable_update_form.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4513</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Campcodes Complete Web-Based School Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/timetable_update_form.php. The manipulation of the argument grade leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263117 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 02:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4511 | Shanghai Sunfull Automation BACnet Server HMI1002-ARM Message buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4511</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shanghai Sunfull Automation BACnet Server HMI1002-ARM 2.0.4. This affects an unknown part of the component Message Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263115. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 01:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4509 | Ruijie RG-UAC add_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4509</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240428. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /view/IPV6/naborTable/add_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument ip_addr/mac_addr leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-263113 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 01:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4510 | Ruijie RG-UAC arp_add_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4510</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240428. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /view/networkConfig/ArpTable/arp_add_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument text_ip_addr/text_mac_addr leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-263114 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 01:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4508 | Ruijie RG-UAC static_route_edit_ipv6.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4508</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240428. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /view/IPV6/ipv6StaticRoute/static_route_edit_ipv6.php. The manipulation of the argument oldipmask/oldgateway/olddevname leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-263112. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 01:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>