<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 17:30:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2020-36773 | Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36773</link><description>Artifex Ghostscript before 9.53.0 has an out-of-bounds write and use-after-free in devices/vector/gdevtxtw.c (for txtwrite) because a single character code in a PDF document can map to more than one Unicode code point (e.g., for a ligature).</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25098 | blockmason credit-protocol UCAC CreditProtocol.sol executeUcacTx denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25098</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in blockmason credit-protocol. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeUcacTx of the file contracts/CreditProtocol.sol of the component UCAC Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is named 082e01f18707ef995e80ebe97fcedb229a55efc5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252799. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25062 | An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XIncl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25062</link><description>An issue was discovered in libxml2 before 2.11.7 and 2.12.x before 2.12.5. When using the XML Reader interface with DTD validation and XInclude expansion enabled, processing crafted XML documents can lead to an xmlValidatePopElement use-after-free.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 16:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6240 | Kernel: marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage in the rsa decryption operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6240</link><description>A Marvin vulnerability side-channel leakage was found in the RSA decryption operation in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a network attacker to decrypt ciphertexts or forge signatures, limiting the services that use that private key.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 14:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25159 | mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso cargos.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25159</link><description>A vulnerability was found in mpedraza2020 Intranet del Monterroso up to 4.50.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file config/cargos.php. The manipulation of the argument dni_profe leads to sql injection. Upgrading to version 4.51.0 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 678190bee1dfd64b54a2b0e88abfd009e78adce8. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-252717 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10129 | planet-freo auth.inc.php comparison</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in planet-freo up to 20150116 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file admin/inc/auth.inc.php. The manipulation of the argument auth leads to incorrect comparison. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 6ad38c58a45642eb8c7844e2f272ef199f59550d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252716.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 04:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33851 | IBM PowerVM Hypervisor information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33851</link><description>IBM PowerVM Hypervisor FW950.00 through FW950.90, FW1020.00 through FW1020.40, and FW1030.00 through FW1030.30 could reveal sensitive partition data to a system administrator.  IBM X-Force ID:  257135.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50947 | IBM Business Automation Workflow cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50947</link><description>IBM Business Automation Workflow 22.0.2, 23.0.1, and 23.0.2 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  275665.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1215 | SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload fetch_data.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester CRUD without Page Reload 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file fetch_data.php. The manipulation of the argument username/city leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252782 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 15:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0853 | OCSP verification bypass with TLS session reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0853</link><description>curl inadvertently kept the SSL session ID for connections in its cache even when the verify status (*OCSP stapling*) test failed. A subsequent transfer to
the same hostname could then succeed if the session ID cache was still fresh, which then skipped the verify status check.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 13:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1064 | Improper Neutralization of HTTP Headers for Scripting Syntax in Crafty Controller 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1064</link><description>A host header injection vulnerability in the HTTP handler component of Crafty Controller allows a remote, unauthenticated attacker to trigger a Denial of Service (DoS) condition via a modified host header</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 09:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49950 | The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a cust...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49950</link><description>The Jinja templating in Logpoint SIEM 6.10.0 through 7.x before 7.3.0 does not correctly sanitize log data being displayed when using a custom Jinja template in the Alert view. A remote attacker can craft a cross-site scripting (XSS) payload and send it to any system or device that sends logs to the SIEM. If an alert is created, the payload will execute upon the alert data being viewed with that template, which can lead to sensitive data disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43183 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43183</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows read-only users to arbitrarily change the password of an admin and hijack their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44031 | Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44031</link><description>Incorrect access control in Reprise License Management Software Reprise License Manager v15.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily save sensitive files in insecure locations via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 08:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0895 | The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0895</link><description>The PDF Flipbook, 3D Flipbook – DearFlip plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via outline settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.26 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied data. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0909 | The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0909</link><description>The Anonymous Restricted Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to information disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2. This is due to insufficient restrictions through the REST API on the posts/pages that protections are being place on. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access protected content.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:48:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23550 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) may be vulnerable to sensitive information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23550</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch (UCD) could disclose sensitive user information when installing the Windows agent.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37528 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37528</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attack to exploit an application parameter during execution of the Save Report.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1200 | Jspxcms information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1200</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Jspxcms 10.2.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /template/1/default/. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252698 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31004 | IBM Security Access Manager Container gain access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31004</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote attacker to gain access to the underlying system using man in the middle techniques.  IBM X-Force ID:  254765.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31006 | IBM Security Access Manager Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31006</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to a denial of service attacks on the DSC server.  IBM X-Force ID:  254776.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32327 | IBM Security Access Manager Container XML external entity injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32327</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) is vulnerable to an XML External Entity Injection (XXE) attack when processing XML data. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  254783.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32329 | IBM Security Access Manager Container improper file validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32329</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a user to download files from an incorrect repository due to improper file validation.  IBM X-Force ID:  254972.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43016 | IBM Security Access Manager Container unauthorized access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43016</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a remote user to log into the server due to a user account with an empty password.  IBM X-Force ID:  266154.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30999 | IBM Security Access Manager denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30999</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service due to uncontrolled resource consumption.  IBM X-Force ID:  254651.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31005 | IBM Security Access Manager Container privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31005</link><description>IBM Security Access Manager Container (IBM Security Verify Access Appliance 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1 and IBM Security Verify Access Docker 10.0.0.0 through 10.0.6.1) could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to an improper security configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  254767.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1199 | CodeAstro Employee Task Management System attendance-info.php denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1199</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Employee Task Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file \employee-tasks-php\attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument aten_id leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252697 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:48:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1198 | openBI Phar User.php addxinzhi deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1198</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in openBI up to 6.0.3. Affected is the function addxinzhi of the file application/controllers/User.php of the component Phar Handler. The manipulation of the argument outimgurl leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252696.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 23:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1197 | SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager HTTP GET Request delete-testimonial.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1197</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file delete-testimonial.php of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument testimony leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252695.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 22:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1196 | SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager HTTP POST Request add-testimonial.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1196</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Testimonial Page Manager 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file add-testimonial.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/description/testimony leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-252694 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1195 | iTop VPN IOCTL ITopVpnCallbackProcess.sys denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1195</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in iTop VPN up to 4.0.0.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library ITopVpnCallbackProcess.sys of the component IOCTL Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The identifier VDB-252685 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23553 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23553</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform exists due to missing a specific http header attribute.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1194 | Armcode AlienIP Locate Host denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1194</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Armcode AlienIP 2.41. Affected is an unknown function of the component Locate Host Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252684. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1193 | Navicat MySQL Conecction denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1193</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Navicat 12.0.29. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component MySQL Conecction Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252683. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37531 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37531</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a form field of a webpage by a user with privileged access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37530 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37530</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a webpage trying to retrieve cookie stored information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1192 | South River WebDrive New Secure WebDAV denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in South River WebDrive 18.00.5057. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component New Secure WebDAV. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252682 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 20:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37529 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37529</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code into a webpage trying to retrieve cookie stored information.  This is not the same vulnerability as identified in CVE-2023-37530.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1191 | Hyper CdCatalog HCF File denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Hyper CdCatalog 2.3.1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the component HCF File Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252681 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25006 | XenForo before 2.2.14 allows Directory Traversal (with write access) by an authenticated user who has permissions to administer styles, and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25006</link><description>XenForo before 2.2.14 allows Directory Traversal (with write access) by an authenticated user who has permissions to administer styles, and uses a ZIP archive for Styles Import.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1190 | Global Scape CuteFTP denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Global Scape CuteFTP 9.3.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument Host/Username/Password leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252680. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1189 | AMPPS Encryption Passphrase denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in AMPPS 2.7 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Encryption Passphrase Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 4.0 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252679. NOTE: The vendor explains that AMPPS 4.0 is a complete overhaul and the code was re-written.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37527 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affects HCL BigFix Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37527</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Web Reports component of HCL BigFix Platform can possibly allow an attacker to execute malicious javascript code in the application session or in database, via remote injection, while rendering content in a web page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:18:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1188 | Rizone Soft Notepad3 Encryption Passphrase denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1188</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Rizone Soft Notepad3 1.0.2.350. Affected is an unknown function of the component Encryption Passphrase Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252678 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 18:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1187 | Munsoft Easy Outlook Express Recovery Registration Key denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1187</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Munsoft Easy Outlook Express Recovery 2.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Registration Key Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-252677 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1186 | Munsoft Easy Archive Recovery Registration Key denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1186</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Munsoft Easy Archive Recovery 2.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Registration Key Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252676. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23635 | AntiSamy malicious input can provoke XSS when preserving comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23635</link><description>AntiSamy is a library for performing fast, configurable cleansing of HTML coming from untrusted sources. Prior to 1.7.5, there is a potential for a mutation XSS (mXSS) vulnerability in AntiSamy caused by flawed parsing of the HTML being sanitized. To be subject to this vulnerability the `preserveComments` directive must be enabled in your policy file. As a result, certain crafty inputs can result in elements in comment tags being interpreted as executable when using AntiSamy's sanitized output. Patched in AntiSamy 1.7.5 and later.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24560 | Vyper external calls can overflow return data to return input buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24560</link><description>Vyper is a Pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum Virtual Machine. When calls to external contracts are made, we write the input buffer starting at byte 28, and allocate the return buffer to start at byte 0 (overlapping with the input buffer). When checking RETURNDATASIZE for dynamic types, the size is compared only to the minimum allowed size for that type, and not to the returned value's length. As a result, malformed return data can cause the contract to mistake data from the input buffer for returndata.  When the called contract returns invalid ABIv2 encoded data, the calling contract can read different invalid data (from the dirty buffer) than the called contract returned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45036 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45036</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45037 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45037</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47561 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47561</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47562 | Photo Station</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47562</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Photo Station 6.4.2 ( 2023/12/15 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47564 | Qsync Central</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47564</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment for critical resource vulnerability has been reported to affect Qsync Central. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to read or modify the resource via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
Qsync Central 4.4.0.15 ( 2024/01/04 ) and later
Qsync Central 4.3.0.11 ( 2024/01/11 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47566 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47566</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47567 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47567</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47568 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47568</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to inject malicious code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50359 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50359</link><description>An unchecked return value vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow local authenticated administrators to place the system in a state that could lead to a crash or other unintended behaviors via unspecified vectors.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-29504 | Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition, versions before 4.1.5, and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain a Missing Requi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-29504</link><description>Dell BSAFE Crypto-C Micro Edition, versions before 4.1.5, and Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain a Missing Required Cryptographic Step Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32967 | QTS, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32967</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to bypass intended access restrictions via a network.
QTS 5.x, QuTS hero are not affected.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39297 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39297</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39302 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39302</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39303 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39303</link><description>An improper authentication vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41273 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41273</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41274 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41274</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41275 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41275</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41276 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41276</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41277 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41277</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41278 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41278</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41279 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41279</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41280 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41280</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.2.2533 build 20230926 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.2.2534 build 20230927 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41281 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41281</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41282 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41282</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41283 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41283</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41292 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41292</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45025 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45025</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45026 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45026</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45027 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45027</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45028 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45028</link><description>An uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to launch a denial-of-service (DoS) attack via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.5.2645 build 20240116 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.5.2647 build 20240118 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45035 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45035</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24470 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update_post.php co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24470</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the update_post.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-21575 | Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain an Observable Timing Discrepancy Vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-21575</link><description>Dell BSAFE Micro Edition Suite, versions before 4.5.2, contain an Observable Timing Discrepancy Vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24160 | MRCMS 3.0 contains a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /admin/system/saveinfo.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24160</link><description>MRCMS 3.0 contains a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /admin/system/saveinfo.do.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:12:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51838 | Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51838</link><description>Ylianst MeshCentral 1.1.16 suffers from Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24161 | MRCMS 3.0 contains an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in /admin/file/edit.do as the incoming path parameter is not filtered.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24161</link><description>MRCMS 3.0 contains an Arbitrary File Read vulnerability in /admin/file/edit.do as the incoming path parameter is not filtered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22107 | An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method systemSettingsDnsDataAction at /opt/webapp/src/AppBundle/Control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22107</link><description>An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method systemSettingsDnsDataAction at /opt/webapp/src/AppBundle/Controller/React/SystemSettingsController.php is vulnerable to command injection via the /old/react/v1/api/system/dns/data endpoint. An authenticated attacker can abuse it to inject an arbitrary command and compromise the platform.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22108 | An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method setTermsHashAction at /opt/webapp/lib/PureApi/CCApi.class.php is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22108</link><description>An issue was discovered in GTB Central Console 15.17.1-30814.NG. The method setTermsHashAction at /opt/webapp/lib/PureApi/CCApi.class.php is vulnerable to an unauthenticated SQL injection via /ccapi.php that an attacker can abuse in order to change the Administrator password to a known value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24757 | open-irs .env Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24757</link><description>open-irs is an issue response robot that reponds to issues in the installed repository. The `.env` file was accidentally uploaded when working with git actions. This problem is fixed in 1.0.1. Discontinuing all sensitive keys and turning into secrets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:43:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-34381 | Dell BSAFE SSL-J version 7.0 and all versions prior to 6.5, and Dell BSAFE Crypto-J versions prior to 6.2.6.1 contain an unmaintained third-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-34381</link><description>Dell BSAFE SSL-J version 7.0 and all versions prior to 6.5, and Dell BSAFE Crypto-J versions prior to 6.2.6.1 contain an unmaintained third-party component vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the compromise of the impacted system. This is a Critical vulnerability and Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1185 | Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1185</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Nsasoft NBMonitor Network Bandwidth Monitor 1.6.5.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-252675. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23831 | Privilege escalation through CSRF attack on &amp;#x27;setup.pl&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23831</link><description>LedgerSMB is a free web-based double-entry accounting system. When a LedgerSMB database administrator has an active session in /setup.pl, an attacker can trick the admin into clicking on a link which automatically submits a request to setup.pl without the admin's consent.  This request can be used to create a new user account with full application (/login.pl) privileges, leading to privilege escalation.  The vulnerability is patched in versions 1.10.30 and 1.11.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24029 | JFinalCMS 5.0.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via /admin/content/data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24029</link><description>JFinalCMS 5.0.0 is vulnerable to SQL injection via /admin/content/data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24760 | Mailcow Docker Container Exposure to Local Network</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24760</link><description>mailcow is a dockerized email package, with multiple containers linked in one bridged network. A security vulnerability has been identified in mailcow affecting versions &lt; 2024-01c. This vulnerability potentially allows attackers on the same subnet to connect to exposed ports of a Docker container, even when the port is bound to 127.0.0.1. The vulnerability has been addressed by implementing additional iptables/nftables rules. These rules drop packets for Docker containers on ports 3306, 6379, 8983, and 12345, where the input interface is not `br-mailcow` and the output interface is `br-mailcow`.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6387 | Incorrect buffer parsing in Bluetooth LE sample code may lead to buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6387</link><description>A potential buffer overflow exists in the Bluetooth LE HCI CPC sample application in the Gecko SDK which may result in a denial of service or remote code execution</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23824 | mailcow ipixel flood attack leads to Denial of Service in admin page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23824</link><description>mailcow is a dockerized email package, with multiple containers linked in one bridged network. The application is vulnerable to pixel flood attack, once the payload has been successfully uploaded in the logo the application goes slow and doesn't respond in the admin page. It is tested on the versions 2023-12a and prior and patched in version 2024-01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38273 | IBM Cloud Pak System information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38273</link><description>IBM Cloud Pak System 2.3.1.1, 2.3.2.0, and 2.3.3.7 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  260733.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47142 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47142</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 could allow an attacker on the organization's local network to escalate their privileges due to unauthorized API access.  IBM X-Force ID:  270267.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47144 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47144</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  270271.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6676 | Cross Site Request Forgery in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6676</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects CyberMath: from v1.4 before v1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0269 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0269</link><description>ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 7270 and below are vulnerable to the Authenticated SQL injection in File-Summary DrillDown. This issue has been fixed and released in version 7271.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47143 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47143</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.10 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers.  This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.  IBM X-Force ID:  270270.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1184 | Nsasoft Network Sleuth Registration denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Nsasoft Network Sleuth 3.0.0.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation leads to denial of service. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-252674 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47148 | IBM Storage Protect Plus Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47148</link><description>IBM Storage Protect Plus Server 10.1.0 through 10.1.15.2 Admin Console could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information due to improper validation of unsecured endpoints which could be used in further attacks against the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  270599.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6675 | Malicious File Upload in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6675</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects CyberMath: from v.1.4 before v.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6673 | Reflected XSS in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6673</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CyberMath: from v.1.4 before v.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0253 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0253</link><description>ManageEngine ADAudit Plus versions 7270 and below are vulnerable to the Authenticated SQL injection in home Graph-Data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6672 | Stored XSS in National Keep&amp;#x27;s CyberMath</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6672</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in National Keep Cyber Security Services CyberMath allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CyberMath: from v1.4 before v1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:43:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1201 | PanteraSoft HDD Health search path or unquoted item vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1201</link><description>Search path or unquoted item vulnerability in HDD Health affecting versions 4.2.0.112 and earlier. This vulnerability could allow a local attacker to store a malicious executable file within the unquoted search path, resulting in privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0844 | The Popup More Popups, Lightboxes, and more popup modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in version 2.1.6 via th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0844</link><description>The Popup More Popups, Lightboxes, and more popup modules plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in version 2.1.6 via the ycfChangeElementData() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files ending with "Form.php" on the server , allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0963 | The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's CP_CALCULATED_FIELDS shortcode...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0963</link><description>The Calculated Fields Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's CP_CALCULATED_FIELDS shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.52 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied 'location' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50488 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.0406.435.4120 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50488</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v23.0406.435.4120 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51820 | An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v.2.3.38.12558 allows a physically proximate attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51820</link><description>An issue in Blurams Lumi Security Camera (A31C) v.2.3.38.12558 allows a physically proximate attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24388 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS versions v4.6.2 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24388</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in XunRuiCMS versions v4.6.2 and before, allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information via crafted malicious requests to the background login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51072 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the NOC component of Nagios XI version up to and including 2024R1 allows low-privileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51072</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the NOC component of Nagios XI version up to and including 2024R1 allows low-privileged users to execute malicious HTML or JavaScript code via the audio file upload functionality from the Operation Center section. This allows any authenticated user to execute arbitrary JavaScript code on behalf of other users, including the administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39611 | An issue in Software FX Chart FX 7 version 7.0.4962.20829 allows attackers to enumerate and read files from the local filesystem by sending ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39611</link><description>An issue in Software FX Chart FX 7 version 7.0.4962.20829 allows attackers to enumerate and read files from the local filesystem by sending crafted web requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0338 | Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in XAMPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0338</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been found in XAMPP affecting version 8.2.4 and earlier. An attacker could execute arbitrary code through a long file debug argument that controls the Structured Exception Handler (SEH).</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23895 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Cups Easy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23895</link><description>A vulnerability has been reported in Cups Easy (Purchase &amp; Inventory), version 1.0, whereby user-controlled inputs are not sufficiently encoded, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability via /cupseasylive/locationcreate.php, in the locationid parameter. Exploitation of this vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted URL to an authenticated user and steal their session cookie credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48645 | An issue was discovered in the Archibus app 4.0.3 for iOS. It uses a local database that is synchronized with a Web central server instance ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48645</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Archibus app 4.0.3 for iOS. It uses a local database that is synchronized with a Web central server instance every time the application is opened, or when the refresh button is used. There is a SQL injection in the search work request feature in the Maintenance module of the app. This allows performing queries on the local database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:17:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22851 | Directory Traversal Vulnerability in LiveConfig before v.2.5.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22851</link><description>Directory Traversal Vulnerability in LiveConfig before v.2.5.2 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request to the /static/ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24524 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the add_menu.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24524</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in flusity-CMS v.2.33, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the add_menu.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22281 | Zip Slip Vulnerability in B&amp;amp;R Automation Studio Project Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22281</link><description>: Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Relative Path Traversal.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24682 | Automation Studio and PVI Multiple unquoted service path vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24682</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio, B&amp;R Industrial Automation NET/PVI allows Target Programs with Elevated Privileges.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.6, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7 SP, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6 SP, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4 SP; NET/PVI: from 4.0 through 4.6, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:20:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-24681 | Automation Studio and PVI Multiple incorrect permission assignments for services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-24681</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.6.0 through 4.6.X, from 4.7.0 before 4.7.7 SP, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.6 SP, from 4.9.0 before 4.9.4 SP.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-22282 | RCE in B&amp;amp;R Automation Studio with crafted project files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-22282</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in B&amp;R Industrial Automation Automation Studio allows Local Execution of Code.This issue affects Automation Studio: from 4.0 through 4.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21780 | Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. Processing a specially crafted command may result in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21780</link><description>Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. Processing a specially crafted command may result in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Note that the affected products are no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23978 | Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. By processing invalid values, arbitrary code may be exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23978</link><description>Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in HOME SPOT CUBE2 V102 and earlier. By processing invalid values, arbitrary code may be executed. Note that the affected products are no longer supported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43756 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43756</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker causes information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45734 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45734</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow an adjacent attacker arbitrary code execution through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49118 | Dsoftbus has an out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49118</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker causes information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0285 | Dsoftbus has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0285</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21845 | Dsoftbus has an integer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21845</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause heap overflow through  integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21851 | Dsoftbus has an integer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21851</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause heap overflow through  integer overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21860 | Dsoftbus has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21860</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions

allow an adjacent attacker arbitrary code execution in any apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21863 | Dsoftbus has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21863</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1143 | Central Dogma versions prior to 0.64.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), which could allow for the leakage of user sessions and s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1143</link><description>Central Dogma versions prior to 0.64.0 is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting (XSS), which could allow for the leakage of user sessions and subsequent authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 06:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46045 | Graphviz 2.36 before 10.0.0 has an out-of-bounds read via a crafted config6a file. NOTE: exploitability may be uncommon because this file is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46045</link><description>Graphviz 2.36 before 10.0.0 has an out-of-bounds read via a crafted config6a file. NOTE: exploitability may be uncommon because this file is typically owned by root.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1047 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1047</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the register_reference() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.28. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the connected API keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1162 | The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1162</link><description>The Orbit Fox by ThemeIsle plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.10.29. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the register_reference() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers  to update the connected API keys via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21485 | Versions of the package dash-core-components before 2.13.0; all versions of the package dash-core-components; versions of the package dash b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21485</link><description>Versions of the package dash-core-components before 2.13.0; all versions of the package dash-core-components; versions of the package dash before 2.15.0; all versions of the package dash-html-components; versions of the package dash-html-components before 2.0.16 are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when the href of the a tag is controlled by an adversary. An authenticated attacker who stores a view that exploits this vulnerability could steal the data that's visible to another user who opens that view - not just the data already included on the page, but they could also, in theory, make additional requests and access other data accessible to this user. In some cases, they could also steal the access tokens of that user, which would allow the attacker to act as that user, including viewing other apps and resources hosted on the same server.&#13;&#13;**Note:**&#13;&#13;This is only exploitable in Dash apps that include some mechanism to store user input to be reloaded by a different user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24482 | Aprktool before 2.9.3 on Windows allows ../ and /.. directory traversal.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24482</link><description>Aprktool before 2.9.3 on Windows allows ../ and /.. directory traversal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0685 | The Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Second Order SQL Injection...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0685</link><description>The Ninja Forms Contact Form – The Drag and Drop Form Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Second Order SQL Injection via the email address value submitted through forms in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject SQL in their email address that will append additional into the already existing query when an administrator triggers a personal data export.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1073 | The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'filter_array' parameter in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1073</link><description>The SlimStat Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'filter_array' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38020 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App log injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38020</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow an authenticated user to manipulate output written to log files.  IBM X-Force ID:  260576.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38019 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App directory traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38019</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to traverse directories on the system. An attacker could send a specially crafted URL request containing "dot dot" sequences (/../) to view arbitrary files on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  260575.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38263 | IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App improper access controls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38263</link><description>IBM SOAR QRadar Plugin App 1.0 through 5.0.3 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  260577.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40744 | IBM Aspera Faspex cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40744</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.6 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.  IBM X-Force ID:  236441.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46159 | IBM Storage Ceph denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46159</link><description>IBM Storage Ceph 5.3z1, 5.3z5, and 6.1z1 could allow an authenticated user on the network to cause a denial of service from RGW.  IBM X-Force ID:  268906.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22320 | IBM Operational Decision Manager code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22320</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.10.3, 8.10.4, 8.10.5.1, 8.11, 8.11.0.1, and 8.12.0.1 could allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by an unsafe deserialization. By sending specially crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM.  IBM X-Force ID:  279146.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22319 | IBM Operational Decision Manager LDAP injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22319</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.10.3, 8.10.4, 8.10.5.1, 8.11, 8.11.0.1, and 8.12.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to conduct an LDAP injection. By sending a request with a specially crafted request, an attacker could exploit this vulnerability to inject unsanitized content into the LDAP filter.  IBM X-Force ID:  279145.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22533 | Before Beetl v3.15.12, the rendering template has a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability. When the incoming template is contr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22533</link><description>Before Beetl v3.15.12, the rendering template has a server-side template injection (SSTI) vulnerability. When the incoming template is controllable, it will be filtered by the DefaultNativeSecurityManager blacklist. Because blacklist filtering is not strict, the blacklist can be bypassed, leading to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32333 | IBM Maximo Asset Management improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32333</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 could allow a remote attacker to log into the admin panel due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  255073.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22779 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kihron ServerRPExposer v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22779</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in Kihron ServerRPExposer v.1.0.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the loadServerPack in ServerResourcePackProviderMixin.java.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46344 | A vulnerability in Solar-Log Base 15 Firmware 6.0.1 Build 161, and possibly other Solar-Log Base products, allows an attacker to escalate th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46344</link><description>A vulnerability in Solar-Log Base 15 Firmware 6.0.1 Build 161, and possibly other Solar-Log Base products, allows an attacker to escalate their privileges by exploiting a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the switch group function under /#ilang=DE&amp;b=c_smartenergy_swgroups in the web portal. The vulnerability can be exploited to gain the rights of an installer or PM, which can then be used to gain administrative access to the web portal and execute further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48792 | Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the report export option.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48792</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the report export option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22899 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the syncNtpTime func...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22899</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the syncNtpTime function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22900 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setNetworkCardIn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22900</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the setNetworkCardInfo function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22901 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to use default MYSQL credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22901</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to use default MYSQL credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22902 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to be configured with default root credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22902</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to be configured with default root credentials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22903 | Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the deleteUpdateAPK ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22903</link><description>Vinchin Backup &amp; Recovery v7.2 was discovered to contain an authenticated remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the deleteUpdateAPK function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23746 | Miro Desktop 0.8.18 on macOS allows Electron code injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23746</link><description>Miro Desktop 0.8.18 on macOS allows Electron code injection.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 02:05:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48793 | Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 allows SQL Injection in the aggregate report feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48793</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine ADAudit Plus through 7250 allows SQL Injection in the aggregate report feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50328 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50328</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 may allow a remote attacker to view session identifiers passed via URL query strings.  IBM X-Force ID:  275110.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50934 | IBM PowerSC improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50934</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses single-factor authentication which can lead to unnecessary risk of compromise when compared with the benefits of a dual-factor authentication scheme.  IBM X-Force ID:  275114.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50935 | IBM PowerSC forced browsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50935</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 fails to properly restrict access to a URL or resource, which may allow a remote attacker to obtain unauthorized access to application functionality and/or resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  275115.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50938 | IBM PowerSC clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50938</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 could allow a remote attacker to hijack the clicking action of the victim. By persuading a victim to visit a malicious Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to hijack the victim's click actions and possibly launch further attacks against the victim.  IBM X-Force ID:  275128.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50941 | IBM PowerSC session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50941</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 does not provide logout functionality, which could allow an authenticated user to gain access to an unauthorized user using session fixation.  IBM X-Force ID:  275131.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50962 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50962</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 MFA does not implement the "HTTP Strict Transport Security" (HSTS) web security policy mechanism.  IBM X-Force ID:  276004.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50327 | IBM PowerSC weak security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50327</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses insecure HTTP methods which could allow a remote attacker to perform unauthorized file request modification.  IBM X-Force ID:  275109.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50936 | IBM PowerSC session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50936</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 does not invalidate session after logout which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.  IBM X-Force ID:  275116.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50940 | IBM PowerSC cross-resource origin sharing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50940</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses Cross-Origin Resource Sharing (CORS) which could allow an attacker to carry out privileged actions and retrieve sensitive information as the domain name is not being limited to only trusted domains.  IBM X-Force ID:  275130.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50326 | IBM PowerSC information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50326</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.  IBM X-Force ID:  275107.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50933 | IBM PowerSC HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50933</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.  IBM X-Force ID:  275113.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50937 | IBM PowerSC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50937</link><description>IBM PowerSC 1.3, 2.0, and 2.1 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.  IBM X-Force ID:  275117.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21399 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21399</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>