<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:13:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-49488 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openfiler ESA v2.99.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49488</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Openfiler ESA v2.99.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the nic parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49494 | DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component select_media_post_wangEdi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49494</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7.111 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component select_media_post_wangEditor.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49796 | MindsDB Arbitrary File Write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49796</link><description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a limited file write vulnerability in `file.py` Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:46:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49490 | XunRuiCMS v4.5.5 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49490</link><description>XunRuiCMS v4.5.5 was discovered to contain a reflective cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the component /admin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5955 | Contact Form Email &amp;lt; 1.3.44 - Editor+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5955</link><description>The Contact Form Email WordPress plugin before 1.3.44 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5749 | EmbedPress &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5749</link><description>The EmbedPress WordPress plugin before 3.9.2 does not sanitise and escape user input before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5750 | EmbedPress &amp;lt; 3.9.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5750</link><description>The EmbedPress WordPress plugin before 3.9.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page containing a specific content, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5757 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt; 2.1.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5757</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding WordPress plugin before 2.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5907 | File Manager &amp;lt; 6.3 - Admin+ Arbitrary OS File/Folder Access + Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5907</link><description>The File Manager WordPress plugin before 6.3 does not restrict the file managers root directory, allowing an administrator to set a root outside of the WordPress root directory, giving access to system files and directories even in a multisite setup, where site administrators should not be allowed to modify the sites files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5940 | WP Not Login Hide &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5940</link><description>The WP Not Login Hide (WPNLH) WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6035 | EazyDocs &amp;lt; 2.3.4 - Subscriber + SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6035</link><description>The EazyDocs WordPress plugin before 2.3.4 does not properly sanitize and escape "data" parameter before using it in an SQL statement via an AJAX action, which could allow any authenticated users, such as subscribers, to perform SQL Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49795 | MindsDB Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49795</link><description>MindsDB connects artificial intelligence models to real time data. Versions prior to 23.11.4.1 contain a server-side request forgery vulnerability in `file.py`. This can lead to limited information disclosure. Users should use MindsDB's `staging` branch or v23.11.4.1, which contain a fix for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 19:10:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48715 | Tuleap vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting on the edition page of a release</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48715</link><description>Tuleap is an open source suite to improve management of software developments and collaboration. Prior to version 15.2.99.103 or Tuleap Community Edition and prior to versions 15.2-4 and 15.1-8 of Tuleap Enterprise Edition, the name of the releases are not properly escaped on the edition page of a release. A malicious user with the ability to create a FRS release could force a victim having write permissions in the FRS to execute uncontrolled code. Tuleap Community Edition 15.2.99.103, Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.2-4, and Tuleap Enterprise Edition 15.1-8 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6679 | Kernel: null pointer dereference in dpll_pin_parent_pin_set() in drivers/dpll/dpll_netlink.c</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6679</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability was found in dpll_pin_parent_pin_set() in drivers/dpll/dpll_netlink.c in the Digital Phase Locked Loop (DPLL) subsystem in the  Linux kernel. This issue could be exploited to trigger a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6538 | System Management Unit (SMU) versions prior to 14.8.7825.01, used to manage Hitachi Vantara NAS products is susceptible to unintended information disclosure via unprivileged access to SMU configuration backup data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6538</link><description>SMU versions prior to 14.8.7825.01 are susceptible to unintended information disclosure, through URL manipulation. Authenticated users in Storage, Server or combined Server+Storage administrative roles are able to access SMU configuration backup, that would normally be barred to those specific administrative roles.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:57:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6194 | In Eclipse Memory Analyzer versions 0.7 to 1.14.0, report definition XML files are not filtered to prohibit
document type definition (DTD) r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6194</link><description>In Eclipse Memory Analyzer versions 0.7 to 1.14.0, report definition XML files are not filtered to prohibit
document type definition (DTD) references to external entities.
This means that if a user chooses to use a malicious report definition XML file containing an external entity reference
to generate a report then Eclipse Memory Analyzer may access external files or URLs defined via a DTD in the report definition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6671 | Cross-Site Request Forgery on OPEN JOURNAL SYSTEMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6671</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered on OJS, that consists in a CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) attack that forces an end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they're currently authenticated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49417 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setOpModeCfg.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49417</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 has a stack overflow vulnerability via setOpModeCfg.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49418 | TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022has a stack overflow vulnerability via setIpPortFilterRules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49418</link><description>TOTOLink A7000R V9.1.0u.6115_B20201022has a stack overflow vulnerability via setIpPortFilterRules.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6186 | Link targets allow arbitrary script execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6186</link><description>Insufficient macro permission validation of The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows an attacker to execute built-in macros without warning.

In affected versions LibreOffice supports hyperlinks with macro or similar built-in command targets that can be executed when activated without warning the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:18:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6185 | Improper input validation enabling arbitrary Gstreamer pipeline injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6185</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in GStreamer integration of The Document Foundation LibreOffice allows an attacker to execute arbitrary GStreamer plugins.

In affected versions the filename of the embedded video is not sufficiently escaped when passed to GStreamer enabling an attacker to run arbitrary gstreamer plugins depending on what plugins are installed on the target system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49964 | An issue was discovered in Hyland Alfresco Community Edition through 7.2.0. By inserting malicious content in the folder.get.html.ftl file, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49964</link><description>An issue was discovered in Hyland Alfresco Community Edition through 7.2.0. By inserting malicious content in the folder.get.html.ftl file, an attacker may perform SSTI (Server-Side Template Injection) attacks, which can leverage FreeMarker exposed objects to bypass restrictions and achieve RCE (Remote Code Execution). NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-12873.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 07:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5500 | Frauscher: FDS102 for FAdC/FAdCi remote code execution vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5500</link><description>This vulnerability allows an remote attacker with low privileges to misuse Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') to gain full control of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 07:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49355 | decToString in decNumber/decNumber.c in jq 88f01a7 has a one-byte out-of-bounds write via the " []-1.2e-1111111111" input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49355</link><description>decToString in decNumber/decNumber.c in jq 88f01a7 has a one-byte out-of-bounds write via the " []-1.2e-1111111111" input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 06:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6181 | An oversight in BCB handling of reboot reason that allows for persistent code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6181</link><description>An oversight in BCB handling of reboot reason that allows for persistent code execution</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48417 | Missing Permission checks resulting in unauthorized access and Manipulation in KeyChainActivity Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48417</link><description>Missing Permission checks resulting in unauthorized access and Manipulation in KeyChainActivity Application</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48424 | U-Boot shell vulnerability resulting in Privilege escalation in a production device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48424</link><description>U-Boot shell vulnerability resulting in Privilege escalation in a production device</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48425 | U-Boot vulnerability resulting in persistent Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48425</link><description>U-Boot vulnerability resulting in persistent Code Execution</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6659 | Campcodes Web-Based Student Clearance System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6659</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Web-Based Student Clearance System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /libsystem/login.php. The manipulation of the argument student leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247367.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:14:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50465 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Monica (aka MonicaHQ) 4.0.0 via an SVG document uploaded by an authenticated use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50465</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Monica (aka MonicaHQ) 4.0.0 via an SVG document uploaded by an authenticated user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6658 | SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6658</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ajax-api.php?action=save_attendance. The manipulation of the argument class_id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 23:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50463 | The caddy-geo-ip (aka GeoIP) middleware through 0.6.0 for Caddy 2, when trust_header X-Forwarded-For is used, allows attackers to spoof thei...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50463</link><description>The caddy-geo-ip (aka GeoIP) middleware through 0.6.0 for Caddy 2, when trust_header X-Forwarded-For is used, allows attackers to spoof their source IP address via an X-Forwarded-For header, which may bypass a protection mechanism (trusted_proxy directive in reverse_proxy or IP address range restrictions).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 22:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6657 | SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System student_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6657</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Simple Student Attendance System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /modals/student_form.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247365 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6656 | DeepFaceLab DFLJPG.py deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6656</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in DeepFaceLab pretrained DF.wf.288res.384.92.72.22. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file DFLIMG/DFLJPG.py. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247364. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48614 | Special:Ask in Semantic MediaWiki before 4.0.2 allows Reflected XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48614</link><description>Special:Ask in Semantic MediaWiki before 4.0.2 allows Reflected XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50453 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. It uses the public endpoint /api/v1/signshow for its login screen. This endpoint returns int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50453</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. It uses the public endpoint /api/v1/signshow for its login screen. This endpoint returns internal configuration data of user object attributes, such as selectable values, which should not be visible to the public.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50454 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. In several subsystems, SSL/TLS was used to establish connections to external services withou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50454</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. In several subsystems, SSL/TLS was used to establish connections to external services without proper validation of hostname and certificate authority. This is exploitable by man-in-the-middle attackers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50455 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. Due to lack of rate limiting in the "email address verification" feature, an attacker could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50455</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. Due to lack of rate limiting in the "email address verification" feature, an attacker could send many requests for a known address to cause Denial Of Service (generation of many emails, which would also spam the victim).</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50456 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. An attacker can trigger phishing links in generated notification emails via a crafted first ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50456</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. An attacker can trigger phishing links in generated notification emails via a crafted first or last name.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50457 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. When listing tickets linked to a knowledge base answer, or knowledge base answers of a ticke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50457</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.2.0. When listing tickets linked to a knowledge base answer, or knowledge base answers of a ticket, a user could see entries for which they lack permissions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5868 | Postgresql: memory disclosure in aggregate function calls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5868</link><description>A memory disclosure vulnerability was found in PostgreSQL that allows remote users to access sensitive information by exploiting certain aggregate function calls with 'unknown'-type arguments. Handling 'unknown'-type values from string literals without type designation can disclose bytes, potentially revealing notable and confidential information. This issue exists due to excessive data output in aggregate function calls, enabling remote users to read some portion of system memory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5869 | Postgresql: buffer overrun from integer overflow in array modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5869</link><description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL that allows authenticated database users to execute arbitrary code through missing overflow checks during SQL array value modification. This issue exists due to an integer overflow during array modification where a remote user can trigger the overflow by providing specially crafted data. This enables the execution of arbitrary code on the target system, allowing users to write arbitrary bytes to memory and extensively read the server's memory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5870 | Postgresql: role pg_signal_backend can signal certain superuser processes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5870</link><description>A flaw was found in PostgreSQL involving the pg_cancel_backend role that signals background workers, including the logical replication launcher, autovacuum workers, and the autovacuum launcher. Successful exploitation requires a non-core extension with a less-resilient background worker and would affect that specific background worker only. This issue may allow a remote high privileged user to launch a denial of service (DoS) attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:13:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50449 | JFinalCMS 5.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to read files via ../ Directory Traversal in the /common/down/file fileKey parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50449</link><description>JFinalCMS 5.0.0 could allow a remote attacker to read files via ../ Directory Traversal in the /common/down/file fileKey parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50446 | An issue was discovered in Mullvad VPN Windows app before 2023.6-beta1. Insufficient permissions on a directory allow any local unprivileged...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50446</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mullvad VPN Windows app before 2023.6-beta1. Insufficient permissions on a directory allow any local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 17:07:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6655 | Hongjing e-HR Login Interface loadhistroyorgtree sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6655</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Hongjing e-HR 2020. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /w_selfservice/oauthservlet/%2e./.%2e/general/inform/org/loadhistroyorgtree of the component Login Interface. The manipulation of the argument parentid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247358 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:45:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6654 | PHPEMS Session Data session.cls.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPEMS 6.x/7.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality in the library lib/session.cls.php of the component Session Data Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247357 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:12:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6653 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System Create a new Subject subject.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/subject.php of the component Create a new Subject. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247346 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6652 | code-projects Matrimonial Site register.php register sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Matrimonial Site 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function register of the file /register.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247345 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6651 | code-projects Matrimonial Site sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Matrimonial Site 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /auth/auth.php?user=1. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247344.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 11:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6650 | SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System login.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument cashier leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247343.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6649 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata with the input &lt;script&gt;alert(5)&lt;/script&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-247342 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6648 | PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Nipah Virus Testing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file password-recovery.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-247341 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 08:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6647 | AMTT HiBOS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in AMTT HiBOS 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation of the argument Type leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-247340. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 07:09:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50431 | sec_attest_info in drivers/accel/habanalabs/common/habanalabs_ioctl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.6.5 allows an information leak to user s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50431</link><description>sec_attest_info in drivers/accel/habanalabs/common/habanalabs_ioctl.c in the Linux kernel through 6.6.5 allows an information leak to user space because info-&gt;pad0 is not initialized.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 22:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50430 | The Goodix Fingerprint Device, as shipped in Dell Inspiron 15 computers, does not follow the Secure Device Connection Protocol (SDCP) when e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50430</link><description>The Goodix Fingerprint Device, as shipped in Dell Inspiron 15 computers, does not follow the Secure Device Connection Protocol (SDCP) when enrolling via Linux, and accepts an unauthenticated configuration packet to select the Windows template database, which allows bypass of Windows Hello authentication by enrolling an attacker's fingerprint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 22:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6646 | linkding cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6646</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in linkding 1.23.0. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation of the argument q leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.23.1 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-247338 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early, responded in a very professional manner and immediately released a fixed version of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 21:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50429 | IzyBat Orange casiers before 20230803_1 allows getEnsemble.php ensemble SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50429</link><description>IzyBat Orange casiers before 20230803_1 allows getEnsemble.php ensemble SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 21:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50428 | In Bitcoin Core through 26.0 and Bitcoin Knots before 25.1.knots20231115, datacarrier size limits can be bypassed by obfuscating data as cod...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50428</link><description>In Bitcoin Core through 26.0 and Bitcoin Knots before 25.1.knots20231115, datacarrier size limits can be bypassed by obfuscating data as code (e.g., with OP_FALSE OP_IF), as exploited in the wild by Inscriptions in 2022 and 2023.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 19:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46899 | SyncTrayzor 1.1.29 enables CEF (Chromium Embedded Framework) remote debugging, allowing a local attacker to control the application.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46899</link><description>SyncTrayzor 1.1.29 enables CEF (Chromium Embedded Framework) remote debugging, allowing a local attacker to control the application.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 18:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47254 | An OS Command Injection in the CLI interface on DrayTek Vigor167 version 5.2.2, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47254</link><description>An OS Command Injection in the CLI interface on DrayTek Vigor167 version 5.2.2, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary system commands and escalate privileges via any account created within the web interface.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 07:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46932 | Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GPAC version 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46932</link><description>Heap Buffer Overflow vulnerability in GPAC version 2.3-DEV-rev617-g671976fcc-master, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and cause a denial of service (DoS) via str2ulong class in src/media_tools/avilib.c in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5756 | The Digital Publications by Supsystic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5756</link><description>The Digital Publications by Supsystic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.7.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the AJAX action handler. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute AJAX actions via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6120 | The Welcart e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.6 via the upload_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6120</link><description>The Welcart e-Commerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.6 via the upload_certificate_file function. This makes it possible for administrators to upload .pem or .crt files to arbitrary locations on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28873 | An XSS issue in wiki and discussion pages in Seafile 9.0.6 allows attackers to inject JavaScript into the Markdown editor.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28873</link><description>An XSS issue in wiki and discussion pages in Seafile 9.0.6 allows attackers to inject JavaScript into the Markdown editor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28874 | The next parameter in the /accounts/login endpoint of Seafile 9.0.6 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary sites.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28874</link><description>The next parameter in the /accounts/login endpoint of Seafile 9.0.6 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary sites.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28869 | Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers read the contents of arbitrary files on the operating system...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28869</link><description>Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers read the contents of arbitrary files on the operating system by creating a symbolic link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28870 | Insecure File Permissions in Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allow attackers to write to configuration files ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28870</link><description>Insecure File Permissions in Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allow attackers to write to configuration files from low-privileged user accounts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28871 | Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers to read registry information of the operating system by crea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28871</link><description>Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers to read registry information of the operating system by creating a symbolic link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28868 | Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files on the operating system by creatin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28868</link><description>Support Assistant in NCP Secure Enterprise Client before 12.22 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files on the operating system by creating a symbolic link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 06:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47465 | An issue in GPAC v.2.2.1 and before allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the ctts_box_read function of file src/is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47465</link><description>An issue in GPAC v.2.2.1 and before allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via the ctts_box_read function of file src/isomedia/box_code_base.c.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47722 | IBM API Connect information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47722</link><description>IBM API Connect V10.0.5.3 and V10.0.6.0 stores user credentials in browser cache which can be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  271912.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28523 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28523</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 12.10 and 14.10 onsmsync is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking which could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code.  IBM X-Force ID:  250753.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28526 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28526</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 12.10 and 14.10 archecker is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking which could allow a local user to cause a segmentation fault.  IBM X-Force ID:  251204.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28527 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28527</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 12.10 and 14.10 cdr is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking which could allow a local user to cause a segmentation fault. IBM X-Force ID: 251206.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-25835 | Micro Focus ArcSight Management Center Remote Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-25835</link><description>A potential vulnerability has been identified in Micro Focus ArcSight Management Center. The vulnerability could be remotely exploited resulting in stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6394 | Quarkus: graphql operations over websockets bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6394</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. This issue occurs when receiving a request over websocket with no role-based permission specified on the GraphQL operation, Quarkus processes the request without authentication despite the endpoint being secured. This can allow an attacker to access information and functionality outside of normal granted API permissions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 02:04:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49797 | Local Privilege Escalation in pyinstaller on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49797</link><description>PyInstaller bundles a Python application and all its dependencies into a single package. A PyInstaller built application, elevated as a privileged process, may be tricked by an unprivileged attacker into deleting files the unprivileged user does not otherwise have access to. A user is affected if **all** the following are satisfied: 1. The user runs an application containing either `matplotlib` or `win32com`. 2. The application is ran as administrator (or at least a user with higher privileges than the attacker). 3. The user's temporary directory is not locked to that specific user (most likely due to `TMP`/`TEMP` environment variables pointing to an unprotected, arbitrary, non default location). Either: A. The attacker is able to very carefully time the replacement of a temporary file with a symlink. This switch must occur exactly between `shutil.rmtree()`'s builtin symlink check and the deletion itself B: The application was built with Python 3.7.x or earlier which has no protection against Directory Junctions links. The vulnerability has been addressed in PR #7827 which corresponds to `pyinstaller &gt;= 5.13.1`. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 01:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>