<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:10:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-0182 | SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal Admin Login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0182</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249440.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50094 | reNgine through 2.0.2 allows OS Command Injection if an adversary has a valid session ID. The attack places shell metacharacters in an api/t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50094</link><description>reNgine through 2.0.2 allows OS Command Injection if an adversary has a valid session ID. The attack places shell metacharacters in an api/tools/waf_detector/?url= string. The commands are executed as root via subprocess.check_output.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50096 | STMicroelectronics STSAFE-A1xx middleware before 3.3.7 allows MCU code execution if an adversary has the ability to read from and write to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50096</link><description>STMicroelectronics STSAFE-A1xx middleware before 3.3.7 allows MCU code execution if an adversary has the ability to read from and write to the I2C bus. This is caused by an StSafeA_ReceiveBytes buffer overflow in the X-CUBE-SAFEA1 Software Package for STSAFE-A sample applications (1.2.0), and thus can affect user-written code that was derived from a published sample application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0181 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Admin Panel admin_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0181</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_user.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname/Username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249433 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 16:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5877 | affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt; 3.4.3 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5877</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit WordPress plugin before 3.4.3 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to it's affiliate-toolkit-starter/tools/atkp_imagereceiver.php endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URL's, including RFC1918 private addresses, leading to a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6000 | Popup Builder &amp;lt; 4.2.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6000</link><description>The Popup Builder WordPress plugin before 4.2.3 does not prevent simple visitors from updating existing popups, and injecting raw JavaScript in them, which could lead to Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6037 | WP TripAdvisor Review Slider &amp;lt; 11.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6037</link><description>The WP TripAdvisor Review Slider WordPress plugin before 11.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6064 | PayHere Payment Gateway &amp;lt; 2.2.12 - Unauthenticated Log Data Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6064</link><description>The PayHere Payment Gateway WordPress plugin before 2.2.12 automatically creates publicly-accessible log files containing sensitive information when transactions occur.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6113 | WP Staging (Free &amp;lt; 3.1.3, Pro &amp;lt; 5.1.3) - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6113</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin before 3.1.3 and WP STAGING Pro WordPress Backup Plugin before 5.1.3 do not prevent visitors from leaking key information about ongoing backups processes, allowing unauthenticated attackers to download said backups later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6271 | Backup Migration Staging &amp;lt; 1.3.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6271</link><description>The Backup Migration WordPress plugin before 1.3.6 stores in-progress backups information in easy to find, publicly-accessible files, which may allow attackers monitoring those to leak sensitive information from the site's backups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6421 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.2.83 - Unauthenticated Protected File Download Password Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6421</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.2.83 does not protect file download's passwords, leaking it upon receiving an invalid one.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6485 | Html5 Video Player &amp;lt; 2.5.19 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6485</link><description>The Html5 Video Player WordPress plugin before 2.5.19 does not sanitise and escape some of its player settings, which combined with missing capability checks around the plugin could allow any authenticated users, such as low as subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks against high privilege users like admins</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21732 | FlyCms through abbaa5a allows XSS via the permission management feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21732</link><description>FlyCms through abbaa5a allows XSS via the permission management feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51503 | WordPress WooCommerce Payments Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.2 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51503</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Automattic WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo.This issue affects WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo: from n/a through 6.9.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51423 | WordPress WebinarIgnition Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.05.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51423</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Saleswonder Team Webinar Plugin: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition.This issue affects Webinar Plugin: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition: from n/a through 3.05.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51469 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51469</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51547 | WordPress Fluent Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Fluent Support – WordPress Helpdesk and Customer Support Ticket Plugin.This issue affects Fluent Support – WordPress Helpdesk and Customer Support Ticket Plugin: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52131 | WordPress Page Generator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WP Zinc Page Generator.This issue affects Page Generator: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52132 | WordPress WP Adminify Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jewel Theme WP Adminify.This issue affects WP Adminify: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52133 | WordPress Most And Least Read Posts Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.16 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WhileTrue Most And Least Read Posts Widget.This issue affects Most And Least Read Posts Widget: from n/a through 2.5.16.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52134 | WordPress GEO my WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eyal Fitoussi GEO my WordPress.This issue affects GEO my WordPress: from n/a through 4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52185 | WordPress Everest Backup Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52185</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Everestthemes Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin.This issue affects Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7193 | MTab Bookmark Installation install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7193</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MTab Bookmark up to 1.2.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file public/install.php of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249395. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7191 | S-CMS reg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. This affects an unknown part of the file member/reg.php. The manipulation of the argument M_login/M_email leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249393 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7190 | S-CMS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7190</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/ad.php?action=ad. The manipulation of the argument A_text/A_url/A_contact leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249392. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7189 | S-CMS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7189</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /s/index.php?action=statistics. The manipulation of the argument lid leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249391. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7188 | Shipping 100 Fahuo100 login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shipping 100 Fahuo100 up to 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file member/login.php. The manipulation of the argument M_pwd leads to sql injection. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249390 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7187 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=ie8 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7186 | 7-card Fakabao notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file member/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 13:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7185 | 7-card Fakabao wxpay_notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file shop/wxpay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249387. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7184 | 7-card Fakabao notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file shop/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7183 | 7-card Fakabao alipay_notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7183</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file shop/alipay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249385 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49777 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49777</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52180 | WordPress Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52180</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Really Simple Plugins Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes.This issue affects Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes: from n/a through 8.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39157 | WordPress JetElements For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.10 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39157</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetElements For Elementor.This issue affects JetElements For Elementor: from n/a through 2.6.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52181 | WordPress Theme per user Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52181</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Presslabs Theme per user.This issue affects Theme per user: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52182 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52182</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6094 | OnCell G3150A-LTE Series: Web Server Transmits Cleartext Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6094</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OnCell G3150A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.3 and prior.  The vulnerability results from a lack of protection for sensitive information during transmission. An attacker eavesdropping on the traffic between the web browser and server may obtain sensitive information. 

This type of attack could be executed to gather sensitive information or to facilitate a subsequent attack against the target.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6093 | OnCell G3150A-LTE Series: clickhacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6093</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OnCell G3150A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.3 and prior.  The vulnerability result from incorrectly restricts frame objects, which lead to user confusion about which interface the user is interacting with.

This vulnerability may lead attacker to trick user into interacting with the application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7130 | code-projects College Notes Gallery login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects College Notes Gallery 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249133 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 09:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46901 | examples/6lbr/apps/6lbr-webserver/httpd.c in CETIC-6LBR (aka 6lbr) 1.5.0 has a strcat stack-based buffer overflow via a request for a long U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46901</link><description>examples/6lbr/apps/6lbr-webserver/httpd.c in CETIC-6LBR (aka 6lbr) 1.5.0 has a strcat stack-based buffer overflow via a request for a long URL over a 6LoWPAN network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 07:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52286 | Tencent tdsqlpcloud through 1.8.5 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to discover database credentials via an index.php/api/install/get_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52286</link><description>Tencent tdsqlpcloud through 1.8.5 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to discover database credentials via an index.php/api/install/get_db_info request, a related issue to CVE-2023-42387.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 07:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52284 | Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime (aka WebAssembly Micro Runtime or WAMR) before 1.3.0 can have an "double free or corruption" error for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52284</link><description>Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime (aka WebAssembly Micro Runtime or WAMR) before 1.3.0 can have an "double free or corruption" error for a valid WebAssembly module because push_pop_frame_ref_offset is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 06:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46900 | Sympa before 6.2.62 relies on a cookie parameter for certain security objectives, but does not ensure that this parameter exists and has an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46900</link><description>Sympa before 6.2.62 relies on a cookie parameter for certain security objectives, but does not ensure that this parameter exists and has an unpredictable value. Specifically, the cookie parameter is both a salt for stored passwords and an XSS protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52277 | Royal RoyalTSX before 6.0.2.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (Heap Memory Corruption and application crash) or possibly have ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52277</link><description>Royal RoyalTSX before 6.0.2.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (Heap Memory Corruption and application crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact via a long hostname in an RTSZ file, if the victim clicks on Test Connection. This occurs during SecureGatewayHost object processing in RAPortCheck.createNWConnection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 03:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52275 | Gallery3d on Tecno Camon X CA7 devices allows attackers to view hidden images by navigating to data/com.android.gallery3d/.privatealbum/.enc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52275</link><description>Gallery3d on Tecno Camon X CA7 devices allows attackers to view hidden images by navigating to data/com.android.gallery3d/.privatealbum/.encryptfiles and guessing the correct image file extension.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 02:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52269 | MDaemon SecurityGateway through 9.0.3 allows XSS via a crafted Message Content Filtering rule. This might allow domain administrators to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52269</link><description>MDaemon SecurityGateway through 9.0.3 allows XSS via a crafted Message Content Filtering rule. This might allow domain administrators to conduct attacks against global administrators.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 01:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52266 | ehttp 1.0.6 before 17405b9 has an epoll_socket.cpp read_func use-after-free. An attacker can make many connections over a short time to trig...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52266</link><description>ehttp 1.0.6 before 17405b9 has an epoll_socket.cpp read_func use-after-free. An attacker can make many connections over a short time to trigger this.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 23:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52267 | ehttp 1.0.6 before 17405b9 has a simple_log.cpp _log out-of-bounds-read during error logging for long strings.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52267</link><description>ehttp 1.0.6 before 17405b9 has a simple_log.cpp _log out-of-bounds-read during error logging for long strings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 23:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52265 | IDURAR (aka idurar-erp-crm) through 2.0.1 allows stored XSS via a PATCH request with a crafted JSON email template in the /api/email/update ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52265</link><description>IDURAR (aka idurar-erp-crm) through 2.0.1 allows stored XSS via a PATCH request with a crafted JSON email template in the /api/email/update data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 22:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52264 | The beesblog (aka Bees Blog) component before 1.6.2 for thirty bees allows Reflected XSS because controllers/front/post.php sharing_url is m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52264</link><description>The beesblog (aka Bees Blog) component before 1.6.2 for thirty bees allows Reflected XSS because controllers/front/post.php sharing_url is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 22:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52263 | Brave Browser before 1.59.40 does not properly restrict the schema for WebUI factory and redirect. This is related to browser/brave_content_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52263</link><description>Brave Browser before 1.59.40 does not properly restrict the schema for WebUI factory and redirect. This is related to browser/brave_content_browser_client.cc and browser/ui/webui/brave_web_ui_controller_factory.cc.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 19:04:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52262 | outdoorbits little-backup-box (aka Little Backup Box) before f39f91c allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because the PHP extra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52262</link><description>outdoorbits little-backup-box (aka Little Backup Box) before f39f91c allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because the PHP extract function is used for untrusted input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6998 | Lockscreen bypass in eWeLink App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6998</link><description>Improper privilege management vulnerability in CoolKit Technology eWeLink on Android and iOS allows application lockscreen bypass.This issue affects eWeLink before 5.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7181 | Muyun DedeBIZ Add Attachment unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7181</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Muyun DedeBIZ up to 6.2.12 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Add Attachment Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249368. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7180 | Tongda OA 2017 delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7180</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tongda OA 2017 up to 11.9 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file general/project/proj/delete.php. The manipulation of the argument PROJ_ID_STR leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 11.10 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249367. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7179 | Campcodes Online College Library System HTTP POST Request category_row.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7179</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online College Library System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/category_row.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249366 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49299 | Apache DolphinScheduler: Arbitrary js execute as root for authenticated users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49299</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache DolphinScheduler. An authenticated user can cause arbitrary, unsandboxed javascript to be executed on the server.This issue affects Apache DolphinScheduler: until 3.1.9.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.1.9, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50110 | TestLink through 1.9.20 allows type juggling for authentication bypass because === is not used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50110</link><description>TestLink through 1.9.20 allows type juggling for authentication bypass because === is not used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7178 | Campcodes Online College Library System HTTP POST Request book_row.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7178</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Online College Library System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/book_row.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249365 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:38:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50589 | Grupo Embras GEOSIAP ERP v2.2.167.02 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the codLogin parameter on the login page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50589</link><description>Grupo Embras GEOSIAP ERP v2.2.167.02 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the codLogin parameter on the login page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50651 | TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /cgi-bin/c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50651</link><description>TOTOLINK X6000R v9.4.0cu.852_B20230719 was discovered to contain a remote command execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7177 | Campcodes Online College Library System HTTP POST Request book_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7177</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online College Library System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/book_add.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument category leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249364.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50578 | Mingsoft MCMS v5.2.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the categoryType parameter at /content/list.do.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50578</link><description>Mingsoft MCMS v5.2.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the categoryType parameter at /content/list.do.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7176 | Campcodes Online College Library System HTTP POST Request return_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7176</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online College Library System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/return_add.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument student leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249363.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51133 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRoute.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51133</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRoute.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51135 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formPasswordSetup.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51135</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formPasswordSetup.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:30:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51136 | TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRebootSchedule.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51136</link><description>TOTOLINK X2000R Gh v1.0.0-B20230221.0948.web was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the function formRebootSchedule.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:30:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50550 | layui up to v2.74 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the data-content parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50550</link><description>layui up to v2.74 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the data-content parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7175 | Campcodes Online College Library System HTTP POST Request borrow_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online College Library System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/borrow_add.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument student leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249362 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 13:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7173 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7173</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file registration.php. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249357 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25096 | MdAlAmin-aol Own Health Record logout.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25096</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MdAlAmin-aol Own Health Record 0.1-alpha/0.2-alpha/0.3-alpha/0.3.1-alpha. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file includes/logout.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 0.4-alpha is able to address this issue. The patch is named 58b413aa40820b49070782c786c526850ab7748f. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249191.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:34:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7172 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System Admin Dashboard sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7172</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Admin Dashboard. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249356.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 09:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52257 | LogoBee 0.2 allows updates.php?id= XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52257</link><description>LogoBee 0.2 allows updates.php?id= XSS.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 07:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52252 | Unified Remote 3.13.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary Lua code because of a wildcarded Access-Control-Allow-Origin for the Remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52252</link><description>Unified Remote 3.13.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary Lua code because of a wildcarded Access-Control-Allow-Origin for the Remote upload endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 05:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41544 | SSTI injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot version 3.5.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted HTTP request to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41544</link><description>SSTI injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot version 3.5.3, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted HTTP request to the /jmreport/loadTableData component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 03:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46486 | A lack of pointer-validation logic in the __scone_dispatch component of SCONE before v5.8.0 for Intel SGX allows attackers to access sensiti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46486</link><description>A lack of pointer-validation logic in the __scone_dispatch component of SCONE before v5.8.0 for Intel SGX allows attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46487 | Improper initialization of x87 and SSE floating-point configuration registers in the __scone_entry component of SCONE before 5.8.0 for Intel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46487</link><description>Improper initialization of x87 and SSE floating-point configuration registers in the __scone_entry component of SCONE before 5.8.0 for Intel SGX allows a local attacker to compromise the execution integrity of floating-point operations in an enclave or access sensitive information via side-channel analysis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38023 | An issue was discovered in SCONE Confidential Computing Platform before 5.8.0 for Intel SGX. Lack of pointer-alignment logic in __scone_disp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38023</link><description>An issue was discovered in SCONE Confidential Computing Platform before 5.8.0 for Intel SGX. Lack of pointer-alignment logic in __scone_dispatch and other entry functions allows a local attacker to access unauthorized information, aka an "AEPIC Leak."</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38021 | An issue was discovered in Fortanix EnclaveOS Confidential Computing Manager (CCM) Platform before 3.32 for Intel SGX. Lack of pointer-align...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38021</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fortanix EnclaveOS Confidential Computing Manager (CCM) Platform before 3.32 for Intel SGX. Lack of pointer-alignment validation logic in entry functions allows a local attacker to access unauthorized information. This relates to the enclave_ecall function and system call layer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38022 | An issue was discovered in Fortanix EnclaveOS Confidential Computing Manager (CCM) Platform before 3.29 for Intel SGX. Insufficient pointer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38022</link><description>An issue was discovered in Fortanix EnclaveOS Confidential Computing Manager (CCM) Platform before 3.29 for Intel SGX. Insufficient pointer validation allows a local attacker to access unauthorized information. This relates to strlen and sgx_is_within_user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:28:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41542 | SQL injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot version 3.5.3, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41542</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot version 3.5.3, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the jmreport/qurestSql component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41543 | SQL injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot v3.5.3, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41543</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in jeecg-boot v3.5.3, allows remote attackers to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the component /sys/replicate/check.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 02:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>