<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 06:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-8502 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide changepass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8502</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /changepass.php. The manipulation of the argument ups leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 06:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8501 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System action.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8501</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /insert-and-view/action.php. The manipulation of the argument content leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 06:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8500 | code-projects Human Resource Integrated System action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8500</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Human Resource Integrated System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /insert-and-view/action.php. The manipulation of the argument content leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 05:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8499 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide cusfindambulence2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8499</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /cusfindambulence2.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 05:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8498 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8498</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /cart/index.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 04:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52131 | The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via the background or text color field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52131</link><description>The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via the background or text color field.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52132 | The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via a title to the view event page.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52132</link><description>The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via a title to the view event page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52133 | The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via a title upon calendar import.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52133</link><description>The Mocca Calendar application before 2.15 for XWiki allows XSS via a title upon calendar import.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8496 | projectworlds Online Admission System viewform.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8496</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /viewform.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 03:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8497 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide cusfindphar2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8497</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /cusfindphar2.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 03:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8495 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System edit_admin_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8495</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_admin_query.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 02:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54349 | In iperf before 3.19.1, iperf_auth.c has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54349</link><description>In iperf before 3.19.1, iperf_auth.c has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54350 | In iperf before 3.19.1, iperf_auth.c has a Base64Decode assertion failure and application exit upon a malformed authentication attempt.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54350</link><description>In iperf before 3.19.1, iperf_auth.c has a Base64Decode assertion failure and application exit upon a malformed authentication attempt.</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54351 | In iperf before 3.19.1, net.c has a buffer overflow when --skip-rx-copy is used (for MSG_TRUNC in recv).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54351</link><description>In iperf before 3.19.1, net.c has a buffer overflow when --skip-rx-copy is used (for MSG_TRUNC in recv).</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 02:12:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54955 | OpenNebula Community Edition (CE) before 7.0.0 and Enterprise Edition (EE) before 6.10.3 have a critical FireEdge race condition that can le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54955</link><description>OpenNebula Community Edition (CE) before 7.0.0 and Enterprise Edition (EE) before 6.10.3 have a critical FireEdge race condition that can lead to full account takeover. By exploiting this, an unauthenticated attacker can obtain a valid JSON Web Token (JWT) belonging to a legitimate user without knowledge of their credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8494 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System delete_student.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8494</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete_student.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8493 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System edit_student_query.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8493</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_student_query.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32253 | Kernel: deadlock in ksmbd_find_crypto_ctx()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32253</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd component. A deadlock is triggered by sending multiple concurrent session setup requests, possibly leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32255 | Kernel: memory leak via ksmbd session setup request with unknown ntlmssp message type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32255</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd component. A memory leak can occur if a client sends a session setup request with an unknown NTLMSSP message type,  potentially leading to resource exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23284 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause a stack buffer overflow. A suc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23284</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause a stack buffer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23285 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where it allows a guest to access global resources. A successful e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23285</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where it allows a guest to access global resources. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23290 | NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a guest could get global GPU metrics which may be influenced...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23290</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a guest could get global GPU metrics which may be influenced by work in other VMs. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:40:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23278 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might cause an improper index validation by issuing a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23278</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker might cause an improper index validation by issuing a call with crafted parameters. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to data tampering  or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23279 | NVIDIA .run Installer for Linux and Solaris contains a vulnerability where an attacker could use a race condition to escalate privileges. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23279</link><description>NVIDIA .run Installer for Linux and Solaris contains a vulnerability where an attacker could use a race condition to escalate privileges. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, denial of service, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23281 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker with local unprivileged access that can win a race conditio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23281</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker with local unprivileged access that can win a race condition might be able to trigger a use-after-free error. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, escalation of privileges, data tampering, denial of service, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23283 | NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux-style hypervisors contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause st...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23283</link><description>NVIDIA vGPU software for Linux-style hypervisors contains a vulnerability in the Virtual GPU Manager, where a malicious guest could cause stack buffer overflow. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution, denial of service, escalation of privileges, information disclosure, or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23286 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could read invalid memory. A successful exploit o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23286</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability where an attacker could read invalid memory. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23287 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may access sensitive system-level information. A successful...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23287</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may access sensitive system-level information. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23288 | NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability  where an attacker may cause an exposure of sensitive system information with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23288</link><description>NVIDIA GPU Display Driver for Windows contains a vulnerability  where an attacker may cause an exposure of sensitive system information with local unprivileged system access. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to Information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23276 | NVIDIA Installer for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may be able to escalate privileges. A successful exploit of this vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23276</link><description>NVIDIA Installer for Windows contains a vulnerability where an attacker may be able to escalate privileges. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to escalation of privileges, denial of service, code execution, information disclosure and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23277 | NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode driver, where an attacker could access memory outsid...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23277</link><description>NVIDIA Display Driver for Linux and Windows contains a vulnerability in the kernel mode driver, where an attacker could access memory outside bounds permitted under normal use cases. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to denial of service, data tampering, or information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8471 | projectworlds Online Admission System adminlogin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8471</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adminlogin.php. The manipulation of the argument a_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 18:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8470 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System deleteroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8470</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/deleteroom.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 17:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8469 | SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System deletegallery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8469</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/deletegallery.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8468 | code-projects Wazifa System reset.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8468</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /controllers/reset.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7500 | Ocean Social Sharing &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7500</link><description>The Ocean Social Sharing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via social icon titles in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7710 | Brave Conversion Engine (PRO) &amp;lt;= 0.7.7 - Authentication Bypass to Administrator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7710</link><description>The Brave Conversion Engine (PRO) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 0.7.7. This is due to the plugin not properly restricting a claimed identity while authenticating with Facebook. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8467 | code-projects Wazifa System regcontrol.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8467</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /controllers/regcontrol.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 11:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6722 | BitFire &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6722</link><description>The BitFire Security – Firewall, WAF, Bot/Spam Blocker, Login Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 4.5 via the bitfire_* directory that automatically gets created and stores potentially sensitive files without any access restrictions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from various files like config.ini, debug.log, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8488 | Ultimate Addons for Elementor (Formerly Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder) &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8488</link><description>The Ultimate Addons for Elementor (Formerly Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_hfe_compatibility_option_callback ()function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update the compatibility option setting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:46:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6832 | All in One Time Clock Lite – Tracking Employee Time Has Never Been Easier &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6832</link><description>The All in One Time Clock Lite – Tracking Employee Time Has Never Been Easier plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'nonce' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:49:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8391 | Magic Edge – Lite &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8391</link><description>The Magic Edge – Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8399 | Mmm Unity Loader &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via attributes Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8399</link><description>The Mmm Unity Loader plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘attributes’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8400 | Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8400</link><description>The Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8466 | code-projects Online Farm System forgot_passfarmer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8466</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /forgot_passfarmer.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 08:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4588 | 360 Photo Spheres &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4588</link><description>The 360 Photo Spheres plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'sphere' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6626 | ShortPixel Adaptive Images – WebP, AVIF, CDN, Image Optimization &amp;lt;= 3.10.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via API URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6626</link><description>The ShortPixel Adaptive Images – WebP, AVIF, CDN, Image Optimization plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the API URL Setting in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6754 | SEO Metrics &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6754</link><description>The SEO Metrics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization checks in both the seo_metrics_handle_connect_button_click() AJAX handler and the seo_metrics_handle_custom_endpoint() function in versions 1.0.5 through 1.0.15. Because the AJAX action only verifies a nonce, without checking the caller’s capabilities, a subscriber-level user can retrieve the token and then access the custom endpoint to obtain full administrator cookies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8152 | WP CTA – Call To Action Plugin, Sticky CTA, Sticky Buttons &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Sticky Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8152</link><description>The WP CTA – Call To Action Plugin, Sticky CTA, Sticky Buttons plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'update_cta_status' and 'change_sticky_sidebar_name' functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the status of a sticky and update the name displayed in the back-end WP CTA Dashboard.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8212 | Medical Addon for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Typewriter Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8212</link><description>The Medical Addon for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Typewriter widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8317 | Custom Word Cloud &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via angle Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8317</link><description>The Custom Word Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘angle’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 07:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8146 | Qi Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via TypeOut Text Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8146</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's TypeOut Text widget in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 04:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7694 | Woffice Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.26 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7694</link><description>The Woffice Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the woffice_file_manager_delete() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.26. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 04:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6076 | CVE-2025-6076</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6076</link><description>Partner Software's Partner Software application and Partner Web application do not sanitize files uploaded on the "reports" tab, allowing an authenticated attacker to upload a malicious file and compromise the device. By default, the software runs as SYSTEM, heightening the severity of the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6077 | CVE-2025-6077</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6077</link><description>Partner Software's Partner Software Product and corresponding Partner Web application use the same default username and password for the administrator account across all versions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6078 | CVE-2025-6078</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6078</link><description>Partner Software's Partner Software application and Partner Web application allows an authenticated user to add notes on the 'Notes' page when viewing a job but does not completely sanitize input, making it possible to add notes with HTML tags and JavaScript, enabling an attacker to add a note containing malicious JavaScript, leading to stored XSS (cross-site scripting).</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54782 | @nestjs/devtools-integration&amp;#x27;s CSRF to Sandbox Escape Allows for RCE against JS Developers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54782</link><description>Nest is a framework for building scalable Node.js server-side applications. In versions 0.2.0 and below, a critical Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability was discovered in the @nestjs/devtools-integration package. When enabled, the package exposes a local development HTTP server with an API endpoint that uses an unsafe JavaScript sandbox (safe-eval-like implementation). Due to improper sandboxing and missing cross-origin protections, any malicious website visited by a developer can execute arbitrary code on their local machine. The package adds HTTP endpoints to a locally running NestJS development server. One of these endpoints, /inspector/graph/interact, accepts JSON input containing a code field and executes the provided code in a Node.js vm.runInNewContext sandbox. This is fixed in version 0.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54790 | Files: Potential for SQL Injection through File Browse and List Operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54790</link><description>Files is a module for managing files inside spaces and user profiles. In versions 0.16.9 and below, Files does not have logic to prevent the exploitation of backend SQL queries without direct output, potentially allowing unauthorized data access. This is fixed in version 0.16.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54796 | Copyparty is vulnerable to Regex Denial of Service (ReDoS) attacks through &amp;quot;Recent Uploads&amp;quot; page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54796</link><description>Copyparty is a portable file server. Versions prior to 1.18.9, the filter parameter for the "Recent Uploads" page allows arbitrary RegExes. If this feature is enabled (which is the default), an attacker can craft a filter which deadlocks the server. This is fixed in version 1.18.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54386 | Traefik&amp;#x27;s Client Plugin is Vulnerable to Path Traversal, Arbitrary File Overwrites and Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54386</link><description>Traefik is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. In versions 2.11.27 and below, 3.0.0 through 3.4.4 and 3.5.0-rc1, a path traversal vulnerability was discovered in WASM Traefik’s plugin installation mechanism. By supplying a maliciously crafted ZIP archive containing file paths with ../ sequences, an attacker can overwrite arbitrary files on the system outside of the intended plugin directory. This can lead to remote code execution (RCE), privilege escalation, persistence, or denial of service. This is fixed in versions 2.11.28, 3.4.5 and 3.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54781 | Himmelblau leaks an Intune service access token in its logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54781</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. When debugging is enabled for Himmelblau in version 1.0.0, the himmelblaud_tasks service leaks an Intune service access token to the system journal. This short-lived token can be used to detect the host's Intune compliance status, and may permit additional administrative operations for the Intune host device (though the API for these operations is undocumented). This is fixed in version 1.1.0. To workaround this issue, ensure that Himmelblau debugging is disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54789 | Files is Vulnerable to Reflected Self-XSS through its File Move Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54789</link><description>Files is a module for managing files inside spaces and user profiles. In versions 0.16.9 and below, the File Move functionality does not contain logic that prevents injection of arbitrary JavaScript, which can lead to Browser JS code execution in the context of the user’s session. This is fixed in version 0.16.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54133 | Cursor&amp;#x27;s MCP Install Deeplink Does Not Show Arguments in its User-Dialog</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54133</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.17 through 1.2, there is a UI information disclosure vulnerability in Cursor's MCP (Model Context Protocol) deeplink handler, allowing attackers to execute 2-click arbitrary system commands through social engineering attacks. When users click malicious `cursor://anysphere.cursor-deeplink/mcp/install` links, the installation dialog does not show the arguments being passed to the command being run. If a user clicks a malicious deeplink, then examines the installation dialog and clicks through, the full command including the arguments will be executed on the machine. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54136 | Cursor&amp;#x27;s Modification of MCP Server Definitions Bypasses Manual Re-approvals</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54136</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions 1.2.4 and below, attackers can achieve remote and persistent code execution by modifying an already trusted MCP configuration file inside a shared GitHub repository or editing the file locally on the target's machine. Once a collaborator accepts a harmless MCP, the attacker can silently swap it for a malicious command (e.g., calc.exe) without triggering any warning or re-prompt. If an attacker has write permissions on a user's active branches of a source repository that contains existing MCP servers the user has previously approved, or allows an attacker has arbitrary file-write locally, the attacker can achieve arbitrary code execution. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54131 | Cursor bypasses its allow list to execute arbitrary commands</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54131</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions below 1.3, an attacker can bypass the allow list in auto-run mode with a backtick (`) or $(cmd). If a user has swapped Cursor from its default settings (requiring approval for every terminal call) to an allowlist, an attacker can execute arbitrary command execution outside of the allowlist without user approval. An attacker can trigger this vulnerability if chained with indirect prompt injection. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:15:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54132 | Cursor&amp;#x27;s Mermaid Diagram Tool is Vulnerable to an Arbitrary Image Fetch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54132</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. In versions below 1.3, Mermaid (which is used to render diagrams) allows embedding images which then get rendered by Cursor in the chat box. An attacker can use this to exfiltrate sensitive information to a third-party attacker controlled server through an image fetch after successfully performing a prompt injection. A malicious model (or hallucination/backdoor) might also trigger this exploit at will. This issue requires prompt injection from malicious data (web, image upload, source code) in order to exploit. In that case, it can send sensitive information to an attacker-controlled external server. This is fixed in version 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54424 | 1Panel Agent Bypasses Certificate Verification Leading to Arbitrary Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54424</link><description>1Panel is a web interface and MCP Server that manages websites, files, containers, databases, and LLMs on a Linux server. In versions 2.0.5 and below, the HTTPS protocol used for communication between the Core and Agent endpoints has incomplete certificate verification during certificate validation, leading to unauthorized interface access. Due to the presence of numerous command execution or high-privilege interfaces in 1Panel, this results in Remote Code Execution (RCE). This is fixed in version 2.0.6. The CVE has been translated from Simplified Chinese using GitHub Copilot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54792 | LocalSend is Vulnerable to Man-in-the-Middle Attacks, Leading to File Interception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54792</link><description>LocalSend is an open-source app to securely share files and messages with nearby devices over local networks without needing an internet connection. In versions 1.16.1 and below, a critical Man-in-the-Middle (MitM) vulnerability in the software's discovery protocol allows an unauthenticated attacker on the same local network to impersonate legitimate devices, silently intercepting, reading, and modifying any file transfer. This can be used to steal sensitive data or inject malware, like ransomware, into files shared between trusted users. The attack is hardly detectable and easy to implement, posing a severe and immediate security risk. This issue was fixed in version 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13978 | LibTIFF fax2ps tiff2pdf.c t2p_read_tiff_init null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13978</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF up to 4.7.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function t2p_read_tiff_init of the file tools/tiff2pdf.c of the component fax2ps. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The patch is named 2ebfffb0e8836bfb1cd7d85c059cd285c59761a4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 21:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10049 | Raidsonic NAS Devices Unauthenticated Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10049</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in multiple Raidsonic NAS devices—specifically tested on IB-NAS5220 and IB-NAS4220—via the unauthenticated timeHandler.cgi endpoint exposed through the web interface. The CGI script fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the timeZone parameter of a POST request, allowing remote attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 21:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10053 | ZPanel &amp;lt;= 10.0.0.2 htpasswd Module Username Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10053</link><description>A remote command execution vulnerability exists in ZPanel version 10.0.0.2 in its htpasswd module. When creating .htaccess files, the inHTUsername field is passed unsanitized to a system() call that invokes the system’s htpasswd binary. By injecting shell metacharacters into the username field, an authenticated attacker can execute arbitrary system commands. Exploitation requires a valid ZPanel account—such as one in the default Users, Resellers, or Administrators groups—but no elevated privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 21:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10057 | Synactis PDF In-The-Box ConnectToSynactic Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10057</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Synactis PDF In-The-Box ActiveX control (PDF_IN_1.ocx), specifically the ConnectToSynactis method. When a long string is passed to this method—intended to populate the ldCmdLine argument of a WinExec call—a strcpy operation overwrites a saved TRegistry class pointer on the stack. This allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of the user by enticing them to visit a malicious webpage that instantiates the vulnerable ActiveX control. The vulnerability was discovered via its use in third-party software such as Logic Print 2013.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 21:14:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10022 | Kloxo &amp;lt;= 6.1.12 Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10022</link><description>Kloxo versions 6.1.12 and earlier contain two setuid root binaries—lxsuexec and lxrestart—that allow local privilege escalation from uid 48. The lxsuexec binary performs a uid check and permits execution of arbitrary commands as root if the invoking user matches uid 48. This flaw enables attackers with Apache-level access to escalate privileges to root without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10044 | OpenEMR ≤ 4.1.1 SQL Injection Privilege Escalation and RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10044</link><description>An authenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in OpenEMR ≤ 4.1.1 Patch 14 that allows a low-privileged attacker to extract administrator credentials and subsequently escalate privileges. Once elevated, the attacker can exploit an unrestricted file upload flaw to achieve remote code execution, resulting in full compromise of the application and its host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10047 | MiniWeb &amp;lt;= Build 300 Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10047</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability exists in MiniWeb HTTP Server &lt;= Build 300 that allows unauthenticated remote attackers to upload arbitrary files to the server’s filesystem. By abusing the upload handler and crafting a traversal path, an attacker can place a malicious .exe in system32, followed by a .mof file in the WMI directory. This triggers execution of the payload with SYSTEM privileges via the Windows Management Instrumentation service. The exploit is only viable on Windows versions prior to Vista.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10048 | D-Link Devices command.php Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10048</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in various legacy D-Link routers—including DIR-300 rev B and DIR-600 (firmware ≤ 2.13 and ≤ 2.14b01, respectively)—due to improper input handling in the unauthenticated command.php endpoint. By sending specially crafted POST requests, a remote attacker can execute arbitrary shell commands with root privileges, allowing full takeover of the device. This includes launching services such as Telnet, exfiltrating credentials, modifying system configuration, and disrupting availability. The flaw stems from the lack of authentication and inadequate sanitation of the cmd parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10050 | D-Link Devices tools_vct.xgi Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10050</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in multiple D-Link routers—confirmed on DIR-300 rev A (v1.05) and DIR-615 rev D (v4.13)—via the authenticated tools_vct.xgi CGI endpoint. The web interface fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input in the pingIp parameter, allowing attackers with valid credentials to inject arbitrary shell commands. Exploitation enables full device compromise, including spawning a telnet daemon and establishing a root shell. The vulnerability is present in firmware versions that expose tools_vct.xgi and use the Mathopd/1.5p6 web server. No vendor patch is available, and affected models are end-of-life.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10051 | InstantCMS &amp;lt;= 1.6 Remote PHP Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10051</link><description>A remote PHP code execution vulnerability exists in InstantCMS version 1.6 and earlier due to unsafe use of eval() within the search view handler. Specifically, user-supplied input passed via the look parameter is concatenated into a PHP expression and executed without proper sanitation. A remote attacker can exploit this flaw by sending a crafted HTTP GET request with a base64-encoded payload in the Cmd header, resulting in arbitrary PHP code execution within the context of the web server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10055 | Havalite CMS Arbitary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10055</link><description>An unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in Havalite CMS version 1.1.7 (and possibly earlier) in the upload.php script. The application fails to enforce proper file extension validation and authentication checks, allowing remote attackers to upload malicious PHP files via a crafted multipart/form-data POST request. Once uploaded, the attacker can access the file directly under havalite/tmp/files/, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10058 | Linksys Routers apply.cgi Remote Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10058</link><description>An authenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in various Linksys router models (tested on WRT160Nv2) running firmware version v2.0.03 via the apply.cgi endpoint. The web interface fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input passed to the ping_size parameter during diagnostic operations. An attacker with valid credentials can inject arbitrary shell commands, enabling remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10059 | D-Link Routers tools_vct.htm OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10059</link><description>An authenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in various D-Link routers (tested on DIR-615H1 running firmware version 8.04) via the tools_vct.htm endpoint. The web interface fails to sanitize input passed from the ping_ipaddr parameter to the tools_vct.htm diagnostic interface, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary shell commands using backtick encapsulation. With default credentials, an attacker can exploit this blind injection vector to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10060 | Netgear Routers pppoe.cgi RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10060</link><description>An authenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in Netgear routers (tested on the DGN2200B model) firmware versions 1.0.0.36 and prior via the pppoe.cgi endpoint. A remote attacker with valid credentials can execute arbitrary commands via crafted input to the pppoe_username parameter. This flaw allows full compromise of the device and may persist across reboots unless configuration is restored.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10061 | Netgear Routers setup.cgi RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10061</link><description>An authenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in Netgear routers (tested on the DGN1000B model firmware versions 1.1.00.24 and 1.1.00.45) via the TimeToLive parameter in the setup.cgi endpoint. The vulnerability arises from improper input neutralization, enabling command injection through crafted POST requests. This flaw enables remote attackers to deploy payloads or manipulate system state post-authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10062 | Linksys Routers apply.cgi Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10062</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in Linksys router's web interface (tested on the E1500 model firmware versions 1.0.00, 1.0.04, and 1.0.05), specifically in the /apply.cgi endpoint. Authenticated attackers can exploit the next_page POST parameter to access arbitrary files outside the intended web root by injecting traversal sequences. This allows exposure of sensitive system files and configuration data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10063 | Netgear SPH200D &amp;lt;= 1.0.4.80 Path Traversal via HTTP GET</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10063</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in the Netgear SPH200D Skype phone firmware versions &lt;= 1.0.4.80 in its embedded web server. Authenticated attackers can exploit crafted GET requests to access arbitrary files outside the web root by injecting traversal sequences. This can expose sensitive system files and configuration data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10046 | Agnitum Outpost Internet Security Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10046</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Agnitum Outpost Internet Security 8.1 that allows an unprivileged user to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges. The flaw resides in the acs.exe component, which exposes a named pipe that accepts unauthenticated commands. By exploiting a directory traversal weakness in the pipe protocol, an attacker can instruct the service to load a malicious DLL from a user-controlled location. The DLL is then executed in the context of the privileged service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53012 | MaterialX&amp;#x27;s Lack of Import Depth Limit Leads to DoS (Denial-Of-Service) Via Stack Exhaustion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53012</link><description>MaterialX is an open standard for the exchange of rich material and look-development content across applications and renderers. In version 1.39.2, nested imports of MaterialX files can lead to a crash via stack memory exhaustion, due to the lack of a limit on the "import chain" depth. When parsing file imports, recursion is used to process nested files; however, there is no limit imposed to the depth of files that can be parsed by the library. By building a sufficiently deep chain of MaterialX files one referencing the next, it is possible to crash the process using the MaterialX library via stack exhaustion. This is fixed in version 1.39.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54564 | uploadsm in ChargePoint Home Flex 5.5.4.13 does not validate a user-controlled string for bz2 decompression, which allows command execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54564</link><description>uploadsm in ChargePoint Home Flex 5.5.4.13 does not validate a user-controlled string for bz2 decompression, which allows command execution as the nobody user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54574 | Squid&amp;#x27;s URN Handling can lead to Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54574</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web. In versions 6.3 and below, Squid is vulnerable to a heap buffer overflow and possible remote code execution attack when processing URN due to incorrect buffer management. This has been fixed in version 6.4. To work around this issue, disable URN access permissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54590 | webfinger.js is vulnerable to Blind SSRF attacks through localhost</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54590</link><description>webfinger.js is a TypeScript-based WebFinger client that runs in both browsers and Node.js environments. In versions 2.8.0 and below, the lookup function accepts user addresses for account checking. However, the ActivityPub specification requires preventing access to localhost services in production. This library does not prevent localhost access, only checking for hosts that start with "localhost" and end with a port. Users can exploit this by creating servers that send GET requests with controlled host, path, and port parameters to query services on the instance's host or local network, enabling blind SSRF attacks. This is fixed in version 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54593 | FreshRSS is vulnerable to RCE attacks by authenticated admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54593</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. In versions 1.26.1 and below, an authenticated administrator user can execute arbitrary code on the FreshRSS server by modifying the update URL to one they control, and gain code execution after running an update. After successfully executing code, user data including hashed passwords can be exfiltrated, the instance can be defaced when file permissions allow. Malicious code can be inserted into the instance to steal plaintext passwords, among others. This is fixed in version 1.26.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54595 | Pearcleaner&amp;#x27;s unauthenticated access to privileged XPC helper allows root command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54595</link><description>Pearcleaner is a free, source-available and fair-code licensed mac app cleaner. The PearcleanerHelper is a privileged helper tool bundled with the Pearcleaner application. It is registered and activated only after the user approves a system prompt to allow privileged operations. Upon approval, the helper is configured as a LaunchDaemon and runs with root privileges. In versions 4.4.0 through 4.5.1, the helper registers an XPC service (com.alienator88.Pearcleaner.PearcleanerHelper) and accepts unauthenticated connections from any local process. It exposes a method that executes arbitrary shell commands. This allows any local unprivileged user to escalate privileges to root once the helper is approved and active. This issue is fixed in version 4.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6011 | Timing Side-Channel in Vault’s Userpass Auth Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6011</link><description>A timing side channel in Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) userpass auth method allowed an attacker to distinguish between existing and non-existing users, and potentially enumerate valid usernames for Vault’s Userpass auth method. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6015 | Vault Login MFA Bypass of Rate Limiting and TOTP Code Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6015</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) login MFA rate limits could be bypassed and TOTP tokens could be reused. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49832 | Asterisk is Vulnerable to Remote DoS and possible RCE Attacks During Memory Allocation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49832</link><description>Asterisk is an open source private branch exchange and telephony toolkit. In versions up to and including 18.26.2, between 20.00.0 and 20.15.0, 20.7-cert6, 21.00.0, 22.00.0 through 22.5.0, there is a remote DoS and possible RCE condition in `asterisk/res/res_stir_shaken /verification.c` that can be exploited when an attacker can set an arbitrary Identity header, or STIR/SHAKEN is enabled, with verification set in the SIP profile associated with the endpoint to be attacked. This is fixed in versions 18.26.3, 20.7-cert6, 20.15.1, 21.10.1 and 22.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53009 | MaterialX Stack Overflow via Lack of MTLX XML Parsing Recursion Limit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53009</link><description>MaterialX is an open standard for the exchange of rich material and look-development content across applications and renderers. In versions 1.39.2 and below, when parsing an MTLX file with multiple nested nodegraph implementations, the MaterialX XML parsing logic can potentially crash due to stack exhaustion. An attacker could intentionally crash a target program that uses OpenEXR by sending a malicious MTLX file. This is fixed in version 1.39.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53010 | MaterialX&amp;#x27;s unchecked nodeGraph-&amp;gt;getOutput return is vulnerable to NULL Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53010</link><description>MaterialX is an open standard for the exchange of rich material and look-development content across applications and renderers. In version 1.39.2, when parsing shader nodes in a MTLX file, the MaterialXCore code accesses a potentially null pointer, which can lead to crashes with maliciously crafted files. An attacker could intentionally crash a target program that uses OpenEXR by sending a malicious MTLX file. This is fixed in version 1.39.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53011 | MaterialX is Vulnerable to NULL Pointer Dereference due to Unchecked implGraphOutput</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53011</link><description>MaterialX is an open standard for the exchange of rich material and look-development content across applications and renderers. In version 1.39.2, when parsing shader nodes in a MTLX file, the MaterialXCore code accesses a potentially null pointer, which can lead to crashes with maliciously crafted files. An attacker could intentionally crash a target program that uses MaterialX by sending a malicious MTLX file. This is fixed in version 1.39.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6004 | Vault Userpass and LDAP User Lockout Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6004</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) user lockout feature could be bypassed for Userpass and LDAP authentication methods. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2824 | IBM Operational Decision Manager HTTP open redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2824</link><description>IBM Operational Decision Manager 8.11.0.1, 8.11.1.0, 8.12.0.1, 9.0.0.1, and 9.5.0 could allow a remote attacker to conduct phishing attacks, using an open redirect attack. By persuading a victim to visit a specially crafted Web site, a remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to spoof the URL displayed to redirect a user to a malicious Web site that would appear to be trusted. This could allow the attacker to obtain highly sensitive information or conduct further attacks against the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6014 | Vault TOTP Secrets Engine Code Reuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6014</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise’s (“Vault”) TOTP Secrets Engine code validation endpoint is susceptible to code reuse within its validity period. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6037 | Vault Certificate Auth Method Did Not Validate Common Name For Non-CA Certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6037</link><description>Vault and Vault Enterprise (“Vault”) TLS certificate auth method did not correctly validate client certificates when configured with a non-CA certificate as [+trusted certificate+|https://developer.hashicorp.com/vault/api-docs/auth/cert#certificate]. In this configuration, an attacker may be able to craft a malicious certificate that could be used to impersonate another user. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32256 | Kernel: ksmbd race issue from smb2 close and logoff with multichannel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32256</link><description>A flaw was found in the Linux kernel's ksmbd component. A race condition between smb2 close operation and logoff in multichannel connections could result in a use-after-free issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5999 | Vault Root Namespace Operator May Elevate Token Privileges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5999</link><description>A privileged Vault operator with write permissions to the root namespace’s identity endpoint could escalate their own or another user’s token privileges to Vault’s root policy. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.0 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.0, 1.19.6, 1.18.11 and 1.16.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6000 | Arbitrary Remote Code Execution via Plugin Catalog Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6000</link><description>A privileged Vault operator within the root namespace with write permission to {{sys/audit}} may obtain code execution on the underlying host if a plugin directory is set in Vault’s configuration. Fixed in Vault Community Edition 1.20.1 and Vault Enterprise 1.20.1, 1.19.7, 1.18.12, and 1.16.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8472 | Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8472</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious Bluetooth device.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of vCard data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26316.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8473 | Alpine iLX-507 UPDM_wstpCBCUpdStart Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8473</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 UPDM_wstpCBCUpdStart Command Injection Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the UPDM_wstpCBCUpdStart function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26317.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8474 | Alpine iLX-507 CarPlay Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8474</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 CarPlay Stack-based Buffer Overflow Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the Apple CarPlay protocol. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26318.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8475 | Alpine iLX-507 AVRCP Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8475</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 AVRCP Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious Bluetooth device.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the AVRCP protocol. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26321.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8476 | Alpine iLX-507 TIDAL Improper Certificate Validation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8476</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 TIDAL Improper Certificate Validation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the TIDAL music streaming application. The issue results from improper certificate validation. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26322.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8477 | Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8477</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 vCard Parsing Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected Alpine iLX-507 devices. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must connect to a malicious Bluetooth device.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of vCard data. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-26324.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8480 | Alpine iLX-507 Command Injection Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8480</link><description>Alpine iLX-507 Command Injection Remote Code Execution. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Alpine iLX-507 devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the Tidal music streaming application. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26357.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50868 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the takeassessment2.php file of CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0. The Q4 POST parameter is not properl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50868</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the takeassessment2.php file of CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0. The Q4 POST parameter is not properly sanitized before being used in SQL queries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50869 | A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the qureydetails.php page of Institute-of-Current-Students 1.0, where the input ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50869</link><description>A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the qureydetails.php page of Institute-of-Current-Students 1.0, where the input fields for Query and Answer do not properly sanitize user input. Authenticated users can inject arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33118 | IBM QRadar SIEM cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33118</link><description>IBM QRadar SIEM 7.5 through 7.5.0 Update Pack 12 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50870 | Institute-of-Current-Students 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The myds GET parameter acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50870</link><description>Institute-of-Current-Students 1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the mydetailsstudent.php endpoint. The myds GET parameter accepts an email address as input and directly returns the corresponding student's personal information without validating the identity or permissions of the requesting user. This allows any authenticated or unauthenticated attacker to enumerate and retrieve sensitive student details by altering the email value in the request URL, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45778 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Language Sloth Web Application v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45778</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Language Sloth Web Application v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Description text field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45150 | Insecure permissions in LangChain-ChatGLM-Webui commit ef829 allows attackers to arbitrarily view and download sensitive files via supplying...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45150</link><description>Insecure permissions in LangChain-ChatGLM-Webui commit ef829 allows attackers to arbitrarily view and download sensitive files via supplying a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48074 | OpenEXR&amp;#x27;s Unbounded File Header Values can Lead to Out-Of-Memory Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48074</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In version 3.3.2, applications trust unvalidated dataWindow size values from file headers, which can lead to excessive memory allocation and performance degradation when processing malicious files. This is fixed in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51501 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the id parameter of the live_edit.module_settings API endpoint in Microweber CMS2.0 allows execution...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51501</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the id parameter of the live_edit.module_settings API endpoint in Microweber CMS2.0 allows execution of arbitrary JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51502 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Microweber CMS 2.0 via the layout parameter on the /admin/page/create page allows arbitrary JavaScri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51502</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Microweber CMS 2.0 via the layout parameter on the /admin/page/create page allows arbitrary JavaScript execution in the context of authenticated admin users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51504 | Microweber CMS 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)in the /projects/profile, homepage endpoint via the last name field.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51504</link><description>Microweber CMS 2.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)in the /projects/profile, homepage endpoint via the last name field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50472 | The modelscope/ms-swift library thru 2.6.1 is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution through deserialization of untrusted data within the `l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50472</link><description>The modelscope/ms-swift library thru 2.6.1 is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution through deserialization of untrusted data within the `load_model_meta()` function of the `ModelFileSystemCache()` class. Attackers can execute arbitrary code and commands by crafting a malicious serialized `.mdl` payload, exploiting the use of `pickle.load()` on data from potentially untrusted sources. This vulnerability allows for remote code execution (RCE) by deceiving victims into loading a seemingly harmless checkpoint during a normal training process, thereby enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code on the targeted machine. Note that the payload file is a hidden file, making it difficult for the victim to detect tampering. More importantly, during the model training process, after the `.mdl` file is loaded and executes arbitrary code, the normal training process remains unaffected'meaning the user remains unaware of the arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52390 | Saurus CMS Community Edition since commit d886e5b0 (2010-04-23) is vulnerable to a SQL Injection vulnerability in the `prepareSearchQuery()`...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52390</link><description>Saurus CMS Community Edition since commit d886e5b0 (2010-04-23) is vulnerable to a SQL Injection vulnerability in the `prepareSearchQuery()` method in `FulltextSearch.class.php`. The application directly concatenates user-supplied input (`$search_word`) into SQL queries without sanitization, allowing attackers to manipulate the SQL logic and potentially extract sensitive information or escalate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:22:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19144 | XML External Entity Injection vulnerability in Quantum DXi6702 2.3.0.3 (11449-53631 Build304) devices via rest/Users?action=authenticate.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19144</link><description>XML External Entity Injection vulnerability in Quantum DXi6702 2.3.0.3 (11449-53631 Build304) devices via rest/Users?action=authenticate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50460 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the ms-swift project version 3.3.0 due to unsafe deserialization in tests/run.py using...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50460</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the ms-swift project version 3.3.0 due to unsafe deserialization in tests/run.py using yaml.load() from the PyYAML library (versions = 5.3.1). If an attacker can control the content of the YAML configuration file passed to the --run_config parameter, arbitrary code can be executed during deserialization. This can lead to full system compromise. The vulnerability is triggered when a malicious YAML file is loaded, allowing the execution of arbitrary Python commands such as os.system(). It is recommended to upgrade PyYAML to version 5.4 or higher, and to use yaml.safe_load() to mitigate the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52361 | Insecure permissions in the script /etc/init.d/lighttpd in AK-Nord USB-Server-LXL Firmware v0.0.16 Build 2023-03-13 allows a locally authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52361</link><description>Insecure permissions in the script /etc/init.d/lighttpd in AK-Nord USB-Server-LXL Firmware v0.0.16 Build 2023-03-13 allows a locally authenticated low-privilege user to execute arbitrary commands with root privilege via editing this script which is executed with root-privileges on any interaction and on every system boot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44139 | Emlog Pro V2.5.7 is vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type via /emlog/admin/plugin.php?action=upload_zip</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44139</link><description>Emlog Pro V2.5.7 is vulnerable to Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type via /emlog/admin/plugin.php?action=upload_zip</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52327 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Restaurant Order System 1.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the payment.php file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52327</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Restaurant Order System 1.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the payment.php file</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45767 | jose v6.0.10 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45767</link><description>jose v6.0.10 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44976 | Hangzhou Shunwang Rentdrv2 before 2024-12-24 allows local users to terminate EDR processes and possibly have unspecified other impact via De...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44976</link><description>Hangzhou Shunwang Rentdrv2 before 2024-12-24 allows local users to terminate EDR processes and possibly have unspecified other impact via DeviceIoControl with control code 0x22E010, as exploited in the wild in October 2023.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46018 | CSC Pay Mobile App 2.19.4 (fixed in version 2.20.0) contains a vulnerability allowing users to bypass payment authorization by disabling Blu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46018</link><description>CSC Pay Mobile App 2.19.4 (fixed in version 2.20.0) contains a vulnerability allowing users to bypass payment authorization by disabling Bluetooth at a specific point during a transaction. This could result in unauthorized use of laundry services and potential financial loss.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41370 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41370</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb/html/view/acceso.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41371 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41371</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb_v4/integra/html/view/acceso.php</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41372 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41372</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/informe_campo_entrevistas.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41373 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41373</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/hislistadoacciones.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41374 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41374</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/hislistadoacciones.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41375 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41375</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/consultaincimails.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41376 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gandia Integra Total</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41376</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability has been found in Gandia Integra Total of TESI from version 2.1.2217.3 to v4.4.2236.1. The vulnerability allows an authenticated attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete databases through the 'idestudio' parameter in /encuestas/integraweb[_v4]/integra/html/view/consultacuotasred.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:43:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4684 | BlockSpare: Gutenberg Blocks &amp;amp; Patterns for Blogs, Magazines, Business Sites &amp;lt;= 3.2.13.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Carousel and Image Slider Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4684</link><description>The BlockSpare: Gutenberg Blocks &amp; Patterns for Blogs, Magazines, Business Sites – Post Grids, Sliders, Carousels, Counters, Page Builder &amp; Starter Site Imports, No Coding Needed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the HTML attributes of Image Carousel and Image Slider widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.13.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6228 | Sina Extension for Elementor &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `Sina Posts`, `Sina Blog Post` and `Sina Table` Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6228</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Header Builder, Footer Builter, Theme Builder, Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the `Sina Posts`, `Sina Blog Post` and `Sina Table` widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 11:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6398 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the IOMap64.sys driver of ASUS AI Suite 3. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6398</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the IOMap64.sys driver of ASUS AI Suite 3. The vulnerability can be triggered by a specially crafted input, which may lead to a system crash (BSOD). Refer to the '

Security Update for for AI Suite 3

' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:03:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8443 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8443</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8442 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide cussignup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8442</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cussignup.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8441 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide pharsignup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8441</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pharsignup.php. The manipulation of the argument phuname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8439 | code-projects Wazifa System updatesettings.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8439</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7646 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.3.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7646</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom script parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.10 even when the user does not have the unfiltered_html capability. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8438 | code-projects Wazifa System postpublish.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8438</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /controllers/postpublish.php. The manipulation of the argument post leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8437 | code-projects Kitchen Treasure userregistration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8437</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Kitchen Treasure 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /userregistration.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31716 | In bootloader, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31716</link><description>In bootloader, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5921 | SureForms &amp;lt; 1.7.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5921</link><description>The SureForms  WordPress plugin before 1.7.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against both authenticated and unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8454 | It was discovered that uscan, a tool to scan/watch upstream sources for new releases of software, included in devscripts (a collection of sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8454</link><description>It was discovered that uscan, a tool to scan/watch upstream sources for new releases of software, included in devscripts (a collection of scripts to make the life of a Debian Package maintainer easier), skips OpenPGP verification for files already downloaded even if a previous verification did fail.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8436 | projectworlds Online Admission System viewdoc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8436</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /viewdoc.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54939 | LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.3.1 has an lsquic_engine_packet_in memory leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54939</link><description>LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.3.1 has an lsquic_engine_packet_in memory leak.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4523 | IDonate 2.0.0 - 2.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via admin_donor_profile_view Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4523</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_donor_profile_view() function in versions 2.0.0 to 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose an administrator’s username, email address, and all donor fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7443 | BerqWP &amp;lt;= 2.2.42 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7443</link><description>The BerqWP – Automated All-In-One Page Speed Optimization for Core Web Vitals, Cache, CDN, Images, CSS, and JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation via the store_javascript_cache.php file in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.42. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7725 | Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal or Stripe, Social Share Buttons, OpenAI &amp;lt;= 26.1.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7725</link><description>The Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal or Stripe, Social Share Buttons, OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the comment feature in all versions up to, and including, 26.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7845 | Stratum – Elementor Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Advanced Google Maps and Image Hotspot Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7845</link><description>The Stratum – Elementor Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Google Maps and Image Hotspot widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8435 | code-projects Online Movie Streaming admin-control.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8435</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Movie Streaming 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-control.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to missing authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8434 | code-projects Online Movie Streaming admin.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8434</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Movie Streaming 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19145 | Quantum SuperLoader 3 V94.0 005E.0h devices allow attackers to access the hardcoded fa account because there are only 65536 possible passwor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19145</link><description>Quantum SuperLoader 3 V94.0 005E.0h devices allow attackers to access the hardcoded fa account because there are only 65536 possible passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53399 | In Sipwise rtpengine before 13.4.1.1, an origin-validation error in the endpoint-learning logic of the media-relay core allows remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53399</link><description>In Sipwise rtpengine before 13.4.1.1, an origin-validation error in the endpoint-learning logic of the media-relay core allows remote attackers to inject or intercept RTP/SRTP media streams via RTP packets (except when the relay is configured for strict source and learning disabled). Version 13.4.1.1 fixes the heuristic mode by limiting exposure to the first five packets, and introduces a recrypt flag that fully prevents SRTP attacks when both mitigations are enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5947 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Authentication Bypass via User Switch Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5947</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's cookie value prior to logging them in through the service_finder_switch_back() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as any user including admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8433 | code-projects Document Management System dell.php unlink path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Document Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function unlink of the file /dell.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5954 | Service Finder SMS System &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5954</link><description>The Service Finder SMS System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to the plugin not restricting user role selection at the time of registration through the aonesms_fn_savedata_after_signup() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as an administrator user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8431 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System add-boat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8431</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-boat.php. The manipulation of the argument boatname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>