<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-47812 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) on Special:RequestImportQueue when displaying request date in ImportDump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47812</link><description>ImportDump is an extension for mediawiki designed to automate user import requests. Anyone who can edit the interface strings of a wiki (typically administrators and interface admins) can embed XSS payloads in the messages for dates, and thus XSS anyone who views Special:RequestImportQueue. This issue has been patched in commit `d054b95` and all users are advised to apply this commit to their branch. Users unable to upgrade may either Prevent access to Special:RequestImportQueue on all wikis, except for the global wiki; and If an interface administrator (or equivalent) level protection is available (which is not provided by default) on the global wiki, protect the affected messages up to that level. This causes the XSS to be virtually useless as users with those rights can already edit Javascript pages. Or Prevent access to Special:RequestImportQueue altogether.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47815 | Cross-site Scripting in IncidentReporting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47815</link><description>IncidentReporting is a MediaWiki extension for moving incident reports from wikitext to database tables. There are a variety of Cross-site Scripting issues, though all of them require elevated permissions. Some are available to anyone who has the `editincidents` right, some are available to those who can edit interface messages (typically administrators and interface admins), and one is available to those who can edit LocalSettings.php. These issues have been addressed in commit `43896a4` and all users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should prevent access to the Special:IncidentReports page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47816 | Users can impersonate import requesters if their actor IDs coincide in ImportDump</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47816</link><description>ImportDump is a mediawiki extension designed to automate user import requests. A user's local actor ID is stored in the database to tell who made what requests. Therefore, if a user on another wiki happens to have the same actor ID as someone on the central wiki, the user on the other wiki can act as if they're the original wiki requester. This can be abused to create new comments, edit the request, and view the request if it's marked private. This issue has been addressed in commit `5c91dfc` and all users are advised to update. Users unable to update may disable the special page outside of their global wiki. See `miraheze/mw-config@e566499` for details on that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47763 | Wasmtime runtime crash when combining tail calls with trapping imports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47763</link><description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly. Wasmtime's implementation of WebAssembly tail calls combined with stack traces can result in a runtime crash in certain WebAssembly modules. The runtime crash may be undefined behavior if Wasmtime was compiled with Rust 1.80 or prior. The runtime crash is a deterministic process abort when Wasmtime is compiled with Rust 1.81 and later. WebAssembly tail calls are a proposal which relatively recently reached stage 4 in the standardization process. Wasmtime first enabled support for tail calls by default in Wasmtime 21.0.0, although that release contained a bug where it was only on-by-default for some configurations. In Wasmtime 22.0.0 tail calls were enabled by default for all configurations. The specific crash happens when an exported function in a WebAssembly module (or component) performs a `return_call` (or `return_call_indirect` or `return_call_ref`) to an imported host function which captures a stack trace (for example, the host function raises a trap). In this situation, the stack-walking code previously assumed there was always at least one WebAssembly frame on the stack but with tail calls that is no longer true. With the tail-call proposal it's possible to have an entry trampoline appear as if it directly called the exit trampoline. This situation triggers an internal assert in the stack-walking code which raises a Rust `panic!()`. When Wasmtime is compiled with Rust versions 1.80 and prior this means that an `extern "C"` function in Rust is raising a `panic!()`. This is technically undefined behavior and typically manifests as a process abort when the unwinder fails to unwind Cranelift-generated frames. When Wasmtime is compiled with Rust versions 1.81 and later this panic becomes a deterministic process abort. Overall the impact of this issue is that this is a denial-of-service vector where a malicious WebAssembly module or component can cause the host to crash. There is no other impact at this time other than availability of a service as the result of the crash is always a crash and no more. This issue was discovered by routine fuzzing performed by the Wasmtime project via Google's OSS-Fuzz infrastructure. We have no evidence that it has ever been exploited by an attacker in the wild. All versions of Wasmtime which have tail calls enabled by default have been patched: * 21.0.x - patched in 21.0.2 * 22.0.x - patched in 22.0.1 * 23.0.x - patched in 23.0.3  * 24.0.x - patched in 24.0.1 * 25.0.x - patched in 25.0.2. Wasmtime versions from 12.0.x (the first release with experimental tail call support) to 20.0.x (the last release with tail-calls off-by-default) have support for tail calls but the support is disabled by default. These versions are not affected in their default configurations, but users who explicitly enabled tail call support will need to either disable tail call support or upgrade to a patched version of Wasmtime. The main workaround for this issue is to disable tail support for tail calls in Wasmtime, for example with `Config::wasm_tail_call(false)`. Users are otherwise encouraged to upgrade to patched versions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47813 | Wasmtime race condition could lead to WebAssembly control-flow integrity and type safety violations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47813</link><description>Wasmtime is an open source runtime for WebAssembly. Under certain concurrent event orderings, a `wasmtime::Engine`'s internal type registry was susceptible to double-unregistration bugs due to a race condition, leading to panics and potentially type registry corruption. That registry corruption could, following an additional and particular sequence of concurrent events, lead to violations of WebAssembly's control-flow integrity (CFI) and type safety. Users that do not use `wasmtime::Engine` across multiple threads are not affected. Users that only create new modules across threads over time are additionally not affected. Reproducing this bug requires creating and dropping multiple type instances (such as `wasmtime::FuncType` or `wasmtime::ArrayType`) concurrently on multiple threads, where all types are associated with the same `wasmtime::Engine`. **Wasm guests cannot trigger this bug.** See the "References" section below for a list of Wasmtime types-related APIs that are affected. Wasmtime maintains an internal registry of types within a `wasmtime::Engine` and an engine is shareable across threads. Types can be created and referenced through creation of a `wasmtime::Module`, creation of `wasmtime::FuncType`, or a number of other APIs where the host creates a function (see "References" below). Each of these cases interacts with an engine to deduplicate type information and manage type indices that are used to implement type checks in WebAssembly's `call_indirect` function, for example. This bug is a race condition in this management where the internal type registry could be corrupted to trigger an assert or contain invalid state. Wasmtime's internal representation of a type has individual types (e.g. one-per-host-function) maintain a registration count of how many time it's been used. Types additionally have state within an engine behind a read-write lock such as lookup/deduplication information. The race here is a time-of-check versus time-of-use (TOCTOU) bug where one thread atomically decrements a type entry's registration count, observes zero registrations, and then acquires a lock in order to unregister that entry. However, between when this first thread observed the zero-registration count and when it acquires that lock, another thread could perform the following sequence of events: re-register another copy of the type, which deduplicates to that same entry, resurrecting it and incrementing its registration count; then drop the type and decrement its registration count; observe that the registration count is now zero; acquire the type registry lock; and finally unregister the type. Now, when the original thread finally acquires the lock and unregisters the entry, it is the second time this entry has been unregistered. This bug was originally introduced in Wasmtime 19's development of the WebAssembly GC proposal. This bug affects users who are not using the GC proposal, however, and affects Wasmtime in its default configuration even when the GC proposal is disabled. Wasmtime users using 19.0.0 and after are all affected by this issue. We have released the following Wasmtime versions, all of which have a fix for this bug: * 21.0.2 * 22.0.1 * 23.0.3 * 24.0.1 * 25.0.2. If your application creates and drops Wasmtime types on multiple threads concurrently, there are no known workarounds. Users are encouraged to upgrade to a patched release.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9463 | Expedition: Unauthenticated OS Command Injection Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9463</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an unauthenticated attacker to run arbitrary OS commands as root in Expedition, resulting in disclosure of usernames, cleartext passwords, device configurations, and device API keys of PAN-OS firewalls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9464 | Expedition: Authenticated OS Command Injection Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9464</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an authenticated attacker to run arbitrary OS commands as root in Expedition, resulting in disclosure of usernames, cleartext passwords, device configurations, and device API keys of PAN-OS firewalls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9465 | Expedition: SQL Injection Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9465</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an unauthenticated attacker to reveal Expedition database contents, such as password hashes, usernames, device configurations, and device API keys. With this, attackers can also create and read arbitrary files on the Expedition system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9466 | Expedition: Cleartext Storage of Information Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9466</link><description>A cleartext storage of sensitive information vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition allows an authenticated attacker to reveal firewall usernames, passwords, and API keys generated using those credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9467 | Expedition: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability Leads to Firewall Admin Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9467</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks Expedition enables execution of malicious JavaScript in the context of an authenticated Expedition user's browser if that user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to Expedition browser session theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9468 | PAN-OS: Firewall Denial of Service (DoS) via a Maliciously Crafted Packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9468</link><description>A memory corruption vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software allows an unauthenticated attacker to crash PAN-OS due to a crafted packet through the data plane, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. Repeated attempts to trigger this condition will result in PAN-OS entering maintenance mode.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9469 | Cortex XDR Agent: Local Windows User Can Disable the Agent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9469</link><description>A problem with a detection mechanism in the Palo Alto Networks Cortex XDR agent on Windows devices enables a user with Windows non-administrative privileges to disable the agent. This issue may be leveraged by malware to disable the Cortex XDR agent and then to perform malicious activity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9470 | Cortex XSOAR: Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9470</link><description>A vulnerability in Cortex XSOAR allows the disclosure of incident data to users who do not have the privilege to view the data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9471 | PAN-OS: Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability in XML API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9471</link><description>A privilege escalation (PE) vulnerability in the XML API of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated PAN-OS administrator with restricted privileges to use a compromised XML API key to perform actions as a higher privileged PAN-OS administrator. For example, an administrator with "Virtual system administrator (read-only)" access could use an XML API key of a "Virtual system administrator" to perform write operations on the virtual system configuration even though they should be limited to read-only operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9473 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9473</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows allows a locally authenticated non-administrative Windows user to escalate their privileges to NT AUTHORITY/SYSTEM through the use of the repair functionality offered by the .msi file used to install GlobalProtect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43610 | Copilot Studio Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43610</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45746 | An issue was discovered in Trusted Firmware-M through 2.1.0. User provided (and controlled) mailbox messages contain a pointer to a list of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45746</link><description>An issue was discovered in Trusted Firmware-M through 2.1.0. User provided (and controlled) mailbox messages contain a pointer to a list of input arguments (in_vec) and output arguments (out_vec). These list pointers are never validated. Each argument list contains a buffer pointer and a buffer length field. After a PSA call, the length of the output arguments behind the unchecked pointer is updated in mailbox_direct_reply, regardless of the call result. This allows an attacker to write anywhere in the secure firmware, which can be used to take over the control flow, leading to remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42988 | Lack of access control in ChallengeSolves (/api/v1/challenges/&lt;challenge id&gt;/solves) of CTFd v2.0.0 - v3.7.2 allows authenticated users to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42988</link><description>Lack of access control in ChallengeSolves (/api/v1/challenges//solves) of CTFd v2.0.0 - v3.7.2 allows authenticated users to retrieve a list of users who have solved the challenge, regardless of the Account Visibility settings. The issue is fixed in v3.7.3+.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46307 | A loop hole in the payment logic of Sparkshop v1.16 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify the number of products.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46307</link><description>A loop hole in the payment logic of Sparkshop v1.16 allows attackers to arbitrarily modify the number of products.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46316 | DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sub_2C920 function at /cgi-bin/mainfunction.c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46316</link><description>DrayTek Vigor3900 v1.5.1.6 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via the sub_2C920 function at /cgi-bin/mainfunction.cgi. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying a crafted HTTP message.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46292 | A buffer overflow in modsecurity v3.0.12 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input inserted into the name para...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46292</link><description>A buffer overflow in modsecurity v3.0.12 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input inserted into the name parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46304 | A Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libcoap v4.3.5-rc2 and below allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the coap_handle_re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46304</link><description>A Buffer Overflow vulnerability in libcoap v4.3.5-rc2 and below allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the coap_handle_request_put_block function in src/coap_block.c.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25825 | FydeOS for PC 17.1 R114, FydeOS for VMware 17.0 R114, FydeOS for You 17.1 R114, and OpenFyde R114 were discovered to be configured with the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25825</link><description>FydeOS for PC 17.1 R114, FydeOS for VMware 17.0 R114, FydeOS for You 17.1 R114, and OpenFyde R114 were discovered to be configured with the root password saved as a wildcard. This allows attackers to gain root access without a password.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:44:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47670 | ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47670</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: add bounds checking to ocfs2_xattr_find_entry()

Add a paranoia check to make sure it doesn't stray beyond valid memory
region containing ocfs2 xattr entries when scanning for a match.  It will
prevent out-of-bound access in case of crafted images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47671 | USB: usbtmc: prevent kernel-usb-infoleak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47671</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

USB: usbtmc: prevent kernel-usb-infoleak

The syzbot reported a kernel-usb-infoleak in usbtmc_write,
we need to clear the structure before filling fields.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47672 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: don&amp;#x27;t wait for tx queues if firmware is dead</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47672</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: don't wait for tx queues if firmware is dead

There is a WARNING in iwl_trans_wait_tx_queues_empty() (that was
recently converted from just a message), that can be hit if we
wait for TX queues to become empty after firmware died. Clearly,
we can't expect anything from the firmware after it's declared dead.

Don't call iwl_trans_wait_tx_queues_empty() in this case. While it could
be a good idea to stop the flow earlier, the flush functions do some
maintenance work that is not related to the firmware, so keep that part
of the code running even when the firmware is not running.

[edit commit message]</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47673 | wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: pause TCM when the firmware is stopped</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47673</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: iwlwifi: mvm: pause TCM when the firmware is stopped

Not doing so will make us send a host command to the transport while the
firmware is not alive, which will trigger a WARNING.

bad state = 0
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 17434 at drivers/net/wireless/intel/iwlwifi/iwl-trans.c:115 iwl_trans_send_cmd+0x1cb/0x1e0 [iwlwifi]
RIP: 0010:iwl_trans_send_cmd+0x1cb/0x1e0 [iwlwifi]
Call Trace:
 
 iwl_mvm_send_cmd+0x40/0xc0 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_config_scan+0x198/0x260 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_recalc_tcm+0x730/0x11d0 [iwlmvm]
 iwl_mvm_tcm_work+0x1d/0x30 [iwlmvm]
 process_one_work+0x29e/0x640
 worker_thread+0x2df/0x690
 ? rescuer_thread+0x540/0x540
 kthread+0x192/0x1e0
 ? set_kthread_struct+0x90/0x90
 ret_from_fork+0x22/0x30</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7292 | Account Controller allows high count of login attempts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7292</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), a credential stuffing attack is possible through improper restriction of excessive login attempts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8015 | Telerik Report Server Insecure Type Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8015</link><description>In Progress Telerik Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.924), a remote code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7293 | Password policy for new users is not strong enough</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7293</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), a password brute forcing attack is possible through weak password requirements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7294 | Uncontrolled resource consumption of anonymous endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7294</link><description>In Progress® Telerik® Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q3 (10.2.24.806), an HTTP DoS attack is possible on anonymous endpoints without rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7840 | Improper neutralization special element in hyperlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7840</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (2024.3.924), a command injection attack is possible through improper neutralization of hyperlink elements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47421 | Adobe Framemaker | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47421</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47422 | Adobe Framemaker | Untrusted Search Path (CWE-426)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47422</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Untrusted Search Path vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting a malicious path into the search directories, which the application could unknowingly execute. This could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47423 | Adobe Framemaker | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47423</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can be automatically processed or executed by the system. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47424 | Adobe Framemaker | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47424</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47425 | Adobe Framemaker | Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) (CWE-191)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47425</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2020.6, 2022.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Underflow (Wrap or Wraparound) vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9671 | System: pdf invoices of the developer users can be seen if the url is known</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9671</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 3Scale. There is no auth mechanism to see a PDF invoice of a Developer user if the URL is known. Anyone can see the invoice if the URL is known or guessed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9675 | Buildah: buildah allows arbitrary directory mount</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9675</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Buildah. Cache mounts do not properly validate that user-specified paths for the cache are within our cache directory, allowing a `RUN` instruction in a Container file to mount an arbitrary directory from the host (read/write) into the container as long as those files can be accessed by the user running Buildah.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45137 | InDesign Desktop | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45137</link><description>InDesign Desktop versions 19.4, 18.5.3 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which, when executed, could run arbitrary code in the context of the server. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8014 | Telerik Reporting EntityDataSource Insecure Type Resolution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8014</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (18.2.24.924), a code execution attack is possible through object injection via an insecure type resolution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8048 | Telerik Reporting Insecure Expression Evaluation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8048</link><description>In Progress Telerik Reporting versions prior to 2024 Q3 (18.2.24.924), a code execution attack is possible using object injection via insecure expression evaluation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45136 | InCopy | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type (CWE-434)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45136</link><description>InCopy versions 19.4, 18.5.3 and earlier are affected by an Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution by an attacker. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by uploading a malicious file which can then be executed on the server. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47661 | drm/amd/display: Avoid overflow from uint32_t to uint8_t</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Avoid overflow from uint32_t to uint8_t

[WHAT &amp; HOW]
dmub_rb_cmd's ramping_boundary has size of uint8_t and it is assigned
0xFFFF. Fix it by changing it to uint8_t with value of 0xFF.

This fixes 2 INTEGER_OVERFLOW issues reported by Coverity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47662 | drm/amd/display: Remove register from DCN35 DMCUB diagnostic collection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47662</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Remove register from DCN35 DMCUB diagnostic collection

[Why]
These registers should not be read from driver and triggering the
security violation when DMCUB work times out and diagnostics are
collected blocks Z8 entry.

[How]
Remove the register read from DCN35.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47663 | staging: iio: frequency: ad9834: Validate frequency parameter value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

staging: iio: frequency: ad9834: Validate frequency parameter value

In ad9834_write_frequency() clk_get_rate() can return 0. In such case
ad9834_calc_freqreg() call will lead to division by zero. Checking
'if (fout &gt; (clk_freq / 2))' doesn't protect in case of 'fout' is 0.
ad9834_write_frequency() is called from ad9834_write(), where fout is
taken from text buffer, which can contain any value.

Modify parameters checking.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47664 | spi: hisi-kunpeng: Add verification for the max_frequency provided by the firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: hisi-kunpeng: Add verification for the max_frequency provided by the firmware

If the value of max_speed_hz is 0, it may cause a division by zero
error in hisi_calc_effective_speed().
The value of max_speed_hz is provided by firmware.
Firmware is generally considered as a trusted domain. However, as
division by zero errors can cause system failure, for defense measure,
the value of max_speed is validated here. So 0 is regarded as invalid
and an error code is returned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47665 | i3c: mipi-i3c-hci: Error out instead on BUG_ON() in IBI DMA setup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47665</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

i3c: mipi-i3c-hci: Error out instead on BUG_ON() in IBI DMA setup

Definitely condition dma_get_cache_alignment * defined value &gt; 256
during driver initialization is not reason to BUG_ON(). Turn that to
graceful error out with -EINVAL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47666 | scsi: pm80xx: Set phy-&amp;gt;enable_completion only when we wait for it</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47666</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

scsi: pm80xx: Set phy-&gt;enable_completion only when we wait for it

pm8001_phy_control() populates the enable_completion pointer with a stack
address, sends a PHY_LINK_RESET / PHY_HARD_RESET, waits 300 ms, and
returns. The problem arises when a phy control response comes late.  After
300 ms the pm8001_phy_control() function returns and the passed
enable_completion stack address is no longer valid. Late phy control
response invokes complete() on a dangling enable_completion pointer which
leads to a kernel crash.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47667 | PCI: keystone: Add workaround for Errata #i2037 (AM65x SR 1.0)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: keystone: Add workaround for Errata #i2037 (AM65x SR 1.0)

Errata #i2037 in AM65x/DRA80xM Processors Silicon Revision 1.0
(SPRZ452D_July 2018_Revised December 2019 [1]) mentions when an
inbound PCIe TLP spans more than two internal AXI 128-byte bursts,
the bus may corrupt the packet payload and the corrupt data may
cause associated applications or the processor to hang.

The workaround for Errata #i2037 is to limit the maximum read
request size and maximum payload size to 128 bytes. Add workaround
for Errata #i2037 here.

The errata and workaround is applicable only to AM65x SR 1.0 and
later versions of the silicon will have this fixed.

[1] -&gt; https://www.ti.com/lit/er/sprz452i/sprz452i.pdf</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47668 | lib/generic-radix-tree.c: Fix rare race in __genradix_ptr_alloc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47668</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

lib/generic-radix-tree.c: Fix rare race in __genradix_ptr_alloc()

If we need to increase the tree depth, allocate a new node, and then
race with another thread that increased the tree depth before us, we'll
still have a preallocated node that might be used later.

If we then use that node for a new non-root node, it'll still have a
pointer to the old root instead of being zeroed - fix this by zeroing it
in the cmpxchg failure path.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47669 | nilfs2: fix state management in error path of log writing function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47669</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nilfs2: fix state management in error path of log writing function

After commit a694291a6211 ("nilfs2: separate wait function from
nilfs_segctor_write") was applied, the log writing function
nilfs_segctor_do_construct() was able to issue I/O requests continuously
even if user data blocks were split into multiple logs across segments,
but two potential flaws were introduced in its error handling.

First, if nilfs_segctor_begin_construction() fails while creating the
second or subsequent logs, the log writing function returns without
calling nilfs_segctor_abort_construction(), so the writeback flag set on
pages/folios will remain uncleared.  This causes page cache operations to
hang waiting for the writeback flag.  For example,
truncate_inode_pages_final(), which is called via nilfs_evict_inode() when
an inode is evicted from memory, will hang.

Second, the NILFS_I_COLLECTED flag set on normal inodes remain uncleared. 
As a result, if the next log write involves checkpoint creation, that's
fine, but if a partial log write is performed that does not, inodes with
NILFS_I_COLLECTED set are erroneously removed from the "sc_dirty_files"
list, and their data and b-tree blocks may not be written to the device,
corrupting the block mapping.

Fix these issues by uniformly calling nilfs_segctor_abort_construction()
on failure of each step in the loop in nilfs_segctor_do_construct(),
having it clean up logs and segment usages according to progress, and
correcting the conditions for calling nilfs_redirty_inodes() to ensure
that the NILFS_I_COLLECTED flag is cleared.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46870 | drm/amd/display: Disable DMCUB timeout for DCN35</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46870</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Disable DMCUB timeout for DCN35

[Why]
DMCUB can intermittently take longer than expected to process commands.

Old ASIC policy was to continue while logging a diagnostic error - which
works fine for ASIC without IPS, but with IPS this could lead to a race
condition where we attempt to access DCN state while it's inaccessible,
leading to a system hang when the NIU port is not disabled or register
accesses that timeout and the display configuration in an undefined
state.

[How]
We need to investigate why these accesses take longer than expected, but
for now we should disable the timeout on DCN35 to avoid this race
condition. Since the waits happen only at lower interrupt levels the
risk of taking too long at higher IRQ and causing a system watchdog
timeout are minimal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46871 | drm/amd/display: Correct the defined value for AMDGPU_DMUB_NOTIFICATION_MAX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46871</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Correct the defined value for AMDGPU_DMUB_NOTIFICATION_MAX

[Why &amp; How]
It actually exposes '6' types in enum dmub_notification_type. Not 5. Using smaller
number to create array dmub_callback &amp; dmub_thread_offload has potential to access
item out of array bound. Fix it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47658 | crypto: stm32/cryp - call finalize with bh disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47658</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: stm32/cryp - call finalize with bh disabled

The finalize operation in interrupt mode produce a produces a spinlock
recursion warning. The reason is the fact that BH must be disabled
during this process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47659 | smack: tcp: ipv4, fix incorrect labeling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47659</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smack: tcp: ipv4, fix incorrect labeling

Currently, Smack mirrors the label of incoming tcp/ipv4 connections:
when a label 'foo' connects to a label 'bar' with tcp/ipv4,
'foo' always gets 'foo' in returned ipv4 packets. So,
1) returned packets are incorrectly labeled ('foo' instead of 'bar')
2) 'bar' can write to 'foo' without being authorized to write.

Here is a scenario how to see this:

* Take two machines, let's call them C and S,
   with active Smack in the default state
   (no settings, no rules, no labeled hosts, only builtin labels)

* At S, add Smack rule 'foo bar w'
   (labels 'foo' and 'bar' are instantiated at S at this moment)

* At S, at label 'bar', launch a program
   that listens for incoming tcp/ipv4 connections

* From C, at label 'foo', connect to the listener at S.
   (label 'foo' is instantiated at C at this moment)
   Connection succeedes and works.

* Send some data in both directions.
* Collect network traffic of this connection.

All packets in both directions are labeled with the CIPSO
of the label 'foo'. Hence, label 'bar' writes to 'foo' without
being authorized, and even without ever being known at C.

If anybody cares: exactly the same happens with DCCP.

This behavior 1st manifested in release 2.6.29.4 (see Fixes below)
and it looks unintentional. At least, no explanation was provided.

I changed returned packes label into the 'bar',
to bring it into line with the Smack documentation claims.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47660 | fsnotify: clear PARENT_WATCHED flags lazily</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47660</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fsnotify: clear PARENT_WATCHED flags lazily

In some setups directories can have many (usually negative) dentries.
Hence __fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() function can take a
significant amount of time. Since the bulk of this function happens
under inode-&gt;i_lock this causes a significant contention on the lock
when we remove the watch from the directory as the
__fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() call from fsnotify_recalc_mask()
races with __fsnotify_update_child_dentry_flags() calls from
__fsnotify_parent() happening on children. This can lead upto softlockup
reports reported by users.

Fix the problem by calling fsnotify_update_children_dentry_flags() to
set PARENT_WATCHED flags only when parent starts watching children.

When parent stops watching children, clear false positive PARENT_WATCHED
flags lazily in __fsnotify_parent() for each accessed child.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46237 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the patname, pataddress, and medhis parameters in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46237</link><description>PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the patname, pataddress, and medhis parameters in doctor/add-patient.php and doctor/edit-patient.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45138 | Substance3D - Stager | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45138</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45139 | Substance3D - Stager | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45139</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45140 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45140</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45141 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45141</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45142 | Substance3D - Stager | Write-what-where Condition (CWE-123)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45142</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Write-what-where Condition vulnerability that could allow an attacker to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. This vulnerability allows an attacker to write a controlled value to an arbitrary memory location, potentially leading to code execution. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45143 | Substance3D - Stager | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45143</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45144 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45144</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45152 | Substance3D - Stager | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45152</link><description>Substance3D - Stager versions 3.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9286 | SQLi in TRtek Software&amp;#x27;s Distant Education Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection'), Improper Input Validation vulnerability in TRtek Software Distant Education Platform allows SQL Injection, Parameter Injection.This issue affects Distant Education Platform: before 3.2024.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9680 | An attacker was able to achieve code execution in the content process by exploiting a use-after-free in Animation timelines. We have had rep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9680</link><description>An attacker was able to achieve code execution in the content process by exploiting a use-after-free in Animation timelines. We have had reports of this vulnerability being exploited in the wild. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 131.0.2, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.3.1, and Firefox ESR &lt; 115.16.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45720 | Apache Subversion: Command line argument injection on Windows platforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45720</link><description>On Windows platforms, a "best fit" character encoding conversion of command line arguments to Subversion's executables (e.g., svn.exe, etc.) may lead to unexpected command line argument interpretation, including argument injection and execution of other programs, if a specially crafted command line argument string is processed.

All versions of Subversion up to and including Subversion 1.14.3 are affected on Windows platforms only. Users are recommended to upgrade to version Subversion 1.14.4, which fixes this issue.

Subversion is not affected on UNIX-like platforms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:14:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28168 | Apache XML Graphics FOP: XML External Entity (XXE) Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28168</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference ('XXE') vulnerability in Apache XML Graphics FOP.

This issue affects Apache XML Graphics FOP: 2.9.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.10, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 12:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47334 | WordPress Zoho Flow for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47334</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Zoho Flow Zoho Flow for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Zoho Flow for WordPress: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 10:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45145 | Lightroom Desktop | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45145</link><description>Lightroom Desktop versions 7.4.1, 13.5, 12.5.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9575 | Local File Inclusion in pretix-widget WordPress plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9575</link><description>Local File Inclusion vulnerability in pretix Widget WordPress plugin pretix-widget on Windows allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects pretix Widget WordPress plugin: from 1.0.0 through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47410 | Animate | Stack-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-121)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47410</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47411 | Animate | Access of Uninitialized Pointer (CWE-824)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47411</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an Access of Uninitialized Pointer vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47412 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47412</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47413 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47413</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47414 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47414</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47415 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47415</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47416 | Animate | Integer Overflow or Wraparound (CWE-190)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47416</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47417 | Animate | Heap-based Buffer Overflow (CWE-122)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47417</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47418 | Animate | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47418</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47419 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47419</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47420 | Animate | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47420</link><description>Animate versions 23.0.7, 24.0.4 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20787 | Substance3D - Painter | Out-of-bounds Read (CWE-125)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20787</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 10.0.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45146 | Dimension | Use After Free (CWE-416)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45146</link><description>Dimension versions 4.0.3 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45150 | Dimension | Out-of-bounds Write (CWE-787)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45150</link><description>Dimension versions 4.0.3 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 08:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9451 | Embed PDF Viewer &amp;lt;= 2.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height and width Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9451</link><description>The Embed PDF Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'height' and 'width' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 07:41:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39586 | Dell AppSync Server, version 4.3 through 4.6, contains an XML External Entity Injection vulnerability. An adjacent high privileged attacker ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39586</link><description>Dell AppSync Server, version 4.3 through 4.6, contains an XML External Entity Injection vulnerability. An adjacent high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39436 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39436</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39437 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39437</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39438 | In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39438</link><description>In linkturbonative service, there is a possible command injection due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39439 | In DRM service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39439</link><description>In DRM service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39440 | In DRM service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39440</link><description>In DRM service, there is a possible system crash due to null pointer dereference. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9449 | Auto iFrame &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via tag Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9449</link><description>The Auto iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'tag' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:49:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45872 | An issue was discovered in Qt before 6.2.11 and 6.3.x through 6.6.x before 6.6.1. When a QML image refers to an image whose content is not k...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45872</link><description>An issue was discovered in Qt before 6.2.11 and 6.3.x through 6.6.x before 6.6.1. When a QML image refers to an image whose content is not known yet, there is an assumption that it is an SVG document, leading to a denial of service (application crash) if it is not actually an SVG document.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46586 | cgi.c in weborf .0.17, 0.18, 0.19, and 0.20 (before 1.0) lacks '\0' termination of the path for CGI scripts because strncpy is misused.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46586</link><description>cgi.c in weborf .0.17, 0.18, 0.19, and 0.20 (before 1.0) lacks '\0' termination of the path for CGI scripts because strncpy is misused.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5968 | Photo Gallery by 10Web &amp;lt;= 1.8.27 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5968</link><description>The Photo Gallery by 10Web  WordPress plugin before 1.8.28 does not properly sanitise and escape some of its Gallery settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 06:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45359 | An issue was discovered in the Vector Skin component for MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-toc-toggle-button-label is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45359</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Vector Skin component for MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-toc-toggle-button-label is not escaped, but should be, because the line param can have markup.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45361 | An issue was discovered in VectorComponentUserLinks.php in the Vector Skin component in MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. ve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45361</link><description>An issue was discovered in VectorComponentUserLinks.php in the Vector Skin component in MediaWiki before 1.39.5 and 1.40.x before 1.40.1. vector-intro-page MalformedTitleException is uncaught if it is not a valid title, leading to incorrect web pages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:59:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37154 | check_by_ssh in Nagios nagios-plugins 2.4.5 allows arbitrary command execution via ProxyCommand, LocalCommand, and PermitLocalCommand with \...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37154</link><description>check_by_ssh in Nagios nagios-plugins 2.4.5 allows arbitrary command execution via ProxyCommand, LocalCommand, and PermitLocalCommand with \${IFS}. This has been categorized both as fixed in e8810de, and as intended behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36325 | i2p before 2.3.0 (Java) allows de-anonymizing the public IPv4 and IPv6 addresses of i2p hidden services (aka eepsites) via a correlation att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36325</link><description>i2p before 2.3.0 (Java) allows de-anonymizing the public IPv4 and IPv6 addresses of i2p hidden services (aka eepsites) via a correlation attack across the IPv4 and IPv6 addresses that occurs when a tunneled, replayed message has a behavior discrepancy (it may be dropped, or may result in a Wrong Destination response). An attack would take days to complete.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42934 | OpenIPMI before 2.0.36 has an out-of-bounds array access (for authentication type) in the ipmi_sim simulator, resulting in denial of service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42934</link><description>OpenIPMI before 2.0.36 has an out-of-bounds array access (for authentication type) in the ipmi_sim simulator, resulting in denial of service or (with very low probability) authentication bypass or code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45160 | Incorrect credential validation in LemonLDAP::NG 2.18.x and 2.19.x before 2.19.2 allows attackers to bypass OAuth2 client authentication via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45160</link><description>Incorrect credential validation in LemonLDAP::NG 2.18.x and 2.19.x before 2.19.2 allows attackers to bypass OAuth2 client authentication via an empty client_password parameter (client secret).</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47191 | pam_oath.so in oath-toolkit 2.6.7 through 2.6.11 before 2.6.12 allows root privilege escalation because, in the context of PAM code running ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47191</link><description>pam_oath.so in oath-toolkit 2.6.7 through 2.6.11 before 2.6.12 allows root privilege escalation because, in the context of PAM code running as root, it mishandles usersfile access, such as by calling fchown in the presence of a symlink.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32608 | HDF5 library through 1.14.3 has memory corruption in H5A__close resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32608</link><description>HDF5 library through 1.14.3 has memory corruption in H5A__close resulting in the corruption of the instruction pointer and causing denial of service or potential code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 05:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45179 | An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to insufficient input validation, the C-MOR web int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45179</link><description>An issue was discovered in za-internet C-MOR Video Surveillance 5.2401 and 6.00PL01. Due to insufficient input validation, the C-MOR web interface is vulnerable to OS command injection attacks. It was found out that different functionality is vulnerable to OS command injection attacks, for example for generating new X.509 certificates, or setting the time zone. These OS command injection vulnerabilities in the script generatesslreq.pml can be exploited as a low-privileged authenticated user to execute commands in the context of the Linux user www-data via shell metacharacters in HTTP POST data (e.g., the city parameter). The OS command injection vulnerability in the script settimezone.pml or setdatetime.pml (e.g., via the year parameter) requires an administrative user for the C-MOR web interface. By also exploiting a privilege-escalation vulnerability, it is possible to execute commands on the C-MOR system with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:57:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35288 | Nitro PDF Pro before 13.70.8.82 and 14.x before 14.26.1.0 allows Local Privilege Escalation in the MSI Installer because custom actions occu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35288</link><description>Nitro PDF Pro before 13.70.8.82 and 14.x before 14.26.1.0 allows Local Privilege Escalation in the MSI Installer because custom actions occur unsafely in repair mode. CertUtil is run in a conhost.exe window, and there is a mechanism allowing CTRL+o to launch cmd.exe as NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25284 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Method via the threeDsMethod.jsp threeDSMethodData parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25284</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Method via the threeDsMethod.jsp threeDSMethodData parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25285 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows form action hijacking via threeDsMethod.jsp?threeDSMethodData= or the threeDSMethodNotificationURL parameter. The destin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25285</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows form action hijacking via threeDsMethod.jsp?threeDSMethodData= or the threeDSMethodNotificationURL parameter. The destination web site for a form submission can be modified.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25286 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows CSRF in the Authorization Method via modified Origin and Referer HTTP headers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25286</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows CSRF in the Authorization Method via modified Origin and Referer HTTP headers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:47:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25282 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows XSS in its 3DSMethod Authentication via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25282</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows XSS in its 3DSMethod Authentication via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=challenge&amp;amp;txn= substring.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25283 | 3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Challenge via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25283</link><description>3DSecure 2.0 allows reflected XSS in the 3DS Authorization Challenge via a modified params parameter in a /rest/online request with a /redirect?action=challenge&amp;amp;txn= substring.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7963 | CMSMasters Content Composer &amp;lt;= 1.8.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7963</link><description>The CMSMasters Content Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's multiple shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9602 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.100 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory write via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9602</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.100 allowed a remote attacker to perform an out of bounds memory write via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 23:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9603 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.100 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9603</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 129.0.6668.100 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 23:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9412 | Improper Authorization Vulnerability in Rockwell Automation Verve® Asset Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9412</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation affected products that could allow an unauthorized user to sign in. While removal of all role mappings is unlikely, it could occur in the case of unexpected or accidental removal by the administrator. If exploited, an unauthorized user could access data they previously but should no longer have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 19:30:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27457 | Improper check for unusual or exceptional conditions in Intel(R) TDX Module firmware before version 1.5.06 may allow a privileged user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27457</link><description>Improper check for unusual or exceptional conditions in Intel(R) TDX Module firmware before version 1.5.06 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36814 | An arbitrary file read vulnerability in Adguard Home before v0.107.52 allows authenticated attackers to access arbitrary files as root on th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36814</link><description>An arbitrary file read vulnerability in Adguard Home before v0.107.52 allows authenticated attackers to access arbitrary files as root on the underlying Operating System via placing a crafted file into a readable directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25885 | An issue in the getcolor function in utils.py of xhtml2pdf v0.2.13 allows attackers to cause a Regular expression Denial of Service (ReDOS) ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25885</link><description>An issue in the getcolor function in utils.py of xhtml2pdf v0.2.13 allows attackers to cause a Regular expression Denial of Service (ReDOS) via supplying a crafted string.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47773 | Anonymous cache poisoning via XHR requests in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47773</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. An attacker can make several XHR requests until the cache is poisoned with a response without any preloaded data. This issue only affects anonymous visitors of the site. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should disable anonymous cache by setting the `DISCOURSE_DISABLE_ANON_CACHE` environment variable to a non-empty value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47780 | Information Disclosure in TYPO3 Page Tree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47780</link><description>TYPO3 is a free and open source Content Management Framework. Backend users could see items in the backend page tree without having access if the mounts pointed to pages restricted for their user/group, or if no mounts were configured but the pages allowed access to "everybody." However, affected users could not manipulate these pages. Users are advised to update to TYPO3 versions 10.4.46 ELTS, 11.5.40 LTS, 12.4.21 LTS, 13.3.1 that fix the problem described. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47822 | Access token from query string is inserted into logs in Directus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47822</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Access tokens from query strings are not redacted and are potentially exposed in system logs which may be persisted. The access token in `req.query` is not redacted when the `LOG_STYLE` is set to `raw`. If these logs are not properly sanitized or protected, an attacker with access to it can potentially gain administrative control, leading to unauthorized data access and manipulation. This impacts systems where the `LOG_STYLE` is set to `raw`. The `access_token` in the query could potentially be a long-lived static token. Users with impacted systems should rotate their static tokens if they were provided using query string. This vulnerability has been patched in release version 10.13.2 and subsequent releases as well. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46410 | PublicCMS V4.0.202406.d was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via a crafted script to the Category Managment ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46410</link><description>PublicCMS V4.0.202406.d was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via a crafted script to the Category Managment feature</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47823 | Livewire Remote Code Execution (RCE) on File Uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47823</link><description>Livewire is a full-stack framework for Laravel that allows for dynamic UI components without leaving PHP. In livewire/livewire `&lt; v3.5.2`, the file extension of an uploaded file is guessed based on the MIME type. As a result, the actual file extension from the file name is not validated. An attacker can therefore bypass the validation by uploading a file with a valid MIME type (e.g., `image/png`) and a “.php” file extension. If the following criteria are met, the attacker can carry out an RCE attack: 1. Filename is composed of the original file name using `$file-&gt;getClientOriginalName()`. 2. Files stored directly on your server in a public storage disk. 3. Webserver is configured to execute “.php” files. This issue has been addressed in release version 3.5.2. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43488 | Visual Studio Code extension for Arduino Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43488</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43550 | Windows Secure Channel Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43550</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43551 | Windows Storage Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43551</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43552 | Windows Shell Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43552</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43553 | NT OS Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43553</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43555 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43555</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43556 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43556</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43557 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43557</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43558 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43558</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43559 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43559</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43560 | Microsoft Windows Storage Port Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43560</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43561 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43561</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43562 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43562</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43563 | Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43563</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43564 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43564</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43565 | Windows Network Address Translation (NAT) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43565</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43567 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43567</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43570 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43570</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43571 | Sudo for Windows Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43571</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43572 | Microsoft Management Console Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43572</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43574 | Microsoft Speech Application Programming Interface (SAPI) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43574</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43575 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43575</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43582 | Remote Desktop Protocol Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43582</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43583 | Winlogon Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43583</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43584 | Windows Scripting Engine Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43584</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43585 | Code Integrity Guard Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43585</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43589 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43589</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43590 | Visual C++ Redistributable Installer Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43590</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43591 | Azure Command Line Integration (CLI) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43591</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43592 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43592</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43593 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43593</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43599 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43599</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43603 | Visual Studio Collector Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43603</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43611 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43611</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43614 | Microsoft Defender for Endpoint for Linux Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43614</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20659 | Windows Hyper-V Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20659</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30092 | Windows Hyper-V Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30092</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35215 | NULL pointer dereference in IP socket options processing of the Networking Stack in QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) version(s) 7.1 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35215</link><description>NULL pointer dereference in IP socket options processing of the Networking Stack in QNX Software Development Platform (SDP) version(s) 7.1 and 7.0 could allow an attacker with local access to cause a denial-of-service condition in the context of the Networking Stack process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37976 | Windows Resume Extensible Firmware Interface Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37976</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37979 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37979</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37982 | Windows Resume Extensible Firmware Interface Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37982</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37983 | Windows Resume Extensible Firmware Interface Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37983</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38029 | Microsoft OpenSSH for Windows Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38029</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38097 | Azure Monitor Agent Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38097</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38124 | Windows Netlogon Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38124</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38129 | Windows Kerberos Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38129</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38149 | BranchCache Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38149</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38179 | Azure Stack Hyperconverged Infrastructure (HCI) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38179</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38212 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38212</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38229 | .NET and Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38229</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38261 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38261</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38262 | Windows Remote Desktop Licensing Service Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38262</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38265 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38265</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43453 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43453</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43456 | Windows Remote Desktop Services Tampering Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43456</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43468 | Microsoft Configuration Manager Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43468</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43480 | Azure Service Fabric for Linux Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43480</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43481 | Power BI Report Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43481</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43483 | .NET, .NET Framework, and Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43483</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43484 | .NET, .NET Framework, and Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43484</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43485 | .NET and Visual Studio Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43485</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43497 | DeepSpeed Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43497</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43500 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43500</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43501 | Windows Common Log File System Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43501</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43502 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43502</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43503 | Microsoft SharePoint Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43503</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43504 | Microsoft Excel Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43504</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43505 | Microsoft Office Visio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43505</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43506 | BranchCache Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43506</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43508 | Windows Graphics Component Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43508</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43509 | Windows Graphics Component Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43509</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43511 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43511</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43512 | Windows Standards-Based Storage Management Service Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43512</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43513 | BitLocker Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43513</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43514 | Windows Resilient File System (ReFS) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43514</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43515 | Internet Small Computer Systems Interface (iSCSI) Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43515</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43516 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43516</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43517 | Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43517</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43518 | Windows Telephony Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43518</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43519 | Microsoft WDAC OLE DB provider for SQL Server Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43519</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43520 | Windows Kernel Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43520</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43521 | Windows Hyper-V Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43521</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43522 | Windows Local Security Authority (LSA) Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43522</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43523 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43523</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43524 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43524</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43525 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43525</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43526 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43526</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43527 | Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43527</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43528 | Windows Secure Kernel Mode Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43528</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43529 | Windows Print Spooler Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43529</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43532 | Remote Registry Service Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43532</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43533 | Remote Desktop Client Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43533</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43534 | Windows Graphics Component Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43534</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43535 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43535</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43536 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43536</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43537 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43537</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43538 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43538</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43540 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43540</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43541 | Microsoft Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43541</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43542 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43542</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43543 | Windows Mobile Broadband Driver Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43543</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43544 | Microsoft Simple Certificate Enrollment Protocol Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43544</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43545 | Windows Online Certificate Status Protocol (OCSP) Server Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43545</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43546 | Windows Cryptographic Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43546</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43547 | Windows Kerberos Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43547</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43549 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43549</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43554 | Windows Kernel-Mode Driver Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43554</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43573 | Windows MSHTML Platform Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43573</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43576 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43576</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43581 | Microsoft OpenSSH for Windows Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43581</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43601 | Visual Studio Code for Linux Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43601</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43604 | Outlook for Android Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43604</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43607 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43607</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43608 | Windows Routing and Remote Access Service (RRAS) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43608</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43609 | Microsoft Office Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43609</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43612 | Power BI Report Server Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43612</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43615 | Microsoft OpenSSH for Windows Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43615</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43616 | Microsoft Office Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43616</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46539 | Insecure permissions in the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) component of Fire-Boltt Artillery Smart Watch NJ-R6E-10.3 allow attackers to cause a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46539</link><description>Insecure permissions in the Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) component of Fire-Boltt Artillery Smart Watch NJ-R6E-10.3 allow attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3057 | A flaw exists whereby a user can make a specific call to a FlashArray endpoint allowing privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3057</link><description>A flaw exists whereby a user can make a specific call to a FlashArray endpoint allowing privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44349 | A SQL injection vulnerability in login portal in AnteeoWMS before v4.7.34 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44349</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability in login portal in AnteeoWMS before v4.7.34 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the username parameter and disclosure of some data in the underlying DB.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45918 | Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform &lt;=7.6.6.4391 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /client/get_gis_fence.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45918</link><description>Fujian Kelixin Communication Command and Dispatch Platform &lt;=7.6.6.4391 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /client/get_gis_fence.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47007 | A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService.exe of Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to ca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47007</link><description>A NULL pointer dereference in WLAvalancheService.exe of Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47008 | Server-side request forgery in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47008</link><description>Server-side request forgery in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47009 | Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47009</link><description>Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47010 | Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47010</link><description>Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47011 | Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47011</link><description>Path Traversal in Ivanti Avalanche before version 6.4.5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak sensitive information</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8626 | Logix Controllers Vulnerable to Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8626</link><description>Due to a memory leak, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the Rockwell Automation affected products. A malicious actor could exploit this vulnerability by performing multiple actions on certain web pages of the product causing the affected products to become fully unavailable and require a power cycle to recover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9167 | Under specific circumstances, insecure permissions in Ivanti Velocity License Server before version 5.2 allows a local authenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9167</link><description>Under specific circumstances, insecure permissions in Ivanti Velocity License Server before version 5.2 allows a local authenticated attacker to achieve local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9381 | Path traversal in Ivanti CSA before version 5.0.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to bypass restrictions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9381</link><description>Path traversal in Ivanti CSA before version 5.0.2 allows a remote authenticated attacker with admin privileges to bypass restrictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9620 | Event-driven automation in ansible automation platform (aap): ansible event-driven automation (eda) lacks encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9620</link><description>A flaw was found in Event-Driven Automation (EDA) in Ansible Automation Platform (AAP), which lacks encryption of sensitive information. An attacker with network access could exploit this vulnerability by sniffing the plaintext data transmitted between the EDA and AAP. An attacker with system access could exploit this vulnerability by reading the plaintext data stored in EDA and AAP databases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9621 | Io.quarkiverse.cxf:quarkus-cxf: quarkus cxf may log user password and secret to application log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9621</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Quarkus CXF. Passwords and other secrets may appear in the  application log in spite of the user configuring them to be hidden. This issue requires some special configuration to be vulnerable, such as SOAP logging enabled, application set client, and endpoint logging properties, and the attacker must have access to the application log.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9622 | Resteasy-netty4-cdi: resteasy-netty4: http request smuggling leading to client timeouts in resteasy-netty4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the resteasy-netty4 library arising from improper handling of HTTP requests using smuggling techniques. When an HTTP smuggling request with an ASCII control character is sent, it causes the Netty HttpObjectDecoder to transition into a BAD_MESSAGE state. As a result, any subsequent legitimate requests on the same connection are ignored, leading to client timeouts, which may impact systems using load balancers and expose them to risk.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47161 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 password could be exposed via Sonar runner REST API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47161</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 password could be exposed via Sonar runner REST API</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:54:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47948 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 path traversal leading to information disclosure was possible via server backups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47948</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 path traversal leading to information disclosure was possible via server backups</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47949 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 path traversal allowed backup file write to arbitrary location</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47949</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 path traversal allowed backup file write to arbitrary location</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47950 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 stored XSS was possible in Backup configuration settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47950</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 stored XSS was possible in Backup configuration settings</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47951 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 stored XSS was possible via server global settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47951</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2024.07.3 stored XSS was possible via server global settings</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:54:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8215 | Payload Injection Attack via Management REST interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8215</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Payara Platform Payara Server (Admin Console modules) allows Remote Code Inclusion.This issue affects Payara Server: from 5.20.0 before 5.68.0, from 6.0.0 before 6.19.0, from 6.2022.1 before 6.2024.10, from 4.1.2.191.1 before 4.1.2.191.51.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45230 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.1, 5.0 before 5.0.9, and 4.2 before 4.2.16. The urlize() and urlizetrunc() template filters...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45230</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.1 before 5.1.1, 5.0 before 5.0.9, and 4.2 before 4.2.16. The urlize() and urlizetrunc() template filters are subject to a potential denial-of-service attack via very large inputs with a specific sequence of characters.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45231 | An issue was discovered in Django v5.1.1, v5.0.9, and v4.2.16. The django.contrib.auth.forms.PasswordResetForm class, when used in a view im...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45231</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django v5.1.1, v5.0.9, and v4.2.16. The django.contrib.auth.forms.PasswordResetForm class, when used in a view implementing password reset flows, allows remote attackers to enumerate user e-mail addresses by sending password reset requests and observing the outcome (only when e-mail sending is consistently failing).</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45880 | A command injection vulnerability exists in Motorola CX2L router v1.0.2 and below. The vulnerability is present in the SetStationSettings fu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45880</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in Motorola CX2L router v1.0.2 and below. The vulnerability is present in the SetStationSettings function. The system directly invokes the system function to execute commands for setting parameters such as MAC address without proper input filtering. This allows malicious users to inject and execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:56:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33506 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in FortiManager 7.4.2 and below, 7.2.5 and below, 7.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33506</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in FortiManager 7.4.2 and below, 7.2.5 and below, 7.0.12 and below allows a remote authenticated attacker assigned to an Administrative Domain (ADOM) to access device summary of unauthorized ADOMs via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45330 | A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.2 through 7.2.5 allows attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45330</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiAnalyzer versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.3, 7.2.2 through 7.2.5 allows attacker to escalate its privileges via specially crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8431 | Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 3.2.21 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Private Gallery Title Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8431</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Images, Slider in Rbs Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the ajaxGetGalleryJson() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.21. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve private post titles.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8482 | Royal Elementor Addons and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.3.986 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Team Member Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8482</link><description>The Royal Elementor Addons and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘url’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.982 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8488 | Survey Maker – Customer Satisfaction Questionnaire, Chat Survey, Calculation Form, Payment Forms &amp;lt;= 4.9.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8488</link><description>The Survey Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Survey fields in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9207 | BuddyPress Docs &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9207</link><description>The BuddyPress Docs plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:16:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8884 | CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists that
could cause exposure of credentials when attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8884</link><description>CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability exists that
could cause exposure of credentials when attacker has access to application on network over
http</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9005 | CWE-502: Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists that could allow code to be
remotely executed on the server when unsafely de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9005</link><description>CWE-502: Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability exists that could allow code to be
remotely executed on the server when unsafely deserialized data is posted to the web server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:36:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8422 | CWE-416: Use After Free vulnerability exists that could cause arbitrary code execution, denial
of service and loss of confidentiality &amp; inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8422</link><description>CWE-416: Use After Free vulnerability exists that could cause arbitrary code execution, denial
of service and loss of confidentiality &amp; integrity when application user opens a malicious Zelio
Soft 2 project file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8518 | CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause a crash of the Zelio Soft
2 application when a specially crafted pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8518</link><description>CWE-20: Improper Input Validation vulnerability exists that could cause a crash of the Zelio Soft
2 application when a specially crafted project file is loaded by an application user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:36:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3506 | Camera Driver possible Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3506</link><description>A possible buffer overflow in selected cameras' drivers from XProtect Device Pack can allow an attacker with access to internal network to execute commands on Recording Server under strict conditions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8433 | Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8433</link><description>The Easy Mega Menu Plugin for WordPress – ThemeHunk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘themehunk_megamenu_bg_image' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Please note that this was partially fixed in 1.1.0 due to the missing authorization protection that was added.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8629 | WooCommerce Multilingual &amp;amp; Multicurrency with WPML &amp;lt;= 5.3.7 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8629</link><description>The WooCommerce Multilingual &amp; Multicurrency with WPML plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 09:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47195 | A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). gdb.exe in affected applications ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47195</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). gdb.exe in affected applications allows a specific executable file to be loaded from the current working directory. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to inject arbitrary code and escalate privileges in installations where administrators or processes with elevated privileges launch gdb.exe from a user-writable directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47196 | A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). vsimk.exe in affected application...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47196</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). vsimk.exe in affected applications allows a specific tcl file to be loaded from the current working directory. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to inject arbitrary code and escalate privileges in installations where administrators or processes with elevated privileges launch vsimk.exe from a user-writable directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47553 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47553</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly validate user input to the ```ssmctl-client``` command.
This could allow an authenticated, lowly privileged remote attacker to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47562 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47562</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly neutralize special elements in user input to the ```ssmctl-client``` command.
This could allow an authenticated, lowly privileged local attacker to execute privileged commands in the underlying OS.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47563 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47563</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly validate a file path that is supplied to an endpoint intended to create CSR files.
This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to create files in writable directories outside the intended location and thus compromise integrity of files in those writable directories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47565 | A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47565</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Siemens SINEC Security Monitor (All versions &lt; V4.9.0). The affected application does not properly validate that user input complies with a list of allowed values.
This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to compromise the integrity of the configuration of the affected application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4534 | Limit Login Attempts (Spam Protection) &amp;lt;= 5.3 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4534</link><description>The Limit Login Attempts (Spam Protection) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 5.3. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52952 | A vulnerability has been identified in HiMed Cockpit 12 pro (J31032-K2017-H259) (All versions &gt;= V11.5.1 &lt; V11.6.2), HiMed Cockpit 14 pro+ (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52952</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in HiMed Cockpit 12 pro (J31032-K2017-H259) (All versions &gt;= V11.5.1 &lt; V11.6.2), HiMed Cockpit 14 pro+ (J31032-K2017-H435) (All versions &gt;= V11.5.1 &lt; V11.6.2), HiMed Cockpit 18 pro (J31032-K2017-H260) (All versions &gt;= V11.5.1 &lt; V11.6.2), HiMed Cockpit 18 pro+ (J31032-K2017-H436) (All versions &gt;= V11.5.1 &lt; V11.6.2). The Kiosk Mode of the affected devices contains a restricted desktop environment escape vulnerability. This could allow an unauthenticated local attacker to escape the restricted environment and gain access to the underlying operating system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41798 | A vulnerability has been identified in SENTRON 7KM PAC3200 (All versions). Affected devices only provide a 4-digit PIN to protect from admin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41798</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SENTRON 7KM PAC3200 (All versions). Affected devices only provide a 4-digit PIN to protect from administrative access via Modbus TCP interface. Attackers with access to the Modbus TCP interface could easily bypass this protection by brute-force attacks or by sniffing the Modbus clear text communication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41902 | A vulnerability has been identified in JT2Go (All versions &lt; V2406.0003). The affected application contains a stack-based buffer overflow vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41902</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in JT2Go (All versions &lt; V2406.0003). The affected application contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability that could be triggered while parsing specially crafted PDF files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41981 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Nastran 2306 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2312 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2406 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41981</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Nastran 2306 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2312 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.5000). The affected application is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow while parsing specially crafted BDF files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45463 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45463</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45464 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45464</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45465 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45465</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45466 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45466</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds read past the end of an allocated structure while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45467 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45467</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45468 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45468</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45469 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45469</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds write vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted WRL file.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45470 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45470</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds write vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted WRL file.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45471 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45471</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain an out of bounds write vulnerability when parsing a specially crafted WRL file.
This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45472 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45472</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. An attacker could leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45473 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45473</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. An attacker could leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45474 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45474</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. An attacker could leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45475 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45475</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted WRL files. An attacker could leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45476 | A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45476</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2302 (All versions &lt; V2302.0016), Tecnomatix Plant Simulation V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.0005). The affected applications contain a null pointer dereference vulnerability while parsing specially crafted WRL files. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to crash the application causing denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46886 | The web server of affected devices does not properly validate input that is used for a user redirection. This could allow an attacker to mak...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46886</link><description>The web server of affected devices does not properly validate input that is used for a user redirection. This could allow an attacker to make the server redirect the legitimate user to an attacker-chosen URL. For a successful exploit, the legitimate user must actively click on an attacker-crafted link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46887 | The web server of affected devices do not properly authenticate user request to the '/ClientArea/RuntimeInfoData.mwsl' endpoint. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46887</link><description>The web server of affected devices do not properly authenticate user request to the '/ClientArea/RuntimeInfoData.mwsl' endpoint. This could allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to gain knowledge about current actual and configured maximum cycle times as well as about configured maximum communication load.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47046 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Nastran 2306 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2312 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2406 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47046</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Nastran 2306 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2312 (All versions), Simcenter Nastran 2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.5000). The affected application is vulnerable to memory corruption while parsing specially crafted BDF files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47194 | A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). vish2.exe in affected application...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47194</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in ModelSim (All versions &lt; V2024.3), Questa (All versions &lt; V2024.3). vish2.exe in affected applications allows a specific DLL file to be loaded from the current working directory. This could allow an authenticated local attacker to inject arbitrary code and escalate privileges in installations where administrators or processes with elevated privileges launch vish2.exe from a user-writable directory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8911 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.0.11 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary User Password Change via SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8911</link><description>The LatePoint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary User Password Change via SQL Injection in versions up to, and including, 5.0.11. This is due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change user passwords and potentially take over administrator accounts. Note that changing a WordPress user's password is only possible if the "Use WordPress users as customers" setting is enabled, which is disabled by default. Without this setting enabled, only the passwords of plugin customers, which are stored and managed in a separate database table, can be modified.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8943 | LatePoint &amp;lt;= 5.0.12 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8943</link><description>The LatePoint plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in versions up to, and including,  5.0.12. This is due to insufficient verification on the user being supplied during the booking customer step. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as any existing user on the site, such as an administrator, if they have access to the user id. Note that logging in as a WordPress user is only possible if the "Use WordPress users as customers" setting is enabled, which is disabled by default. The vulnerability is partially patched in version 5.0.12 and fully patched in version 5.0.13.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47095 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in Follet School Solutions Destiny</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47095</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Follet School Solutions Destiny before v22.0.1 AU1 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary client-side code via the expiredSupportMessage parameter of handleloginform.do.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8964 | Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv &amp;lt;= 7.2.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8964</link><description>The Image Optimizer, Resizer and CDN – Sirv plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34662 | Improper access control in ActivityManager prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 in select Android 12, 13 and SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 in select And...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34662</link><description>Improper access control in ActivityManager prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 in select Android 12, 13 and SMR Sep-2024 Release 1 in select Android 14 allows local attackers to execute privileged behaviors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34663 | Integer overflow in libSEF.quram.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34663</link><description>Integer overflow in libSEF.quram.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34664 | Improper check for exception conditions in Knox Guard prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Knox Guard in a mu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34664</link><description>Improper check for exception conditions in Knox Guard prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows physical attackers to bypass Knox Guard in a multi-user environment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34665 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.264 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34665</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.264 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34666 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.264 format in a specific mode in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34666</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.264 format in a specific mode in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34667 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.265 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34667</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.265 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34668 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.263 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34668</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.263 format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34669 | Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.263+ format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34669</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in parsing h.263+ format in librtppayload.so prior to SMR Oct-2024 Release 1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code with system privilege. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34670 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Sound Assistant prior to version 6.1.0.9 allows local attackers to get sensitive infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34670</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in Sound Assistant prior to version 6.1.0.9 allows local attackers to get sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34671 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in translation혻in Samsung Internet prior to version 26.0.3.1 allows local attackers to ge...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34671</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication in translation혻in Samsung Internet prior to version 26.0.3.1 allows local attackers to get sensitive information. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34672 | Improper input validation in SamsungVideoPlayer prior to versions 7.3.29.1 in Android 12, 7.3.36.1 in Android 13, and 7.3.41.230 in Android ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34672</link><description>Improper input validation in SamsungVideoPlayer prior to versions 7.3.29.1 in Android 12, 7.3.36.1 in Android 13, and 7.3.41.230 in Android 14 allows local attackers to access video file of other users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7206 | Firmware extraction and Hardware SSL Pinning Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7206</link><description>SSL Pinning Bypass in eWeLink Some hardware products allows local ATTACKER to Decrypt TLS communication and Extract secrets to clone the device via Flash the modified firmware</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:27:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8983 | Custom Twitter Feeds &amp;lt; 2.2.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8983</link><description>Custom Twitter Feeds  WordPress plugin before 2.2.3 is not filtering some of its settings allowing high privilege users to inject scripts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9021 | Relevanssi &amp;lt; 4.23.1 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9021</link><description>In the process of testing the Relevanssi  WordPress plugin before 4.23.1, a vulnerability was found that allows you to implement Stored XSS on behalf of the Contributor+ by embedding malicious script, which entails account takeover backdoor</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:27:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9292 | Bridge Core &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9292</link><description>The Bridge Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'formforall' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 05:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21532 | All versions of the package ggit are vulnerable to Command Injection via the fetchTags(branch) API, which allows user input to specify the b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21532</link><description>All versions of the package ggit are vulnerable to Command Injection via the fetchTags(branch) API, which allows user input to specify the branch to be fetched and then concatenates this string along with a git command which is then passed to the unsafe exec() Node.js child process API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 05:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21533 | All versions of the package ggit are vulnerable to Arbitrary Argument Injection via the clone() API, which allows specifying the remote URL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21533</link><description>All versions of the package ggit are vulnerable to Arbitrary Argument Injection via the clone() API, which allows specifying the remote URL to clone and the file on disk to clone to. The library does not sanitize for user input or validate a given URL scheme, nor does it properly pass command-line flags to the git binary using the double-dash POSIX characters (--) to communicate the end of options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 05:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9026 | PHP-FPM logs from children may be altered</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9026</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.30, 8.2.* before 8.2.24, 8.3.* before 8.3.12, when using PHP-FPM SAPI and it is configured to catch workers output through catch_workers_output = yes, it may be possible to pollute the final log or remove up to 4 characters from the log messages by manipulating log message content. Additionally, if PHP-FPM is configured to use syslog output, it may be possible to further remove log data using the same vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8927 | cgi.force_redirect configuration is bypassable due to the environment variable collision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8927</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.30, 8.2.* before 8.2.24, 8.3.* before 8.3.12, HTTP_REDIRECT_STATUS variable is used to check whether or not CGI binary is being run by the HTTP server. However, in certain scenarios, the content of this variable can be controlled by the request submitter via HTTP headers, which can lead to cgi.force_redirect option not being correctly applied. In certain configurations this may lead to arbitrary file inclusion in PHP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:21:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8926 | PHP CGI Parameter Injection Vulnerability (CVE-2024-4577 bypass)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8926</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.30, 8.2.* before 8.2.24, 8.3.* before 8.3.12, when using a certain non-standard configurations of Windows codepages, the fixes for  CVE-2024-4577 https://github.com/advisories/GHSA-vxpp-6299-mxw3  may still be bypassed and the same command injection related to Windows "Best Fit" codepage behavior can be achieved. This may allow a malicious user to pass options to PHP binary being run, and thus reveal the source code of scripts, run arbitrary PHP code on the server, etc.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:56:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8925 | Erroneous parsing of multipart form data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8925</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.30, 8.2.* before 8.2.24, 8.3.* before 8.3.12, erroneous parsing of multipart form data contained in an HTTP POST request could lead to legitimate data not being processed. This could lead to malicious attacker able to control part of the submitted data being able to exclude portion of other data, potentially leading to erroneous application behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37179 | Insecure File Operations vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (Web Intelligence)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37179</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform allows an authenticated user to send a specially crafted request to the Web Intelligence Reporting Server to download any file from the machine hosting the service, causing high impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45277 | Prototype Pollution vulnerability in SAP HANA Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45277</link><description>The SAP HANA Node.js client package versions from 2.0.0 before 2.21.31 is impacted by Prototype Pollution vulnerability allowing an attacker to add arbitrary properties to global object prototypes. This is due to improper user input sanitation when using the nestTables feature causing low impact on the availability of the application. This has no impact on Confidentiality and Integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45278 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP Commerce Backoffice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45278</link><description>SAP Commerce Backoffice does not sufficiently encode user controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. After successful exploitation, an attacker can cause limited impact on confidentiality and integrity of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45282 | HTTP Verb Tampering in SAP S/4 HANA(Manage Bank Statements)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45282</link><description>Fields which are in 'read only' state in Bank Statement Draft in Manage Bank Statements application, could be modified by MERGE method. The property of an OData entity representing assumably immutable method is not protected against external modifications leading to integrity violations. Confidentiality and Availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47594 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal (KMC)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47594</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Enterprise Portal (KMC) does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, resulting in Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in KMC servlet. An attacker could craft a script and trick the user into clicking it. When a victim who is registered on the portal clicks on such link, confidentiality and integrity of their web browser session could be compromised.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39806 | Liteos_a has an out-of-bounds Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39806</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause information leak through out-of-bounds Read.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39831 | AccessTokenManager has an use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39831</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 allow a local attacker with high privileges arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43696 | Liteos_a has an Memory Leak vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43696</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS by memory leak.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43697 | Liteos_a has an Improper Input Validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43697</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45382 | Liteos_a has an Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45382</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.1.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 03:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47969 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47969</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47781 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Special:RequestWikiQueue when displaying sitename in CreateWiki</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47781</link><description>CreateWiki is an extension used at Miraheze for requesting &amp; creating wikis. The name of requested wikis is not escaped on Special:RequestWikiQueue, so a user can insert arbitrary HTML that is displayed in the request wiki queue when requesting a wiki. If a wiki creator comes across the XSS payload, their user session can be abused to retrieve deleted wiki requests, which typically contains private information. Likewise, this can also be abused on those with the ability to suppress requests to view sensitive information. This issue has been patched with commit `693a220` and all users are advised to apply the patch. Users unable to upgrade should disable Javascript and/or prevent access to the vulnerable page (Special:RequestWikiQueue).</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47782 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in Special:WikiDiscover when displaying wiki information in WikiDiscover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47782</link><description>WikiDiscover is an extension designed for use with a CreateWiki managed farm to display wikis. Special:WikiDiscover is a special page that lists all wikis on the wiki farm. However, the special page does not make any effort to escape the wiki name or description. Therefore, if a wiki sets its name and/or description to an XSS payload, the XSS will execute whenever the wiki is shown on Special:WikiDiscover. This issue has been patched with commit `2ce846dd93` and all users are advised to apply that patch. User unable to upgrade should block access to `Special:WikiDiscover`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47817 | Unvalidated paragraph widget values can be used for Cross-site Scripting in lara-zeus</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47817</link><description>Lara-zeus Dynamic Dashboard simple way to manage widgets for your website landing page, and filament dashboard and Lara-zeus artemis is a collection of themes for the lara-zeus ecosystem. If values passed to a paragraph widget are not valid and contain a specific set of characters, applications are vulnerable to XSS attack against a user who opens a page on which a paragraph widget is rendered. Users are advised to upgrade to the appropriate fix versions detailed in the advisory metadata. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47968 | Improper resource shutdown in middle of certain operations on some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47968</link><description>Improper resource shutdown in middle of certain operations on some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45873 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in VegaBird Yaazhini 2.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code / maintain persistence via placing a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45873</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in VegaBird Yaazhini 2.0.2 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code / maintain persistence via placing a crafted DLL file in the same directory as Yaazhini.exe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45874 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in VegaBird Vooki 5.2.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code / maintain persistence via placing a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45874</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in VegaBird Vooki 5.2.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code / maintain persistence via placing a crafted DLL file in the same directory as Vooki.exe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47814 | use-after-free when closing buffers in Vim</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47814</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. A use-after-free was found in Vim &lt; 9.1.0764. When closing a buffer (visible in a window) a BufWinLeave auto command can cause an use-after-free if this auto command happens to re-open the same buffer in a new split window. Impact is low since the user must have intentionally set up such a strange auto command and run some buffer unload commands. However this may lead to a crash. This issue has been addressed in version 9.1.0764 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47818 | Logged-in users with any role can delete arbitrary files in @saltcorn/server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47818</link><description>Saltcorn is an extensible, open source, no-code database application builder. A logged-in user with any role can delete arbitrary files on the filesystem by calling the `sync/clean_sync_dir` endpoint. The `dir_name` POST parameter is not validated/sanitized and is used to construct the `syncDir` that is deleted by calling `fs.rm`. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.0.0-beta16 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45919 | A security flaw has been discovered in Solvait version 24.4.2 that allows an attacker to elevate their privileges. By manipulating the Reque...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45919</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Solvait version 24.4.2 that allows an attacker to elevate their privileges. By manipulating the Request ID and Action Type parameters in /AssignToMe/SetAction, an attacker can bypass approval workflows leading to unauthorized access to sensitive information or approval of fraudulent requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47967 | Improper resource initialization handling in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47967</link><description>Improper resource initialization handling in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47772 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via chat excerpts when content security policy (CSP) disabled in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47772</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. An attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript on users' browsers by sending a maliciously crafted chat message and replying to it. This issue only affects sites with CSP disabled. This problem is patched in the latest version of Discourse. All users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should ensure CSP is enabled on the forum. Users who do upgrade should also consider enabling a CSP as well as a proactive measure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47974 | Race condition during resource shutdown in some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47974</link><description>Race condition during resource shutdown in some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:13:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47610 | Stored Cross-site Scripting Vulnerability in Markdown Editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47610</link><description>InvenTree is an Open Source Inventory Management System. In affected versions of InvenTree it is possible for a registered user to store javascript in markdown notes fields, which are then displayed to other logged in users who visit the same page and executed. The vulnerability has been addressed as follows: 1. HTML sanitization has been enabled in the front-end markdown rendering library - `easymde`. 2. Stored markdown is also validated on the backend, to ensure that malicious markdown is not stored in the database. These changes are available in release versions 0.16.5 and later. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no workarounds, an update is required to get the new validation functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43362 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when creating external links in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43362</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. The `fileurl` parameter is not properly sanitized when saving external links in `links.php` . Morever, the said fileurl is placed in some html code which is passed to the `print` function in `link.php` and `index.php`, finally leading to stored XSS. Users with the privilege to create external links can manipulate the `fileurl` parameter in the http post request while creating external links to perform stored XSS attacks. The vulnerability known as XSS (Cross-Site Scripting) occurs when an application allows untrusted user input to be displayed on a web page without proper validation or escaping. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.2.28. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43363 | Remote code execution via Log Poisoning in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43363</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. An admin user can create a device with a malicious hostname containing php code and repeat the installation process (completing only step 5 of the installation process is enough, no need to complete the steps before or after it) to use a php file as the cacti log file. After having the malicious hostname end up in the logs (log poisoning), one can simply go to the log file url to execute commands to achieve RCE. This issue has been addressed in version 1.2.28 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43364 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when creating external links in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43364</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. The `title` parameter is not properly sanitized when saving external links in links.php . Morever, the said title parameter is stored in the database and reflected back to user in index.php, finally leading to stored XSS. Users with the privilege to create external links can manipulate the `title` parameter in the http post request while creating external links to perform stored XSS attacks. The vulnerability known as XSS (Cross-Site Scripting) occurs when an application allows untrusted user input to be displayed on a web page without proper validation or escaping. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.2.28. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43365 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) when creating external links in Cacti</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43365</link><description>Cacti is an open source performance and fault management framework. The`consolenewsection` parameter is not properly sanitized when saving external links in links.php . Morever, the said consolenewsection parameter is stored in the database and reflected back to user in `index.php`, finally leading to stored XSS. Users with the privilege to create external links can manipulate the “consolenewsection” parameter in the http post request while creating external links to perform stored XSS attacks. The vulnerability known as XSS (Cross-Site Scripting) occurs when an application allows untrusted user input to be displayed on a web page without proper validation or escaping. This issue has been addressed in release version 1.2.28. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47973 | In some Solidigm DC Products, a defect in device overprovisioning may provide information disclosure to an attacker.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47973</link><description>In some Solidigm DC Products, a defect in device overprovisioning may provide information disclosure to an attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:44:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43789 | Denial of service by the absence of restrictions on replies to posts in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43789</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. A user can create a post with many replies, and then attempt to fetch them all at once. This can potentially reduce the availability of a Discourse instance. This problem has been patched in the latest version of Discourse. All users area are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45051 | Bypass of email address validation via encoded email addresses in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45051</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. A maliciously crafted email address could allow an attacker to bypass domain-based restrictions and gain access to private sites, categories and/or groups. This issue has been patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. All users area are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45297 | Prevent topic list filtering by hidden tags for unauthorized users in Discourse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45297</link><description>Discourse is an open source platform for community discussion. Users can see topics with a hidden tag if they know the label/name of that tag. This issue has been patched in the latest stable, beta and tests-passed version of Discourse. All users area are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45060 | Unauthenticated Cross-Site-Scripting (XSS) in sample file in PHPSpreadsheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45060</link><description>PHPSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. One of the sample scripts in PhpSpreadsheet is susceptible to a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to improper handling of input where a number is expected leading to formula injection. The code in in `45_Quadratic_equation_solver.php` concatenates the user supplied parameters directly into spreadsheet formulas. This allows an attacker to take control over the formula and output unsanitized data into the page, resulting in JavaScript execution. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.29.2, 2.1.1, and 2.3.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45290 | Path traversal and Server-Side Request Forgery when opening XLSX files in PHPSpreadsheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45290</link><description>PHPSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. It's possible for an attacker to construct an XLSX file which links media from external URLs. When opening the XLSX file, PhpSpreadsheet retrieves the image size and type by reading the file contents, if the provided path is a URL. By using specially crafted `php://filter` URLs an attacker can leak the contents of any file or URL. Note that this vulnerability is different from GHSA-w9xv-qf98-ccq4, and resides in a different component. An attacker can access any file on the server, or leak information form arbitrary URLs, potentially exposing sensitive information such as AWS IAM credentials. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.29.2, 2.1.1, and 2.3.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45291 | Path traversal and Server-Side Request Forgery in HTML writer when embedding images is enabled in PHPSpreadsheet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45291</link><description>PHPSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. It's possible for an attacker to construct an XLSX file that links images from arbitrary paths. When embedding images has been enabled in HTML writer with `$writer-&gt;setEmbedImages(true);` those files will be included in the output as `data:` URLs, regardless of the file's type. Also URLs can be used for embedding, resulting in a Server-Side Request Forgery vulnerability. When embedding images has been enabled, an attacker can read arbitrary files on the server and perform arbitrary HTTP GET requests. Note that any PHP protocol wrappers can be used, meaning that if for example the `expect://` wrapper is enabled, also remote code execution is possible. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.29.2, 2.1.1, and 2.3.0. All users are advised to upgrade. there are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45292 | PhpSpreadsheet HTML writer is vulnerable to Cross-Site Scripting via JavaScript hyperlinks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45292</link><description>PHPSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. `\PhpOffice\PhpSpreadsheet\Writer\Html` does not sanitize "javascript:" URLs from hyperlink `href` attributes, resulting in a Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.29.2, 2.1.1, and 2.3.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45293 | XML External Entity Reference (XXE) in PHPSpreadsheet&amp;#x27;s XLSX reader</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45293</link><description>PHPSpreadsheet is a pure PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. The security scanner responsible for preventing XXE attacks in the XLSX reader can be bypassed by slightly modifying the XML structure, utilizing white-spaces. On servers that allow users to upload their own Excel (XLSX) sheets, Server files and sensitive information can be disclosed by providing a crafted sheet. The security scan function in src/PhpSpreadsheet/Reader/Security/XmlScanner.php contains a flawed XML encoding check to retrieve the input file's XML encoding in the toUtf8 function. The function searches for the XML encoding through a defined regex which looks for `encoding="*"` and/or `encoding='*'`, if not found, it defaults to the UTF-8 encoding which bypasses the conversion logic. This logic can be used to pass a UTF-7 encoded XXE payload, by utilizing a whitespace before or after the = in the attribute definition. Sensitive information disclosure through the XXE on sites that allow users to upload their own excel spreadsheets, and parse them using PHPSpreadsheet's Excel parser. This issue has been addressed in release versions 1.29.1, 2.1.1, and 2.3.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47079 | Unauthorized usage of remote hardware module because of missing channel verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47079</link><description>Meshtastic is an open source, off-grid, decentralized, mesh network built to run on affordable, low-power devices. Meshtastic firmware is an open source firmware implementation for the broader project. The remote hardware module of the firmware does not have proper checks to ensure a remote hardware control message was received should be considered valid. This issue has been addressed in release version 2.5.1. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31227 | Denial-of-service due to malformed ACL selectors in Redis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31227</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. An authenticated with sufficient privileges may create a malformed ACL selector which, when accessed, triggers a server panic and subsequent denial of service. The problem exists in Redis 7 prior to versions 7.2.6 and 7.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31228 | Denial-of-service due to unbounded pattern matching in Redis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31228</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. Authenticated users can trigger a denial-of-service by using specially crafted, long string match patterns on supported commands such as `KEYS`, `SCAN`, `PSUBSCRIBE`, `FUNCTION LIST`, `COMMAND LIST` and ACL definitions. Matching of extremely long patterns may result in unbounded recursion, leading to stack overflow and process crash. This problem has been fixed in Redis versions 6.2.16, 7.2.6, and 7.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31449 | Lua library commands may lead to stack overflow and RCE in Redis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31449</link><description>Redis is an open source, in-memory database that persists on disk. An authenticated user may use a specially crafted Lua script to trigger a stack buffer overflow in the bit library, which may potentially lead to remote code execution. The problem exists in all versions of Redis with Lua scripting. This problem has been fixed in Redis versions 6.2.16, 7.2.6, and 7.4.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47971 | Improper error handling in firmware of some SSD DC Products may allow an attacker to enable denial of service.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47971</link><description>Improper error handling in firmware of some SSD DC Products may allow an attacker to enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47972 | Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially control the performance of the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47972</link><description>Improper resource management in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker to potentially control the performance of the resource.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47976 | Improper access removal handling in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with physical access to gain unauthorized ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47976</link><description>Improper access removal handling in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with physical access to gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47975 | Improper access control validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with physical access to gain unauthorized ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47975</link><description>Improper access control validation in firmware of some Solidigm DC Products may allow an attacker with physical access to gain unauthorized access or an attacker with local access to potentially enable denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:09:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44068 | An issue was discovered in the m2m scaler driver in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850,and W92...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44068</link><description>An issue was discovered in the m2m scaler driver in Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850,and W920. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45894 | BlueCMS 1.6 suffers from Arbitrary File Deletion via the file_name parameter in an /admin/database.php?act=del request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45894</link><description>BlueCMS 1.6 suffers from Arbitrary File Deletion via the file_name parameter in an /admin/database.php?act=del request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47556 | Pre-Auth RCE via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47556</link><description>Pre-Auth RCE via Path Traversal</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47557 | Pre-Auth RCE via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47557</link><description>Pre-Auth RCE via Path Traversal</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47558 | Authenticated RCE via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47558</link><description>Authenticated RCE via Path Traversal</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47559 | Authenticated RCE via Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47559</link><description>Authenticated RCE via Path Traversal</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42831 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Elaine's Realtime CRM Automation v6.18.17 allows attackers to execute arbitrary Java...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42831</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Elaine's Realtime CRM Automation v6.18.17 allows attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the web browser of a user via injecting a crafted payload into the dialog parameter at wrapper_dialog.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44674 | D-Link COVR-2600R FW101b05 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. In the function sub_24E28, the HTTP_REFERER is obtained through an environment ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44674</link><description>D-Link COVR-2600R FW101b05 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow. In the function sub_24E28, the HTTP_REFERER is obtained through an environment variable, and this field is controllable, allowing it to be used as the value for src.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 18:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47555 | Missing Authentication - User &amp;amp; System Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47555</link><description>Missing Authentication - User &amp; System Configuration</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:57:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46076 | RuoYi v4.7.9 and before has a security flaw that allows escaping from comments within the code generation feature, enabling the injection of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46076</link><description>RuoYi v4.7.9 and before has a security flaw that allows escaping from comments within the code generation feature, enabling the injection of malicious code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:47:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27458 | A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Hotkey Support software, which might allow local escalation of privilege. H...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27458</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Hotkey Support software, which might allow local escalation of privilege. HP is releasing mitigation for the potential vulnerability. Customers using HP Programmable Key are recommended to update HP Hotkey Support.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46300 | itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46300</link><description>itsourcecode Placement Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the Full Name field in registration.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46278 | Teedy 1.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the management console.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46278</link><description>Teedy 1.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the management console.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46446 | Mecha CMS 3.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. An attacker can construct cookies and URIs that bypass user identity checks. Parameter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46446</link><description>Mecha CMS 3.0.0 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. An attacker can construct cookies and URIs that bypass user identity checks. Parameters can then be passed through the POST method, resulting in the Deletion of Arbitrary Files or Website Takeover.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46041 | IoT Haat Smart Plug IH-IN-16A-S v5.16.1 is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46041</link><description>IoT Haat Smart Plug IH-IN-16A-S v5.16.1 is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46040 | IoT Haat Smart Plug IH-IN-16A-S IH-IN-16A-S v5.16.1 suffers from Insufficient Session Expiration. The lack of validation of the authenticati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46040</link><description>IoT Haat Smart Plug IH-IN-16A-S IH-IN-16A-S v5.16.1 suffers from Insufficient Session Expiration. The lack of validation of the authentication token at the IoT Haat during the Access Point Pairing mode leads the attacker to replay the Wi-Fi packets and forcefully turn off the access point after the authentication token has expired.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9570 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formEasySetTimezone buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formEasySetTimezone of the file /goform/formEasySetTimezone. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:43:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28709 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in LimeSurvey before 6.5.12+240611 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28709</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in LimeSurvey before 6.5.12+240611 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the title and comment fields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28710 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in LimeSurvey before 6.5.0+240319 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a lack of input ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28710</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in LimeSurvey before 6.5.0+240319 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a lack of input validation and output encoding in the Alert Widget's message component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45932 | Krayin CRM v1.3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the organization name field in /admin/contacts/organizations/edit/2.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45932</link><description>Krayin CRM v1.3.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via the organization name field in /admin/contacts/organizations/edit/2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6361 | A vulnerability has been discovered in Winhex affecting version 16.1 SR-1 and 20.4. This vulnerability consists of a buffer overflow control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6361</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Winhex affecting version 16.1 SR-1 and 20.4. This vulnerability consists of a buffer overflow controlling the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) registers. This could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a long filename argument.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6362 | A vulnerability has been discovered in Winhex affecting version 16.1 SR-1 and 20.4. This vulnerability consists of a buffer overflow control...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6362</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Winhex affecting version 16.1 SR-1 and 20.4. This vulnerability consists of a buffer overflow controlling the Structured Exception Handler (SEH) registers. This could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code via a long filename argument.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45933 | OnlineNewsSite v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the Title and summary f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45933</link><description>OnlineNewsSite v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) which allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the Title and summary fields in the /admin/post/edit/ endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9569 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formEasySetPassword buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9569</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formEasySetPassword of the file /goform/formEasySetPassword. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9574 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9574</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SOPlanning &lt;1.45, via /soplanning/www/user_groupes.php in the by parameter, which could allow a remote user to submit a specially crafted query, allowing an attacker to retrieve all the information stored in the DB.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9571 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9571</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SOPlanning &lt;1.45, due to lack of proper validation of user input via /soplanning/www/process/xajax_server.php, affecting multiple parameters. This could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and partially take control of their browser session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9572 | Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9572</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SOPlanning &lt;1.45, due to lack of proper validation of user input via /soplanning/www/process/groupe_save.php, in the groupe_id parameter. This could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal their session details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9573 | SQL Injection vulnerability in SOPlanning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9573</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SOPlanning &lt;1.45, through /soplanning/www/groupe_list.php, in the by parameter, which could allow a remote user to send a specially crafted query and extract all the information stored on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9568 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formAdvNetwork buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9568</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. Affected is the function formAdvNetwork of the file /goform/formAdvNetwork. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9576 | Improper access control in Linux Workbooth Distro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9576</link><description>Vulnerability in Distro Linux Workbooth v2.5 that allows to escalate privileges to the root user by manipulating the network configuration script.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9567 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formAdvFirewall buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9567</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. This issue affects the function formAdvFirewall of the file /goform/formAdvFirewall. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21455 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21455</link><description>Memory corruption when a compat IOCTL call is followed by another IOCTL call from userspace to a driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23369 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23369</link><description>Memory corruption when invalid length is provided from HLOS for FRS/UDS request/response buffers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23370 | Use After Free in Automotive Multimedia</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23370</link><description>Memory corruption when a process invokes IOCTL calls from user-space to create a HAB virtual channel and another process invokes IOCTL calls to destroy the same.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23374 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in Power Management IC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23374</link><description>Memory corruption is possible when an attempt is made from userspace or console to write some haptics effects pattern to the haptics debugfs file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23375 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in RIL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23375</link><description>Memory corruption during the network scan request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23376 | Use After Free in ComputerVision</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23376</link><description>Memory corruption while sending the persist buffer command packet from the user-space to the kernel space through the IOCTL call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23378 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23378</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls for MSM module from the user space during audio playback and record.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23379 | Double Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23379</link><description>Memory corruption while unmapping the fastrpc map when two threads can free the same map in concurrent scenario.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33049 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33049</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing noninheritance IE of Extension element when length of IE is 2 of beacon frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33064 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33064</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing the multiple MBSSID IEs from the beacon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33065 | Improper Input Validation in Camera</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33065</link><description>Memory corruption while taking snapshot when an offset variable is set by camera driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33066 | Improper Input Validation in WLAN Resource Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33066</link><description>Memory corruption while redirecting log file to any file location with any file name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33069 | Use After Free in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33069</link><description>Transient DOS when transmission of management frame sent by host is not successful and error status is received in the host.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33070 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33070</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing ESP IE from beacon/probe response frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33071 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33071</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the MBSSID IE from the beacons when IE length is 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33073 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33073</link><description>Information disclosure while parsing the BSS parameter change count or MLD capabilities fields of the ML IE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38397 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38397</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing probe response and assoc response frame.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38399 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38399</link><description>Memory corruption while processing user packets to generate page faults.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38425 | Improper Authorization in Performance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38425</link><description>Information disclosure while sending implicit broadcast containing APP launch information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43047 | Use After Free in DSP Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43047</link><description>Memory corruption while maintaining memory maps of HLOS memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9566 | D-Link DIR-619L B1 formDeviceReboot buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9566</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-619L B1 2.06. This vulnerability affects the function formDeviceReboot of the file /goform/formDeviceReboot. The manipulation of the argument next_page leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42027 | The E2EE password entropy generated by Rocket.Chat Mobile prior to version 4.5.1 is insufficient, allowing attackers to crack it if they hav...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42027</link><description>The E2EE password entropy generated by Rocket.Chat Mobile prior to version 4.5.1 is insufficient, allowing attackers to crack it if they have the appropriate time and resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46325 | TP-Link WR740N V6 has a stack overflow vulnerability via the ssid parameter in /userRpm/popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm url.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46325</link><description>TP-Link WR740N V6 has a stack overflow vulnerability via the ssid parameter in /userRpm/popupSiteSurveyRpm.htm url.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45153 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45153</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.20 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47344 | WordPress uListing plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47344</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in StylemixThemes uListing.This issue affects uListing: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 05:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47335 | WordPress Bit Form plugin &amp;lt;= 2.13.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47335</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Bit Form Bit Form – Contact Form Plugin allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Bit Form – Contact Form Plugin: from n/a through 2.13.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 05:35:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20090 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20090</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09028313; Issue ID: MSV-1703.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20091 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20091</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09028313; Issue ID: MSV-1701.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20092 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20092</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09028313; Issue ID: MSV-1700.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20093 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20093</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09028313; Issue ID: MSV-1699.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20094 | In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20094</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00843282; Issue ID: MSV-1535.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20095 | In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20095</link><description>In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08996894; Issue ID: MSV-1636.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20096 | In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20096</link><description>In m4u, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08996900; Issue ID: MSV-1635.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20097 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20097</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09028313; Issue ID: MSV-1630.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20098 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20098</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08996886; Issue ID: MSV-1626.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20099 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20099</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08997492; Issue ID: MSV-1625.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20100 | In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20100</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08998449; Issue ID: MSV-1603.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20101 | In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20101</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08998901; Issue ID: MSV-1602.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20102 | In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20102</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bounds read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08998892; Issue ID: MSV-1601.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20103 | In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20103</link><description>In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09001358; Issue ID: MSV-1599.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 02:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9565 | D-Link DIR-605L formSetPassword buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9565</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01 BETA and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetPassword of the file /goform/formSetPassword. The manipulation of the argument curTime leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 01:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9564 | D-Link DIR-605L formWlanWizardSetup buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9564</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-605L 2.13B01 BETA. Affected is the function formWlanWizardSetup of the file /goform/formWlanWizardSetup. The manipulation of the argument webpage leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 01:48:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>