<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 13:26:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6114 | itsourcecode Monbela Tourist Inn Online Reservation System controller.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6114</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Monbela Tourist Inn Online Reservation System up to 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file controller.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 13:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6115 | itsourcecode Simple Online Hotel Reservation System add_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6115</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add_room.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268867.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 13:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6111 | itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6111</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268857 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 12:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6112 | itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6112</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument log_email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 12:48:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5967 | Keycloak: leak of configured ldap bind credentials through the keycloak admin console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5967</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. The LDAP testing endpoint allows changing the Connection URL  independently without re-entering the currently configured LDAP bind credentials. This flaw allows an attacker with admin access (permission manage-realm) to change the LDAP host URL ("Connection URL") to a machine they control. The Keycloak server will connect to the attacker's host and try to authenticate with the configured credentials, thus leaking them to the attacker. As a consequence, an attacker who has compromised the admin console or compromised a user with sufficient privileges can leak domain credentials and attack the domain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 12:16:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6109 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System addmeasurement.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6109</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file addmeasurement.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268855.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6110 | itsourcecode Magbanua Beach Resort Online Reservation System controller.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6110</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Magbanua Beach Resort Online Reservation System up to 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file controller.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268856.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38504 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 the Guest User Account was enabled for attaching files to articles</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38504</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 the Guest User Account was enabled for attaching files to articles</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38505 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 user access token was sent to the third-party site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38505</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 user access token was sent to the third-party site</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38506 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 user without appropriate permissions could enable the auto-attach option for workflows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38506</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2024.2.34646 user without appropriate permissions could enable the auto-attach option for workflows</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38507 | In JetBrains Hub before 2024.2.34646 stored XSS via project description was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38507</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2024.2.34646 stored XSS via project description was possible</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5953 | 389-ds-base: malformed userpassword hash may cause denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5953</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability was found in the 389-ds-base LDAP server. This issue may allow an authenticated user to cause a server denial of service while attempting to log in with a user with a malformed hash in their password.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6108 | Genexis Tilgin Home Gateway Login cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Genexis Tilgin Home Gateway 322_AS0500-03_05_13_05. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /vood/cgi-bin/vood_view.cgi?act=index&amp;lang;=EN# of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument errmsg leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-268854 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5899 | Improper trust check in Bazel Build intellij plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5899</link><description>When Bazel Plugin in intellij imports a project (either using "import project" or "Auto import") the dialog for trusting the project is not displayed. This comes from the fact that both call the method ProjectBuilder.createProject which then calls ProjectManager.getInstance().createProject. This method, as its name suggests is intended to create a new project, not to import an existing one. 
We recommend upgrading to version 2024.06.04.0.2 or beyond for the IntelliJ, CLion and Android Studio Bazel plugins.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 08:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5533 | Divi &amp;lt;= 4.25.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5533</link><description>The Divi theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in all versions up to, and including, 4.25.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 07:55:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0066 | Johan Fagerström, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that a O3C feature may expose sensitive traffic between the client (Ax...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0066</link><description>Johan Fagerström, member of the AXIS OS Bug Bounty Program, has found that a O3C feature may expose sensitive traffic between the client (Axis device) and (O3C) server. If O3C is not being used this flaw does not apply. 
Axis has released patched AXIS OS versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3276 | FooBox (Free and Premium) &amp;lt; 2.7.28 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3276</link><description>The Lightbox &amp; Modal Popup WordPress Plugin  WordPress plugin before 2.7.28, foobox-image-lightbox-premium WordPress plugin before 2.7.28 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4094 | Simple Share Buttons Adder &amp;lt; 8.5.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4094</link><description>The Simple Share Buttons Adder WordPress plugin before 8.5.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as editors to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5172 | Expert Invoice &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 -Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5172</link><description>The Expert Invoice WordPress plugin through 1.0.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5527 | Business Directory Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4.3 - Authenticated (Author+) CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5527</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to CSV Injection in versions up to, and including, 6.4.3 via the class-csv-exporter.php file. This allows authenticated attackers, with author-level permissions and above, to embed untrusted input into CSV files exported by administrators, which can result in code execution when these files are downloaded and opened on a local system with a vulnerable configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33620 | Absolute path traversal vulnerability exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerability is exploited, the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33620</link><description>Absolute path traversal vulnerability exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerability is exploited, the file contents including sensitive information on the server may be retrieved by an unauthenticated remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33622 | Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33622</link><description>Missing authentication for critical function vulnerability exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerability is exploited, sensitive information may be obtained and/or the information stored in the database may be altered by a remote authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34024 | Observable response discrepancy issue exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerability is exploited, an un...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34024</link><description>Observable response discrepancy issue exists in ID Link Manager and FUJITSU Software TIME CREATOR. If this vulnerability is exploited, an unauthenticated remote attacker may determine if a username is valid or not.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37079 | vCenter Server contains a heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37079</link><description>vCenter Server contains a heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted network packet potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37080 | vCenter Server contains a heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37080</link><description>vCenter Server contains a heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCERPC protocol. A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted network packet potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37081 | The vCenter Server contains multiple local privilege escalation vulnerabilities due to misconfiguration of sudo. An authenticated local user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37081</link><description>The vCenter Server contains multiple local privilege escalation vulnerabilities due to misconfiguration of sudo. An authenticated local user with non-administrative privileges may exploit these issues to elevate privileges to root on vCenter Server Appliance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 05:53:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5860 | Tickera &amp;lt;= 3.5.2.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Susbcriber+) Ticket Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5860</link><description>The Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the tc_dl_delete_tickets AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete all tickets associated with events.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 03:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0845 | PDF Viewer for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via render</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0845</link><description>The PDF Viewer for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the render function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1634 | Scheduling Plugin – Online Booking for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.5.10 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Service Disconnection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1634</link><description>The Scheduling Plugin – Online Booking for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'cbsb_disconnect_settings' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.10. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect the plugin from the startbooking service and remove connection data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4375 | Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider &amp;lt;= 3.9.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ms_layer Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4375</link><description>The Master Slider – Responsive Touch Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ms_layer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'css_id' user supplied attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5541 | Ibtana - WordPress Website Builder &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.3 - Unauthenticated reCAPTCHA Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5541</link><description>The Ibtana – WordPress Website Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'ibtana_visual_editor_register_ajax_json_endpont' function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update option values for reCAPTCHA keys on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to bypass reCAPTCHA on the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6084 | itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System uploadImage unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6084</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Pool of Bethesda Online Reservation System up to 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function uploadImage of the file /admin/mod_room/controller.php?action=add. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268825 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6083 | PHPVibe Media Upload Page upload-mp3.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6083</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPVibe 11.0.46. Affected is an unknown function of the file /app/uploading/upload-mp3.php of the component Media Upload Page. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268824. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 23:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6080 | Intelbras InControl unquoted search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6080</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Intelbras InControl 2.21.56. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to unquoted search path. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 23:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6082 | PHPVibe Global Options Page functionalities.global.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6082</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPVibe 11.0.46. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file functionalities.global.php of the component Global Options Page. The manipulation of the argument site-logo-text leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268823. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 23:22:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6067 | SourceCodester Music Class Enrollment System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6067</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Music Class Enrollment System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /mces/?p=class/view_class. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268795.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6065 | itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6065</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Bakery Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument user_email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268793 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6066 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System payment_report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6066</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file payment_report.php. The manipulation of the argument month_of leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268794 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 21:15:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37828 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in Vermeg Agile Reporter v23.2.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37828</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) in Vermeg Agile Reporter v23.2.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Message field under the Set Broadcast Message module.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6063 | GPAC MP4Box dmx_m2ts.c m2tsdmx_on_event null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6063</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GPAC 2.5-DEV-rev228-g11067ea92-master. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function m2tsdmx_on_event of the file src/filters/dmx_m2ts.c of the component MP4Box. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 8767ed0a77c4b02287db3723e92c2169f67c85d5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268791.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6064 | GPAC MP4Box loader_xmt.c xmt_node_end use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6064</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GPAC 2.5-DEV-rev228-g11067ea92-master. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function xmt_node_end of the file src/scene_manager/loader_xmt.c of the component MP4Box. The manipulation leads to use after free. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is f4b3e4d2f91bc1749e7a924a8ab171af03a355a8/c1b9c794bad8f262c56f3cf690567980d96662f5. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268792.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37057 | An issue in JLINK Unionman Technology Co. Ltd Jlink AX1800 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the router's authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37057</link><description>An issue in JLINK Unionman Technology Co. Ltd Jlink AX1800 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the router's authentication mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34833 | Sourcecodester Payroll Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload. Users can upload images via the "save_settings" page. An unauthe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34833</link><description>Sourcecodester Payroll Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to File Upload. Users can upload images via the "save_settings" page. An unauthenticated attacker can leverage this functionality to upload a malicious PHP file instead. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability results in the ability to execute arbitrary code as the user running the web server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37058 | Insecure Permissions vulnerability in JLINK Unionman Technology Co. Ltd Jlink AX1800 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37058</link><description>Insecure Permissions vulnerability in JLINK Unionman Technology Co. Ltd Jlink AX1800 v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37798 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in search-appointment.php in the Admin Panel in Phpgurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0 all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37798</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in search-appointment.php in the Admin Panel in Phpgurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the search input field.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37305 | Buffer overflow in deserialization in oqs-provider</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37305</link><description>oqs-provider is a provider for the OpenSSL 3 cryptography library that adds support for post-quantum cryptography in TLS, X.509, and S/MIME using post-quantum algorithms from liboqs. Flaws have been identified in the way oqs-provider handles lengths decoded with DECODE_UINT32 at the start of serialized hybrid (traditional + post-quantum) keys and signatures. Unchecked length values are later used for memory reads and writes; malformed input can lead to crashes or information leakage. Handling of plain/non-hybrid PQ key operation is not affected. This issue has been patched in in v0.6.1. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no workarounds for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37893 | MFA bypass in oauth flow in Firefly III</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37893</link><description>Firefly III is a free and open source personal finance manager. In affected versions an MFA bypass in the Firefly III OAuth flow may allow malicious users to bypass the MFA-check. This allows malicious users to use password spraying to gain access to Firefly III data using passwords stolen from other sources. As OAuth applications are easily enumerable using an incrementing id, an attacker could try sign an OAuth application up to a users profile quite easily if they have created one. The attacker would also need to know the victims username and password. This problem has been patched in Firefly III v6.1.17 and up. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should Use a unique password for their Firefly III instance and store their password securely, i.e. in a password manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37896 | SQL injection vulnerability in Gin-vue-admin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37896</link><description>Gin-vue-admin is a backstage management system based on vue and gin. Gin-vue-admin &lt;= v2.6.5 has SQL injection vulnerability. The SQL injection vulnerabilities occur when a web application allows users to input data into SQL queries without sufficiently validating or sanitizing the input. Failing to properly enforce restrictions on user input could mean that even a basic form input field can be used to inject arbitrary and potentially dangerous SQL commands. This could lead to unauthorized access to the database, data leakage, data manipulation, or even complete compromise of the database server. This vulnerability has been addressed in commit `53d033821` which has been included in release version 2.6.6. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37895 | API Key Leak in lobe-chat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37895</link><description>Lobe Chat is an open-source LLMs/AI chat framework. In affected versions if an attacker can successfully authenticate through SSO/Access Code, they can obtain the real backend API Key by modifying the base URL to their own attack URL on the frontend and setting up a server-side request. This issue has been addressed in version 0.162.25. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6061 | GPAC MP4Box isoffin_read.c isoffin_process infinite loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6061</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GPAC 2.5-DEV-rev228-g11067ea92-master and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function isoffin_process of the file src/filters/isoffin_read.c of the component MP4Box. The manipulation leads to infinite loop. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 20c0f29139a82779b86453ce7f68d0681ec7624c. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The identifier VDB-268789 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6062 | GPAC MP4Box load_text.c swf_svg_add_iso_sample null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6062</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GPAC 2.5-DEV-rev228-g11067ea92-master and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function swf_svg_add_iso_sample of the file src/filters/load_text.c of the component MP4Box. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 31e499d310a48bd17c8b055a0bfe0fe35887a7cd. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. VDB-268790 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37891 | Proxy-Authorization request header isn&amp;#x27;t stripped during cross-origin redirects in urllib3</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37891</link><description>urllib3 is a user-friendly HTTP client library for Python. When using urllib3's proxy support with `ProxyManager`, the `Proxy-Authorization` header is only sent to the configured proxy, as expected. However, when sending HTTP requests *without* using urllib3's proxy support, it's possible to accidentally configure the `Proxy-Authorization` header even though it won't have any effect as the request is not using a forwarding proxy or a tunneling proxy. In those cases, urllib3 doesn't treat the `Proxy-Authorization` HTTP header as one carrying authentication material and thus doesn't strip the header on cross-origin redirects. Because this is a highly unlikely scenario, we believe the severity of this vulnerability is low for almost all users. Out of an abundance of caution urllib3 will automatically strip the `Proxy-Authorization` header during cross-origin redirects to avoid the small chance that users are doing this on accident. Users should use urllib3's proxy support or disable automatic redirects to achieve safe processing of the `Proxy-Authorization` header, but we still decided to strip the header by default in order to further protect users who aren't using the correct approach. We believe the number of usages affected by this advisory is low. It requires all of the following to be true to be exploited: 1. Setting the `Proxy-Authorization` header without using urllib3's built-in proxy support. 2. Not disabling HTTP redirects. 3. Either not using an HTTPS origin server or for the proxy or target origin to redirect to a malicious origin. Users are advised to update to either version 1.26.19 or version 2.2.2. Users unable to upgrade may use the `Proxy-Authorization` header with urllib3's `ProxyManager`, disable HTTP redirects using `redirects=False` when sending requests, or not user the `Proxy-Authorization` header as mitigations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37902 | Path thraversal in DeepJavaLibrary</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37902</link><description>DeepJavaLibrary(DJL) is an Engine-Agnostic Deep Learning Framework in Java. DJL versions 0.1.0 through 0.27.0 do not prevent absolute path archived artifacts from inserting archived files directly into the system, overwriting system files. This is fixed in DJL 0.28.0 and patched in DJL Large Model Inference containers version 0.27.0. Users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37890 | Denial of service when handling a request with many HTTP headers in ws</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37890</link><description>ws is an open source WebSocket client and server for Node.js. A request with a number of headers exceeding theserver.maxHeadersCount threshold could be used to crash a ws server. The vulnerability was fixed in ws@8.17.1 (e55e510) and backported to ws@7.5.10 (22c2876), ws@6.2.3 (eeb76d3), and ws@5.2.4 (4abd8f6). In vulnerable versions of ws, the issue can be mitigated in the following ways: 1. Reduce the maximum allowed length of the request headers using the --max-http-header-size=size and/or the maxHeaderSize options so that no more headers than the server.maxHeadersCount limit can be sent. 2. Set server.maxHeadersCount to 0 so that no limit is applied.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36543 | Incorrect access control in the Kafka Connect REST API in the STRIMZI Project 0.41.0 and earlier allows an attacker to deny the service for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36543</link><description>Incorrect access control in the Kafka Connect REST API in the STRIMZI Project 0.41.0 and earlier allows an attacker to deny the service for Kafka Mirroring, potentially mirror the topics' content to his Kafka cluster via a malicious connector (bypassing Kafka ACL if it exists), and potentially steal Kafka SASL credentials, by querying the MirrorMaker Kafka REST API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38449 | A Directory Traversal vulnerability in KasmVNC 1.3.1.230e50f7b89663316c70de7b0e3db6f6b9340489 and possibly earlier versions allows remote au...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38449</link><description>A Directory Traversal vulnerability in KasmVNC 1.3.1.230e50f7b89663316c70de7b0e3db6f6b9340489 and possibly earlier versions allows remote authenticated attackers to browse parent directories and read the content of files outside the scope of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37840 | SQL injection vulnerability in processscore.php in Itsourcecode Learning Management System Project In PHP With Source Code v1.0 allows remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37840</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in processscore.php in Itsourcecode Learning Management System Project In PHP With Source Code v1.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL commands via the LessonID parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6059 | Ingenico Estate Manager News Feed messages cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6059</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Ingenico Estate Manager 2023. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /emgui/rest/ums/messages of the component News Feed. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268787. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25103 | Use-after-free vulnerability in lighttpd  &amp;lt;= 1.4.50</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25103</link><description>There exists a use-after-free-vulnerability in lighttpd &lt;= 1.4.50 that can allow access to do a case-insensitive comparison against the reused pointer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37794 | Improper input validation in CVC5 Solver v1.1.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SMT2 input file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37794</link><description>Improper input validation in CVC5 Solver v1.1.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SMT2 input file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37795 | A segmentation fault in CVC5 Solver v1.1.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SMT-LIB input file containing t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37795</link><description>A segmentation fault in CVC5 Solver v1.1.3 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted SMT-LIB input file containing the `set-logic` command with specific formatting errors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6058 | LabVantage LIMS cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6058</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in LabVantage LIMS 2017. This affects an unknown part of the file /labvantage/rc?command=page&amp;amp;page=SampleHistoricalList&amp;_iframename=list&amp;__crc=crc_1701669816260. The manipulation of the argument height/width leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268785 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:27:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36973 | misc: microchip: pci1xxxx: fix double free in the error handling of gp_aux_bus_probe()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36973</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

misc: microchip: pci1xxxx: fix double free in the error handling of gp_aux_bus_probe()

When auxiliary_device_add() returns error and then calls
auxiliary_device_uninit(), callback function
gp_auxiliary_device_release() calls ida_free() and
kfree(aux_device_wrapper) to free memory. We should't
call them again in the error handling path.

Fix this by skipping the redundant cleanup functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37662 | TP-LINK TL-7DR5130 v1.0.23 is vulnerable to TCP DoS or hijacking attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can disconnect or hijac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37662</link><description>TP-LINK TL-7DR5130 v1.0.23 is vulnerable to TCP DoS or hijacking attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can disconnect or hijack the traffic between the victim and any remote server by sending out forged TCP RST messages to evict NAT mappings in the router.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6056 | nasirkhan Laravel Starter Password Reset forgot-password observable response discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6056</link><description>A vulnerability was found in nasirkhan Laravel Starter up to 11.8.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /forgot-password of the component Password Reset Handler. The manipulation of the argument Email leads to observable response discrepancy. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268784. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36527 | puppeteer-renderer v.3.2.0 and before is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Attackers can exploit the URL parameter using the file protocol ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36527</link><description>puppeteer-renderer v.3.2.0 and before is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. Attackers can exploit the URL parameter using the file protocol to read sensitive information from the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37661 | TP-LINK TL-7DR5130 v1.0.23 is vulnerable to forged ICMP redirect message attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can hijack the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37661</link><description>TP-LINK TL-7DR5130 v1.0.23 is vulnerable to forged ICMP redirect message attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can hijack the traffic between the victim and any remote server by sending out forged ICMP redirect messages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37663 | Redmi router RB03 v1.0.57 is vulnerable to forged ICMP redirect message attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can hijack the t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37663</link><description>Redmi router RB03 v1.0.57 is vulnerable to forged ICMP redirect message attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can hijack the traffic between the victim and any remote server by sending out forged ICMP redirect messages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37664 | Redmi router RB03 v1.0.57 is vulnerable to TCP DoS or hijacking attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can disconnect or hijack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37664</link><description>Redmi router RB03 v1.0.57 is vulnerable to TCP DoS or hijacking attacks. An attacker in the same WLAN as the victim can disconnect or hijack the traffic between the victim and any remote server by sending out forged TCP RST messages to evict NAT mappings in the router.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:30:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36578 | akbr update 1.0.0 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via update/index.js.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36578</link><description>akbr update 1.0.0 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via update/index.js.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36573 | almela obx before v.0.0.4 has a Prototype Pollution issue which allows arbitrary code execution via the obx/build/index.js:656), reduce (@al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36573</link><description>almela obx before v.0.0.4 has a Prototype Pollution issue which allows arbitrary code execution via the obx/build/index.js:656), reduce (@almela/obx/build/index.js:470), Object.set (obx/build/index.js:269) component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36574 | A Prototype Pollution issue in flatten-json 1.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via module.exports.unflattenJSON (flatten-jso...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36574</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in flatten-json 1.0.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via module.exports.unflattenJSON (flatten-json/index.js:42)</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0397 | Memory race condition in ssl.SSLContext certificate store methods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0397</link><description>A defect was discovered in the Python “ssl” module where there is a memory
race condition with the ssl.SSLContext methods “cert_store_stats()” and
“get_ca_certs()”. The race condition can be triggered if the methods are
called at the same time as certificates are loaded into the SSLContext,
such as during the TLS handshake with a certificate directory configured.
This issue is fixed in CPython 3.10.14, 3.11.9, 3.12.3, and 3.13.0a5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36575 | A Prototype Pollution issue in getsetprop 1.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via global.accessor.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36575</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in getsetprop 1.1.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via global.accessor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36577 | apphp js-object-resolver &lt; 3.1.1 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via Module.setNestedProperty.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36577</link><description>apphp js-object-resolver &lt; 3.1.1 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via Module.setNestedProperty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:28:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36581 | A Prototype Pollution issue in abw badger-database 1.2.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via dist/badger-database.esm.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36581</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in abw badger-database 1.2.1 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via dist/badger-database.esm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4032 | Incorrect IPv4 and IPv6 private ranges</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4032</link><description>The “ipaddress” module contained incorrect information about whether certain IPv4 and IPv6 addresses were designated as “globally reachable” or “private”. This affected the is_private and is_global properties of the ipaddress.IPv4Address, ipaddress.IPv4Network, ipaddress.IPv6Address, and ipaddress.IPv6Network classes, where values wouldn’t be returned in accordance with the latest information from the IANA Special-Purpose Address Registries.

CPython 3.12.4 and 3.13.0a6 contain updated information from these registries and thus have the intended behavior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:28:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36582 | alexbinary object-deep-assign 1.0.11 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the extend() method of Module.deepAssign (/src/index.js)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36582</link><description>alexbinary object-deep-assign 1.0.11 is vulnerable to Prototype Pollution via the extend() method of Module.deepAssign (/src/index.js)</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37158 | Evmos is missing precompile checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37158</link><description>Evmos is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Hub on the Cosmos Network. Preliminary checks on actions computed by the clawback vesting accounts are performed in the ante handler. Evmos core, implements two different ante handlers: one for Cosmos transactions and one for Ethereum transactions. Checks performed on the two implementation are different. The vulnerability discovered allowed a clawback account to bypass Cosmos ante handler checks by sending an Ethereum transaction targeting a precompile used to interact with a Cosmos SDK module. This vulnerability is fixed in 18.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37159 | Evmos is missing create validator check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37159</link><description>Evmos is the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Hub on the Cosmos Network. This vulnerability allowed a user to create a validator using vested tokens to deposit the self-bond. This vulnerability is fixed in 18.0.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 14:20:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37619 | StrongShop v1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the spec_group_id parameter at /spec/inde...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37619</link><description>StrongShop v1.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the spec_group_id parameter at /spec/index.blade.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37620 | PHPVOD v4.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the id parameter at /view/admin/view.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37620</link><description>PHPVOD v4.0 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the id parameter at /view/admin/view.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37621 | StrongShop v1.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the component /shippingOptionConfig/inde...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37621</link><description>StrongShop v1.0 was discovered to contain a Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability via the component /shippingOptionConfig/index.blade.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37622 | Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the num parameter at /flow/flow.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37622</link><description>Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the num parameter at /flow/flow.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37623 | Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /kaoqin/tpl_kaoqin_locationchange...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37623</link><description>Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /kaoqin/tpl_kaoqin_locationchange.html component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37624 | Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /chajian/inputChajian.php. compon...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37624</link><description>Xinhu RockOA v2.6.3 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the /chajian/inputChajian.php. component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37625 | zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /index.php...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37625</link><description>zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /index.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38469 | zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /pay.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38469</link><description>zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /pay.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38470 | zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /own.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38470</link><description>zhimengzhe iBarn v1.5 was discovered to contain a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability via the $search parameter at /own.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36580 | A Prototype Pollution issue in cdr0 sg 1.0.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36580</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in cdr0 sg 1.0.10 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36583 | A Prototype Pollution issue in byondreal accessor &lt;= 1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via @byondreal/accessor/index.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36583</link><description>A Prototype Pollution issue in byondreal accessor &lt;= 1.0.0 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via @byondreal/accessor/index.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37848 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Online-Bookstore-Project-In-PHP v1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_delete.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37848</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Online-Bookstore-Project-In-PHP v1.0 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the admin_delete.php component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6057 | Improper authentication in the vault password feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.31.0 and earlier allows an attacker that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6057</link><description>Improper authentication in the vault password feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.31.0 and earlier allows an attacker that has compromised an access to an RDM instance to bypass the vault master password via the offline mode feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:16:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6055 | Improper removal of sensitive information in data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.32.0 and earlier on Win...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6055</link><description>Improper removal of sensitive information in data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.1.32.0 and earlier on Windows allows an attacker that obtains the exported settings to recover powershell credentials configured on the data source via stealing the configuration file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5741 | XSS in inventory view</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5741</link><description>Stored XSS in inventory tree rendering in Checkmk before 2.3.0p7, 2.2.0p28, 2.1.0p45 and 2.0.0 (EOL)</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36277 | Improper verification of cryptographic signature issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" App versions prior to 1.3.5 for Android and i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36277</link><description>Improper verification of cryptographic signature issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" App versions prior to 1.3.5 for Android and iOS. The affected app cannot detect event data with invalid signatures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36279 | Reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" A...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36279</link><description>Reliance on obfuscation or encryption of security-relevant inputs without integrity checking issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" App versions prior to 1.3.5 for Android and iOS. If this vulnerability is exploited, the content of direct messages (DMs) between users may be manipulated by a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36289 | Reusing a nonce, key pair in encryption issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" App versions prior to 1.3.5 for Android and iOS. If th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36289</link><description>Reusing a nonce, key pair in encryption issue exists in "FreeFrom - the nostr client" App versions prior to 1.3.5 for Android and iOS. If this vulnerability is exploited, the content of direct messages (DMs) between users may be manipulated by a man-in-the-middle attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6048 | Openfind MailGates and MailAudit - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6048</link><description>Openfind's MailGates and MailAudit fail to properly filter user input when analyzing email attachments. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this vulnerability to inject system commands and execute them on the remote server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5650 | DLL Hijacking vulnerability has been found in CENTUM CAMS Log server provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. If an attacker is somehow ab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5650</link><description>DLL Hijacking vulnerability has been found in CENTUM CAMS Log server provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation. If an attacker is somehow able to intrude into a computer that installed affected product or access to a shared folder, by replacing the DLL file with a tampered one, it is possible to execute arbitrary programs with the authority of the SYSTEM account.

The affected products and versions are as follows:
CENTUM CS 3000 R3.08.10 to R3.09.50
CENTUM VP R4.01.00 to R4.03.00, R5.01.00 to R5.04.20, R6.01.00 to R6.11.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 06:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3236 | Easy Notify Lite &amp;lt; 1.1.33 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3236</link><description>The Popup Builder WordPress plugin before 1.1.33 does not sanitise and escape some of its Notification fields, which could allow users such as contributor and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 06:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4305 | PostX &amp;lt; 4.1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4305</link><description>The Post Grid Gutenberg Blocks and WordPress Blog Plugin  WordPress plugin before 4.1.0 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 06:10:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6047 | GeoVision EOL device - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6047</link><description>Certain EOL GeoVision devices fail to properly filter user input for the specific functionality. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject and execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 06:10:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6046 | SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC - OS Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6046</link><description>SECOM WRTR-304GN-304TW-UPSC V02(unsupported-when-assigned) does not properly filter user input in the specific functionality. Unauthenticated remote attackers can exploit this vulnerability to inject and execute arbitrary system commands on the device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6045 | D-Link router - Hidden Backdoor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6045</link><description>Certain models of D-Link wireless routers contain an undisclosed factory testing backdoor. Unauthenticated attackers on the local area network can force the device to enable Telnet service by accessing a specific URL and can log in by using the administrator credentials obtained from analyzing the firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5163 | Improper permission settings for mobile applications (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user password and account security risks.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5163</link><description>Improper permission settings for mobile applications (com.transsion.carlcare) may lead to user password and account security risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6044 | D-Link router - Arbitrary File Reading</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6044</link><description>Certain models of D-Link wireless routers have a path traversal vulnerability. Unauthenticated attackers on the same local area network can read arbitrary system files by manipulating the URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 02:44:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6043 | SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System admin_class.php login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6043</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Best House Rental Management System 1.0. This affects the function login of the file admin_class.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268767.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 01:09:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6042 | itsourcecode Real Estate Management System property-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6042</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file property-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-268766 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6041 | itsourcecode Gym Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6041</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Gym Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-268765 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:07:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6039 | Feng Office Workspaces sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6039</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Feng Office 3.11.1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the component Workspaces. The manipulation of the argument dim leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-268752.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 22:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34451 | Ghost through 5.85.1 allows remote attackers to bypass an authentication rate-limit protection mechanism by using many X-Forwarded-For heade...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34451</link><description>Ghost through 5.85.1 allows remote attackers to bypass an authentication rate-limit protection mechanism by using many X-Forwarded-For headers with different values. NOTE: the vendor's position is that Ghost should be installed with a reverse proxy that allows only trusted X-Forwarded-For headers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 21:26:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27636 | Progress Sitefinity before 15.0.0 allows XSS by authenticated users via the content form in the SF Editor.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27636</link><description>Progress Sitefinity before 15.0.0 allows XSS by authenticated users via the content form in the SF Editor.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38396 | An issue was discovered in iTerm2 3.5.x before 3.5.2. Unfiltered use of an escape sequence to report a window title, in combination with the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38396</link><description>An issue was discovered in iTerm2 3.5.x before 3.5.2. Unfiltered use of an escape sequence to report a window title, in combination with the built-in tmux integration feature (enabled by default), allows an attacker to inject arbitrary code into the terminal, a different vulnerability than CVE-2024-38395.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38465 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows username enumeration because of the response discrepancy of incorrect versus erro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38465</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows username enumeration because of the response discrepancy of incorrect versus error.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38466 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 has a 123456Qw default password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38466</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 has a 123456Qw default password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38467 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized user information retrieval via the queryUser API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38467</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized user information retrieval via the queryUser API.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38468 | Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized password resets via the resetPassword API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38468</link><description>Shenzhen Guoxin Synthesis image system before 8.3.0 allows unauthorized password resets via the resetPassword API.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38461 | irodsServerMonPerf in iRODS before 4.3.2 attempts to proceed with use of a path even if it is not a directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38461</link><description>irodsServerMonPerf in iRODS before 4.3.2 attempts to proceed with use of a path even if it is not a directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38462 | iRODS before 4.3.2 provides an msiSendMail function with a problematic dependency on the mail binary, such as in the mailMS.cpp#L94-L106 ref...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38462</link><description>iRODS before 4.3.2 provides an msiSendMail function with a problematic dependency on the mail binary, such as in the mailMS.cpp#L94-L106 reference.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38459 | langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) before 0.0.61 for LangChain provides Python REPL access without an opt-in step. NOTE; th...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38459</link><description>langchain_experimental (aka LangChain Experimental) before 0.0.61 for LangChain provides Python REPL access without an opt-in step. NOTE; this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2024-27444.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38460 | In SonarQube before 10.4 and 9.9.4 LTA, encrypted values generated using the Settings Encryption feature are potentially exposed in cleartex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38460</link><description>In SonarQube before 10.4 and 9.9.4 LTA, encrypted values generated using the Settings Encryption feature are potentially exposed in cleartext as part of the URL parameters in the logs (such as SonarQube Access Logs, Proxy Logs, etc).</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:57:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38457 | Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows CSRF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38457</link><description>Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows CSRF.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38458 | Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows code injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38458</link><description>Xenforo before 2.2.16 allows code injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38454 | ExpressionEngine before 7.4.11 allows XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38454</link><description>ExpressionEngine before 7.4.11 allows XSS.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38448 | htags in GNU Global through 6.6.12 allows code execution in situations where dbpath (aka -d) is untrusted, because shell metacharacters may ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38448</link><description>htags in GNU Global through 6.6.12 allows code execution in situations where dbpath (aka -d) is untrusted, because shell metacharacters may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38443 | C/sorting/binary_insertion_sort.c in The Algorithms - C through e5dad3f has a segmentation fault for deep recursion, which may affect common...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38443</link><description>C/sorting/binary_insertion_sort.c in The Algorithms - C through e5dad3f has a segmentation fault for deep recursion, which may affect common use cases such as sorting an array of 50 elements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38439 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[PASSWDLEN] to '\0' in FPLoginExt in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38439</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[PASSWDLEN] to '\0' in FPLoginExt in login in etc/uams/uams_pam.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38440 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of incorrectly using FPLoginExt in BN_bin2bn in etc/...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38440</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of incorrectly using FPLoginExt in BN_bin2bn in etc/uams/uams_dhx_pam.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38441 | Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[len] to '\0' in FPMapName in afp_map...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38441</link><description>Netatalk 3.2.0 has an off-by-one error and resultant heap-based buffer overflow because of setting ibuf[len] to '\0' in FPMapName in afp_mapname in etc/afp/directory.c.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 12:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36397 | Vantiva - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36397</link><description>Vantiva - MediaAccess DGA2232 v19.4 - CWE-79: Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 08:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38428 | url.c in GNU Wget through 1.24.5 mishandles semicolons in the userinfo subcomponent of a URI, and thus there may be insecure behavior in whi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38428</link><description>url.c in GNU Wget through 1.24.5 mishandles semicolons in the userinfo subcomponent of a URI, and thus there may be insecure behavior in which data that was supposed to be in the userinfo subcomponent is misinterpreted to be part of the host subcomponent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 02:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38427 | In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX before 85ce74e, a logic flaw in CIccTagXmlProfileSequenceId::ParseXml in IccXML/IccLibXML/IccTa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38427</link><description>In International Color Consortium DemoIccMAX before 85ce74e, a logic flaw in CIccTagXmlProfileSequenceId::ParseXml in IccXML/IccLibXML/IccTagXml.cpp results in unconditionally returning false.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38395 | In iTerm2 before 3.5.2, the "Terminal may report window title" setting is not honored, and thus remote code execution might occur but "is no...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38395</link><description>In iTerm2 before 3.5.2, the "Terminal may report window title" setting is not honored, and thus remote code execution might occur but "is not trivially exploitable."</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>