<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-6831 | Seth Fogie, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible to edit and/or remove views without the neces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6831</link><description>Seth Fogie, member of AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible to edit and/or remove views without the necessary permission due to a client-side-only check. 
Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please 
refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6476 | Gee-netics, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to gain system privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6476</link><description>Gee-netics, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program has found that it is possible for a non-admin user to gain system privileges by redirecting a file deletion upon service restart. 
 Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6749 | Seth Fogie, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that the Incident report feature may expose sensitive creden...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6749</link><description>Seth Fogie, member of the AXIS Camera Station Pro Bug Bounty Program, has found that the Incident report feature may expose sensitive credentials on the AXIS Camera Station windows client. If Incident report is not being used with credentials configured this flaw does not apply. 

 Axis has released patched versions for the highlighted flaw. Please refer to the Axis security advisory for more information and solution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10857 | Product Input Fields for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.9 -  Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10857</link><description>The Product Input Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.9 via the handle_downloads() function due to insufficient file path validation/sanitization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11002 | InPost Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.1.4.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via inpost_gallery_get_shortcode_template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11002</link><description>The The InPost Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the inpost_gallery_get_shortcode_template AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4.2. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10471 | Everest Forms &amp;lt; 3.0.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10471</link><description>The Everest Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.0.4.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10542 | Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 6.43.2 - Authorization Bypass via Reverse DNS Spoofing to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10542</link><description>The Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Arbitrary Plugin Installation due to an authorization bypass via reverse DNS spoofing on the checkWithoutToken function in all versions up to, and including, 6.43.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10570 | Security &amp;amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 2.145 - Authorization Bypass via Reverse DNS Spoofing to Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10570</link><description>The Security &amp; Malware scan by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized SQL Injection due to an authorization bypass via reverse DNS spoofing on the checkWithoutToken function in all versions up to, and including, 2.145, as well as insufficient input sanitization and validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10781 | Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk &amp;lt;= 6.44 - Authorization Bypass due to Missing Empty Value Check to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Plugin Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10781</link><description>The Spam protection, Anti-Spam, FireWall by CleanTalk plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Arbitrary Plugin Installation due to an missing empty value check on the 'api_key' value in the 'perform' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.44. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to install and activate arbitrary plugins which can be leveraged to achieve remote code execution if another vulnerable plugin is installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 05:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53278 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Admin UI Customize versions prior to ver 1.5.14. If a malicious admin user customizes the ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53278</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WP Admin UI Customize versions prior to ver 1.5.14. If a malicious admin user customizes the admin screen with some malicious contents, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the other users who are accessing the admin screen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 04:47:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11342 | Skt NURCaptcha &amp;lt;= 3.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery  to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11342</link><description>The Skt NURCaptcha plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the skt-nurc-admin.php file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11418 | Additional Order Filters for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.21 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11418</link><description>The Additional Order Filters for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'shipping_method_filter' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49353 | IBM Watson Speech Services Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49353</link><description>IBM Watson Speech Services Cartridge for IBM Cloud Pak for Data 4.0.0 through 5.0.2 does not properly check inputs to resources that are used concurrently, which might lead to unexpected states, possibly resulting in a crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49351 | IBM Workload Scheduler information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49351</link><description>IBM Workload Scheduler 9.5, 10.1, and 10.2 stores user credentials in plain text which can be read by a local user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49595 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and before, contain an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A high privileged ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49595</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and before, contain an Authentication Bypass by Capture-replay vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49596 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and prior, contain a Missing Authorization vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49596</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, version WMS 4.4 and prior, contain a Missing Authorization vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Denial of service and arbitrary file deletion</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49597 | Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions WMS 4.4 and prior, contain an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49597</link><description>Dell Wyse Management Suite, versions WMS 4.4 and prior, contain an Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability. A high privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Protection mechanism bypass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 03:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10729 | Booking &amp;amp; Appointment Plugin for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10729</link><description>The Booking &amp; Appointment Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'save_google_calendar_data' function in versions up to, and including, 6.9.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions or above to update the site options arbitrarily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11677 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Vendor Details Page his_admin_add_vendor.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_add_vendor.php of the component Add Vendor Details Page. The manipulation of the argument v_name/v_adr/v_number/v_email/v_phone/v_desc leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11678 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System his_doc_register_patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11678</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /backend/doc/his_doc_register_patient.php. The manipulation of the argument pat_fname/pat_ailment/pat_lname/pat_age/pat_dob/pat_number/pat_phone/pat_type/pat_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 02:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52899 | IBM Data Virtualization Manager code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52899</link><description>IBM Data Virtualization Manager for z/OS 1.1 and 1.2 could allow an authenticated user to inject malicious JDBC URL parameters and execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11675 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Patient Details Page his_admin_register_patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11675</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_register_patient.php of the component Add Patient Details Page. The manipulation of the argument pat_fname/pat_ailment/pat_lname/pat_age/pat_dob/pat_number/pat_phone/pat_type/pat_addr leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11676 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System Add Laboratory Equipment Page his_admin_add_lab_equipment.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /backend/admin/his_admin_add_lab_equipment.php of the component Add Laboratory Equipment Page. The manipulation of the argument eqp_code/eqp_name/eqp_vendor/eqp_desc/eqp_dept/eqp_status/eqp_qty leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11674 | CodeAstro Hospital Management System his_doc_update-account.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11674</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /backend/doc/his_doc_update-account.php. The manipulation of the argument doc_dpic leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53843 | Reflected XSS Vulnerability in Authentication Flow URL Handling in @dapperduckling/keycloak-connector-server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53843</link><description>@dapperduckling/keycloak-connector-server is an opinionated series of libraries for Node.js applications and frontend clients to interface with keycloak. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the authentication flow of the application. This issue arises due to improper sanitization of the URL parameters, allowing the URL bar's contents to be injected and reflected into the HTML page. An attacker could craft a malicious URL to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of a victim who visits the link. Any application utilizing this authentication library is vulnerable. Users of the application are at risk if they can be lured into clicking on a crafted malicious link. The vulnerability has been patched in version 2.5.5 by ensuring proper sanitization and escaping of user input in the affected URL parameters. Users are strongly encouraged to upgrade. If upgrading is not immediately possible, users can implement the following workarounds: 1. Employ a Web Application Firewall (WAF) to block malicious requests containing suspicious URL parameters. or 2. Apply input validation and escaping directly within the application’s middleware or reverse proxy layer, specifically targeting the affected parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11673 | 1000 Projects Bookstore Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11673</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in 1000 Projects Bookstore Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 23:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53096 | mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path behaviour</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53096</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: resolve faulty mmap_region() error path behaviour

The mmap_region() function is somewhat terrifying, with spaghetti-like
control flow and numerous means by which issues can arise and incomplete
state, memory leaks and other unpleasantness can occur.

A large amount of the complexity arises from trying to handle errors late
in the process of mapping a VMA, which forms the basis of recently
observed issues with resource leaks and observable inconsistent state.

Taking advantage of previous patches in this series we move a number of
checks earlier in the code, simplifying things by moving the core of the
logic into a static internal function __mmap_region().

Doing this allows us to perform a number of checks up front before we do
any real work, and allows us to unwind the writable unmap check
unconditionally as required and to perform a CONFIG_DEBUG_VM_MAPLE_TREE
validation unconditionally also.

We move a number of things here:

1. We preallocate memory for the iterator before we call the file-backed
   memory hook, allowing us to exit early and avoid having to perform
   complicated and error-prone close/free logic. We carefully free
   iterator state on both success and error paths.

2. The enclosing mmap_region() function handles the mapping_map_writable()
   logic early. Previously the logic had the mapping_map_writable() at the
   point of mapping a newly allocated file-backed VMA, and a matching
   mapping_unmap_writable() on success and error paths.

   We now do this unconditionally if this is a file-backed, shared writable
   mapping. If a driver changes the flags to eliminate VM_MAYWRITE, however
   doing so does not invalidate the seal check we just performed, and we in
   any case always decrement the counter in the wrapper.

   We perform a debug assert to ensure a driver does not attempt to do the
   opposite.

3. We also move arch_validate_flags() up into the mmap_region()
   function. This is only relevant on arm64 and sparc64, and the check is
   only meaningful for SPARC with ADI enabled. We explicitly add a warning
   for this arch if a driver invalidates this check, though the code ought
   eventually to be fixed to eliminate the need for this.

With all of these measures in place, we no longer need to explicitly close
the VMA on error paths, as we place all checks which might fail prior to a
call to any driver mmap hook.

This eliminates an entire class of errors, makes the code easier to reason
about and more robust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53097 | mm: krealloc: Fix MTE false alarm in __do_krealloc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53097</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm: krealloc: Fix MTE false alarm in __do_krealloc

This patch addresses an issue introduced by commit 1a83a716ec233 ("mm:
krealloc: consider spare memory for __GFP_ZERO") which causes MTE
(Memory Tagging Extension) to falsely report a slab-out-of-bounds error.

The problem occurs when zeroing out spare memory in __do_krealloc. The
original code only considered software-based KASAN and did not account
for MTE. It does not reset the KASAN tag before calling memset, leading
to a mismatch between the pointer tag and the memory tag, resulting
in a false positive.

Example of the error:
==================================================================
swapper/0: BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in __memset+0x84/0x188
swapper/0: Write at addr f4ffff8005f0fdf0 by task swapper/0/1
swapper/0: Pointer tag: [f4], memory tag: [fe]
swapper/0:
swapper/0: CPU: 4 UID: 0 PID: 1 Comm: swapper/0 Not tainted 6.12.
swapper/0: Hardware name: MT6991(ENG) (DT)
swapper/0: Call trace:
swapper/0:  dump_backtrace+0xfc/0x17c
swapper/0:  show_stack+0x18/0x28
swapper/0:  dump_stack_lvl+0x40/0xa0
swapper/0:  print_report+0x1b8/0x71c
swapper/0:  kasan_report+0xec/0x14c
swapper/0:  __do_kernel_fault+0x60/0x29c
swapper/0:  do_bad_area+0x30/0xdc
swapper/0:  do_tag_check_fault+0x20/0x34
swapper/0:  do_mem_abort+0x58/0x104
swapper/0:  el1_abort+0x3c/0x5c
swapper/0:  el1h_64_sync_handler+0x80/0xcc
swapper/0:  el1h_64_sync+0x68/0x6c
swapper/0:  __memset+0x84/0x188
swapper/0:  btf_populate_kfunc_set+0x280/0x3d8
swapper/0:  __register_btf_kfunc_id_set+0x43c/0x468
swapper/0:  register_btf_kfunc_id_set+0x48/0x60
swapper/0:  register_nf_nat_bpf+0x1c/0x40
swapper/0:  nf_nat_init+0xc0/0x128
swapper/0:  do_one_initcall+0x184/0x464
swapper/0:  do_initcall_level+0xdc/0x1b0
swapper/0:  do_initcalls+0x70/0xc0
swapper/0:  do_basic_setup+0x1c/0x28
swapper/0:  kernel_init_freeable+0x144/0x1b8
swapper/0:  kernel_init+0x20/0x1a8
swapper/0:  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
==================================================================</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53098 | drm/xe/ufence: Prefetch ufence addr to catch bogus address</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53098</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/xe/ufence: Prefetch ufence addr to catch bogus address

access_ok() only checks for addr overflow so also try to read the addr
to catch invalid addr sent from userspace.

(cherry picked from commit 9408c4508483ffc60811e910a93d6425b8e63928)</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53099 | bpf: Check validity of link-&amp;gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53099</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Check validity of link-&gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo()

If a newly-added link type doesn't invoke BPF_LINK_TYPE(), accessing
bpf_link_type_strs[link-&gt;type] may result in an out-of-bounds access.

To spot such missed invocations early in the future, checking the
validity of link-&gt;type in bpf_link_show_fdinfo() and emitting a warning
when such invocations are missed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53100 | nvme: tcp: avoid race between queue_lock lock and destroy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53100</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: tcp: avoid race between queue_lock lock and destroy

Commit 76d54bf20cdc ("nvme-tcp: don't access released socket during
error recovery") added a mutex_lock() call for the queue-&gt;queue_lock
in nvme_tcp_get_address(). However, the mutex_lock() races with
mutex_destroy() in nvme_tcp_free_queue(), and causes the WARN below.

DEBUG_LOCKS_WARN_ON(lock-&gt;magic != lock)
WARNING: CPU: 3 PID: 34077 at kernel/locking/mutex.c:587 __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
Modules linked in: nvmet_tcp nvmet nvme_tcp nvme_fabrics iw_cm ib_cm ib_core pktcdvd nft_fib_inet nft_fib_ipv4 nft_fib_ipv6 nft_fib nft_reject_inet nf_reject_ipv4 nf_reject_ipv6 nft_reject nft_ct nft_chain_nat nf_nat nf_conntrack nf_defrag_ipv6 nf_defrag_ipv4 ip_set nf_tables qrtr sunrpc ppdev 9pnet_virtio 9pnet pcspkr netfs parport_pc parport e1000 i2c_piix4 i2c_smbus loop fuse nfnetlink zram bochs drm_vram_helper drm_ttm_helper ttm drm_kms_helper xfs drm sym53c8xx floppy nvme scsi_transport_spi nvme_core nvme_auth serio_raw ata_generic pata_acpi dm_multipath qemu_fw_cfg [last unloaded: ib_uverbs]
CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 34077 Comm: udisksd Not tainted 6.11.0-rc7 #319
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:__mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
Code: 08 84 d2 0f 85 c8 04 00 00 8b 15 ef b6 c8 01 85 d2 0f 85 78 f4 ff ff 48 c7 c6 20 93 ee af 48 c7 c7 60 91 ee af e8 f0 a7 6d fd &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 5e f4 ff ff 48 b8 00 00 00 00 00 fc ff df 4c 89 f2 48 c1
RSP: 0018:ffff88811305f760 EFLAGS: 00010286
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88812c652058 RCX: 0000000000000000
RDX: 0000000000000000 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: 0000000000000001
RBP: ffff88811305f8b0 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: ffffed1075c36341
R10: ffff8883ae1b1a0b R11: 0000000000010498 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 0000000000000000 R14: dffffc0000000000 R15: ffff88812c652058
FS:  00007f9713ae4980(0000) GS:ffff8883ae180000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007fcd78483c7c CR3: 0000000122c38000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 
 ? __warn.cold+0x5b/0x1af
 ? __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
 ? report_bug+0x1ec/0x390
 ? handle_bug+0x3c/0x80
 ? exc_invalid_op+0x13/0x40
 ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x20
 ? __mutex_lock+0xcf0/0x1220
 ? nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 ? __pfx___mutex_lock+0x10/0x10
 ? __lock_acquire+0xd6a/0x59e0
 ? nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 nvme_tcp_get_address+0xc2/0x1e0 [nvme_tcp]
 ? __pfx_nvme_tcp_get_address+0x10/0x10 [nvme_tcp]
 nvme_sysfs_show_address+0x81/0xc0 [nvme_core]
 dev_attr_show+0x42/0x80
 ? __asan_memset+0x1f/0x40
 sysfs_kf_seq_show+0x1f0/0x370
 seq_read_iter+0x2cb/0x1130
 ? rw_verify_area+0x3b1/0x590
 ? __mutex_lock+0x433/0x1220
 vfs_read+0x6a6/0xa20
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? __pfx_vfs_read+0x10/0x10
 ksys_read+0xf7/0x1d0
 ? __pfx_ksys_read+0x10/0x10
 ? __x64_sys_openat+0x105/0x1d0
 do_syscall_64+0x93/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? __pfx_ksys_read+0x10/0x10
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on_prepare+0x16d/0x400
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? lockdep_hardirqs_on+0x78/0x100
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 ? do_syscall_64+0x9f/0x180
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e
RIP: 0033:0x7f9713f55cfa
Code: 55 48 89 e5 48 83 ec 20 48 89 55 e8 48 89 75 f0 89 7d f8 e8 e8 74 f8 ff 48 8b 55 e8 48 8b 75 f0 4
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53101 | fs: Fix uninitialized value issue in from_kuid and from_kgid</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53101</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs: Fix uninitialized value issue in from_kuid and from_kgid

ocfs2_setattr() uses attr-&gt;ia_mode, attr-&gt;ia_uid and attr-&gt;ia_gid in
a trace point even though ATTR_MODE, ATTR_UID and ATTR_GID aren't set.

Initialize all fields of newattrs to avoid uninitialized variables, by
checking if ATTR_MODE, ATTR_UID, ATTR_GID are initialized, otherwise 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53102 | nvme: make keep-alive synchronous operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53102</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvme: make keep-alive synchronous operation

The nvme keep-alive operation, which executes at a periodic interval,
could potentially sneak in while shutting down a fabric controller.
This may lead to a race between the fabric controller admin queue
destroy code path (invoked while shutting down controller) and hw/hctx
queue dispatcher called from the nvme keep-alive async request queuing
operation. This race could lead to the kernel crash shown below:

Call Trace:
    autoremove_wake_function+0x0/0xbc (unreliable)
    __blk_mq_sched_dispatch_requests+0x114/0x24c
    blk_mq_sched_dispatch_requests+0x44/0x84
    blk_mq_run_hw_queue+0x140/0x220
    nvme_keep_alive_work+0xc8/0x19c [nvme_core]
    process_one_work+0x200/0x4e0
    worker_thread+0x340/0x504
    kthread+0x138/0x140
    start_kernel_thread+0x14/0x18

While shutting down fabric controller, if nvme keep-alive request sneaks
in then it would be flushed off. The nvme_keep_alive_end_io function is
then invoked to handle the end of the keep-alive operation which
decrements the admin-&gt;q_usage_counter and assuming this is the last/only
request in the admin queue then the admin-&gt;q_usage_counter becomes zero.
If that happens then blk-mq destroy queue operation (blk_mq_destroy_
queue()) which could be potentially running simultaneously on another
cpu (as this is the controller shutdown code path) would forward
progress and deletes the admin queue. So, now from this point onward
we are not supposed to access the admin queue resources. However the
issue here's that the nvme keep-alive thread running hw/hctx queue
dispatch operation hasn't yet finished its work and so it could still
potentially access the admin queue resource while the admin queue had
been already deleted and that causes the above crash.

This fix helps avoid the observed crash by implementing keep-alive as a
synchronous operation so that we decrement admin-&gt;q_usage_counter only
after keep-alive command finished its execution and returns the command
status back up to its caller (blk_execute_rq()). This would ensure that
fabric shutdown code path doesn't destroy the fabric admin queue until
keep-alive request finished execution and also keep-alive thread is not
running hw/hctx queue dispatch operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53597 | masterstack_imgcap v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the endpoint /submit.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53597</link><description>masterstack_imgcap v0.0.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the endpoint /submit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53554 | A Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in the component /project/new/scrum of Taiga v 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53554</link><description>A Client-Side Template Injection (CSTI) vulnerability in the component /project/new/scrum of Taiga v 8.6.1 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by injecting a malicious payload within the new project details.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50671 | Incorrect access control in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows attackers with Authenticated User roles to obtain email add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50671</link><description>Incorrect access control in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows attackers with Authenticated User roles to obtain email addresses via the "Get users" feature. The vulnerability occurs due to a flaw in permission verification logic, where the wildcard character in permitted URLs grants unintended access to endpoints restricted to users with Super Admin roles. This makes it possible for attackers to disclose the email addresses of all users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:58:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50672 | A NoSQL injection vulnerability in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50672</link><description>A NoSQL injection vulnerability in Adapt Learning Adapt Authoring Tool &lt;= 0.11.3 allows unauthenticated attackers to reset user and administrator account passwords via the "Reset password" feature. The vulnerability occurs due to insufficient validation of user input, which is used as a query in Mongoose's find() function. This makes it possible for attackers to perform a full takeover of the administrator account. Attackers can then use the newly gained administrative privileges to upload a custom plugin to perform remote code execution (RCE) on the server hosting the web application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53556 | An Open Redirect vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary websites via appending a crafted link to /log...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53556</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability in Taiga v6.8.1 allows attackers to redirect users to arbitrary websites via appending a crafted link to /login?next= in the login page URL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53258 | download_all_submissions allows student to download another student&amp;#x27;s submissions in Autolab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53258</link><description>Autolab is a course management service that enables auto-graded programming assignments. From Autolab versions v.3.0.0 onward students can download all assignments from another student, as long as they are logged in, using the download_all_submissions feature. This can allow for leakage of submissions to unauthorized users, such as downloading submissions from other students in the class, or even instructor test submissions, given they know their user IDs. This issue has been patched in commit `1aa4c769` which is not yet in a release version, but is expected to be included in version 3.0.3. Users are advised to either manually patch or to wait for version 3.0.3. As a workaround administrators can disable the feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53268 | Lack of validation on openExternal allows 1 click remote code execution in joplin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53268</link><description>Joplin is an open source, privacy-focused note taking app with sync capabilities for Windows, macOS, Linux, Android and iOS. In affected versions attackers are able to abuse the fact that openExternal is used without any filtering of URI schemes to obtain remote code execution in Windows environments. This issue has been addressed in version 3.0.3 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53261 | Cross-Site Scripting attack (XSS) on dev mode 404 page in SvelteKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53261</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. "Unsanitized input from *the request URL* flows into `end`, where it is used to render an HTML page returned to the user. This may result in a Cross-Site Scripting attack (XSS)." The files `packages/kit/src/exports/vite/dev/index.js` and `packages/kit/src/exports/vite/utils.js` both contain user controllable data which under specific conditions may flow to dev mode pages. There is little to no expected impact. The Vite development is not exposed to the network by default and even if someone were able to trick a developer into executing an XSS against themselves, a development database should not have any sensitive data. None the less this issue has been addressed in version 2.8.3 and all users are advised to upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53262 | Unescaped error message included on error page in SvelteKit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53262</link><description>SvelteKit is a framework for rapidly developing robust, performant web applications using Svelte. The static error.html template for errors contains placeholders that are replaced without escaping the content first. error.html is the page that is rendered when everything else fails. It can contain the following placeholders: %sveltekit.status% — the HTTP status, and %sveltekit.error.message% — the error message.  This leads to possible injection if an app explicitly creates an error with a message that contains user controlled content. Only applications where user provided input is used in the `Error` message will be vulnerable, so the vast majority of applications will not be vulnerable This issue has been addressed in version 2.8.3 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:22:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53255 | Reflected Cross-site Scripting in /admin?page=media via file Parameter in BoidCMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53255</link><description>BoidCMS is a free and open-source flat file CMS for building simple websites and blogs, developed using PHP and uses JSON as a database. In affected versions a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the /admin?page=media endpoint in the file parameter, allowing an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript code. This code could be used to steal the user's session cookie, perform phishing attacks, or deface the website. This issue has been addressed in version 2.1.2 and all users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52811 | Acks not validated before logged to qlog leads to buffer overflow in ngtcp2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52811</link><description>The ngtcp2 project is an effort to implement IETF QUIC protocol in C. In affected versions acks are not validated before being written to the qlog leading to a buffer overflow. In `ngtcp2_conn::conn_recv_pkt` for an ACK, there was new logic that got added to skip `conn_recv_ack` if an ack has already been processed in the payload. However, this causes us to also skip `ngtcp2_pkt_validate_ack`. The ack which was skipped still got written to qlog. The bug occurs in `ngtcp2_qlog::write_ack_frame`. It is now possible to reach this code with an invalid ack, suppose `largest_ack=0` and `first_ack_range=15`. Subtracting `largest_ack - first_ack_range` will lead to an integer underflow which is 20 chars long. However, the ngtcp2 qlog code assumes the number written is a signed integer and only accounts for 19 characters of overhead (see `NGTCP2_QLOG_ACK_FRAME_RANGE_OVERHEAD`). Therefore, we overwrite the buffer causing a heap overflow. This is high priority and could potentially impact many users if they enable qlog. qlog is disabled by default. Due to its overhead, it is most likely used for debugging purpose, but the actual use is unknown. ngtcp2 v1.9.1 fixes the bug and users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should not turn on qlog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32468 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation (&amp;quot;Cross-site Scripting&amp;quot;) in deno_doc HTML generator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32468</link><description>Deno is a runtime for JavaScript and TypeScript written in rust. Several cross-site scripting vulnerabilities existed in the `deno_doc` crate which lead to Self-XSS with deno doc --html. 1.) XSS in generated `search_index.js`, `deno_doc` outputs a JavaScript file for searching. However, the generated file used `innerHTML` on unsanitzed HTML input. 2.) XSS via property, method and enum names, `deno_doc` did not sanitize property names, method names and enum names. The first XSS most likely didn't have an impact since `deno doc --html` is expected to be used locally with own packages.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51723 | Vulnerability in Management Console Impacts BlackBerry AtHoc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51723</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Management Console of BlackBerry AtHoc version 7.15 could allow an attacker to potentially execute actions in the context of the victim's session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52529 | Layer 7 policy enforcement may not occur in policies with wildcarded port ranges in Cilium</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52529</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. For users with the following configuration: 1. An allow policy that selects a Layer 3 destination and a port range `AND` 2. A Layer 7 allow policy that selects a specific port within the first policy's range the Layer 7 enforcement would not occur for the traffic selected by the Layer 7 policy. This issue only affects users who use Cilium's port range functionality, which was introduced in Cilium v1.16. This issue is patched in PR #35150. This issue affects Cilium v1.16 between v1.16.0 and v1.16.3 inclusive. This issue is patched in Cilium v1.16.4. Users are advised to upgrade. Users with network policies that match the pattern described above can work around the issue by rewriting any policies that use port ranges to individually specify the ports permitted for traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53599 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /scroll.php endpoint of LafeLabs Chaos v0.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53599</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the /scroll.php endpoint of LafeLabs Chaos v0.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8272 | macOS Universal Audio (UAConnect) &amp;lt;= 2.7.0  - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8272</link><description>The com.uaudio.bsd.helper service, responsible for handling privileged operations, fails to implement critical client validation during XPC inter-process communication (IPC). Specifically, the service does not verify the code requirements, entitlements, or security flags of any client attempting to establish a connection. This lack of proper validation allows unauthorized clients to exploit the service's methods and escalate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:54:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7915 | macOS Sensei Mac Cleaner Local Privilege Escalation via PID Reuse - Race Condition Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7915</link><description>The application Sensei Mac Cleaner contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability, allowing an attacker to perform multiple operations as the root user. These operations include arbitrary file deletion and writing, loading and unloading daemons, manipulating file permissions, and loading extensions, among other actions.


The vulnerable module org.cindori.SenseiHelper can be contacted via XPC. While the module performs client validation, it relies on the client's PID obtained through the public processIdentifier property of the NSXPCConnection class. This approach makes the module susceptible to a PID Reuse Attack, enabling an attacker to impersonate a legitimate client and send crafted XPC messages to invoke arbitrary methods exposed by the HelperProtocol interface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52787 | An issue in the upload_documents method of libre-chat v0.0.6 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via supplying a crafted filename i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52787</link><description>An issue in the upload_documents method of libre-chat v0.0.6 allows attackers to execute a path traversal via supplying a crafted filename in an uploaded file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45756 | An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-open-tickets 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.2, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45756</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-open-tickets 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.2, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x before 23.04.3, and 22.10.x before 22.10.2. SQL injection can occur in the form to create a ticket. Exploitation is only accessible to authenticated users with high-privileged access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45755 | An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-dsm-server 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x befo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45755</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-dsm-server 24.10.x before 24.10.0, 24.04.x before 24.04.3, 23.10.x before 23.10.1, 23.04.x before 23.04.3, and 22.10.x before 22.10.2. SQL injection can occur in the form to configure Centreon DSM slots. Exploitation is only accessible to authenticated users with high-privileged access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26280 | IBM Jazz Foundation improper access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26280</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 and 7.0.3

 could allow a user to change their dashboard using a specially crafted HTTP request due to improper access control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45181 | IBM Jazz Foundation cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45181</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2 and below are vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:52:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11670 | Incorrect authorization in the permission validation component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11670</link><description>Incorrect authorization in the permission validation component of Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows a malicious authenticated user to bypass the "View Password" permission via specific actions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11671 | Improper authentication in SQL data source MFA validation in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.17 and earlier on Windows allows an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11671</link><description>Improper authentication in SQL data source MFA validation in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.17 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user to bypass the MFA validation via data source switching.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11672 | Incorrect authorization in the add permission component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows an aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11672</link><description>Incorrect authorization in the add permission component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.2.21 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated malicious user to bypass the "Add" permission via the import in vault feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27134 | Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27134</link><description>Excessive directory permissions in MLflow leads to local privilege escalation when using spark_udf. This behavior can be exploited by a local attacker to gain elevated permissions by using a ToCToU attack. The issue is only relevant when the spark_udf() MLflow API is called.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11403 | Out of Bounds Memory Read/Write in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11403</link><description>There exists an out of bounds read/write in LibJXL versions prior to commit 9cc451b91b74ba470fd72bd48c121e9f33d24c99. The JPEG decoder used by the JPEG XL encoder when doing JPEG recompression (i.e. if using JxlEncoderAddJPEGFrame on untrusted input) does not properly check bounds in the presence of incomplete codes. This could lead to an out-of-bounds write. In jpegli which is released as part of the same project, the same vulnerability is present. However, the relevant buffer is part of a bigger structure, and the code makes no assumptions on the values that could be overwritten. The issue could however cause jpegli to read uninitialised memory, or addresses of functions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11498 | Resource exhaustion via Stack overflow in libjxl</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11498</link><description>There exists a stack buffer overflow in libjxl. A specifically-crafted file can cause the JPEG XL decoder to use large amounts of stack space (up to 256mb is possible, maybe 512mb), potentially exhausting the stack. An attacker can craft a file that will cause excessive memory usage. We recommend upgrading past commit 65fbec56bc578b6b6ee02a527be70787bbd053b0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12491 | Framework Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12491</link><description>Improper control of framework service permissions with possibility of some sensitive device information leakage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-12492 | Wifi information acquisition vulnerability in Framework Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-12492</link><description>Improper handling of WiFi information by framework services can allow certain malicious applications to obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33862 | Improper access control mechanism in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33862</link><description>IPP software prior to v1.71 is vulnerable to default credential vulnerability. This could
lead attackers to identify and access vulnerable systems.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11664 | eNMS TGZ File controller.py multiselect_filtering path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11664</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in eNMS up to 4.2. Affected by this issue is the function multiselect_filtering of the file eNMS/controller.py of the component TGZ File Handler. The manipulation leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as 22b0b443acca740fc83b5544165c1f53eff3f529. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-33861 | Insufficient verification of authenticity in IPP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-33861</link><description>IPP software versions prior to v1.71 do not sufficiently verify the authenticity of data, in a
way that causes it to accept invalid data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-23282 | Stored Cross-site Scripting reported in Intelligent Power Manager v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-23282</link><description>Eaton Intelligent Power Manager (IPM) prior to 1.70 is vulnerable to stored Cross site scripting. The
vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation of input from certain resources by the IPM software.
The attacker would need access to the local Subnet and an administrator interaction to compromise
the system</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11663 | Codezips E-Commerce Site search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11663</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Codezips E-Commerce Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:43:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11662 | welliamcao OpsManage API Endpoint deploy_api.py deploy_host_vars deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11662</link><description>A vulnerability was found in welliamcao OpsManage 3.0.1/3.0.2/3.0.3/3.0.4/3.0.5. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function deploy_host_vars of the file /apps/api/views/deploy_api.py of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10270 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-services: keycloak denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak-services package. If untrusted data is passed to the SearchQueryUtils method, it could lead to a denial of service (DoS) scenario by exhausting system resources due to a Regex complexity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10451 | Org.keycloak:keycloak-quarkus-server: sensitive data exposure in keycloak build process</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10451</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. This issue occurs because sensitive runtime values, such as passwords, may be captured during the Keycloak build process and embedded as default values in bytecode, leading to unintended information disclosure. In Keycloak 26, sensitive data specified directly in environment variables during the build process is also stored as a default values, making it accessible during runtime. Indirect usage of environment variables for SPI options and Quarkus properties is also vulnerable due to unconditional expansion by PropertyMapper logic, capturing sensitive data as default values in all Keycloak versions up to 26.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10492 | Keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak path trasversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10492</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. A user with high privileges could read sensitive information from a Vault file that is not within the expected context. This attacker must have previous high access to the Keycloak server in order to perform resource creation, for example, an LDAP provider configuration and set up a Vault read file, which will only inform whether that file exists or not.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11661 | Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System Profile Image profile.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11661</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Codezips Free Exam Hall Seating Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file profile.php of the component Profile Image Handler. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The researcher submit confuses the vulnerability class of this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9666 | Org.keycloak/keycloak-quarkus-server: keycloak proxy header handling denial-of-service (dos) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9666</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Keycloak Server. The Keycloak Server is vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to improper handling of proxy headers. When Keycloak is configured to accept incoming proxy headers, it may accept non-IP values, such as obfuscated identifiers, without proper validation. This issue can lead to costly DNS resolution operations, which an attacker could exploit to tie up IO threads and potentially cause a denial of service.
The attacker must have access to send requests to a Keycloak instance that is configured to accept proxy headers, specifically when reverse proxies do not overwrite incoming headers, and Keycloak is configured to trust these headers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11660 | code-projects Farmacia usuario.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11660</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file usuario.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 07:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11659 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_iperf command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11659</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_iperf. The manipulation of the argument iperf leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6538 | Openshift-console: openshift console:  server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6538</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift Console. A Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) attack can happen if an attacker supplies all or part of a URL to the server to query. The server is considered to be in a privileged network position and can often reach exposed services that aren't readily available to clients due to network filtering. Leveraging such an attack vector, the attacker can have an impact on other services and potentially disclose information or have other nefarious effects on the system.
The /api/dev-console/proxy/internet endpoint on the OpenShit Console allows authenticated users to have the console's pod perform arbitrary and fully controlled HTTP(s) requests. The full response to these requests is returned by the endpoint.
While the name of this endpoint suggests the requests are only bound to the internet, no such checks are in place. An authenticated user can therefore ask the console to perform arbitrary HTTP requests from outside the cluster to a service inside the cluster.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:44:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10709 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10709</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10710 | YaDisk Files &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10710</link><description>The YaDisk Files WordPress plugin through 1.2.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11658 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT ajax_getChannelList command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11658</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/ajax_getChannelList. The manipulation of the argument countryCode leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6393 | NextGEN Gallery &amp;lt; 3.59.5 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6393</link><description>The Photo Gallery, Sliders, Proofing and   WordPress plugin before 3.59.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its Images settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7056 | WPForms &amp;lt; 1.9.1.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7056</link><description>The WPForms  WordPress plugin before 1.9.1.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 06:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11657 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_nslookup command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11657</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/diag_nslookup. The manipulation of the argument diag_nslookup leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11656 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_ping6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11656</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/network/diag_ping6. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping6 leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 05:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-11311 | Information Exposure in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-11311</link><description>This record is rejected as duplicate. All references should point to CVE-2021-1904.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11655 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_pinginterface command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11655</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/network/diag_pinginterface. The manipulation of the argument diag_ping leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11654 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute6 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11654</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute6. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute6 leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11483 | Automation-gateway: improper scope handling in oauth2 tokens for aap 2.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11483</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the Ansible Automation Platform (AAP). This flaw allows attackers to escalate privileges by improperly leveraging read-scoped OAuth2 tokens to gain write access. This issue affects API endpoints that rely on ansible_base.oauth2_provider for OAuth2 authentication. While the impact is limited to actions within the user’s assigned permissions, it undermines scoped access controls, potentially allowing unintended modifications in the application and consuming services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11653 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT diag_traceroute command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11653</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/network/diag_traceroute. The manipulation of the argument diag_traceroute leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:46:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11652 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT sn_https command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11652</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/sn_package/sn_https. The manipulation of the argument https_enable leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53930 | WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53930</link><description>WikiDocs before 1.0.65 allows stored XSS by authenticated users via data that comes after $$\\, which is mishandled by a KaTeX parser.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11651 | EnGenius ENH1350EXT/ENS500-AC/ENS620EXT wifi_schedule command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11651</link><description>A vulnerability was found in EnGenius ENH1350EXT, ENS500-AC and ENS620EXT up to 20241118. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/network/wifi_schedule. The manipulation of the argument wifi_schedule_day_em_5 leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 03:22:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11650 | Tenda i9 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11650</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i9 1.0.0.8(3828) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11649 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System search-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11649</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 02:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11648 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System add-customer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11648</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/add-customer.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11647 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11647</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 01:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11646 | 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System edit-services.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11646</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000 Projects Beauty Parlour Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-services.php. The manipulation of the argument sername leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 23:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53916 | In OpenStack Neutron through 25.0.0, neutron/extensions/tagging.py can use an incorrect ID during policy enforcement. NOTE: 935883 has the "...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53916</link><description>In OpenStack Neutron through 25.0.0, neutron/extensions/tagging.py can use an incorrect ID during policy enforcement. NOTE: 935883 has the "Work in Progress" status as of 2024-11-24.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 23:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11665 | Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11665</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in hardy-barth cph2_echarge_firmware allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects cph2_echarge_firmware: through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11666 | Unauthenticated Remote Command Injection in eCharge Salia PLCC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11666</link><description>Affected devices beacon to eCharge cloud infrastructure asking if there are any command they should run. This communication is established over an insecure channel since peer verification is disabled everywhere. Therefore, remote unauthenticated users  suitably positioned on the network between an EV charger controller and eCharge infrastructure can execute arbitrary commands with elevated privileges on affected devices.

This issue affects cph2_echarge_firmware: through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 22:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53909 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24334. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53909</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24334. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53910 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24336. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53910</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24336. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53911 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24339. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53911</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24339. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53912 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24341. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53912</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24341. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53913 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24343. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53913</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24343. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53914 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24344. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53914</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24344. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53915 | An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24405. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53915</link><description>An issue was discovered in the server in Veritas Enterprise Vault before 15.2, ZDI-CAN-24405. It allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code because untrusted data, received on a .NET Remoting TCP port, is deserialized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53901 | The Imager package before 1.025 for Perl has a heap-based buffer overflow leading to denial of service, or possibly unspecified other impact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53901</link><description>The Imager package before 1.025 for Perl has a heap-based buffer overflow leading to denial of service, or possibly unspecified other impact, when the trim() method is called on a crafted input image.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 16:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53899 | virtualenv before 20.26.6 allows command injection through the activation scripts for a virtual environment. Magic template strings are not ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53899</link><description>virtualenv before 20.26.6 allows command injection through the activation scripts for a virtual environment. Magic template strings are not quoted correctly when replacing. NOTE: this is not the same as CVE-2024-9287.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 16:23:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11233 | Single byte overread with convert.quoted-printable-decode filter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11233</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, due to an error in convert.quoted-printable-decode filter certain data can lead to buffer overread by one byte, which can in certain circumstances lead to crashes or disclose content of other memory areas.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11234 | Configuring a proxy in a stream context might allow for CRLF injection in URIs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11234</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, when using streams with configured proxy and "request_fulluri" option, the URI is not properly sanitized which can lead to HTTP request smuggling and allow the attacker to use the proxy to perform arbitrary HTTP requests originating from the server, thus potentially gaining access to resources not normally available to the external user.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11236 | Integer overflow in the firebird and dblib quoters causing OOB writes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11236</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.31, 8.2.* before 8.2.26, 8.3.* before 8.3.14, uncontrolled long string inputs to ldap_escape() function on 32-bit systems can cause an integer overflow, resulting in an out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 02:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>