<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-33671 | An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. The Backup Exec Deduplication Multi-threaded Streaming Agent can b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33671</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. The Backup Exec Deduplication Multi-threaded Streaming Agent can be leveraged to perform arbitrary file deletion on protected files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33672 | An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.4. The Multi-Threaded Agent used in NetBackup can be leveraged to perform arbitrary f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33672</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.4. The Multi-Threaded Agent used in NetBackup can be leveraged to perform arbitrary file deletion on protected files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33673 | An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. Improper access controls allow for DLL Hijacking in the Windows DL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33673</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. Improper access controls allow for DLL Hijacking in the Windows DLL Search path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48682 | In deletefiles in FDUPES before 2.2.0, a TOCTOU race condition allows arbitrary file deletion via a symlink.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48682</link><description>In deletefiles in FDUPES before 2.2.0, a TOCTOU race condition allows arbitrary file deletion via a symlink.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33669 | An issue was discovered in Passbolt Browser Extension before 4.6.2. It can send multiple requests to HaveIBeenPwned while a password is bein...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33669</link><description>An issue was discovered in Passbolt Browser Extension before 4.6.2. It can send multiple requests to HaveIBeenPwned while a password is being typed, which results in an information leak. This allows an attacker capable of observing Passbolt's HTTPS queries to the Pwned Password API to more easily brute force passwords that are manually typed by the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33670 | Passbolt API before 4.6.2 allows HTML injection in a URL parameter, resulting in custom content being displayed when a user visits the craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33670</link><description>Passbolt API before 4.6.2 allows HTML injection in a URL parameter, resulting in custom content being displayed when a user visits the crafted URL. Although the injected content is not executed as JavaScript due to Content Security Policy (CSP) restrictions, it may still impact the appearance and user interaction of the page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33666 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. Users with customer access to a ticket could have accessed time accounting details of this t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33666</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. Users with customer access to a ticket could have accessed time accounting details of this ticket via the API. This data should be available only to agents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33667 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. An authenticated agent could perform a remote Denial of Service attack by calling an endpoin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33667</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. An authenticated agent could perform a remote Denial of Service attack by calling an endpoint that accepts a generic method name, which was not properly sanitized against an allowlist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33668 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. The Zammad Upload Cache uses insecure, partially guessable FormIDs to identify content. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33668</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. The Zammad Upload Cache uses insecure, partially guessable FormIDs to identify content. An attacker could try to brute force them to upload malicious content to article drafts they have no access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33665 | angular-translate through 2.19.1 allows XSS via a crafted key that is used by the translate directive. NOTE: the vendor indicates that there...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33665</link><description>angular-translate through 2.19.1 allows XSS via a crafted key that is used by the translate directive. NOTE: the vendor indicates that there is no documentation indicating that a key is supposed to be safe against XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32868 | ZITADEL&amp;#x27;s Improper Lockout Mechanism Leads to MFA Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32868</link><description>ZITADEL provides users the possibility to use Time-based One-Time-Password (TOTP) and One-Time-Password (OTP) through SMS and Email. While ZITADEL already gives administrators the option to define a `Lockout Policy` with a maximum amount of failed password check attempts, there was no such mechanism for (T)OTP checks. This issue has been patched in version 2.50.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32651 | Server Side Template Injection in Jinja2 allows Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32651</link><description>changedetection.io is an open source web page change detection, website watcher, restock monitor and notification service. There is a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI) in Jinja2 that allows Remote Command Execution on the server host. Attackers can run any system command without any restriction and they could use a reverse shell. The impact is critical as the attacker can completely takeover the server machine. This can be reduced if changedetection is behind a login page, but this isn't required by the application (not by default and not enforced).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33661 | Portainer before 2.20.0 allows redirects when the target is not index.yaml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33661</link><description>Portainer before 2.20.0 allows redirects when the target is not index.yaml.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33663 | python-jose through 3.3.0 has algorithm confusion with OpenSSH ECDSA keys and other key formats. This is similar to CVE-2022-29217.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33663</link><description>python-jose through 3.3.0 has algorithm confusion with OpenSSH ECDSA keys and other key formats. This is similar to CVE-2022-29217.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33664 | python-jose through 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) during a decode via a crafted JSON Web Encryp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33664</link><description>python-jose through 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) during a decode via a crafted JSON Web Encryption (JWE) token with a high compression ratio, aka a "JWT bomb." This is similar to CVE-2024-21319.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0916 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in UvDesk Community</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0916</link><description>Unauthenticated file upload allows remote code execution.
This issue affects UvDesk Community: from 1.0.0 through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3265 | WP Advanced Search &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3265</link><description>The Advanced Search WordPress plugin through 1.1.6 does not properly escape parameters appended to an SQL query, making it possible for users with the administrator role to conduct SQL Injection attacks in the context of a multisite WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31609 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BOSSCMS v3.10 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the header code and footer code fields ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31609</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BOSSCMS v3.10 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the header code and footer code fields in code configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31610 | File Upload vulnerability in the function for employees to upload avatars in Code-Projects Simple School Management System v1.0 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31610</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in the function for employees to upload avatars in Code-Projects Simple School Management System v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36029 | BigBlueButton Greenlight Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36029</link><description>Greenlight is an end-user interface for BigBlueButton servers. Versions prior to 2.13.0 have an open redirect vulnerability in the Login page due to unchecked the value of the `return_to` cookie. Versions 2.13.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36028 | BigBlueButton Greenlight Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36028</link><description>Greenlight is an end-user interface for BigBlueButton servers. Versions prior to 2.13.0 have an open redirect vulnerability in the Login page due to unchecked the value of the `return_to` cookie. Versions 2.13.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32324 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v.3.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32324</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v.3.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the vpn_client_ip variable of the config_vpn_pptp function in rc program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 19:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31615 | ThinkCMF 6.0.9 is vulnerable to File upload via UeditorController.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31615</link><description>ThinkCMF 6.0.9 is vulnerable to File upload via UeditorController.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 19:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30939 | An issue discovered in Yealink VP59 Teams Editions with firmware version 91.15.0.118 allows a physically proximate attacker to gain control ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30939</link><description>An issue discovered in Yealink VP59 Teams Editions with firmware version 91.15.0.118 allows a physically proximate attacker to gain control of an account via a flaw in the factory reset procedure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32649 | vyper performs double eval of the argument of sqrt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32649</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `sqrt` builtin can result in double eval vulnerability when the argument has side-effects. It can be seen that the `build_IR` function of the `sqrt` builtin doesn't cache the argument to the stack. As such, it can be evaluated multiple times (instead of retrieving the value from the stack). No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32648 | vyper default functions don&amp;#x27;t respect nonreentrancy keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32648</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. Prior to version 0.3.0, default functions don't respect nonreentrancy keys and the lock isn't emitted. No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, using a lock on a `default` function is a very sparsely used pattern. As such, the impact is low. Version 0.3.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3623 | Mirror-registry: default database secret key stored in plain-text on initial configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3623</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default database secret key, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same database secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to access sensitive information from Quay's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3624 | Mirror-registry: database user and password stored in plain-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3624</link><description>A flaw was found in how Quay's database is stored in plain-text in mirror-registry on the jinja's config.yaml file. This flaw allows a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3625 | Mirror-registry: redis password stored in plain-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3625</link><description>A flaw was found in Quay, where Quay's database is stored in plain text in mirror-registry on Jinja's config.yaml file. This issue leaves the possibility of a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's Redis instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2905 | Rpm-ostree: world-readable /etc/shadow file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2905</link><description>A security vulnerability has been discovered within rpm-ostree, pertaining to the /etc/shadow file in default builds having the world-readable bit enabled. This issue arises from the default permissions being set at a higher level than recommended, potentially exposing sensitive authentication data to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32647 | vyper performs double eval of raw_args in create_from_blueprint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32647</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `create_from_blueprint` builtin can result in a double eval vulnerability when `raw_args=True` and the `args` argument has side-effects. It can be seen that the `_build_create_IR` function of the `create_from_blueprint` builtin doesn't cache the mentioned `args` argument to the stack. As such, it can be evaluated multiple times (instead of retrieving the value from the stack). No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3508 | Bzip2: compressed content bomb leads to denial of service of bombastic api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3508</link><description>A flaw was found in Bombastic, which allows authenticated users to upload compressed (bzip2 or zstd) SBOMs. The API endpoint verifies the presence of some fields and values in the JSON. To perform this verification, the uploaded file must first be decompressed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3622 | Mirror-registry: plain-text default csrf secret key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3622</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default secret, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to craft session cookies and as a consequence, it may lead to gaining access to the affected Quay instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32646 | vyper performs double eval of the slice args when buffer from adhoc locations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32646</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `slice` builtin can result in a double eval vulnerability when the buffer argument is either `msg.data`, `self.code` or `&lt;address&gt;.code` and either the `start` or `length` arguments have side-effects. It can be easily triggered only with the versions `&lt;0.3.4` as `0.3.4` introduced the unique symbol fence. No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32645 | vyper performs incorrect topic logging in raw_log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32645</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.13.0 and prior, incorrect values can be logged when `raw_log` builtin is called with memory or storage arguments to be used as topics. A contract search was performed and no vulnerable contracts were found in production. The `build_IR` function of the `RawLog` class fails to properly unwrap the variables provided as topics. Consequently, incorrect values are logged as topics. As of time of publication, no fixed version is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32481 | vyper&amp;#x27;s range(start, start + N) reverts for negative numbers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32481</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. Starting in version 0.3.8 and prior to version 0.4.0b1, when looping over a `range` of the form `range(start, start + N)`, if `start` is negative, the execution will always revert. This issue is caused by an incorrect assertion inserted by the code generation of the range `stmt.parse_For_range()`. The issue arises when `start` is signed, instead of using `sle`, `le` is used and `start` is interpreted as an unsigned integer for the comparison. If it is a negative number, its 255th bit is set to `1` and is hence interpreted as a very large unsigned integer making the assertion always fail. Any contract having a `range(start, start + N)` where `start` is a signed integer with the possibility for `start` to be negative is affected. If a call goes through the loop while supplying a negative `start` the execution will revert. Version 0.4.0b1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32467 | Meteraphsere vulnerable to unauthorized viewing by workspace members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32467</link><description>MeterSphere is an open source continuous testing platform. Prior to version 2.10.14-lts, members without space permissions can view member information from other workspaces beyond their authority. Version 2.10.14-lts fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28241 | GlPI-Agent MSI package installation doesn&amp;#x27;t update folder security profile when using non default installation folder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28241</link><description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. Prior to version 1.7.2, a local user can modify GLPI-Agent code or used DLLs to modify agent logic and even gain higher privileges. Users should upgrade to GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 to receive a patch. As a workaround, use the default installation folder which involves installed folder is automatically secured by the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2467 | Perl-crypt-openssl-rsa: side-channel attack in pkcs#1 v1.5 padding mode (marvin attack)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2467</link><description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the perl-Crypt-OpenSSL-RSA package, which could be sufficient to recover plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28240 | GLPI-Agent&amp;#x27;s MSI package installation permits local users to change Agent configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28240</link><description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. A vulnerability that only affects GLPI-Agent installed on windows via MSI packaging can allow a local user to cause denial of agent service by replacing GLPI server url with a wrong url or disabling the service. Additionally, in the case the Deploy task is installed, a local malicious user can trigger privilege escalation configuring a malicious server providing its own deploy task payload. GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, edit GLPI-Agent related key under `HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Uninstall` and add `SystemComponent` DWORD value setting it to `1` to hide GLPI-Agent from installed applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1657 | Ansible automation platform: insecure websocket used when interacting with eda server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1657</link><description>A flaw was found in the ansible automation platform. An insecure WebSocket connection was being used in installation from the Ansible rulebook EDA server. An attacker that has access to any machine in the CIDR block could download all rulebook data from the WebSocket, resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1726 | Quarkus: security checks for some inherited endpoints performed after serialization in resteasy reactive may trigger a denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1726</link><description>A flaw was discovered in the RESTEasy Reactive implementation in Quarkus. Due to security checks for some JAX-RS endpoints being performed after serialization, more processing resources are consumed while the HTTP request is checked. In certain configurations, if an attacker has knowledge of any POST, PUT, or PATCH request paths, they can potentially identify vulnerable endpoints and trigger excessive resource usage as the endpoints process the requests. This can result in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25624 | iris-web vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25624</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform aiming to help incident responders sharing technical details during investigations. Due to an improper setup of Jinja2 environment, reports generation in `iris-web` is prone to a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI). Successful exploitation of the vulnerability can lead to an arbitrary Remote Code Execution. An authenticated administrator has to upload a crafted report template containing the payload. Upon generation of a report based on the weaponized report, any user can trigger the vulnerability.  The vulnerability is patched in IRIS v2.4.6. No workaround is available. It is recommended to update as soon as possible. Until patching, review the report templates and keep the administrative privileges that include the upload of report templates limited to dedicated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31574 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TWCMS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31574</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TWCMS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0874 | Coredns: cd bit response is cached and served later</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0874</link><description>A flaw was found in coredns. This issue could lead to invalid cache entries returning due to incorrectly implemented caching.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1102 | Jberet: jberet-core logging database credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1102</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jberet-core logging. An exception in 'dbProperties' might display user credentials such as the username and password for the database-connection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1139 | Cluster-monitoring-operator: credentials leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1139</link><description>A credentials leak vulnerability was found in the cluster monitoring operator in OCP.  This issue may allow a remote attacker who has basic login credentials to check the pod manifest to discover a repository pull secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29660 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the stepselec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29660</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the stepselect_main.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32358 | An issue in Jpress v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the custom plug-in module function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32358</link><description>An issue in Jpress v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the custom plug-in module function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30890 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ED01-CMS v.1.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the categories.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30890</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ED01-CMS v.1.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the categories.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32236 | An issue in CmsEasy v.7.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the update function in the index.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32236</link><description>An issue in CmsEasy v.7.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the update function in the index.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6717 | Keycloak: xss via assertion consumer service url in saml post-binding flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6717</link><description>A flaw was found in the SAML client registration in Keycloak that could allow an administrator to register malicious JavaScript URIs as Assertion Consumer Service POST Binding URLs (ACS), posing a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) risk. This issue may allow a malicious admin in one realm or a client with registration access to target users in different realms or applications, executing arbitrary JavaScript in their contexts upon form submission. This can enable unauthorized access and harmful actions, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the complete KC instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6787 | Keycloak: session hijacking via re-authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6787</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak that occurs from an error in the re-authentication mechanism within org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows hijacking an active Keycloak session by triggering a new authentication process with the query parameter "prompt=login," prompting the user to re-enter their credentials. If the user cancels this re-authentication by selecting "Restart login," an account takeover may occur, as the new session, with a different SUB, will possess the same SID as the previous session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6484 | Keycloak: log injection during webauthn authentication or registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6484</link><description>A log injection flaw was found in Keycloak. A text string may be injected through the authentication form when using the WebAuthn authentication mode. This issue may have a minor impact to the logs integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6544 | Keycloak: authorization bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6544</link><description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak package. This issue occurs due to a permissive regular expression hardcoded for filtering which allows hosts to register a dynamic client. A malicious user with enough information about the environment could jeopardize an environment with this specific Dynamic Client Registration and TrustedDomain configuration previously unauthorized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6596 | Openshift: incomplete fix for rapid reset (cve-2023-44487/cve-2023-39325)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6596</link><description>An incomplete fix was shipped for the Rapid Reset (CVE-2023-44487/CVE-2023-39325) vulnerability for an OpenShift Containers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5675 | Quarkus: authorization flaw in quarkus resteasy reactive and classic when &amp;quot;quarkus.security.jaxrs.deny-unannotated-endpoints&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;quarkus.security.jaxrs.default-roles-allowed&amp;quot; properties are used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5675</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. When a Quarkus RestEasy Classic or Reactive JAX-RS endpoint has its methods declared in the abstract Java class or customized by Quarkus extensions using the annotation processor, the authorization of these methods will not be enforced if it is enabled by either 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.deny-unannotated-endpoints' or 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.default-roles-allowed' properties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33592 | WordPress Radio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.73 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33592</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in SoftLab Radio Player.This issue affects Radio Player: from n/a through 2.0.73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22373 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the JPEG2000Codec::DecodeByStreamsCommon functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22373</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the JPEG2000Codec::DecodeByStreamsCommon functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted DICOM file can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22391 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LookupTable::SetLUT functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22391</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LookupTable::SetLUT functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25569 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the RAWCodec::DecodeBytes functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25569</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the RAWCodec::DecodeBytes functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted DICOM file can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4172 | idcCMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4172</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in idcCMS 1.35. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_cl.php?mudi=revPwd. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261991.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4006 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4024 | Improper Authentication in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4171 | Tenda W30E WizardHandle fromWizardHandle stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4171</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda W30E 1.0/1.0.1.25. Affected is the function fromWizardHandle of the file /goform/WizardHandle. The manipulation of the argument PPW leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4170 | Tenda 4G300 sub_429A30 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4170</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sub_429A30. The manipulation of the argument list1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-261989 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33247 | Sourcecodester Employee Task Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin-manage-user.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33247</link><description>Sourcecodester Employee Task Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin-manage-user.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4169 | Tenda 4G300 sub_4279CC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4169</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sub_42775C/sub_4279CC. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261988. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3597 | Keycloak: secondary factor bypass in step-up authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3597</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak, where it does not correctly validate its client step-up authentication in org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows a remote user authenticated with a password to register a false second authentication factor along with an existing one and bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25026 | IBM WebSphere Application Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25026</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5, 9.0 and IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.4 are vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially crafted request.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  281516.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4167 | Tenda 4G300 sub_422AA4 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4167</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_422AA4. The manipulation of the argument year/month/day/hour/minute/second leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-261986 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4168 | Tenda 4G300 sub_4260F0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4168</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sub_4260F0. The manipulation of the argument upfilen leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261987. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4175 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4175</link><description>Unicode transformation vulnerability in Hyperion affecting version 2.0.15. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a malicious payload with Unicode characters that will be replaced by ASCII characters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4174 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4174</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server affecting version 2.0.15. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute malicious Javascript code on the client by injecting that code into the URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4165 | Tenda G3 modifyDhcpRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4165</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda G3 15.11.0.17(9502). Affected is the function modifyDhcpRule of the file /goform/modifyDhcpRule. The manipulation of the argument bindDhcpIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261984. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4166 | Tenda 4G300 sub_41E858 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4166</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_41E858. The manipulation of the argument GO/page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-261985 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1347 | Improper Authentication in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2434 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2829 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3730 | The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'swpm_paypal_subscription_cancel_li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3730</link><description>The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'swpm_paypal_subscription_cancel_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32676 | WordPress LoginPress Pro plugin &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32676</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in LoginPress LoginPress Pro.This issue affects LoginPress Pro: from n/a before 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4164 | Tenda G3 ModifyPppAuthWhiteMac formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4164</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda G3 15.11.0.17(9502). This issue affects the function formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac of the file /goform/ModifyPppAuthWhiteMac. The manipulation of the argument pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261983. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25583 | Crafted responses can lead to a denial of service in Recursor if recursive forwarding is configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25583</link><description>A crafted response from an upstream server the recursor has been configured to forward-recurse to can cause a Denial of Service in the Recursor. The default configuration of the Recursor does not use recursive forwarding and is not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52220 | WordPress MonsterInsights plugin &amp;lt;= 8.21.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52220</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MonsterInsights Google Analytics by Monster Insights.This issue affects Google Analytics by Monster Insights: from n/a through 8.21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3994 | The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3994</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tutor_instructor_list' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4035 | The Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4035</link><description>The Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image alt text in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.7.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32961 | WordPress Blocksy theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.33 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative Themes HQ Blocksy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.33.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4077 | WordPress UDesign theme &amp;lt;= 4.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4077</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AndonDesign UDesign allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects UDesign: from n/a through 4.7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30560 | WordPress DX-Watermark plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Upload and XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30560</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in 大侠WP DX-Watermark.This issue affects DX-Watermark: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31266 | WordPress Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31266</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in AlgolPlus Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce allows Code Injection.This issue affects Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25917 | WordPress WP Setup Wizard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.1 - Auth. Full Database Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25917</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in CodeRevolution WP Setup Wizard.This issue affects WP Setup Wizard: from n/a through 1.0.8.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3733 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3733</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51484 | WordPress Login as User or Customer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51484</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in wp-buy Login as User or Customer (User Switching) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Login as User or Customer (User Switching): from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22144 | WordPress Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall plugin &amp;lt;= 4.21.96 - Unauthenticated Predictable Nonce Brute-Force Leading to RCE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22144</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Eli Scheetz Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall gotmls allows Code Injection.This issue affects Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall: from n/a through 4.21.96.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51482 | WordPress Eazy Plugin Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Auth. Arbitrary Options Update lead to RCE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51482</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in EazyPlugins Eazy Plugin Manager allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Eazy Plugin Manager: from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51478 | WordPress Build App Online plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51478</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Abdul Hakeem Build App Online allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Build App Online: from n/a through 1.0.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3893 | The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3893</link><description>The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the rtcl_fb_gallery_image_delete AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3929 | The Content Views – Post Grid &amp; Filter, Recent Posts, Category Posts, &amp; More (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3929</link><description>The Content Views – Post Grid &amp; Filter, Recent Posts, Category Posts, &amp; More (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the  Widget Post Overlay block in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3988 | The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3988</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Sina Fancy Text Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4173 | Inconsistent firewall rules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4173</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav ova versions before Brocade SANnav v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a exposes Kafka in the wan interface due to inconsistent firewall rules.

The vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform various attacks, including DOS, the Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6237 | Excessive time spent checking invalid RSA public keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6237</link><description>Issue summary: Checking excessively long invalid RSA public keys may take
a long time.

Impact summary: Applications that use the function EVP_PKEY_public_check()
to check RSA public keys may experience long delays. Where the key that
is being checked has been obtained from an untrusted source this may lead
to a Denial of Service.

When function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is called on RSA public keys,
a computation is done to confirm that the RSA modulus, n, is composite.
For valid RSA keys, n is a product of two or more large primes and this
computation completes quickly. However, if n is an overly large prime,
then this computation would take a long time.

An application that calls EVP_PKEY_public_check() and supplies an RSA key
obtained from an untrusted source could be vulnerable to a Denial of Service
attack.

The function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is not called from other OpenSSL
functions however it is called from the OpenSSL pkey command line
application. For that reason that application is also vulnerable if used
with the '-pubin' and '-check' options on untrusted data.

The OpenSSL SSL/TLS implementation is not affected by this issue.

The OpenSSL 3.0 and 3.1 FIPS providers are affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2907 | AGCA – Custom Dashboard &amp;amp; Login Page &amp;lt; 7.2.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Image URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2907</link><description>The AGCA  WordPress plugin before 7.2.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 05:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4161 | Syslog traffic sent in clear-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4161</link><description>In Brocade SANnav, before Brocade SANnav v2.3.0, syslog traffic received
 clear text. This could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to 
capture sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4159 | Protection mechanisms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4159</link><description>Brocade SANnav before Brocade SANnav v2.3.1 lacks protection mechanisms on port 2377/TCP and 7946/TCP, which could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to reach Kafka APIs and send malicious data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26926 | binder: check offset alignment in binder_get_object()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26926</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

binder: check offset alignment in binder_get_object()

Commit 6d98eb95b450 ("binder: avoid potential data leakage when copying
txn") introduced changes to how binder objects are copied. In doing so,
it unintentionally removed an offset alignment check done through calls
to binder_alloc_copy_from_buffer() -&gt; check_buffer().

These calls were replaced in binder_get_object() with copy_from_user(),
so now an explicit offset alignment check is needed here. This avoids
later complications when unwinding the objects gets harder.

It is worth noting this check existed prior to commit 7a67a39320df
("binder: add function to copy binder object from buffer"), likely
removed due to redundancy at the time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23527 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23527</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability in WLAvalancheService component of Ivanti Avalanche before 6.4.3, in certain conditions can allow an unauthenticated remote attacker to read sensitive information in memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29205 | An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the web component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti P...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29205</link><description>An Improper Check for Unusual or Exceptional Conditions vulnerability in the web component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to send specially crafted requests in-order-to cause service disruptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:23:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26923 | af_unix: Fix garbage collector racing against connect()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26923</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Fix garbage collector racing against connect()

Garbage collector does not take into account the risk of embryo getting
enqueued during the garbage collection. If such embryo has a peer that
carries SCM_RIGHTS, two consecutive passes of scan_children() may see a
different set of children. Leading to an incorrectly elevated inflight
count, and then a dangling pointer within the gc_inflight_list.

sockets are AF_UNIX/SOCK_STREAM
S is an unconnected socket
L is a listening in-flight socket bound to addr, not in fdtable
V's fd will be passed via sendmsg(), gets inflight count bumped

connect(S, addr)	sendmsg(S, [V]); close(V)	__unix_gc()
----------------	-------------------------	-----------

NS = unix_create1()
skb1 = sock_wmalloc(NS)
L = unix_find_other(addr)
unix_state_lock(L)
unix_peer(S) = NS
			// V count=1 inflight=0

 			NS = unix_peer(S)
 			skb2 = sock_alloc()
			skb_queue_tail(NS, skb2[V])

			// V became in-flight
			// V count=2 inflight=1

			close(V)

			// V count=1 inflight=1
			// GC candidate condition met

						for u in gc_inflight_list:
						  if (total_refs == inflight_refs)
						    add u to gc_candidates

						// gc_candidates={L, V}

						for u in gc_candidates:
						  scan_children(u, dec_inflight)

						// embryo (skb1) was not
						// reachable from L yet, so V's
						// inflight remains unchanged
__skb_queue_tail(L, skb1)
unix_state_unlock(L)
						for u in gc_candidates:
						  if (u.inflight)
						    scan_children(u, inc_inflight_move_tail)

						// V count=1 inflight=2 (!)

If there is a GC-candidate listening socket, lock/unlock its state. This
makes GC wait until the end of any ongoing connect() to that socket. After
flipping the lock, a possibly SCM-laden embryo is already enqueued. And if
there is another embryo coming, it can not possibly carry SCM_RIGHTS. At
this point, unix_inflight() can not happen because unix_gc_lock is already
taken. Inflight graph remains unaffected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26924 | netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: do not free live element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26924</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_set_pipapo: do not free live element

Pablo reports a crash with large batches of elements with a
back-to-back add/remove pattern.  Quoting Pablo:

  add_elem("00000000") timeout 100 ms
  ...
  add_elem("0000000X") timeout 100 ms
  del_elem("0000000X") &lt;---------------- delete one that was just added
  ...
  add_elem("00005000") timeout 100 ms

  1) nft_pipapo_remove() removes element 0000000X
  Then, KASAN shows a splat.

Looking at the remove function there is a chance that we will drop a
rule that maps to a non-deactivated element.

Removal happens in two steps, first we do a lookup for key k and return the
to-be-removed element and mark it as inactive in the next generation.
Then, in a second step, the element gets removed from the set/map.

The _remove function does not work correctly if we have more than one
element that share the same key.

This can happen if we insert an element into a set when the set already
holds an element with same key, but the element mapping to the existing
key has timed out or is not active in the next generation.

In such case its possible that removal will unmap the wrong element.
If this happens, we will leak the non-deactivated element, it becomes
unreachable.

The element that got deactivated (and will be freed later) will
remain reachable in the set data structure, this can result in
a crash when such an element is retrieved during lookup (stale
pointer).

Add a check that the fully matching key does in fact map to the element
that we have marked as inactive in the deactivation step.
If not, we need to continue searching.

Add a bug/warn trap at the end of the function as well, the remove
function must not ever be called with an invisible/unreachable/non-existent
element.

v2: avoid uneeded temporary variable (Stefano)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26925 | netfilter: nf_tables: release mutex after nft_gc_seq_end from abort path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26925</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: release mutex after nft_gc_seq_end from abort path

The commit mutex should not be released during the critical section
between nft_gc_seq_begin() and nft_gc_seq_end(), otherwise, async GC
worker could collect expired objects and get the released commit lock
within the same GC sequence.

nf_tables_module_autoload() temporarily releases the mutex to load
module dependencies, then it goes back to replay the transaction again.
Move it at the end of the abort phase after nft_gc_seq_end() is called.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20248 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20248</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data in a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20249 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20249</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco TelePresence Management Suite (TMS) Software could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the interface. This vulnerability is due to insufficient input validation by the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by inserting malicious data in a specific data field in the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:57:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20313 | A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20313</link><description>A vulnerability in the OSPF version 2 (OSPFv2) feature of Cisco IOS XE Software could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause an affected device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition. This vulnerability is due to improper validation of OSPF updates that are processed by a device. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a malformed OSPF update to the device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause the affected device to reload, resulting in a DoS condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:47:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20295 | A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform comma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20295</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of the Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, local attacker to perform command injection attacks on the underlying operating system and elevate privileges to root. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have read-only or higher privileges on an affected device. This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user-supplied input. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted CLI command. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20356 | A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20356</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with Administrator-level privileges to perform command injection attacks on an affected system and elevate their privileges to root. This vulnerability is due to insufficient user input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted commands to the web-based management interface of the affected software. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate their privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32879 | social-auth-app-django Improper Handling of Case Sensitivity vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32879</link><description>Python Social Auth is a social authentication/registration mechanism. Prior to version 5.4.1, due to default case-insensitive collation in MySQL or MariaDB databases, third-party authentication user IDs are not case-sensitive and could cause different IDs to match. This issue has been addressed by a fix released in version 5.4.1. An immediate workaround would be to change collation of the affected field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20358 | A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20358</link><description>A vulnerability in the Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) restore functionality that is available in Cisco ASA Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability. This vulnerability exists because the contents of a backup file are improperly sanitized at restore time. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by restoring a crafted backup file to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying Linux operating system as root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4126 | Tenda W15E SetSysTimeCfg formSetSysTime stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4126</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetSysTime of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument manualTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261869 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4127 | Tenda W15E guestWifiRuleRefresh stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4127</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function guestWifiRuleRefresh. The manipulation of the argument qosGuestDownstream leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. VDB-261870 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32876 | NewPipe has potential security vulnerability when importing settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32876</link><description>NewPipe is an Android app for video streaming written in Java. It supports exporting and importing backups, as a way to let users move their data to a new device effortlessly. However, in versions 0.13.4 through 0.26.1, importing a backup file from an untrusted source could have resulted in Arbitrary Code Execution. This is because backups are serialized/deserialized using Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol, which can allow constructing any class in the app, unless properly restricted.

To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need to build a backup file containing the exploit, and then persuade a user into importing it. During the import process, the malicious code would be executed, possibly crashing the app, stealing user data from the NewPipe app, performing nasty actions through Android APIs, and attempting Android JVM/Sandbox escapes through vulnerabilities in the Android OS.

The attack can take place only if the user imports a malicious backup file, so an attacker would need to trick a user into importing a backup file from a source they can control. The implementation details of the malicious backup file can be independent of the attacked user or the device they are being run on, and do not require additional privileges.

All NewPipe versions from 0.13.4 to 0.26.1 are vulnerable. NewPipe version 0.27.0 fixes the issue by doing the following: Restrict the classes that can be deserialized when calling Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol, by adding a whitelist with only innocuous data-only classes that can't lead to Arbitrary Code Execution; deprecate backups serialized with Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol; use JSON serialization for all newly created backups (but still include an alternative file serialized with Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol in the backup zip for backwards compatibility); show a warning to the user when attempting to import a backup where the only available serialization mode is Java's Object Serialization Stream Protocol (note that in the future this serialization mode will be removed completely).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4125 | Tenda W15E setStaticRoute formSetStaticRoute stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4125</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetStaticRoute of the file /goform/setStaticRoute. The manipulation of the argument staticRouteIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261868. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4141 | Out-of-bounds array write in Xpdf 4.05 due to incorrect bounds check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4141</link><description>Out-of-bounds array write in Xpdf 4.05 and earlier, triggered by an invalid character code in a Type 1 font. The root problem was a bounds check that was being optimized away by modern compilers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4123 | Tenda W15E SetPortMapping formSetPortMapping stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4123</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected by this issue is the function formSetPortMapping of the file /goform/SetPortMapping. The manipulation of the argument portMappingServer/portMappingProtocol/portMappingWan/porMappingtInternal/portMappingExternal leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261866 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4124 | Tenda W15E SetRemoteWebManage formSetRemoteWebManage stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4124</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. This affects the function formSetRemoteWebManage of the file /goform/SetRemoteWebManage. The manipulation of the argument remoteIP leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261867. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20353 | A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20353</link><description>A vulnerability in the management and VPN web servers for Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause the device to reload unexpectedly, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to incomplete error checking when parsing an HTTP header. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted HTTP request to a targeted web server on a device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause a DoS condition when the device reloads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20359 | A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20359</link><description>A vulnerability in a legacy capability that allowed for the preloading of VPN clients and plug-ins and that has been available in Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) Software and Cisco Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code with root-level privileges. Administrator-level privileges are required to exploit this vulnerability.
&#13; This vulnerability is due to improper validation of a file when it is read from system flash memory. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by copying a crafted file to the disk0: file system of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the affected device after the next reload of the device, which could alter system behavior. Because the injected code could persist across device reboots, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:30:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4121 | Tenda W15E formQOSRuleDel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4121</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected is the function formQOSRuleDel. The manipulation of the argument qosIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261864. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4122 | Tenda W15E setDebugCfg formSetDebugCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4122</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetDebugCfg of the file /goform/setDebugCfg. The manipulation of the argument enable/level/module leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261865 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4120 | Tenda W15E modifyIpMacBind formIPMacBindModify stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4120</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formIPMacBindModify of the file /goform/modifyIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindRuleId/IPMacBindRuleIp/IPMacBindRuleMac/IPMacBindRuleRemark leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261863. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0151 | Insufficient argument checking in Secure state Entry functions in software using Cortex-M Security Extensions (CMSE), that has been compiled...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0151</link><description>Insufficient argument checking in Secure state Entry functions in software using Cortex-M Security Extensions (CMSE), that has been compiled using toolchains that implement 'Arm v8-M Security Extensions Requirements on Development Tools' prior to version 1.4, allows an attacker to pass values to Secure state that are out of range for types smaller than 32-bits. Out of range values might lead to incorrect operations in secure state due.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4119 | Tenda W15E delIpMacBind formIPMacBindDel stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4119</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formIPMacBindDel of the file /goform/delIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261862 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51477 | WordPress BuddyBoss Theme theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.60 - Unauth. Arbitrary WordPress Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51477</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in BUDDYBOSS DMCC BuddyBoss Theme allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects BuddyBoss Theme: from n/a through 2.4.60.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23228 | This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Locked Notes content may have b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23228</link><description>This issue was addressed through improved state management. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3. Locked Notes content may have been unexpectedly unlocked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23271 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, Safari 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23271</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, Safari 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, watchOS 10.3. A malicious website may cause unexpected cross-origin behavior.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27791 | The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, iOS 16.7.5 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27791</link><description>The issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, tvOS 17.3, macOS Ventura 13.6.4, iOS 16.7.5 and iPadOS 16.7.5, macOS Monterey 12.7.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3. An app may be able to corrupt coprocessor memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51472 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.7 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51472</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3371 | Insufficient validation of external input in Compass may enable MITM attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3371</link><description>MongoDB Compass may accept and use insufficiently validated input from an untrusted external source. This may cause unintended application behavior, including data disclosure and enabling attackers to impersonate users. This issue affects MongoDB Compass versions 1.35.0 to 1.40.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51471 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.7 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Options Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51471</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4118 | Tenda W15E addIpMacBind formIPMacBindAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4118</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formIPMacBindAdd of the file /goform/addIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument IPMacBindRule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261861 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51425 | WordPress Rencontre plugin &amp;lt;= 3.10.1 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51425</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Jacques Malgrange Rencontre – Dating Site allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Rencontre – Dating Site: from n/a through 3.10.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47774 | WordPress Jetpack plugin &amp;lt; 12.7 - Auth. Iframe Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47774</link><description>Improper Restriction of Rendered UI Layers or Frames vulnerability in Automattic Jetpack allows Clickjacking.This issue affects Jetpack: from n/a before 12.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48763 | WordPress JetFormBuilder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48763</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS vulnerability in Crocoblock JetFormBuilder allows Code Injection.This issue affects JetFormBuilder: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51405 | WordPress BookingPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.74 - Booking Price Manipulation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51405</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Repute Infosystems BookingPress allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects BookingPress: from n/a through 1.0.74.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4116 | Tenda W15E DelDhcpRule formDelDhcpRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4116</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formDelDhcpRule of the file /goform/DelDhcpRule. The manipulation of the argument delDhcpIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261859. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4117 | Tenda W15E DelPortMapping formDelPortMapping stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4117</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formDelPortMapping of the file /goform/DelPortMapping. The manipulation of the argument portMappingIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261860. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31090 | WordPress Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.60 - Unrestricted Zip Extraction vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31090</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Unlimited Elements Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates) allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Unlimited Elements For Elementor (Free Widgets, Addons, Templates): from n/a through 1.5.60.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32127 | WordPress Multi Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.6 - Unauth Arbitrary rating value change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32127</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Daniel Powney Multi Rating allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects Multi Rating: from n/a through 5.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47504 | WordPress Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.16.4 - Auth. Arbitrary Attachment Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47504</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Elementor Elementor Website Builder allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Elementor Website Builder: from n/a through 3.16.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25790 | WordPress WoodMart theme &amp;lt;= 7.0.4 - Unauth Arbitrary Shortcodes Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25790</link><description>Improper Authentication, Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in xtemos WoodMart allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects WoodMart: from n/a through 7.0.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32078 | WordPress FV Player plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.44.7212 - Unvalidated Redirects and Forwards vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32078</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Foliovision FV Flowplayer Video Player.This issue affects FV Flowplayer Video Player: from n/a through 7.5.44.7212.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32432 | WordPress Ovic Addon Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32432</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ovic Team Ovic Addon Toolkit.This issue affects Ovic Addon Toolkit: from n/a through 2.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4115 | Tenda W15E AddDnsForward formAddDnsForward stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4115</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda W15E 15.11.0.14. Affected is the function formAddDnsForward of the file /goform/AddDnsForward. The manipulation of the argument DnsForwardRule leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261858 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32675 | WordPress Order Limit for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32675</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xfinity Soft Order Limit for WooCommerce.This issue affects Order Limit for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32677 | WordPress LoginPress Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Unauth. License Activation/Deactivation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32677</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LoginPress LoginPress Pro.This issue affects LoginPress Pro: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32678 | WordPress TrackShip for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32678</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in TrackShip TrackShip for WooCommerce.This issue affects TrackShip for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32699 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Compare plugin &amp;lt;= 2.37.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32699</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Compare.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Compare: from n/a through 2.37.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32728 | WordPress Paid Membership Subscriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 2.11.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32728</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cozmoslabs Paid Member Subscriptions.This issue affects Paid Member Subscriptions: from n/a through 2.11.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32773 | WordPress Royal Elementor Kit theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.116 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32773</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Royal Royal Elementor Kit.This issue affects Royal Elementor Kit: from n/a through 1.0.116.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4113 | Tenda TX9 SetSysTimeCfg sub_42D4DC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4113</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This vulnerability affects the function sub_42D4DC of the file /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261856. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4114 | Tenda TX9 PowerSaveSet sub_42C014 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4114</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This issue affects the function sub_42C014 of the file /goform/PowerSaveSet. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-261857 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32793 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32793</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro: from n/a through 2.12.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32794 | WordPress Paid Memberships Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.10 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32794</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Paid Memberships Pro.This issue affects Paid Memberships Pro: from n/a through 2.12.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32795 | WordPress WPCal.io  &amp;lt;= 0.9.5.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32795</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Revmakx WPCal.Io – Easy Meeting Scheduler.This issue affects WPCal.Io – Easy Meeting Scheduler: from n/a through 0.9.5.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32806 | WordPress Headline Analyzer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32806</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CoSchedule Headline Analyzer.This issue affects Headline Analyzer: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32872 | Umbraco Workflow&amp;#x27;s Backoffice users can execute arbitrary SQL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32872</link><description>Umbraco workflow provides workflows for the Umbraco content management system. Prior to versions 10.3.9, 12.2.6, and 13.0.6, an Umbraco Backoffice user can modify requests to a particular API endpoint to include SQL, which will be executed by the server. Umbraco Workflow versions 10.3.9, 12.2.6, 13.0.6, as well as Umbraco Plumber version 10.1.2, contain a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32947 | WordPress WP ADA Compliance Check Basic plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32947</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AlumniOnline Web Services LLC WP ADA Compliance Check Basic.This issue affects WP ADA Compliance Check Basic: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32958 | WordPress Slash Admin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.1 - CSRF to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32958</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Giorgos Sarigiannidis Slash Admin allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Slash Admin: from n/a through 3.8.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23989 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9.2 - Content Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23989</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25785 | WordPress WP Post Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Vote Manipulation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25785</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Shoaib Saleem WP Post Rating allows Functionality Misuse.This issue affects WP Post Rating: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4112 | Tenda TX9 SetVirtualServerCfg sub_42CB94 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4112</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. This affects the function sub_42CB94 of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261855. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4111 | Tenda TX9 SetLEDCfg sub_42BD7C stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4111</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 22.03.02.10. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_42BD7C of the file /goform/SetLEDCfg. The manipulation of the argument time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261854 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28825 | Brute-force protection ineffective for some login methods</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28825</link><description>Improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts on some authentication methods in Checkmk before 2.3.0b5 (beta), 2.2.0p26, 2.1.0p43, and in Checkmk 2.0.0 (EOL) facilitates password brute-forcing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23985 | WordPress Quiz Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.9.4 - Content Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23985</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Quiz Maker team Quiz Maker.This issue affects Quiz Maker: from n/a through 6.3.9.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23976 | WordPress RegistrationMagic plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.9.2 - Arbitrary Price Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23976</link><description>Incorrect Default Permissions vulnerability in Metagauss RegistrationMagic allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects RegistrationMagic: from n/a through 5.1.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:02:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45852 | WordPress WP-FormAssembly plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Auth. Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45852</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in FormAssembly / Drew Buschhorn WP-FormAssembly allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WP-FormAssembly: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32954 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32954</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Tribulant Newsletters.This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32772 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.9 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32772</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32785 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32785</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor addons allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.8.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32789 | WordPress Seers plugin &amp;lt;= 8.0.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32789</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Seers allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects Seers: from n/a through 8.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32702 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Repute info systems ARForms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32707 | WordPress Image Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.125 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32707</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GhozyLab Image Slider Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Image Slider Widget: from n/a through 1.1.125.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32711 | WordPress myCred plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32711</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in myCred allows Stored XSS.This issue affects myCred: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32808 | WordPress ProfileGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.9 - Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32808</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Metagauss ProfileGrid.This issue affects ProfileGrid : from n/a through 5.7.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32823 | WordPress Rate My Post plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32823</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in FeedbackWP Rate my Post – WP Rating System.This issue affects Rate my Post – WP Rating System: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32721 | WordPress Jeg Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32721</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jegtheme Jeg Elementor Kit allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Jeg Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32722 | WordPress Coupon &amp;amp; Discount Code Reveal Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32722</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Coupon &amp; Discount Code Reveal Button allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Coupon &amp; Discount Code Reveal Button: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32723 | WordPress Advanced Floating Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32723</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Code Tides Advanced Floating Content allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Floating Content: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32791 | WordPress Premium Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 4.10.25 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32791</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 4.10.25.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32801 | WordPress Widget Post Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32801</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ShapedPlugin Widget Post Slider allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Widget Post Slider: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32815 | WordPress All-in-one Like Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32815</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeroen Peters All-in-one Like Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects All-in-one Like Widget: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32833 | WordPress List Custom Taxonomy Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32833</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Nick Halsey List Custom Taxonomy Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects List Custom Taxonomy Widget: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:43:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32834 | WordPress WooCommerce Shipping Label plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebToffee WooCommerce Shipping Label allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WooCommerce Shipping Label: from n/a through 2.3.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32950 | WordPress WP Media Category Management plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DeBAAT WP Media Category Management allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Media Category Management: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32952 | WordPress Max Addons Pro for Bricks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32952</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BloomPixel Max Addons Pro for Bricks allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Max Addons Pro for Bricks: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32956 | WordPress RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32956</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rometheme RomethemeKit For Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects RomethemeKit For Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32706 | WordPress ARForms plugin &amp;lt;= 6.4 - Auth. SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32706</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Repute info systems ARForms.This issue affects ARForms: from n/a through 6.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28976 | Dell Repository Manager, versions prior to 3.4.5, contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in API module. A local attacker with low privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28976</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, versions prior to 3.4.5, contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in API module. A local attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized write access to the files stored on the server filesystem with the privileges of the running web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28977 | Dell Repository Manager, versions 3.4.2 through 3.4.4,contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in logger module. A local attacker with low pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28977</link><description>Dell Repository Manager, versions 3.4.2 through 3.4.4,contains a Path Traversal vulnerability in logger module. A local attacker with low privileges could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unauthorized read access to the files stored on the server filesystem with the privileges of the running web application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32709 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32709</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Plechev Andrey WP-Recall.This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32710 | WordPress WP-Recall plugin &amp;lt;= 16.26.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32710</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Plechev Andrey WP-Recall.This issue affects WP-Recall: from n/a through 16.26.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32716 | WordPress StreamWeasels Twitch Integration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - API Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32716</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in StreamWeasels StreamWeasels Twitch Integration.This issue affects StreamWeasels Twitch Integration: from n/a through 1.7.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32726 | WordPress Frontend Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure on PII vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32726</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in vinoth06. Frontend Dashboard.This issue affects Frontend Dashboard: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28963 | Telemetry Dashboard v1.0.0.7 for Dell ThinOS 2402 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated user with lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28963</link><description>Telemetry Dashboard v1.0.0.7 for Dell ThinOS 2402 contains a sensitive information disclosure vulnerability. An unauthenticated user with local access to the device could exploit this vulnerability to read sensitive proxy settings information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32780 | WordPress VikRentCar Car Rental Management System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Invoices vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32780</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in E4J s.R.L. VikRentCar.This issue affects VikRentCar: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32781 | WordPress Email Customizer for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32781</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in ThemeHigh Email Customizer for WooCommerce.This issue affects Email Customizer for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32782 | WordPress HT Mega plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.7 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32782</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in HasThemes HT Mega.This issue affects HT Mega: from n/a through 2.4.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32788 | WordPress FG Joomla to Wordpress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.20.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32788</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Frédéric GILLES FG Joomla to WordPress.This issue affects FG Joomla to WordPress: from n/a through 4.20.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32796 | WordPress WP Fusion Lite  &amp;lt;= 3.42.10 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32796</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Very Good Plugins WP Fusion Lite.This issue affects WP Fusion Lite: from n/a through 3.42.10.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:57:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32816 | WordPress Combo Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.78 - Sensitive Data Exposure via API vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32816</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in PickPlugins Post Grid.This issue affects Post Grid: from n/a through 2.2.78.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32825 | WordPress Simply Static plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Log File vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32825</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Patrick Posner Simply Static.This issue affects Simply Static: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32953 | WordPress Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.5 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32953</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in Newsletters.This issue affects Newsletters: from n/a through 4.9.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32817 | WordPress Import and export users and customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.26.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32817</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Import and export users and customers.This issue affects Import and export users and customers: from n/a through 1.26.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32835 | WordPress Export and Import Users and Customers plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32835</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WebToffee Import Export WordPress Users.This issue affects Import Export WordPress Users: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32718 | WordPress The Pack Elementor addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8.2 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32718</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Webangon The Pack Elementor.This issue affects The Pack Elementor addons: from n/a through 2.0.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32836 | WordPress WP-Lister Lite for eBay plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.11 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32836</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in WP Lab WP-Lister Lite for eBay.This issue affects WP-Lister Lite for eBay: from n/a through 3.5.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32775 | WordPress Embed Google Photos album plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32775</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Pavex Embed Google Photos album.This issue affects Embed Google Photos album: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32803 | WordPress SuperFaktura WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.40.3 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32803</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in 2day.Sk, Webikon SuperFaktura WooCommerce.This issue affects SuperFaktura WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.40.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32812 | WordPress Podlove Podcast Publisher plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.11 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32812</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Podlove Podlove Podcast Publisher.This issue affects Podlove Podcast Publisher: from n/a through 4.0.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:27:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32819 | WordPress Culqi plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.14 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32819</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Culqi.This issue affects Culqi: from n/a through 3.0.14.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32948 | WordPress ARMember – Membership Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.28 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32948</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Repute Infosystems ARMember.This issue affects ARMember: from n/a through 4.0.28.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32955 | WordPress FV Flowplayer Video Player plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.43.7212 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32955</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Foliovision FV Flowplayer Video Player.This issue affects FV Flowplayer Video Player: from n/a through 7.5.43.7212.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32951 | WordPress Max Addons Pro for Bricks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Reset vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32951</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BloomPixel Max Addons Pro for Bricks.This issue affects Max Addons Pro for Bricks: from n/a through 1.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31406 | Active debug code vulnerability exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31406</link><description>Active debug code vulnerability exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the device may perform unauthorized operations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32051 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32051</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in RoamWiFi R10 prior to 4.8.45. If this vulnerability is exploited, a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker with access to the device may obtain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33531 | cdbattags lua-resty-jwt 0.2.3 allows attackers to bypass all JWT-parsing signature checks by crafting a JWT with an enc header with the valu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33531</link><description>cdbattags lua-resty-jwt 0.2.3 allows attackers to bypass all JWT-parsing signature checks by crafting a JWT with an enc header with the value A256GCM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7253 | Import WP &amp;lt; 2.13.1 - Admin+ Server-side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7253</link><description>The Import WP  WordPress plugin before 2.13.1 does not prevent users with the administrator role from pinging conducting SSRF attacks, which may be a problem in multisite configurations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1743 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 29.8 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1743</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 29.8 does not sanitise and escape various parameters before outputting them back in pages and attributes, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1756 | WooCommerce Customers Manager &amp;lt; 29.8 - Subscriber+ Email Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1756</link><description>The WooCommerce Customers Manager WordPress plugin before 29.8 does not have authorisation and CSRF in an AJAX action, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber, to call it and retrieve the list of customer email addresses along with their id, first name and last name</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2402 | Better Comments &amp;lt; 1.5.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2402</link><description>The Better Comments WordPress plugin before 1.5.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2404 | Better Comments &amp;lt; 1.5.6 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2404</link><description>The Better Comments WordPress plugin before 1.5.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow low privilege users such as Subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2972 | Floating Chat Widget &amp;lt; 3.1.9 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2972</link><description>The Floating Chat Widget: Contact Chat Icons, WhatsApp, Telegram Chat, Line Messenger, WeChat, Email, SMS, Call Button  WordPress plugin before 3.1.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3261 | Strong Testimonials &amp;lt; 3.1.12 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3261</link><description>The Strong Testimonials WordPress plugin before 3.1.12 does not validate and escape some of its Testimonial fields before outputting them back in a page/post, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks. The attack requires a specific view to be performed</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28613 | SQL Injection vulnerability in PHP Task Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28613</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in PHP Task Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the task_id parameter of the task-details.php, and edit-task.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 03:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4093 | SourceCodester Simple Subscription Website view_application.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4093</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Subscription Website 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file view_application.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261822 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 01:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>