<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:12:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-5053 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.1.18 -  Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Mailchimp Integration Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5053</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized Malichimp API key update due to an insufficient capability check on the verifyRequest function in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.18. This makes it possible for Form Managers with a Subscriber-level access and above to modify the Mailchimp API key used for integration. At the same time, missing Mailchimp API key validation allows the redirect of the integration requests to the attacker-controlled server.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 11:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8368 | code-projects Hospital Management System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8368</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8367 | HM Courts &amp;amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office Markdown NotificationService.java injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8367</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HM Courts &amp; Tribunals Service Probate Back Office up to c1afe0cdb2b2766d9e24872c4e827f8b82a6cd31. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/uk/gov/hmcts/probate/service/NotificationService.java of the component Markdown Handler. The manipulation leads to injection. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The patch is identified as d90230d7cf575e5b0852d56660104c8bd2503c34. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 04:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8366 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System Update My Profile Page index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /index.php?id=userProfileEdit of the component Update My Profile Page. The manipulation of the argument fname/lname/email with the input  leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 18:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44946 | kcm: Serialise kcm_sendmsg() for the same socket.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44946</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

kcm: Serialise kcm_sendmsg() for the same socket.

syzkaller reported UAF in kcm_release(). [0]

The scenario is

  1. Thread A builds a skb with MSG_MORE and sets kcm-&gt;seq_skb.

  2. Thread A resumes building skb from kcm-&gt;seq_skb but is blocked
     by sk_stream_wait_memory()

  3. Thread B calls sendmsg() concurrently, finishes building kcm-&gt;seq_skb
     and puts the skb to the write queue

  4. Thread A faces an error and finally frees skb that is already in the
     write queue

  5. kcm_release() does double-free the skb in the write queue

When a thread is building a MSG_MORE skb, another thread must not touch it.

Let's add a per-sk mutex and serialise kcm_sendmsg().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_unlink include/linux/skbuff.h:2366 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_dequeue include/linux/skbuff.h:2385 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_queue_purge_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:3175 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in __skb_queue_purge include/linux/skbuff.h:3181 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in kcm_release+0x170/0x4c8 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:1691
Read of size 8 at addr ffff0000ced0fc80 by task syz-executor329/6167

CPU: 1 PID: 6167 Comm: syz-executor329 Tainted: G    B              6.8.0-rc5-syzkaller-g9abbc24128bc #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
Call trace:
 dump_backtrace+0x1b8/0x1e4 arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:291
 show_stack+0x2c/0x3c arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:298
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:88 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0xd0/0x124 lib/dump_stack.c:106
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:377 [inline]
 print_report+0x178/0x518 mm/kasan/report.c:488
 kasan_report+0xd8/0x138 mm/kasan/report.c:601
 __asan_report_load8_noabort+0x20/0x2c mm/kasan/report_generic.c:381
 __skb_unlink include/linux/skbuff.h:2366 [inline]
 __skb_dequeue include/linux/skbuff.h:2385 [inline]
 __skb_queue_purge_reason include/linux/skbuff.h:3175 [inline]
 __skb_queue_purge include/linux/skbuff.h:3181 [inline]
 kcm_release+0x170/0x4c8 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:1691
 __sock_release net/socket.c:659 [inline]
 sock_close+0xa4/0x1e8 net/socket.c:1421
 __fput+0x30c/0x738 fs/file_table.c:376
 ____fput+0x20/0x30 fs/file_table.c:404
 task_work_run+0x230/0x2e0 kernel/task_work.c:180
 exit_task_work include/linux/task_work.h:38 [inline]
 do_exit+0x618/0x1f64 kernel/exit.c:871
 do_group_exit+0x194/0x22c kernel/exit.c:1020
 get_signal+0x1500/0x15ec kernel/signal.c:2893
 do_signal+0x23c/0x3b44 arch/arm64/kernel/signal.c:1249
 do_notify_resume+0x74/0x1f4 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:148
 exit_to_user_mode_prepare arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:169 [inline]
 exit_to_user_mode arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:178 [inline]
 el0_svc+0xac/0x168 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:713
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x84/0xfc arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:730
 el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:598

Allocated by task 6166:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x40/0x78 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_alloc_info+0x70/0x84 mm/kasan/generic.c:626
 unpoison_slab_object mm/kasan/common.c:314 [inline]
 __kasan_slab_alloc+0x74/0x8c mm/kasan/common.c:340
 kasan_slab_alloc include/linux/kasan.h:201 [inline]
 slab_post_alloc_hook mm/slub.c:3813 [inline]
 slab_alloc_node mm/slub.c:3860 [inline]
 kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x204/0x4c0 mm/slub.c:3903
 __alloc_skb+0x19c/0x3d8 net/core/skbuff.c:641
 alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:1296 [inline]
 kcm_sendmsg+0x1d3c/0x2124 net/kcm/kcmsock.c:783
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:745 [inline]
 sock_sendmsg+0x220/0x2c0 net/socket.c:768
 splice_to_socket+0x7cc/0xd58 fs/splice.c:889
 do_splice_from fs/splice.c:941 [inline]
 direct_splice_actor+0xec/0x1d8 fs/splice.c:1164
 splice_direct_to_actor+0x438/0xa0c fs/splice.c:1108
 do_splice_direct_actor 
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 13:29:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4539 | Web Application Firewall &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4539</link><description>The Web Application Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 09:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4100 | WP Cerber Security &amp;lt;= 9.4 - IP Protection Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4100</link><description>The WP Cerber Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Protection bypass in versions up to, and including 9.4 due to the plugin improperly checking for a visitor's IP address. This makes it possible for an attacker whose IP address has been blocked to bypass this control by setting the X-Forwarded-For: HTTP header to an IP Address that hasn't been blocked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4536 | IP Vault – WP Firewall &amp;lt;= 1.1 - IP Address Spoofing to Protection Mechanism Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4536</link><description>The IP Vault – WP Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Address Spoofing in versions up to, and including, 1.1. This is due to insufficient restrictions on where the IP Address information is being retrieved for request logging and login restrictions. Attackers can supply the X-Forwarded-For header with with a different IP Address that will be logged and can be used to bypass settings that may have blocked out an IP address or country from logging in.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7717 | WP Events Manager &amp;lt;= 2.1.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7717</link><description>The WP Events Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘order’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8108 | Share This Image &amp;lt;= 2.01 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via alignment Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8108</link><description>The Share This Image plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'alignment' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.01 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0109 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause a crash by passing in a malformed ELF file. A suc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0109</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause a crash by passing in a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may cause an out of bounds read in the unprivileged process memory which could lead to a limited denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0110 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause an out-of-bound write by passing in a malformed E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0110</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command `cuobjdump` where a user may cause an out-of-bound write by passing in a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to code execution or denial of service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0111 | NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command 'cuobjdump' where a user may cause a crash or produce incorrect output by passing a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0111</link><description>NVIDIA CUDA Toolkit contains a vulnerability in command 'cuobjdump' where a user may cause a crash or produce incorrect output by passing a malformed ELF file. A successful exploit of this vulnerability may lead to a limited denial of service or data tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39579 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39579</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.0 contains an incorrect privilege assignment vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain root-level access.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8276 | WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via align Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8276</link><description>The WPZOOM Portfolio Lite – Filterable Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘align’ attribute within the 'wp:wpzoom-blocks' Gutenberg block in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39578 | Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39578</link><description>Dell PowerScale OneFS versions 8.2.2.x through 9.8.0.1 contains a UNIX symbolic link (symlink) following vulnerability. A local high privileged attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to denial of service, information tampering.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 07:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44945 | netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44945</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nfnetlink: Initialise extack before use in ACKs

Add missing extack initialisation when ACKing BATCH_BEGIN and BATCH_END.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 06:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3886 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3886</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_check_envato_code function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5212 | tagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via envato_code[]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5212</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘envato_code[]’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping within the on_ajax_register_forum_user function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 04:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7435 | Attire &amp;lt;= 2.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7435</link><description>The Attire theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.6 via deserialization of untrusted input. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:50:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39747 | IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39747</link><description>IBM Sterling Connect:Direct Web Services 6.0, 6.1, 6.2, and 6.3 uses default credentials for potentially critical functionality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 02:19:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8006 | NULL pointer dereference in libpcap before 1.10.5 with remote packet capture support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8006</link><description>Remote packet capture support is disabled by default in libpcap.  When a user builds libpcap with remote packet capture support enabled, one of the functions that become available is pcap_findalldevs_ex().  One of the function arguments can be a filesystem path, which normally means a directory with input data files.  When the specified path cannot be used as a directory, the function receives NULL from opendir(), but does not check the return value and passes the NULL value to readdir(), which causes a NULL pointer derefence.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 01:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45304 | OwnableTwoStep allows a pending owner to accept ownership after the original owner has renounced ownership in cairo-contracts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45304</link><description>Cairo-Contracts are OpenZeppelin Contracts written in Cairo for Starknet, a decentralized ZK Rollup. This vulnerability can lead to unauthorized ownership transfer, contrary to the original owner's intention of leaving the contract without an owner. It introduces a security risk where an unintended party (pending owner) can gain control of the contract after the original owner has renounced ownership. This could also be used by a malicious owner to simulate leaving a contract without an owner, to later regain ownership by previously having proposed himself as a pending owner. This issue has been addressed in release version 0.16.0. All users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7256 | Double-free in libpcap before 1.10.5 with remote packet capture support.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7256</link><description>In affected libpcap versions during the setup of a remote packet capture the internal function sock_initaddress() calls getaddrinfo() and possibly freeaddrinfo(), but does not clearly indicate to the caller function whether freeaddrinfo() still remains to be called after the function returns.  This makes it possible in some scenarios that both the function and its caller call freeaddrinfo() for the same allocated memory block.  A similar problem was reported in Apple libpcap, to which Apple assigned CVE-2023-40400.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 23:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6586 | Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows users with the necessary permissions, such as Administrator or Editor, to create and share dashboards. A d...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6586</link><description>Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows users with the necessary permissions, such as Administrator or Editor, to create and share dashboards. A dashboard that contains HTML elements which point to a threat actor controlled source can trigger an SSRF request when exported, via a POST request to /api/v1/dashboards//export. The forged request contains the value of the exporting user’s session token. A threat actor could obtain the session token of any user who exports the dashboard. The obtained session token can be used to perform actions as the victim on the application, resulting in session takeover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 22:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6585 | Multiple stored cross-site scripting (“XSS”) vulnerabilities in the markdown dashboard and dashboard comment functionality of Lightdash vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6585</link><description>Multiple stored cross-site scripting (“XSS”) vulnerabilities in the markdown dashboard and dashboard comment functionality of Lightdash version 0.1024.6 allows remote authenticated threat actors to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable web pages. A threat actor could potentially exploit this vulnerability to store malicious JavaScript which executes in the context of a user’s session with the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 22:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44682 | ShopXO 6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the backend that allows attackers to execute code by changing POST parameters.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44682</link><description>ShopXO 6.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the backend that allows attackers to execute code by changing POST parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:55:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44684 | TpMeCMS 1.3.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /h.php/page?ref=addtabs via the "Title," "Images," and "Content" fields.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44684</link><description>TpMeCMS 1.3.3.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in /h.php/page?ref=addtabs via the "Title," "Images," and "Content" fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:55:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44683 | Seacms v13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via admin-video.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44683</link><description>Seacms v13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) via admin-video.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8347 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Master.php delete_record sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8347</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_record of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_record. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8348 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System Master.php delete_category sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8348</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function delete_category of the file /classes/Master.php?f=delete_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:45:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8285 | Kroxylicious: missing upstream kafka tls hostname verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8285</link><description>A flaw was found in Kroxylicious. When establishing the connection with the upstream Kafka server using a TLS secured connection, Kroxylicious fails to properly verify the server's hostname, resulting in an insecure connection. For a successful attack to be performed, the attacker needs to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack or compromise any external systems, such as DNS or network routing configuration. This issue is considered a high complexity attack, with additional high privileges required, as the attack would need access to the Kroxylicious configuration or a peer system. The result of a successful attack impacts both data integrity and confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8346 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System SystemSettings.php update_settings_info sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8346</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected is the function update_settings_info of the file /classes/SystemSettings.php?f=update_settings. The manipulation of the argument name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38868 | Incorrect Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38868</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Endpoint Central affected by Incorrect authorization vulnerability while isolating the devices.This issue affects Endpoint Central: before 11.3.2406.08 and before 11.3.2400.15</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:54:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21658 | Insufficient control of region value length in discourse-calendar</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21658</link><description>discourse-calendar is a discourse plugin which adds the ability to create a dynamic calendar in the first post of a topic. The limit on region value length is too generous. This allows a malicious actor to cause a Discourse instance to use excessive bandwidth and disk space. This issue has been patched in main the main branch. There are no workarounds for this vulnerability. Please upgrade as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6204 | SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6204</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions before 5715 are vulnerable to SQL Injection in the reports module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45047 | Potential mXSS vulnerability due to improper HTML escaping in svelte</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45047</link><description>svelte performance oriented web framework. A potential mXSS vulnerability exists in Svelte for versions up to but not including 4.2.19. Svelte improperly escapes HTML on server-side rendering. The assumption is that attributes will always stay as such, but in some situation the final DOM tree rendered on browsers is different from what Svelte expects on server-side rendering. This may be leveraged to perform XSS attacks, and a type of the XSS is known as mXSS (mutation XSS). More specifically, this can occur when injecting malicious content into an attribute within a `noscript` tag. This issue has been addressed in release version 4.2.19. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8345 | SourceCodester Music Gallery Site Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8345</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /classes/Users.php?f=delete. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 17:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8344 | Campcodes Supplier Management System edit_area.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8344</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Supplier Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit_area.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44918 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_datarelate.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44918</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component admin_datarelate.php of SeaCMS v12.9 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8235 | Libvirt: crash of virtinterfaced via virconnectlistinterfaces()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8235</link><description>A flaw was found in libvirt. A refactor of the code fetching the list of interfaces for multiple APIs introduced a corner case on platforms where allocating 0 bytes of memory results in a NULL pointer. This corner case would lead to a NULL-pointer dereference and subsequent crash of virtinterfaced. This issue could allow clients connecting to the read-only socket to crash the virtinterfaced daemon.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44916 | Vulnerability in admin_ip.php in Seacms v13.1, when action=set, allows attackers to control IP parameters that are written to the data/admin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44916</link><description>Vulnerability in admin_ip.php in Seacms v13.1, when action=set, allows attackers to control IP parameters that are written to the data/admin/ip.php file and could result in arbitrary command execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8343 | SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System User Registration Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8343</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Sentiment Based Movie Rating System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save_client of the component User Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8342 | SourceCodester Petshop Management System add_client.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8342</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Petshop Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/add_client.php. The manipulation of the argument image_profile leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8340 | SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System Actions.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8340</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Actions.php?a=login. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8341 | SourceCodester Petshop Management System add_user.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8341</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Petshop Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /controllers/add_user.php. The manipulation of the argument avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8338 | HFO4 shudong-share File Extension fileReceive.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HFO4 shudong-share 2.4.7. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /includes/fileReceive.php of the component File Extension Handler. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8339 | SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System Connection Code ?page=tracks sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Electric Billing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /?page=tracks of the component Connection Code Handler. The manipulation of the argument code leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:44:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8336 | SourceCodester Music Gallery Site Master.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Music Gallery Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /php-music/classes/Master.php?f=delete_music. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8337 | SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Contact Manager with Export to VCF 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file index.html. The manipulation of the argument contact_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8334 | master-nan Sweet-CMS log.go LogHandler neutralization for logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in master-nan Sweet-CMS up to 5f441e022b8876f07cde709c77b5be6d2f262e3f. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function LogHandler of the file middleware/log.go. The manipulation leads to improper output neutralization for logs. The attack may be initiated remotely. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The identifier of the patch is 2024c370e6c78b07b358c9d4257fa5d1be732c38. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8335 | OpenRapid RapidCMS runlogon.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in OpenRapid RapidCMS up to 1.3.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /resource/runlogon.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8260 | OPA SMB Force-Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8260</link><description>A SMB force-authentication vulnerability exists in all versions of OPA for Windows prior to v0.68.0. The vulnerability exists because of improper input validation, allowing a user to pass an arbitrary SMB share instead of a Rego file as an argument to OPA CLI or to one of the OPA Go library’s functions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8332 | master-nan Sweet-CMS index sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in master-nan Sweet-CMS up to 5f441e022b8876f07cde709c77b5be6d2f262e3f. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /table/index. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The name of the patch is 146359646a5a90cb09156dbd0013b7df77f2aa6c. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:42:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8331 | OpenRapid RapidCMS user-move-run.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in OpenRapid RapidCMS up to 1.3.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/user/user-move-run.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:20:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48944 | sched: Fix yet more sched_fork() races</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48944</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sched: Fix yet more sched_fork() races

Where commit 4ef0c5c6b5ba ("kernel/sched: Fix sched_fork() access an
invalid sched_task_group") fixed a fork race vs cgroup, it opened up a
race vs syscalls by not placing the task on the runqueue before it
gets exposed through the pidhash.

Commit 13765de8148f ("sched/fair: Fix fault in reweight_entity") is
trying to fix a single instance of this, instead fix the whole class
of issues, effectively reverting this commit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7122 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7122</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7858 | Media Library Folders &amp;lt;= 8.2.3 - Missing Authorization on Various Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7858</link><description>The Media Library Folders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several AJAX functions in the media-library-plus.php file in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to perform several actions related to managing media files and folder along with controlling settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8252 | Clean Login &amp;lt;= 1.14.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8252</link><description>The Clean Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.14.5 via the 'template' attribute of the clean-login-register shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8274 | WP Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8274</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via several parameters from 'timeline_obj' in all versions up to, and including, 10.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 09:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44944 | netfilter: ctnetlink: use helper function to calculate expect ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44944</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: ctnetlink: use helper function to calculate expect ID

Delete expectation path is missing a call to the nf_expect_get_id()
helper function to calculate the expectation ID, otherwise LSB of the
expectation object address is leaked to userspace.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8319 | Tourfic &amp;lt;= 2.11.20 - Cross-Site Request Forgery in Multiple Functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8319</link><description>The Tourfic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.20. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the tf_order_status_email_resend_function,  tf_visitor_details_edit_function, tf_checkinout_details_edit_function, tf_order_status_edit_function, tf_order_bulk_action_edit_function, tf_remove_room_order_ids, and tf_delete_old_review_fields functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to resend order status emails, update visitor/order details, edit check-in/out details, edit order status, perform bulk order status updates, remove room order IDs, and delete old review fields, respectively, via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8016 | The Events Calendar Pro &amp;lt;= 7.0.2 - Authenticated (Administrator+) PHP Object Injection to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8016</link><description>The Events Calendar Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.2 via deserialization of untrusted input from the 'filters' parameter in widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. The additional presence of a POP chain allows attackers to execute code remotely. In certain configurations, this can be exploitable by lower level users. We confirmed that this plugin installed with Elementor makes it possible for users with contributor-level access and above to exploit this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34577 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WRC-X3000GS2-B, WRC-X3000GS2-W, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B due to improper processing of input values ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34577</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WRC-X3000GS2-B, WRC-X3000GS2-W, and WRC-X3000GS2A-B due to improper processing of input values in easysetup.cgi. If a user views a malicious web page while logged in to the product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39300 | Missing authentication vulnerability exists in Telnet function of WAB-I1750-PS v1.5.10 and earlier. When Telnet function of the product is e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39300</link><description>Missing authentication vulnerability exists in Telnet function of WAB-I1750-PS v1.5.10 and earlier. When Telnet function of the product is enabled, a remote attacker may login to the product without authentication and alter the product's settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42412 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WAB-I1750-PS and WAB-S1167-PS due to improper processing of input values in menu.cgi. If a user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42412</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in WAB-I1750-PS and WAB-S1167-PS due to improper processing of input values in menu.cgi. If a user views a malicious web page while logged in to the product, an arbitrary script may be executed on the user's web browser.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3673 | Web Directory Free &amp;lt; 1.7.3 - Unauthenticated LFI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3673</link><description>The Web Directory Free WordPress plugin before 1.7.3 does not validate a parameter before using it in an include(), which could lead to Local File Inclusion issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2694 | Betheme &amp;lt;= 27.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2694</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 27.5.6 via deserialization of untrusted input of the 'mfn-page-items' post meta value. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3998 | Betheme | Responsive Multipurpose WordPress &amp;amp; WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 27.5.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3998</link><description>The Betheme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several of the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 27.5.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5879 | HubSpot – CRM, Email Marketing, Live Chat, Forms &amp;amp; Analytics &amp;lt;= 11.1.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HubSpot Meeting Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5879</link><description>The HubSpot – CRM, Email Marketing, Live Chat, Forms &amp; Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' attribute of the HubSpot Meeting Widget in all versions up to, and including, 11.1.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:38:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4401 | Elementor Addon Elements &amp;lt;= 1.13.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id and eae_slider_animation Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4401</link><description>The Elementor Addon Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ and 'eae_slider_animation' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.13.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5024 | MemberPress &amp;lt;= 1.11.29 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via mepr_screenname and mepr_key Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5024</link><description>The Memberpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'mepr_screenname' and 'mepr_key' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.29 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5061 | Enfold &amp;lt;= 6.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wrapper_class and class Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5061</link><description>The Enfold - Responsive Multi-Purpose Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wrapper_class’ and 'class' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5784 | Tutor LMS Pro &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5784</link><description>The Tutor LMS  Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized administrative actions execution due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions like treport_quiz_atttempt_delete and tutor_gc_class_action in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with the subscriber-level access and above, to preform an administrative actions on the site, like comments, posts or users deletion, viewing notifications, etc.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8330 | Gether Technology 6SHR System - Unrestricted File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8330</link><description>6SHR system from Gether Technology does not properly validate uploaded file types, allowing remote attackers with regular privileges to upload web shell scripts and use them to execute arbitrary system commands on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45490 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. xmlparse.c does not reject a negative length for XML_ParseBuffer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45490</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. xmlparse.c does not reject a negative length for XML_ParseBuffer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45491 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. dtdCopy in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for nDefaultAtts on 32-bit platforms (w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45491</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. dtdCopy in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for nDefaultAtts on 32-bit platforms (where UINT_MAX equals SIZE_MAX).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45492 | An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. nextScaffoldPart in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for m_groupSize on 32-bit plat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45492</link><description>An issue was discovered in libexpat before 2.6.3. nextScaffoldPart in xmlparse.c can have an integer overflow for m_groupSize on 32-bit platforms (where UINT_MAX equals SIZE_MAX).</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8327 | HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform - SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8327</link><description>Easy test

Online Learning and Testing Platform from HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8328 | HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8328</link><description>Easy test Online Learning and Testing Platform from HWA JIUH DIGITAL TECHNOLOGY does not properly validate a specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject arbitrary JavaScript code and perform Reflected Cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8329 | Gether Technology 6SHR System - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8329</link><description>6SHR system from Gether Technology does not properly validate the specific page parameter, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to inject SQL command to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45488 | One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Passwords before 7.5.2 allows unauthorized access because of an issue related to cookies. This only af...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45488</link><description>One Identity Safeguard for Privileged Passwords before 7.5.2 allows unauthorized access because of an issue related to cookies. This only affects virtual appliance installations (VMware or HyperV). The fixed versions are 7.0.5.1 LTS, 7.4.2, and 7.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8234 | ** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A command injection vulnerability in the functions formSysCmd(), formUpgradeCert(), and formDelcert() in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8234</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A command injection vulnerability in the functions formSysCmd(), formUpgradeCert(), and formDelcert() in the Zyxel NWA1100-N firmware version 1.00(AACE.1)C0 could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute some OS commands to access system files on an affected device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:46:54 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>