<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:58:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-31013 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in emlog version Pro 2.3, allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31013</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in emlog version Pro 2.3, allow remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the bottom of the homepage in footer_info parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:58:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31010 | SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in Banner.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31010</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ID parameter in Banner.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:58:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31009 | SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via lgid parameter in Banner.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31009</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in SEMCMS v.4.8, allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via lgid parameter in Banner.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2879 | The LayerSlider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ls_get_popup_markup action in versions 7.9.11 and 7.10.0 due to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2879</link><description>The LayerSlider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ls_get_popup_markup action in versions 7.9.11 and 7.10.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24724 | Gibbon through 26.0.00 allows /modules/School%20Admin/messengerSettings.php Server Side Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24724</link><description>Gibbon through 26.0.00 allows /modules/School%20Admin/messengerSettings.php Server Side Template Injection leading to Remote Code Execution because input is passed to the Twig template engine (messengerSettings.php) without sanitization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25864 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Friendica versions after v.2023.12, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25864</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Friendica versions after v.2023.12, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the fpostit.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26495 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Friendica versions after v.2023.12, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26495</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Friendica versions after v.2023.12, allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the BBCode tags in the post content and post comments function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 03:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1327 | The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's image box widget in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1327</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's image box widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28219 | In _imagingcms.c in Pillow before 10.3.0, a buffer overflow exists because strcpy is used instead of strncpy.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28219</link><description>In _imagingcms.c in Pillow before 10.3.0, a buffer overflow exists because strcpy is used instead of strncpy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3162 | The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Testimonial Widget Attributes in all version...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3162</link><description>The Jeg Elementor Kit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Testimonial Widget Attributes in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access or higher, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3227 | Panwei eoffice OA Backend save_image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Panwei eoffice OA up to 9.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /general/system/interface/theme_set/save_image.php of the component Backend. The manipulation of the argument image_type leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259072.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28836 | An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.x before 3.6.0. When negotiating the TLS version on the server side, it can fall back to the TLS 1.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28836</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.x before 3.6.0. When negotiating the TLS version on the server side, it can fall back to the TLS 1.2 implementation of the protocol if it is disabled. If the TLS 1.2 implementation was disabled at build time, a TLS 1.2 client could put a TLS 1.3-only server into an infinite loop processing a TLS 1.2 ClientHello, resulting in a denial of service. If the TLS 1.2 implementation was disabled at runtime, a TLS 1.2 client can successfully establish a TLS 1.2 connection with the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30166 | In Mbed TLS 3.3.0 through 3.5.2 before 3.6.0, a malicious client can cause information disclosure or a denial of service because of a stack ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30166</link><description>In Mbed TLS 3.3.0 through 3.5.2 before 3.6.0, a malicious client can cause information disclosure or a denial of service because of a stack buffer over-read (of less than 256 bytes) in a TLS 1.3 server via a TLS 3.1 ClientHello.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28755 | An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.x before 3.6.0. When an SSL context was reset with the mbedtls_ssl_session_reset() API, the maximum ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28755</link><description>An issue was discovered in Mbed TLS 3.5.x before 3.6.0. When an SSL context was reset with the mbedtls_ssl_session_reset() API, the maximum TLS version to be negotiated was not restored to the configured one. An attacker was able to prevent an Mbed TLS server from establishing any TLS 1.3 connection, potentially resulting in a Denial of Service or forced version downgrade from TLS 1.3 to TLS 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:27:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3225 | SourceCodester PHP Task Management System edit-task.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3225</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file edit-task.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259070 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3226 | Campcodes Online Patient Record Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/login.php. The manipulation of the argument password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259071.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3224 | SourceCodester PHP Task Management System task-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3224</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester PHP Task Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file task-details.php. The manipulation of the argument task_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259069 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 02:06:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3223 | SourceCodester PHP Task Management System admin-manage-user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3223</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester PHP Task Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file admin-manage-user.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259068.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 01:33:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3221 | SourceCodester PHP Task Management System attendance-info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3221</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester PHP Task Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file attendance-info.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259066 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3222 | SourceCodester PHP Task Management System admin-password-change.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3222</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester PHP Task Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file admin-password-change.php. The manipulation of the argument admin_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259067.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3218 | Shibang Communications IP Network Intercom Broadcasting System busyscreenshotpush.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3218</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shibang Communications IP Network Intercom Broadcasting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /php/busyscreenshotpush.php. The manipulation of the argument jsondata[callee]/jsondata[imagename] leads to path traversal: '../filedir'. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259065 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 23:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3209 | UPX bele.h get_ne64 heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3209</link><description>A vulnerability was found in UPX up to 4.2.2. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function get_ne64 of the file bele.h. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259055. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3248 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in attachments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3248</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in the attachments leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 23:19:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3247 | Stack overflow in Xpdf 4.05 due to object loop in PDF object stream</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3247</link><description>In Xpdf 4.05 (and earlier), a PDF object loop in an object stream leads to infinite recursion and a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 23:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3205 | yaml libyaml emitter.c yaml_emitter_emit_flow_sequence_item heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3205</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yaml libyaml up to 0.2.5 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function yaml_emitter_emit_flow_sequence_item of the file /src/libyaml/src/emitter.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259052. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3207 | ermig1979 Simd SimdMemoryStream.h ReadUnsigned heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ermig1979 Simd up to 6.0.134. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ReadUnsigned of the file src/Simd/SimdMemoryStream.h. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259054 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 22:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3203 | c-blosc2 ndlz8x8.c ndlz8_decompress heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3203</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in c-blosc2 up to 2.13.2. Affected is the function ndlz8_decompress of the file /src/c-blosc2/plugins/codecs/ndlz/ndlz8x8.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-259050 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 22:07:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3204 | c-blosc2 ndlz4x4.c ndlz4_decompress heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3204</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in c-blosc2 up to 2.13.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function ndlz4_decompress of the file /src/c-blosc2/plugins/codecs/ndlz/ndlz4x4.c. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-259051. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3202 | codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS Login Page excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3202</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in codelyfe Stupid Simple CMS 1.2.4. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Login Page. The manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-259049 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29434 | An issue in the system image upload interface of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal when uploading a file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29434</link><description>An issue in the system image upload interface of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal when uploading a file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27604 | Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Command execution vulnerability. System commands can be deserialized.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27604</link><description>Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Command execution vulnerability. System commands can be deserialized.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29432 | Alldata v0.4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the tablename parameter at /data/masterdata/datas.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29432</link><description>Alldata v0.4.6 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the tablename parameter at /data/masterdata/datas.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27602 | Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. A total of many modules interface documents have been leaked.For example, the /api...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27602</link><description>Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. A total of many modules interface documents have been leaked.For example, the /api/system/v2/api-docs module.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:49:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27605 | Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. Using users (test) can query information about the users in the system.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27605</link><description>Alldata V0.4.6 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions. Using users (test) can query information about the users in the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25075 | An issue was discovered in Softing uaToolkit Embedded before 1.41.1. When a subscription with a very low MaxNotificationPerPublish parameter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25075</link><description>An issue was discovered in Softing uaToolkit Embedded before 1.41.1. When a subscription with a very low MaxNotificationPerPublish parameter is created, a publish response is mishandled, leading to memory consumption. When that happens often enough, the device will be out of memory, i.e., a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30367 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30367</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23013.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30370 | RARLAB WinRAR Mark-Of-The-Web Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30370</link><description>RARLAB WinRAR Mark-Of-The-Web Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass the Mark-Of-The-Web protection mechanism on affected installations of RARLAB WinRAR. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must perform a specific action on a malicious page.

The specific flaw exists within the archive extraction functionality. A crafted archive entry can cause the creation of an arbitrary file without the Mark-Of-The-Web. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-23156.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30371 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30371</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23355.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30344 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30344</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22733.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30345 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30345</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22742.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30346 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30346</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22745.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30347 | Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30347</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22910.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30348 | Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30348</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22911.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30349 | Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30349</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22912.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30350 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30350</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22708.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30351 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30351</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22799.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30352 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30352</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22800.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30353 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30353</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22807.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30354 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30354</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22808.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30355 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30355</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22809.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30356 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30356</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22811.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30357 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30357</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Type Confusion Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a type confusion condition. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22818.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30358 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30358</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm User-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22821.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30359 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30359</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm 3D Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of 3D objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22888.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30360 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30360</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22797.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30361 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30361</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22877.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30362 | Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30362</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader PDF File Parsing Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22798.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30363 | Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30363</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23008.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30364 | Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30364</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader U3D File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of U3D files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-23009.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30365 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30365</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22947.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30336 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30336</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects in AcroForms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22642.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30337 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30337</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22704.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30338 | Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30338</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22705.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30339 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30339</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Acroforms. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22706.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30340 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30340</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22707.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30341 | Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30341</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Doc Object Out-Of-Bounds Read Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Doc objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22709.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30342 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30342</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22720.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30343 | Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30343</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader Annotation Use-After-Free Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of validating the existence of an object prior to performing operations on the object. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22721.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29834 | Apache Pulsar: Improper Authorization For Namespace and Topic Management Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29834</link><description>This vulnerability allows authenticated users with produce or consume permissions to perform unauthorized operations on partitioned topics, such as unloading topics and triggering compaction. These management operations should be restricted to users with the tenant admin role or superuser role. An authenticated user with produce permission can create subscriptions and update subscription properties on partitioned topics, even though this should be limited to users with consume permissions. This impact analysis assumes that Pulsar has been configured with the default authorization provider. For custom authorization providers, the impact could be slightly different. Additionally, the vulnerability allows an authenticated user to read, create, modify, and delete namespace properties in any namespace in any tenant. In Pulsar, namespace properties are reserved for user provided metadata about the namespace.

This issue affects Apache Pulsar versions from 2.7.1 to 2.10.6, from 2.11.0 to 2.11.4, from 3.0.0 to 3.0.3, from 3.1.0 to 3.1.3, and from 3.2.0 to 3.2.1. 

3.0 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.0.4.
3.1 and 3.2 Apache Pulsar users should upgrade to at least 3.2.2.

Users operating versions prior to those listed above should upgrade to the aforementioned patched versions or newer versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30531 | WordPress Nelio Content plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30531</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Nelio Software Nelio Content.This issue affects Nelio Content: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24888 | WordPress Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.25 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24888</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Kadence WP Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks.This issue affects Gutenberg Blocks by Kadence Blocks: from n/a through 3.2.25.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:26:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30532 | WordPress Builderall Builder for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30532</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Builderall Team Builderall Builder for WordPress.This issue affects Builderall Builder for WordPress: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 18:26:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30335 | Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30335</link><description>Foxit PDF Reader AcroForm Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Foxit PDF Reader. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of Annotation objects. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22641.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:54:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31105 | WordPress Tax Rate Upload plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - CSRF leading to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31105</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Adam Bowen Tax Rate Upload allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Tax Rate Upload: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30806 | An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap overflow in AP4_Dec3Atom::AP4_Dec3Atom at Ap4Dec3Atom.cpp, leading ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30806</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap overflow in AP4_Dec3Atom::AP4_Dec3Atom at Ap4Dec3Atom.cpp, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS), as demonstrated by mp42aac.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30807 | An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in AP4_UnknownAtom::~AP4_UnknownAtom at Ap4Atom.cpp,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30807</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in AP4_UnknownAtom::~AP4_UnknownAtom at Ap4Atom.cpp, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS), as demonstrated by mp42ts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30808 | An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in AP4_SubStream::~AP4_SubStream at Ap4ByteStream.cp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30808</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in AP4_SubStream::~AP4_SubStream at Ap4ByteStream.cpp, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS), as demonstrated by mp42ts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30809 | An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in Ap4Sample.h in AP4_Sample::GetOffset() const, lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30809</link><description>An issue was discovered in Bento4 v1.6.0-641-2-g1529b83. There is a heap-use-after-free in Ap4Sample.h in AP4_Sample::GetOffset() const, leading to a Denial of Service (DoS), as demonstrated by mp42ts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31109 | WordPress Woocommerce Social Media Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31109</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Toastie Studio Woocommerce Social Media Share Buttons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Woocommerce Social Media Share Buttons: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3151 | Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System Stock Movement Page cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3151</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Bdtask Multi-Store Inventory Management System up to 20240325. Affected is an unknown function of the file /stockmovment/stockmovment/delete/ of the component Stock Movement Page. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258924. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2435 | Stored XSS in Timeline View</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2435</link><description>For an attacker with pre-existing access to send a signal to a workflow, the attacker can make the signal name a script that executes when a victim views that signal. The XSS is in the timeline page displaying the workflow execution details of the workflow that was sent the crafted signal.
Access to send a signal to a workflow is determined by how you configured the authorizer on your server. This includes any entity with permission to directly call SignalWorkflowExecution or SignalWithStartWorkflowExecution, or any entity can deploy a worker that has access to call workflow progress APIs (specifically RespondWorkflowTaskCompleted).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28287 | A DOM-based open redirection in the returnUrl parameter of INSTINCT UI Web Client 6.5.0 allows attackers to redirect users to malicious site...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28287</link><description>A DOM-based open redirection in the returnUrl parameter of INSTINCT UI Web Client 6.5.0 allows attackers to redirect users to malicious sites via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22246 | VMware SD-WAN Edge contains an unauthenticated command injection vulnerability potentially leading to remote code execution.

A malicious ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22246</link><description>VMware SD-WAN Edge contains an unauthenticated command injection vulnerability potentially leading to remote code execution.

A malicious actor with local access to the Edge Router UI during 
activation may be able to perform a command injection attack that could 
lead to full control of the router.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22247 | VMware SD-WAN Edge contains a missing authentication and protection mechanism vulnerability.

A malicious actor with physical access to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22247</link><description>VMware SD-WAN Edge contains a missing authentication and protection mechanism vulnerability.

A malicious actor with physical access to the SD-WAN Edge appliance 
during activation can potentially exploit this vulnerability to access 
the BIOS configuration. In addition, the malicious actor may be able to 
exploit the default boot priority configured.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22248 | VMware SD-WAN Orchestrator contains an open redirect vulnerability.

A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacker 
cont...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22248</link><description>VMware SD-WAN Orchestrator contains an open redirect vulnerability.

A malicious actor may be able to redirect a victim to an attacker 
controlled domain due to improper path handling leading to sensitive 
information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30248 | Piccolo Admin&amp;#x27;s raw SVG loading may lead to complete data compromise from admin page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30248</link><description>Piccolo Admin is an admin interface/content management system for Python, built on top of Piccolo. Piccolo's admin panel allows media files to be uploaded. As a default, SVG is an allowed file type for upload. An attacker can upload an SVG which when loaded can allow arbitrary access to the admin page. This vulnerability was patched in version 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:03:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22780 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CA17 TeamsACS v.1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22780</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in CA17 TeamsACS v.1.0.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the errmsg parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 14:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30620 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the serviceName parameter in the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30620</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the serviceName parameter in the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30621 | Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the serverName parameter in the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30621</link><description>Tenda AX1803 v1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow via the serverName parameter in the function fromAdvSetMacMtuWan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30965 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /src/dede/member_scores.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30965</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /src/dede/member_scores.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30946 | DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /src/dede/co_do.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30946</link><description>DedeCMS v5.7 was discovered to contain a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability via /src/dede/co_do.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:15:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50313 | IBM WebSphere Application Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50313</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 could provide weaker than expected security for outbound TLS connections caused by a failure to honor user configuration.  IBM X-Force ID:  274812.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29514 | File Upload vulnerability in lepton v.7.1.0 allows a remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP fi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29514</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in lepton v.7.1.0 allows a remote authenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted PHP file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2389 | Flowmon Unauthenticated Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2389</link><description>In Flowmon versions prior to 11.1.14 and 12.3.5, an operating system command injection vulnerability has been identified. An unauthenticated usercan gain entry to the system via the Flowmon management interface, allowing for the execution of arbitrary system commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:30:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29947 | There is a NULL dereference pointer vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. Due to an insufficient validation of a parameter in a message, an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29947</link><description>There is a NULL dereference pointer vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. Due to an insufficient validation of a parameter in a message, an attacker may send specially crafted messages to an affected product, causing a process abnormality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29948 | There is an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29948</link><description>There is an out-of-bounds read vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. An authenticated attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending specially crafted messages to a vulnerable device, causing a service abnormality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29949 | There is a command injection vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. This could allow an authenticated user with administrative rights to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29949</link><description>There is a command injection vulnerability in some Hikvision NVRs. This could allow an authenticated user with administrative rights to execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:09:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51452 | A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51452</link><description>A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to cause a crash of the service through a crafted payload triggering a missing input size check in the pull_file_v2_proc function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library used by the dji_vtwo_sdk binary implementing the service, compromising it in a term of availability and producing a denial-of-service attack. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51453 | A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51453</link><description>A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to cause a crash of the service through a crafted payload triggering a missing input size check in the process_push_file function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library used by the dji_vtwo_sdk binary implementing the service, compromising it in a term of availability and producing a denial-of-service attack. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51454 | A Out-of-bounds Write issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51454</link><description>A Out-of-bounds Write issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to overwrite a pointer in the process memory through a crafted payload triggering an unsafe memory write operation in the my_tcp_receive function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library used by the dji_vtwo_sdk binary implementing the service, potentially leading to a memory information leak or to an arbitrary code execution. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51455 | A Improper Validation of Array Index issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51455</link><description>A Improper Validation of Array Index issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to corrupt a controlled memory location due to a missing input validation in the on_receive_session_packet_ack function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library used by the dji_vtwo_sdk binary implementing the service, potentially leading to a memory information leak or to an arbitrary code execution. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51456 | A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51456</link><description>A Improper Input Validation issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to trigger an out-of-bound read/write into the process memory through a crafted payload due to a missing input sanity check in the v2_pack_array_to_msg function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library imported by the v2_sdk_service binary implementing the service, potentially leading to a memory information leak or an arbitrary code execution. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6948 | A Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6948</link><description>A Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input issue affecting the v2_sdk_service running on a set of DJI drone devices on the port 10000 could allow an attacker to cause a crash of the service through a crafted payload triggering a missing input size check in the sdk_printf function implemented in the libv2_sdk.so library used by the dji_vtwo_sdk binary implementing the service, compromising it in a term of availability and producing a denial-of-service attack. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6949 | A Missing Authentication for Critical Function issue affecting the HTTP service running on the DJI Mavic Mini 3 Pro on the standard port 80 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6949</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function issue affecting the HTTP service running on the DJI Mavic Mini 3 Pro on the standard port 80 could allow an attacker to enumerate and download videos and pictures saved on the drone internal or external memory without requiring any kind of authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6950 | An Improper Input Validation vulnerability affecting the FTP service running on the DJI Mavic Mini 3 Pro could allow an attacker to craft a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6950</link><description>An Improper Input Validation vulnerability affecting the FTP service running on the DJI Mavic Mini 3 Pro could allow an attacker to craft a malicious packet containing a malformed path provided to the FTP SIZE command that leads to a denial-of-service attack of the FTP service itself.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6951 | A Use of Weak Credentials vulnerability affecting the Wi-Fi network generated by a set of DJI drones could allow a remote attacker to derive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6951</link><description>A Use of Weak Credentials vulnerability affecting the Wi-Fi network generated by a set of DJI drones could allow a remote attacker to derive the WPA2 PSK key and authenticate without permission to the drones Wi- Fi network. This, in turn, allows the attacker to perform unauthorized interaction with the network services exposed by the drone and to potentially decrypt the Wi-Fi traffic exchanged between the drone and the Android/IOS device of the legitimate user during QuickTransfer mode. Affected models are Mavic 3 Pro until v01.01.0300, Mavic 3 until v01.00.1200, Mavic 3 Classic until v01.00.0500, Mavic 3 Enterprise until v07.01.10.03, Matrice 300 until v57.00.01.00, Matrice M30 until v07.01.0022 and Mini 3 Pro until v01.00.0620.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:36:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2745 | Rapid7 InsightVM Sensitive Information Exposure via URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2745</link><description>Rapid7's InsightVM maintenance mode login page suffers from a sensitive information exposure vulnerability whereby, sensitive information is exposed through query strings in the URL when login is attempted before the page is fully loaded. This vulnerability allows attackers to acquire sensitive information such as passwords, auth tokens, usernames etc.

The vulnerability is remediated in version 6.6.244.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1732 | The Sharkdropship for AliExpress Dropshipping and Affiliate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1732</link><description>The Sharkdropship for AliExpress Dropshipping and Affiliate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the wads_removeProductFromShop() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1807 | The Product Sort and Display for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1807</link><description>The Product Sort and Display for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the psad_update_product_cat_custom_meta_ajax function in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to hide product categories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:37:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1946 | The Genesis Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the block content in all versions up to, and includ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1946</link><description>The Genesis Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the block content in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:37:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2931 | The WPFront User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2931</link><description>The WPFront User Role Editor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1.11184 via the wpfront_user_role_editor_assign_roles_user_autocomplete AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to extract retrieve a list of all user email addresses who are registered on the site.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20799 | AMS XSS - /libs/dam/gui/coral/components/commons/navigationpanel/clientlibs/navigationpanel/js/navigationpanel.js</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20799</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.19 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victims browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31004 | An issue in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4StsdAtom.cpp,AP4_StsdAtom::AP4_StsdAtom,m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31004</link><description>An issue in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4StsdAtom.cpp,AP4_StsdAtom::AP4_StsdAtom,mp4fragment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:46:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31005 | An issue in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4MdhdAtom.cpp,AP4_MdhdAtom::AP4_MdhdAtom,m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31005</link><description>An issue in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Ap4MdhdAtom.cpp,AP4_MdhdAtom::AP4_MdhdAtom,mp4fragment</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:46:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1300 | Io.vertx:vertx-core: memory leak when a tcp server is configured with tls and sni support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1300</link><description>A vulnerability in the Eclipse Vert.x toolkit causes a memory leak in TCP servers configured with TLS and SNI support. When processing an unknown SNI server name assigned the default certificate instead of a mapped certificate, the SSL context is erroneously cached in the server name map, leading to memory exhaustion. This flaw allows attackers to send TLS client hello messages with fake server names, triggering a JVM out-of-memory error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31002 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4 BitReader::ReadCach...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31002</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4 BitReader::ReadCache() at Ap4Utils.cpp component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31003 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_MemoryByteStream::W...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31003</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Bento4 Bento v.1.6.0-641 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the AP4_MemoryByteStream::WritePartial at Ap4ByteStream.cpp.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52636 | libceph: just wait for more data to be available on the socket</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52636</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

libceph: just wait for more data to be available on the socket

A short read may occur while reading the message footer from the
socket.  Later, when the socket is ready for another read, the
messenger invokes all read_partial_*() handlers, including
read_partial_sparse_msg_data().  The expectation is that
read_partial_sparse_msg_data() would bail, allowing the messenger to
invoke read_partial() for the footer and pick up where it left off.

However read_partial_sparse_msg_data() violates that and ends up
calling into the state machine in the OSD client.  The sparse-read
state machine assumes that it's a new op and interprets some piece of
the footer as the sparse-read header and returns bogus extents/data
length, etc.

To determine whether read_partial_sparse_msg_data() should bail, let's
reuse cursor-&gt;total_resid.  Because once it reaches to zero that means
all the extents and data have been successfully received in last read,
else it could break out when partially reading any of the extents and
data.  And then osd_sparse_read() could continue where it left off.

[ idryomov: changelog ]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26674 | x86/lib: Revert to _ASM_EXTABLE_UA() for {get,put}_user() fixups</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26674</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/lib: Revert to _ASM_EXTABLE_UA() for {get,put}_user() fixups

During memory error injection test on kernels &gt;= v6.4, the kernel panics
like below. However, this issue couldn't be reproduced on kernels &lt;= v6.3.

  mce: [Hardware Error]: CPU 296: Machine Check Exception: f Bank 1: bd80000000100134
  mce: [Hardware Error]: RIP 10:&lt;ffffffff821b9776&gt; {__get_user_nocheck_4+0x6/0x20}
  mce: [Hardware Error]: TSC 411a93533ed ADDR 346a8730040 MISC 86
  mce: [Hardware Error]: PROCESSOR 0:a06d0 TIME 1706000767 SOCKET 1 APIC 211 microcode 80001490
  mce: [Hardware Error]: Run the above through 'mcelog --ascii'
  mce: [Hardware Error]: Machine check: Data load in unrecoverable area of kernel
  Kernel panic - not syncing: Fatal local machine check

The MCA code can recover from an in-kernel #MC if the fixup type is
EX_TYPE_UACCESS, explicitly indicating that the kernel is attempting to
access userspace memory. However, if the fixup type is EX_TYPE_DEFAULT
the only thing that is raised for an in-kernel #MC is a panic.

ex_handler_uaccess() would warn if users gave a non-canonical addresses
(with bit 63 clear) to {get, put}_user(), which was unexpected.

Therefore, commit

  b19b74bc99b1 ("x86/mm: Rework address range check in get_user() and put_user()")

replaced _ASM_EXTABLE_UA() with _ASM_EXTABLE() for {get, put}_user()
fixups. However, the new fixup type EX_TYPE_DEFAULT results in a panic.

Commit

  6014bc27561f ("x86-64: make access_ok() independent of LAM")

added the check gp_fault_address_ok() right before the WARN_ONCE() in
ex_handler_uaccess() to not warn about non-canonical user addresses due
to LAM.

With that in place, revert back to _ASM_EXTABLE_UA() for {get,put}_user()
exception fixups in order to be able to handle in-kernel MCEs correctly
again.

  [ bp: Massage commit message. ]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26675 | ppp_async: limit MRU to 64K</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26675</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ppp_async: limit MRU to 64K

syzbot triggered a warning [1] in __alloc_pages():

WARN_ON_ONCE_GFP(order &gt; MAX_PAGE_ORDER, gfp)

Willem fixed a similar issue in commit c0a2a1b0d631 ("ppp: limit MRU to 64K")

Adopt the same sanity check for ppp_async_ioctl(PPPIOCSMRU)

[1]:

 WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 11 at mm/page_alloc.c:4543 __alloc_pages+0x308/0x698 mm/page_alloc.c:4543
Modules linked in:
CPU: 1 PID: 11 Comm: kworker/u4:0 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc2-syzkaller-g41bccc98fb79 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/17/2023
Workqueue: events_unbound flush_to_ldisc
pstate: 204000c5 (nzCv daIF +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
 pc : __alloc_pages+0x308/0x698 mm/page_alloc.c:4543
 lr : __alloc_pages+0xc8/0x698 mm/page_alloc.c:4537
sp : ffff800093967580
x29: ffff800093967660 x28: ffff8000939675a0 x27: dfff800000000000
x26: ffff70001272ceb4 x25: 0000000000000000 x24: ffff8000939675c0
x23: 0000000000000000 x22: 0000000000060820 x21: 1ffff0001272ceb8
x20: ffff8000939675e0 x19: 0000000000000010 x18: ffff800093967120
x17: ffff800083bded5c x16: ffff80008ac97500 x15: 0000000000000005
x14: 1ffff0001272cebc x13: 0000000000000000 x12: 0000000000000000
x11: ffff70001272cec1 x10: 1ffff0001272cec0 x9 : 0000000000000001
x8 : ffff800091c91000 x7 : 0000000000000000 x6 : 000000000000003f
x5 : 00000000ffffffff x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000020
x2 : 0000000000000008 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff8000939675e0
Call trace:
  __alloc_pages+0x308/0x698 mm/page_alloc.c:4543
  __alloc_pages_node include/linux/gfp.h:238 [inline]
  alloc_pages_node include/linux/gfp.h:261 [inline]
  __kmalloc_large_node+0xbc/0x1fc mm/slub.c:3926
  __do_kmalloc_node mm/slub.c:3969 [inline]
  __kmalloc_node_track_caller+0x418/0x620 mm/slub.c:4001
  kmalloc_reserve+0x17c/0x23c net/core/skbuff.c:590
  __alloc_skb+0x1c8/0x3d8 net/core/skbuff.c:651
  __netdev_alloc_skb+0xb8/0x3e8 net/core/skbuff.c:715
  netdev_alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:3235 [inline]
  dev_alloc_skb include/linux/skbuff.h:3248 [inline]
  ppp_async_input drivers/net/ppp/ppp_async.c:863 [inline]
  ppp_asynctty_receive+0x588/0x186c drivers/net/ppp/ppp_async.c:341
  tty_ldisc_receive_buf+0x12c/0x15c drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:390
  tty_port_default_receive_buf+0x74/0xac drivers/tty/tty_port.c:37
  receive_buf drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:444 [inline]
  flush_to_ldisc+0x284/0x6e4 drivers/tty/tty_buffer.c:494
  process_one_work+0x694/0x1204 kernel/workqueue.c:2633
  process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:2706 [inline]
  worker_thread+0x938/0xef4 kernel/workqueue.c:2787
  kthread+0x288/0x310 kernel/kthread.c:388
  ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:860</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26676 | af_unix: Call kfree_skb() for dead unix_(sk)-&amp;gt;oob_skb in GC.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26676</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

af_unix: Call kfree_skb() for dead unix_(sk)-&gt;oob_skb in GC.

syzbot reported a warning [0] in __unix_gc() with a repro, which
creates a socketpair and sends one socket's fd to itself using the
peer.

  socketpair(AF_UNIX, SOCK_STREAM, 0, [3, 4]) = 0
  sendmsg(4, {msg_name=NULL, msg_namelen=0, msg_iov=[{iov_base="\360", iov_len=1}],
          msg_iovlen=1, msg_control=[{cmsg_len=20, cmsg_level=SOL_SOCKET,
                                      cmsg_type=SCM_RIGHTS, cmsg_data=[3]}],
          msg_controllen=24, msg_flags=0}, MSG_OOB|MSG_PROBE|MSG_DONTWAIT|MSG_ZEROCOPY) = 1

This forms a self-cyclic reference that GC should finally untangle
but does not due to lack of MSG_OOB handling, resulting in memory
leak.

Recently, commit 11498715f266 ("af_unix: Remove io_uring code for
GC.") removed io_uring's dead code in GC and revealed the problem.

The code was executed at the final stage of GC and unconditionally
moved all GC candidates from gc_candidates to gc_inflight_list.
That papered over the reported problem by always making the following
WARN_ON_ONCE(!list_empty(&amp;gc_candidates)) false.

The problem has been there since commit 2aab4b969002 ("af_unix: fix
struct pid leaks in OOB support") added full scm support for MSG_OOB
while fixing another bug.

To fix this problem, we must call kfree_skb() for unix_sk(sk)-&gt;oob_skb
if the socket still exists in gc_candidates after purging collected skb.

Then, we need to set NULL to oob_skb before calling kfree_skb() because
it calls last fput() and triggers unix_release_sock(), where we call
duplicate kfree_skb(u-&gt;oob_skb) if not NULL.

Note that the leaked socket remained being linked to a global list, so
kmemleak also could not detect it.  We need to check /proc/net/protocol
to notice the unfreed socket.

[0]:
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 2863 at net/unix/garbage.c:345 __unix_gc+0xc74/0xe80 net/unix/garbage.c:345
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 PID: 2863 Comm: kworker/u4:11 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc1-syzkaller-00583-g1701940b1a02 #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 01/25/2024
Workqueue: events_unbound __unix_gc
RIP: 0010:__unix_gc+0xc74/0xe80 net/unix/garbage.c:345
Code: 8b 5c 24 50 e9 86 f8 ff ff e8 f8 e4 22 f8 31 d2 48 c7 c6 30 6a 69 89 4c 89 ef e8 97 ef ff ff e9 80 f9 ff ff e8 dd e4 22 f8 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 e9 7b fd ff ff 48 89 df e8 5c e7 7c f8 e9 d3 f8 ff ff e8
RSP: 0018:ffffc9000b03fba0 EFLAGS: 00010293
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffc9000b03fc10 RCX: ffffffff816c493e
RDX: ffff88802c02d940 RSI: ffffffff896982f3 RDI: ffffc9000b03fb30
RBP: ffffc9000b03fce0 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: fffff52001607f66
R10: 0000000000000003 R11: 0000000000000002 R12: dffffc0000000000
R13: ffffc9000b03fc10 R14: ffffc9000b03fc10 R15: 0000000000000001
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880b9400000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00005559c8677a60 CR3: 000000000d57a000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 process_one_work+0x889/0x15e0 kernel/workqueue.c:2633
 process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:2706 [inline]
 worker_thread+0x8b9/0x12a0 kernel/workqueue.c:2787
 kthread+0x2c6/0x3b0 kernel/kthread.c:388
 ret_from_fork+0x45/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1b/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:242
 &lt;/TASK&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26677 | rxrpc: Fix delayed ACKs to not set the reference serial number</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26677</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

rxrpc: Fix delayed ACKs to not set the reference serial number

Fix the construction of delayed ACKs to not set the reference serial number
as they can't be used as an RTT reference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26678 | x86/efistub: Use 1:1 file:memory mapping for PE/COFF .compat section</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26678</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/efistub: Use 1:1 file:memory mapping for PE/COFF .compat section

The .compat section is a dummy PE section that contains the address of
the 32-bit entrypoint of the 64-bit kernel image if it is bootable from
32-bit firmware (i.e., CONFIG_EFI_MIXED=y)

This section is only 8 bytes in size and is only referenced from the
loader, and so it is placed at the end of the memory view of the image,
to avoid the need for padding it to 4k, which is required for sections
appearing in the middle of the image.

Unfortunately, this violates the PE/COFF spec, and even if most EFI
loaders will work correctly (including the Tianocore reference
implementation), PE loaders do exist that reject such images, on the
basis that both the file and memory views of the file contents should be
described by the section headers in a monotonically increasing manner
without leaving any gaps.

So reorganize the sections to avoid this issue. This results in a slight
padding overhead (&lt; 4k) which can be avoided if desired by disabling
CONFIG_EFI_MIXED (which is only needed in rare cases these days)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26679 | inet: read sk-&amp;gt;sk_family once in inet_recv_error()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26679</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

inet: read sk-&gt;sk_family once in inet_recv_error()

inet_recv_error() is called without holding the socket lock.

IPv6 socket could mutate to IPv4 with IPV6_ADDRFORM
socket option and trigger a KCSAN warning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26680 | net: atlantic: Fix DMA mapping for PTP hwts ring</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26680</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: atlantic: Fix DMA mapping for PTP hwts ring

Function aq_ring_hwts_rx_alloc() maps extra AQ_CFG_RXDS_DEF bytes
for PTP HWTS ring but then generic aq_ring_free() does not take this
into account.
Create and use a specific function to free HWTS ring to fix this
issue.

Trace:
[  215.351607] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  215.351612] DMA-API: atlantic 0000:4b:00.0: device driver frees DMA memory with different size [device address=0x00000000fbdd0000] [map size=34816 bytes] [unmap size=32768 bytes]
[  215.351635] WARNING: CPU: 33 PID: 10759 at kernel/dma/debug.c:988 check_unmap+0xa6f/0x2360
...
[  215.581176] Call Trace:
[  215.583632]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[  215.585745]  ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1c4/0x2df
[  215.590114]  ? show_trace_log_lvl+0x1c4/0x2df
[  215.594497]  ? debug_dma_free_coherent+0x196/0x210
[  215.599305]  ? check_unmap+0xa6f/0x2360
[  215.603147]  ? __warn+0xca/0x1d0
[  215.606391]  ? check_unmap+0xa6f/0x2360
[  215.610237]  ? report_bug+0x1ef/0x370
[  215.613921]  ? handle_bug+0x3c/0x70
[  215.617423]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x14/0x50
[  215.621269]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x16/0x20
[  215.625480]  ? check_unmap+0xa6f/0x2360
[  215.629331]  ? mark_lock.part.0+0xca/0xa40
[  215.633445]  debug_dma_free_coherent+0x196/0x210
[  215.638079]  ? __pfx_debug_dma_free_coherent+0x10/0x10
[  215.643242]  ? slab_free_freelist_hook+0x11d/0x1d0
[  215.648060]  dma_free_attrs+0x6d/0x130
[  215.651834]  aq_ring_free+0x193/0x290 [atlantic]
[  215.656487]  aq_ptp_ring_free+0x67/0x110 [atlantic]
...
[  216.127540] ---[ end trace 6467e5964dd2640b ]---
[  216.132160] DMA-API: Mapped at:
[  216.132162]  debug_dma_alloc_coherent+0x66/0x2f0
[  216.132165]  dma_alloc_attrs+0xf5/0x1b0
[  216.132168]  aq_ring_hwts_rx_alloc+0x150/0x1f0 [atlantic]
[  216.132193]  aq_ptp_ring_alloc+0x1bb/0x540 [atlantic]
[  216.132213]  aq_nic_init+0x4a1/0x760 [atlantic]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26681 | netdevsim: avoid potential loop in nsim_dev_trap_report_work()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26681</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netdevsim: avoid potential loop in nsim_dev_trap_report_work()

Many syzbot reports include the following trace [1]

If nsim_dev_trap_report_work() can not grab the mutex,
it should rearm itself at least one jiffie later.

[1]
Sending NMI from CPU 1 to CPUs 0:
NMI backtrace for cpu 0
CPU: 0 PID: 32383 Comm: kworker/0:2 Not tainted 6.8.0-rc2-syzkaller-00031-g861c0981648f #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 11/17/2023
Workqueue: events nsim_dev_trap_report_work
 RIP: 0010:bytes_is_nonzero mm/kasan/generic.c:89 [inline]
 RIP: 0010:memory_is_nonzero mm/kasan/generic.c:104 [inline]
 RIP: 0010:memory_is_poisoned_n mm/kasan/generic.c:129 [inline]
 RIP: 0010:memory_is_poisoned mm/kasan/generic.c:161 [inline]
 RIP: 0010:check_region_inline mm/kasan/generic.c:180 [inline]
 RIP: 0010:kasan_check_range+0x101/0x190 mm/kasan/generic.c:189
Code: 07 49 39 d1 75 0a 45 3a 11 b8 01 00 00 00 7c 0b 44 89 c2 e8 21 ed ff ff 83 f0 01 5b 5d 41 5c c3 48 85 d2 74 4f 48 01 ea eb 09 &lt;48&gt; 83 c0 01 48 39 d0 74 41 80 38 00 74 f2 eb b6 41 bc 08 00 00 00
RSP: 0018:ffffc90012dcf998 EFLAGS: 00000046
RAX: fffffbfff258af1e RBX: fffffbfff258af1f RCX: ffffffff8168eda3
RDX: fffffbfff258af1f RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffffffff92c578f0
RBP: fffffbfff258af1e R08: 0000000000000000 R09: fffffbfff258af1e
R10: ffffffff92c578f3 R11: ffffffff8acbcbc0 R12: 0000000000000002
R13: ffff88806db38400 R14: 1ffff920025b9f42 R15: ffffffff92c578e8
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff8880b9800000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 000000c00994e078 CR3: 000000002c250000 CR4: 00000000003506f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 &lt;NMI&gt;
 &lt;/NMI&gt;
 &lt;TASK&gt;
  instrument_atomic_read include/linux/instrumented.h:68 [inline]
  atomic_read include/linux/atomic/atomic-instrumented.h:32 [inline]
  queued_spin_is_locked include/asm-generic/qspinlock.h:57 [inline]
  debug_spin_unlock kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:101 [inline]
  do_raw_spin_unlock+0x53/0x230 kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:141
  __raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:150 [inline]
  _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x22/0x70 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:194
  debug_object_activate+0x349/0x540 lib/debugobjects.c:726
  debug_work_activate kernel/workqueue.c:578 [inline]
  insert_work+0x30/0x230 kernel/workqueue.c:1650
  __queue_work+0x62e/0x11d0 kernel/workqueue.c:1802
  __queue_delayed_work+0x1bf/0x270 kernel/workqueue.c:1953
  queue_delayed_work_on+0x106/0x130 kernel/workqueue.c:1989
  queue_delayed_work include/linux/workqueue.h:563 [inline]
  schedule_delayed_work include/linux/workqueue.h:677 [inline]
  nsim_dev_trap_report_work+0x9c0/0xc80 drivers/net/netdevsim/dev.c:842
  process_one_work+0x886/0x15d0 kernel/workqueue.c:2633
  process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:2706 [inline]
  worker_thread+0x8b9/0x1290 kernel/workqueue.c:2787
  kthread+0x2c6/0x3a0 kernel/kthread.c:388
  ret_from_fork+0x45/0x80 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x11/0x20 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:242
 &lt;/TASK&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26682 | wifi: mac80211: improve CSA/ECSA connection refusal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26682</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mac80211: improve CSA/ECSA connection refusal

As mentioned in the previous commit, we pretty quickly found
that some APs have ECSA elements stuck in their probe response,
so using that to not attempt to connect while CSA is happening
we never connect to such an AP.

Improve this situation by checking more carefully and ignoring
the ECSA if cfg80211 has previously detected the ECSA element
being stuck in the probe response.

Additionally, allow connecting to an AP that's switching to a
channel it's already using, unless it's using quiet mode. In
this case, we may just have to adjust bandwidth later. If it's
actually switching channels, it's better not to try to connect
in the middle of that.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26683 | wifi: cfg80211: detect stuck ECSA element in probe resp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26683</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: cfg80211: detect stuck ECSA element in probe resp

We recently added some validation that we don't try to
connect to an AP that is currently in a channel switch
process, since that might want the channel to be quiet
or we might not be able to connect in time to hear the
switching in a beacon. This was in commit c09c4f31998b
("wifi: mac80211: don't connect to an AP while it's in
a CSA process").

However, we promptly got a report that this caused new
connection failures, and it turns out that the AP that
we now cannot connect to is permanently advertising an
extended channel switch announcement, even with quiet.
The AP in question was an Asus RT-AC53, with firmware
3.0.0.4.380_10760-g21a5898.

As a first step, attempt to detect that we're dealing
with such a situation, so mac80211 can use this later.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26684 | net: stmmac: xgmac: fix handling of DPP safety error for DMA channels</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26684</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: stmmac: xgmac: fix handling of DPP safety error for DMA channels

Commit 56e58d6c8a56 ("net: stmmac: Implement Safety Features in
XGMAC core") checks and reports safety errors, but leaves the
Data Path Parity Errors for each channel in DMA unhandled at all, lead to
a storm of interrupt.
Fix it by checking and clearing the DMA_DPP_Interrupt_Status register.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29276 | An issue was discovered in seeyonOA version 8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the importProcess method in WorkFlowDes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29276</link><description>An issue was discovered in seeyonOA version 8, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the importProcess method in WorkFlowDesignerController.class component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26673 | netfilter: nft_ct: sanitize layer 3 and 4 protocol number in custom expectations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26673</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_ct: sanitize layer 3 and 4 protocol number in custom expectations

- Disallow families other than NFPROTO_{IPV4,IPV6,INET}.
- Disallow layer 4 protocol with no ports, since destination port is a
  mandatory attribute for this object.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:00:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52632 | drm/amdkfd: Fix lock dependency warning with srcu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52632</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdkfd: Fix lock dependency warning with srcu

======================================================
WARNING: possible circular locking dependency detected
6.5.0-kfd-yangp #2289 Not tainted
------------------------------------------------------
kworker/0:2/996 is trying to acquire lock:
        (srcu){.+.+}-{0:0}, at: __synchronize_srcu+0x5/0x1a0

but task is already holding lock:
        ((work_completion)(&amp;svms-&gt;deferred_list_work)){+.+.}-{0:0}, at:
	process_one_work+0x211/0x560

which lock already depends on the new lock.

the existing dependency chain (in reverse order) is:

-&gt; #3 ((work_completion)(&amp;svms-&gt;deferred_list_work)){+.+.}-{0:0}:
        __flush_work+0x88/0x4f0
        svm_range_list_lock_and_flush_work+0x3d/0x110 [amdgpu]
        svm_range_set_attr+0xd6/0x14c0 [amdgpu]
        kfd_ioctl+0x1d1/0x630 [amdgpu]
        __x64_sys_ioctl+0x88/0xc0

-&gt; #2 (&amp;info-&gt;lock#2){+.+.}-{3:3}:
        __mutex_lock+0x99/0xc70
        amdgpu_amdkfd_gpuvm_restore_process_bos+0x54/0x740 [amdgpu]
        restore_process_helper+0x22/0x80 [amdgpu]
        restore_process_worker+0x2d/0xa0 [amdgpu]
        process_one_work+0x29b/0x560
        worker_thread+0x3d/0x3d0

-&gt; #1 ((work_completion)(&amp;(&amp;process-&gt;restore_work)-&gt;work)){+.+.}-{0:0}:
        __flush_work+0x88/0x4f0
        __cancel_work_timer+0x12c/0x1c0
        kfd_process_notifier_release_internal+0x37/0x1f0 [amdgpu]
        __mmu_notifier_release+0xad/0x240
        exit_mmap+0x6a/0x3a0
        mmput+0x6a/0x120
        do_exit+0x322/0xb90
        do_group_exit+0x37/0xa0
        __x64_sys_exit_group+0x18/0x20
        do_syscall_64+0x38/0x80

-&gt; #0 (srcu){.+.+}-{0:0}:
        __lock_acquire+0x1521/0x2510
        lock_sync+0x5f/0x90
        __synchronize_srcu+0x4f/0x1a0
        __mmu_notifier_release+0x128/0x240
        exit_mmap+0x6a/0x3a0
        mmput+0x6a/0x120
        svm_range_deferred_list_work+0x19f/0x350 [amdgpu]
        process_one_work+0x29b/0x560
        worker_thread+0x3d/0x3d0

other info that might help us debug this:
Chain exists of:
  srcu --&gt; &amp;info-&gt;lock#2 --&gt; (work_completion)(&amp;svms-&gt;deferred_list_work)

Possible unsafe locking scenario:

        CPU0                    CPU1
        ----                    ----
        lock((work_completion)(&amp;svms-&gt;deferred_list_work));
                        lock(&amp;info-&gt;lock#2);
			lock((work_completion)(&amp;svms-&gt;deferred_list_work));
        sync(srcu);</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52633 | um: time-travel: fix time corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52633</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

um: time-travel: fix time corruption

In 'basic' time-travel mode (without =inf-cpu or =ext), we
still get timer interrupts. These can happen at arbitrary
points in time, i.e. while in timer_read(), which pushes
time forward just a little bit. Then, if we happen to get
the interrupt after calculating the new time to push to,
but before actually finishing that, the interrupt will set
the time to a value that's incompatible with the forward,
and we'll crash because time goes backwards when we do the
forwarding.

Fix this by reading the time_travel_time, calculating the
adjustment, and doing the adjustment all with interrupts
disabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52634 | drm/amd/display: Fix disable_otg_wa logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52634</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Fix disable_otg_wa logic

[Why]
When switching to another HDMI mode, we are unnecesarilly
disabling/enabling FIFO causing both HPO and DIG registers to be set at
the same time when only HPO is supposed to be set.

This can lead to a system hang the next time we change refresh rates as
there are cases when we don't disable OTG/FIFO but FIFO is enabled when
it isn't supposed to be.

[How]
Removing the enable/disable FIFO entirely.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52635 | PM / devfreq: Synchronize devfreq_monitor_[start/stop]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52635</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PM / devfreq: Synchronize devfreq_monitor_[start/stop]

There is a chance if a frequent switch of the governor
done in a loop result in timer list corruption where
timer cancel being done from two place one from
cancel_delayed_work_sync() and followed by expire_timers()
can be seen from the traces[1].

while true
do
        echo "simple_ondemand" &gt; /sys/class/devfreq/1d84000.ufshc/governor
        echo "performance" &gt; /sys/class/devfreq/1d84000.ufshc/governor
done

It looks to be issue with devfreq driver where
device_monitor_[start/stop] need to synchronized so that
delayed work should get corrupted while it is either
being queued or running or being cancelled.

Let's use polling flag and devfreq lock to synchronize the
queueing the timer instance twice and work data being
corrupted.

[1]
...
..
&lt;idle&gt;-0    [003]   9436.209662:  timer_cancel   timer=0xffffff80444f0428
&lt;idle&gt;-0    [003]   9436.209664:  timer_expire_entry   timer=0xffffff80444f0428  now=0x10022da1c  function=__typeid__ZTSFvP10timer_listE_global_addr  baseclk=0x10022da1c
&lt;idle&gt;-0    [003]   9436.209718:  timer_expire_exit   timer=0xffffff80444f0428
kworker/u16:6-14217    [003]   9436.209863:  timer_start   timer=0xffffff80444f0428  function=__typeid__ZTSFvP10timer_listE_global_addr  expires=0x10022da2b  now=0x10022da1c  flags=182452227
vendor.xxxyyy.ha-1593    [004]   9436.209888:  timer_cancel   timer=0xffffff80444f0428
vendor.xxxyyy.ha-1593    [004]   9436.216390:  timer_init   timer=0xffffff80444f0428
vendor.xxxyyy.ha-1593    [004]   9436.216392:  timer_start   timer=0xffffff80444f0428  function=__typeid__ZTSFvP10timer_listE_global_addr  expires=0x10022da2c  now=0x10022da1d  flags=186646532
vendor.xxxyyy.ha-1593    [005]   9436.220992:  timer_cancel   timer=0xffffff80444f0428
xxxyyyTraceManag-7795    [004]   9436.261641:  timer_cancel   timer=0xffffff80444f0428

[2]

 9436.261653][    C4] Unable to handle kernel paging request at virtual address dead00000000012a
[ 9436.261664][    C4] Mem abort info:
[ 9436.261666][    C4]   ESR = 0x96000044
[ 9436.261669][    C4]   EC = 0x25: DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
[ 9436.261671][    C4]   SET = 0, FnV = 0
[ 9436.261673][    C4]   EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
[ 9436.261675][    C4] Data abort info:
[ 9436.261677][    C4]   ISV = 0, ISS = 0x00000044
[ 9436.261680][    C4]   CM = 0, WnR = 1
[ 9436.261682][    C4] [dead00000000012a] address between user and kernel address ranges
[ 9436.261685][    C4] Internal error: Oops: 96000044 [#1] PREEMPT SMP
[ 9436.261701][    C4] Skip md ftrace buffer dump for: 0x3a982d0
...

[ 9436.262138][    C4] CPU: 4 PID: 7795 Comm: TraceManag Tainted: G S      W  O      5.10.149-android12-9-o-g17f915d29d0c #1
[ 9436.262141][    C4] Hardware name: Qualcomm Technologies, Inc.  (DT)
[ 9436.262144][    C4] pstate: 22400085 (nzCv daIf +PAN -UAO +TCO BTYPE=--)
[ 9436.262161][    C4] pc : expire_timers+0x9c/0x438
[ 9436.262164][    C4] lr : expire_timers+0x2a4/0x438
[ 9436.262168][    C4] sp : ffffffc010023dd0
[ 9436.262171][    C4] x29: ffffffc010023df0 x28: ffffffd0636fdc18
[ 9436.262178][    C4] x27: ffffffd063569dd0 x26: ffffffd063536008
[ 9436.262182][    C4] x25: 0000000000000001 x24: ffffff88f7c69280
[ 9436.262185][    C4] x23: 00000000000000e0 x22: dead000000000122
[ 9436.262188][    C4] x21: 000000010022da29 x20: ffffff8af72b4e80
[ 9436.262191][    C4] x19: ffffffc010023e50 x18: ffffffc010025038
[ 9436.262195][    C4] x17: 0000000000000240 x16: 0000000000000201
[ 9436.262199][    C4] x15: ffffffffffffffff x14: ffffff889f3c3100
[ 9436.262203][    C4] x13: ffffff889f3c3100 x12: 00000000049f56b8
[ 9436.262207][    C4] x11: 00000000049f56b8 x10: 00000000ffffffff
[ 9436.262212][    C4] x9 : ffffffc010023e50 x8 : dead000000000122
[ 9436.262216][    C4] x7 : ffffffffffffffff x6 : ffffffc0100239d8
[ 9436.262220][    C4] x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : 0000000000000101
[ 9436.262223][    C4] x3 : 0000000000000080 x2 : ffffff8
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26671 | blk-mq: fix IO hang from sbitmap wakeup race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26671</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-mq: fix IO hang from sbitmap wakeup race

In blk_mq_mark_tag_wait(), __add_wait_queue() may be re-ordered
with the following blk_mq_get_driver_tag() in case of getting driver
tag failure.

Then in __sbitmap_queue_wake_up(), waitqueue_active() may not observe
the added waiter in blk_mq_mark_tag_wait() and wake up nothing, meantime
blk_mq_mark_tag_wait() can't get driver tag successfully.

This issue can be reproduced by running the following test in loop, and
fio hang can be observed in &lt; 30min when running it on my test VM
in laptop.

	modprobe -r scsi_debug
	modprobe scsi_debug delay=0 dev_size_mb=4096 max_queue=1 host_max_queue=1 submit_queues=4
	dev=`ls -d /sys/bus/pseudo/drivers/scsi_debug/adapter*/host*/target*/*/block/* | head -1 | xargs basename`
	fio --filename=/dev/"$dev" --direct=1 --rw=randrw --bs=4k --iodepth=1 \
       		--runtime=100 --numjobs=40 --time_based --name=test \
        	--ioengine=libaio

Fix the issue by adding one explicit barrier in blk_mq_mark_tag_wait(), which
is just fine in case of running out of tag.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26672 | drm/amdgpu: Fix variable &amp;#x27;mca_funcs&amp;#x27; dereferenced before NULL check in &amp;#x27;amdgpu_mca_smu_get_mca_entry()&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26672</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: Fix variable 'mca_funcs' dereferenced before NULL check in 'amdgpu_mca_smu_get_mca_entry()'

Fixes the below:

drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/amdgpu_mca.c:377 amdgpu_mca_smu_get_mca_entry() warn: variable dereferenced before check 'mca_funcs' (see line 368)

357 int amdgpu_mca_smu_get_mca_entry(struct amdgpu_device *adev,
				     enum amdgpu_mca_error_type type,
358                                  int idx, struct mca_bank_entry *entry)
359 {
360         const struct amdgpu_mca_smu_funcs *mca_funcs =
						adev-&gt;mca.mca_funcs;
361         int count;
362
363         switch (type) {
364         case AMDGPU_MCA_ERROR_TYPE_UE:
365                 count = mca_funcs-&gt;max_ue_count;

mca_funcs is dereferenced here.

366                 break;
367         case AMDGPU_MCA_ERROR_TYPE_CE:
368                 count = mca_funcs-&gt;max_ce_count;

mca_funcs is dereferenced here.

369                 break;
370         default:
371                 return -EINVAL;
372         }
373
374         if (idx &gt;= count)
375                 return -EINVAL;
376
377         if (mca_funcs &amp;&amp; mca_funcs-&gt;mca_get_mca_entry)
	        ^^^^^^^^^

Checked too late!</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2839 | The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'colibri_post_title' shortcode i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2839</link><description>The Colibri Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'colibri_post_title' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.263 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes such as 'heading_type'. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2925 | The Beaver Builder  WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button Widget...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2925</link><description>The Beaver Builder  WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Button Widget in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26668 | netfilter: nft_limit: reject configurations that cause integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26668</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nft_limit: reject configurations that cause integer overflow

Reject bogus configs where internal token counter wraps around.
This only occurs with very very large requests, such as 17gbyte/s.

Its better to reject this rather than having incorrect ratelimit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26669 | net/sched: flower: Fix chain template offload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26669</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: flower: Fix chain template offload

When a qdisc is deleted from a net device the stack instructs the
underlying driver to remove its flow offload callback from the
associated filter block using the 'FLOW_BLOCK_UNBIND' command. The stack
then continues to replay the removal of the filters in the block for
this driver by iterating over the chains in the block and invoking the
'reoffload' operation of the classifier being used. In turn, the
classifier in its 'reoffload' operation prepares and emits a
'FLOW_CLS_DESTROY' command for each filter.

However, the stack does not do the same for chain templates and the
underlying driver never receives a 'FLOW_CLS_TMPLT_DESTROY' command when
a qdisc is deleted. This results in a memory leak [1] which can be
reproduced using [2].

Fix by introducing a 'tmplt_reoffload' operation and have the stack
invoke it with the appropriate arguments as part of the replay.
Implement the operation in the sole classifier that supports chain
templates (flower) by emitting the 'FLOW_CLS_TMPLT_{CREATE,DESTROY}'
command based on whether a flow offload callback is being bound to a
filter block or being unbound from one.

As far as I can tell, the issue happens since cited commit which
reordered tcf_block_offload_unbind() before tcf_block_flush_all_chains()
in __tcf_block_put(). The order cannot be reversed as the filter block
is expected to be freed after flushing all the chains.

[1]
unreferenced object 0xffff888107e28800 (size 2048):
  comm "tc", pid 1079, jiffies 4294958525 (age 3074.287s)
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    b1 a6 7c 11 81 88 ff ff e0 5b b3 10 81 88 ff ff  ..|......[......
    01 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 e0 aa b0 84 ff ff ff ff  ................
  backtrace:
    [&lt;ffffffff81c06a68&gt;] __kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x1e8/0x320
    [&lt;ffffffff81ab374e&gt;] __kmalloc+0x4e/0x90
    [&lt;ffffffff832aec6d&gt;] mlxsw_sp_acl_ruleset_get+0x34d/0x7a0
    [&lt;ffffffff832bc195&gt;] mlxsw_sp_flower_tmplt_create+0x145/0x180
    [&lt;ffffffff832b2e1a&gt;] mlxsw_sp_flow_block_cb+0x1ea/0x280
    [&lt;ffffffff83a10613&gt;] tc_setup_cb_call+0x183/0x340
    [&lt;ffffffff83a9f85a&gt;] fl_tmplt_create+0x3da/0x4c0
    [&lt;ffffffff83a22435&gt;] tc_ctl_chain+0xa15/0x1170
    [&lt;ffffffff838a863c&gt;] rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x3cc/0xed0
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac87f0&gt;] netlink_rcv_skb+0x170/0x440
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac6270&gt;] netlink_unicast+0x540/0x820
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac6e28&gt;] netlink_sendmsg+0x8d8/0xda0
    [&lt;ffffffff83793def&gt;] ____sys_sendmsg+0x30f/0xa80
    [&lt;ffffffff8379d29a&gt;] ___sys_sendmsg+0x13a/0x1e0
    [&lt;ffffffff8379d50c&gt;] __sys_sendmsg+0x11c/0x1f0
    [&lt;ffffffff843b9ce0&gt;] do_syscall_64+0x40/0xe0
unreferenced object 0xffff88816d2c0400 (size 1024):
  comm "tc", pid 1079, jiffies 4294958525 (age 3074.287s)
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    40 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 57 f6 38 be 00 00 00 00  @.......W.8.....
    10 04 2c 6d 81 88 ff ff 10 04 2c 6d 81 88 ff ff  ..,m......,m....
  backtrace:
    [&lt;ffffffff81c06a68&gt;] __kmem_cache_alloc_node+0x1e8/0x320
    [&lt;ffffffff81ab36c1&gt;] __kmalloc_node+0x51/0x90
    [&lt;ffffffff81a8ed96&gt;] kvmalloc_node+0xa6/0x1f0
    [&lt;ffffffff82827d03&gt;] bucket_table_alloc.isra.0+0x83/0x460
    [&lt;ffffffff82828d2b&gt;] rhashtable_init+0x43b/0x7c0
    [&lt;ffffffff832aed48&gt;] mlxsw_sp_acl_ruleset_get+0x428/0x7a0
    [&lt;ffffffff832bc195&gt;] mlxsw_sp_flower_tmplt_create+0x145/0x180
    [&lt;ffffffff832b2e1a&gt;] mlxsw_sp_flow_block_cb+0x1ea/0x280
    [&lt;ffffffff83a10613&gt;] tc_setup_cb_call+0x183/0x340
    [&lt;ffffffff83a9f85a&gt;] fl_tmplt_create+0x3da/0x4c0
    [&lt;ffffffff83a22435&gt;] tc_ctl_chain+0xa15/0x1170
    [&lt;ffffffff838a863c&gt;] rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x3cc/0xed0
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac87f0&gt;] netlink_rcv_skb+0x170/0x440
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac6270&gt;] netlink_unicast+0x540/0x820
    [&lt;ffffffff83ac6e28&gt;] netlink_sendmsg+0x8d8/0xda0
    [&lt;ffffffff83793def&gt;] ____sys_sendmsg+0x30f/0xa80

[2]
 # tc qdisc add dev swp1 clsact
 # tc chain add dev swp1 ingress proto ip chain 1 flower dst_ip 0.0.0.0/32
 # tc qdisc del dev
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26670 | arm64: entry: fix ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26670</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

arm64: entry: fix ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD

Currently the ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD workaround isn't
quite right, as it is supposed to be applied after the last explicit
memory access, but is immediately followed by an LDR.

The ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD workaround is used to
handle Cortex-A520 erratum 2966298 and Cortex-A510 erratum 3117295,
which are described in:

* https://developer.arm.com/documentation/SDEN2444153/0600/?lang=en
* https://developer.arm.com/documentation/SDEN1873361/1600/?lang=en

In both cases the workaround is described as:

| If pagetable isolation is disabled, the context switch logic in the
| kernel can be updated to execute the following sequence on affected
| cores before exiting to EL0, and after all explicit memory accesses:
|
| 1. A non-shareable TLBI to any context and/or address, including
|    unused contexts or addresses, such as a `TLBI VALE1 Xzr`.
|
| 2. A DSB NSH to guarantee completion of the TLBI.

The important part being that the TLBI+DSB must be placed "after all
explicit memory accesses".

Unfortunately, as-implemented, the TLBI+DSB is immediately followed by
an LDR, as we have:

| alternative_if ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD
| 	tlbi	vale1, xzr
| 	dsb	nsh
| alternative_else_nop_endif
| alternative_if_not ARM64_UNMAP_KERNEL_AT_EL0
| 	ldr	lr, [sp, #S_LR]
| 	add	sp, sp, #PT_REGS_SIZE		// restore sp
| 	eret
| alternative_else_nop_endif
|
| [ ... KPTI exception return path ... ]

This patch fixes this by reworking the logic to place the TLBI+DSB
immediately before the ERET, after all explicit memory accesses.

The ERET is currently in a separate alternative block, and alternatives
cannot be nested. To account for this, the alternative block for
ARM64_UNMAP_KERNEL_AT_EL0 is replaced with a single alternative branch
to skip the KPTI logic, with the new shape of the logic being:

| alternative_insn "b .L_skip_tramp_exit_\@", nop, ARM64_UNMAP_KERNEL_AT_EL0
| 	[ ... KPTI exception return path ... ]
| .L_skip_tramp_exit_\@:
|
| 	ldr	lr, [sp, #S_LR]
| 	add	sp, sp, #PT_REGS_SIZE		// restore sp
|
| alternative_if ARM64_WORKAROUND_SPECULATIVE_UNPRIV_LOAD
| 	tlbi	vale1, xzr
| 	dsb	nsh
| alternative_else_nop_endif
| 	eret

The new structure means that the workaround is only applied when KPTI is
not in use; this is fine as noted in the documented implications of the
erratum:

| Pagetable isolation between EL0 and higher level ELs prevents the
| issue from occurring.

... and as per the workaround description quoted above, the workaround
is only necessary "If pagetable isolation is disabled".</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52630 | blk-iocost: Fix an UBSAN shift-out-of-bounds warning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52630</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

blk-iocost: Fix an UBSAN shift-out-of-bounds warning

When iocg_kick_delay() is called from a CPU different than the one which set
the delay, @now may be in the past of @iocg-&gt;delay_at leading to the
following warning:

  UBSAN: shift-out-of-bounds in block/blk-iocost.c:1359:23
  shift exponent 18446744073709 is too large for 64-bit type 'u64' (aka 'unsigned long long')
  ...
  Call Trace:
   &lt;TASK&gt;
   dump_stack_lvl+0x79/0xc0
   __ubsan_handle_shift_out_of_bounds+0x2ab/0x300
   iocg_kick_delay+0x222/0x230
   ioc_rqos_merge+0x1d7/0x2c0
   __rq_qos_merge+0x2c/0x80
   bio_attempt_back_merge+0x83/0x190
   blk_attempt_plug_merge+0x101/0x150
   blk_mq_submit_bio+0x2b1/0x720
   submit_bio_noacct_nocheck+0x320/0x3e0
   __swap_writepage+0x2ab/0x9d0

The underflow itself doesn't really affect the behavior in any meaningful
way; however, the past timestamp may exaggerate the delay amount calculated
later in the code, which shouldn't be a material problem given the nature of
the delay mechanism.

If @now is in the past, this CPU is racing another CPU which recently set up
the delay and there's nothing this CPU can contribute w.r.t. the delay.
Let's bail early from iocg_kick_delay() in such cases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52631 | fs/ntfs3: Fix an NULL dereference bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52631</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/ntfs3: Fix an NULL dereference bug

The issue here is when this is called from ntfs_load_attr_list().  The
"size" comes from le32_to_cpu(attr-&gt;res.data_size) so it can't overflow
on a 64bit systems but on 32bit systems the "+ 1023" can overflow and
the result is zero.  This means that the kmalloc will succeed by
returning the ZERO_SIZE_PTR and then the memcpy() will crash with an
Oops on the next line.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21834 | Arkui has a type confusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21834</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through type confusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22092 | Bundlemanager has an authentication bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22092</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a remote attacker bypass permission verification to install apps, although these require user action.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22098 | AVSession has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22098</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in any apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22177 | Audio has an improper preservation of permissions vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22177</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause apps crash through get permission.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22180 | Camera has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22180</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24581 | Arkcompiler runtime has an out-of-bounds write vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24581</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution through out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26658 | bcachefs: grab s_umount only if snapshotting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26658</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bcachefs: grab s_umount only if snapshotting

When I was testing mongodb over bcachefs with compression,
there is a lockdep warning when snapshotting mongodb data volume.

$ cat test.sh
prog=bcachefs

$prog subvolume create /mnt/data
$prog subvolume create /mnt/data/snapshots

while true;do
    $prog subvolume snapshot /mnt/data /mnt/data/snapshots/$(date +%s)
    sleep 1s
done

$ cat /etc/mongodb.conf
systemLog:
  destination: file
  logAppend: true
  path: /mnt/data/mongod.log

storage:
  dbPath: /mnt/data/

lockdep reports:
[ 3437.452330] ======================================================
[ 3437.452750] WARNING: possible circular locking dependency detected
[ 3437.453168] 6.7.0-rc7-custom+ #85 Tainted: G            E
[ 3437.453562] ------------------------------------------------------
[ 3437.453981] bcachefs/35533 is trying to acquire lock:
[ 3437.454325] ffffa0a02b2b1418 (sb_writers#10){.+.+}-{0:0}, at: filename_create+0x62/0x190
[ 3437.454875]
               but task is already holding lock:
[ 3437.455268] ffffa0a02b2b10e0 (&amp;type-&gt;s_umount_key#48){.+.+}-{3:3}, at: bch2_fs_file_ioctl+0x232/0xc90 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.456009]
               which lock already depends on the new lock.

[ 3437.456553]
               the existing dependency chain (in reverse order) is:
[ 3437.457054]
               -&gt; #3 (&amp;type-&gt;s_umount_key#48){.+.+}-{3:3}:
[ 3437.457507]        down_read+0x3e/0x170
[ 3437.457772]        bch2_fs_file_ioctl+0x232/0xc90 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.458206]        __x64_sys_ioctl+0x93/0xd0
[ 3437.458498]        do_syscall_64+0x42/0xf0
[ 3437.458779]        entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76
[ 3437.459155]
               -&gt; #2 (&amp;c-&gt;snapshot_create_lock){++++}-{3:3}:
[ 3437.459615]        down_read+0x3e/0x170
[ 3437.459878]        bch2_truncate+0x82/0x110 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.460276]        bchfs_truncate+0x254/0x3c0 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.460686]        notify_change+0x1f1/0x4a0
[ 3437.461283]        do_truncate+0x7f/0xd0
[ 3437.461555]        path_openat+0xa57/0xce0
[ 3437.461836]        do_filp_open+0xb4/0x160
[ 3437.462116]        do_sys_openat2+0x91/0xc0
[ 3437.462402]        __x64_sys_openat+0x53/0xa0
[ 3437.462701]        do_syscall_64+0x42/0xf0
[ 3437.462982]        entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76
[ 3437.463359]
               -&gt; #1 (&amp;sb-&gt;s_type-&gt;i_mutex_key#15){+.+.}-{3:3}:
[ 3437.463843]        down_write+0x3b/0xc0
[ 3437.464223]        bch2_write_iter+0x5b/0xcc0 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.464493]        vfs_write+0x21b/0x4c0
[ 3437.464653]        ksys_write+0x69/0xf0
[ 3437.464839]        do_syscall_64+0x42/0xf0
[ 3437.465009]        entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76
[ 3437.465231]
               -&gt; #0 (sb_writers#10){.+.+}-{0:0}:
[ 3437.465471]        __lock_acquire+0x1455/0x21b0
[ 3437.465656]        lock_acquire+0xc6/0x2b0
[ 3437.465822]        mnt_want_write+0x46/0x1a0
[ 3437.465996]        filename_create+0x62/0x190
[ 3437.466175]        user_path_create+0x2d/0x50
[ 3437.466352]        bch2_fs_file_ioctl+0x2ec/0xc90 [bcachefs]
[ 3437.466617]        __x64_sys_ioctl+0x93/0xd0
[ 3437.466791]        do_syscall_64+0x42/0xf0
[ 3437.466957]        entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x6e/0x76
[ 3437.467180]
               other info that might help us debug this:

[ 3437.469670] 2 locks held by bcachefs/35533:
               other info that might help us debug this:

[ 3437.467507] Chain exists of:
                 sb_writers#10 --&gt; &amp;c-&gt;snapshot_create_lock --&gt; &amp;type-&gt;s_umount_key#48

[ 3437.467979]  Possible unsafe locking scenario:

[ 3437.468223]        CPU0                    CPU1
[ 3437.468405]        ----                    ----
[ 3437.468585]   rlock(&amp;type-&gt;s_umount_key#48);
[ 3437.468758]                                lock(&amp;c-&gt;snapshot_create_lock);
[ 3437.469030]                                lock(&amp;type-&gt;s_umount_key#48);
[ 3437.469291]   rlock(sb_writers#10);
[ 3437.469434]
                *** DEADLOCK ***

[ 3437.469
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26659 | xhci: handle isoc Babble and Buffer Overrun events properly</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26659</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xhci: handle isoc Babble and Buffer Overrun events properly

xHCI 4.9 explicitly forbids assuming that the xHC has released its
ownership of a multi-TRB TD when it reports an error on one of the
early TRBs. Yet the driver makes such assumption and releases the TD,
allowing the remaining TRBs to be freed or overwritten by new TDs.

The xHC should also report completion of the final TRB due to its IOC
flag being set by us, regardless of prior errors. This event cannot
be recognized if the TD has already been freed earlier, resulting in
"Transfer event TRB DMA ptr not part of current TD" error message.

Fix this by reusing the logic for processing isoc Transaction Errors.
This also handles hosts which fail to report the final completion.

Fix transfer length reporting on Babble errors. They may be caused by
device malfunction, no guarantee that the buffer has been filled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26660 | drm/amd/display: Implement bounds check for stream encoder creation in DCN301</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26660</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Implement bounds check for stream encoder creation in DCN301

'stream_enc_regs' array is an array of dcn10_stream_enc_registers
structures. The array is initialized with four elements, corresponding
to the four calls to stream_enc_regs() in the array initializer. This
means that valid indices for this array are 0, 1, 2, and 3.

The error message 'stream_enc_regs' 4 &lt;= 5 below, is indicating that
there is an attempt to access this array with an index of 5, which is
out of bounds. This could lead to undefined behavior

Here, eng_id is used as an index to access the stream_enc_regs array. If
eng_id is 5, this would result in an out-of-bounds access on the
stream_enc_regs array.

Thus fixing Buffer overflow error in dcn301_stream_encoder_create
reported by Smatch:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/../display/dc/resource/dcn301/dcn301_resource.c:1011 dcn301_stream_encoder_create() error: buffer overflow 'stream_enc_regs' 4 &lt;= 5</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26661 | drm/amd/display: Add NULL test for &amp;#x27;timing generator&amp;#x27; in &amp;#x27;dcn21_set_pipe()&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26661</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Add NULL test for 'timing generator' in 'dcn21_set_pipe()'

In "u32 otg_inst = pipe_ctx-&gt;stream_res.tg-&gt;inst;"
pipe_ctx-&gt;stream_res.tg could be NULL, it is relying on the caller to
ensure the tg is not NULL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26662 | drm/amd/display: Fix &amp;#x27;panel_cntl&amp;#x27; could be null in &amp;#x27;dcn21_set_backlight_level()&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26662</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amd/display: Fix 'panel_cntl' could be null in 'dcn21_set_backlight_level()'

'panel_cntl' structure used to control the display panel could be null,
dereferencing it could lead to a null pointer access.

Fixes the below:
drivers/gpu/drm/amd/amdgpu/../display/dc/hwss/dcn21/dcn21_hwseq.c:269 dcn21_set_backlight_level() error: we previously assumed 'panel_cntl' could be null (see line 250)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26663 | tipc: Check the bearer type before calling tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26663</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tipc: Check the bearer type before calling tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add()

syzbot reported the following general protection fault [1]:

general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000010: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN
KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000080-0x0000000000000087]
...
RIP: 0010:tipc_udp_is_known_peer+0x9c/0x250 net/tipc/udp_media.c:291
...
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK&gt;
 tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add+0x212/0x2f0 net/tipc/udp_media.c:646
 tipc_nl_bearer_add+0x21e/0x360 net/tipc/bearer.c:1089
 genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x1fc/0x2e0 net/netlink/genetlink.c:972
 genl_family_rcv_msg net/netlink/genetlink.c:1052 [inline]
 genl_rcv_msg+0x561/0x800 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1067
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x16b/0x440 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2544
 genl_rcv+0x28/0x40 net/netlink/genetlink.c:1076
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1341 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x53b/0x810 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1367
 netlink_sendmsg+0x8b7/0xd70 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1909
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:730 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0xd5/0x180 net/socket.c:745
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x6ac/0x940 net/socket.c:2584
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x135/0x1d0 net/socket.c:2638
 __sys_sendmsg+0x117/0x1e0 net/socket.c:2667
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0x40/0x110 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x63/0x6b

The cause of this issue is that when tipc_nl_bearer_add() is called with
the TIPC_NLA_BEARER_UDP_OPTS attribute, tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add() is called
even if the bearer is not UDP.

tipc_udp_is_known_peer() called by tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add() assumes that
the media_ptr field of the tipc_bearer has an udp_bearer type object, so
the function goes crazy for non-UDP bearers.

This patch fixes the issue by checking the bearer type before calling
tipc_udp_nl_bearer_add() in tipc_nl_bearer_add().</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26664 | hwmon: (coretemp) Fix out-of-bounds memory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26664</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hwmon: (coretemp) Fix out-of-bounds memory access

Fix a bug that pdata-&gt;cpu_map[] is set before out-of-bounds check.
The problem might be triggered on systems with more than 128 cores per
package.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26665 | tunnels: fix out of bounds access when building IPv6 PMTU error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26665</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tunnels: fix out of bounds access when building IPv6 PMTU error

If the ICMPv6 error is built from a non-linear skb we get the following
splat,

  BUG: KASAN: slab-out-of-bounds in do_csum+0x220/0x240
  Read of size 4 at addr ffff88811d402c80 by task netperf/820
  CPU: 0 PID: 820 Comm: netperf Not tainted 6.8.0-rc1+ #543
  ...
   kasan_report+0xd8/0x110
   do_csum+0x220/0x240
   csum_partial+0xc/0x20
   skb_tunnel_check_pmtu+0xeb9/0x3280
   vxlan_xmit_one+0x14c2/0x4080
   vxlan_xmit+0xf61/0x5c00
   dev_hard_start_xmit+0xfb/0x510
   __dev_queue_xmit+0x7cd/0x32a0
   br_dev_queue_push_xmit+0x39d/0x6a0

Use skb_checksum instead of csum_partial who cannot deal with non-linear
SKBs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26666 | wifi: mac80211: fix RCU use in TDLS fast-xmit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26666</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: mac80211: fix RCU use in TDLS fast-xmit

This looks up the link under RCU protection, but isn't
guaranteed to actually have protection. Fix that.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26667 | drm/msm/dpu: check for valid hw_pp in dpu_encoder_helper_phys_cleanup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26667</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/msm/dpu: check for valid hw_pp in dpu_encoder_helper_phys_cleanup

The commit 8b45a26f2ba9 ("drm/msm/dpu: reserve cdm blocks for writeback
in case of YUV output") introduced a smatch warning about another
conditional block in dpu_encoder_helper_phys_cleanup() which had assumed
hw_pp will always be valid which may not necessarily be true.

Lets fix the other conditional block by making sure hw_pp is valid
before dereferencing it.

Patchwork: https://patchwork.freedesktop.org/patch/574878/</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28226 | Fs has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28226</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a remote attacker cause DOS through improper input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28951 | Arkcompiler runtime has a use after free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28951</link><description>in OpenHarmony v4.0.0 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in pre-installed apps through use after free.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29074 | Telephony has an improper input validation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29074</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker arbitrary code execution in any apps through improper input.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29086 | Arkcompiler runtime has a stack overflow svulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29086</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.4 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26656 | drm/amdgpu: fix use-after-free bug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26656</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/amdgpu: fix use-after-free bug

The bug can be triggered by sending a single amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl
to the AMDGPU DRM driver on any ASICs with an invalid address and size.
The bug was reported by Joonkyo Jung &lt;joonkyoj@yonsei.ac.kr&gt;.
For example the following code:

static void Syzkaller1(int fd)
{
	struct drm_amdgpu_gem_userptr arg;
	int ret;

	arg.addr = 0xffffffffffff0000;
	arg.size = 0x80000000; /*2 Gb*/
	arg.flags = 0x7;
	ret = drmIoctl(fd, 0xc1186451/*amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl*/, &amp;arg);
}

Due to the address and size are not valid there is a failure in
amdgpu_hmm_register-&gt;mmu_interval_notifier_insert-&gt;__mmu_interval_notifier_insert-&gt;
check_shl_overflow, but we even the amdgpu_hmm_register failure we still call
amdgpu_hmm_unregister into  amdgpu_gem_object_free which causes access to a bad address.
The following stack is below when the issue is reproduced when Kazan is enabled:

[  +0.000014] Hardware name: ASUS System Product Name/ROG STRIX B550-F GAMING (WI-FI), BIOS 1401 12/03/2020
[  +0.000009] RIP: 0010:mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x327/0x340
[  +0.000017] Code: ff ff 49 89 44 24 08 48 b8 00 01 00 00 00 00 ad de 4c 89 f7 49 89 47 40 48 83 c0 22 49 89 47 48 e8 ce d1 2d 01 e9 32 ff ff ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b e9 16 ff ff ff 4c 89 ef e8 fa 14 b3 ff e9 36 ff ff ff e8 80
[  +0.000014] RSP: 0018:ffffc90002657988 EFLAGS: 00010246
[  +0.000013] RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 1ffff920004caf35 RCX: ffffffff8160565b
[  +0.000011] RDX: dffffc0000000000 RSI: 0000000000000004 RDI: ffff8881a9f78260
[  +0.000010] RBP: ffffc90002657a70 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: fffff520004caf25
[  +0.000010] R10: 0000000000000003 R11: ffffffff8161d1d6 R12: ffff88810e988c00
[  +0.000010] R13: ffff888126fb5a00 R14: ffff88810e988c0c R15: ffff8881a9f78260
[  +0.000011] FS:  00007ff9ec848540(0000) GS:ffff8883cc880000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  +0.000012] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  +0.000010] CR2: 000055b3f7e14328 CR3: 00000001b5770000 CR4: 0000000000350ef0
[  +0.000010] Call Trace:
[  +0.000006]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[  +0.000007]  ? show_regs+0x6a/0x80
[  +0.000018]  ? __warn+0xa5/0x1b0
[  +0.000019]  ? mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x327/0x340
[  +0.000018]  ? report_bug+0x24a/0x290
[  +0.000022]  ? handle_bug+0x46/0x90
[  +0.000015]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x19/0x50
[  +0.000016]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1b/0x20
[  +0.000017]  ? kasan_save_stack+0x26/0x50
[  +0.000017]  ? mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x23b/0x340
[  +0.000019]  ? mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x327/0x340
[  +0.000019]  ? mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x23b/0x340
[  +0.000020]  ? __pfx_mmu_interval_notifier_remove+0x10/0x10
[  +0.000017]  ? kasan_save_alloc_info+0x1e/0x30
[  +0.000018]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000014]  ? __kasan_kmalloc+0xb1/0xc0
[  +0.000018]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000013]  ? __kasan_check_read+0x11/0x20
[  +0.000020]  amdgpu_hmm_unregister+0x34/0x50 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004695]  amdgpu_gem_object_free+0x66/0xa0 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004534]  ? __pfx_amdgpu_gem_object_free+0x10/0x10 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004291]  ? do_syscall_64+0x5f/0xe0
[  +0.000023]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000017]  drm_gem_object_free+0x3b/0x50 [drm]
[  +0.000489]  amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl+0x306/0x500 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004295]  ? __pfx_amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl+0x10/0x10 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004270]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000014]  ? __this_cpu_preempt_check+0x13/0x20
[  +0.000015]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000013]  ? sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x57/0xc0
[  +0.000020]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.000014]  ? asm_sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x1b/0x20
[  +0.000022]  ? drm_ioctl_kernel+0x17b/0x1f0 [drm]
[  +0.000496]  ? __pfx_amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl+0x10/0x10 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004272]  ? drm_ioctl_kernel+0x190/0x1f0 [drm]
[  +0.000492]  drm_ioctl_kernel+0x140/0x1f0 [drm]
[  +0.000497]  ? __pfx_amdgpu_gem_userptr_ioctl+0x10/0x10 [amdgpu]
[  +0.004297]  ? __pfx_drm_ioctl_kernel+0x10/0x10 [d
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26657 | drm/sched: fix null-ptr-deref in init entity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26657</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/sched: fix null-ptr-deref in init entity

The bug can be triggered by sending an amdgpu_cs_wait_ioctl
to the AMDGPU DRM driver on any ASICs with valid context.
The bug was reported by Joonkyo Jung &lt;joonkyoj@yonsei.ac.kr&gt;.
For example the following code:

    static void Syzkaller2(int fd)
    {
	union drm_amdgpu_ctx arg1;
	union drm_amdgpu_wait_cs arg2;

	arg1.in.op = AMDGPU_CTX_OP_ALLOC_CTX;
	ret = drmIoctl(fd, 0x140106442 /* amdgpu_ctx_ioctl */, &amp;arg1);

	arg2.in.handle = 0x0;
	arg2.in.timeout = 0x2000000000000;
	arg2.in.ip_type = AMD_IP_VPE /* 0x9 */;
	arg2-&gt;in.ip_instance = 0x0;
	arg2.in.ring = 0x0;
	arg2.in.ctx_id = arg1.out.alloc.ctx_id;

	drmIoctl(fd, 0xc0206449 /* AMDGPU_WAIT_CS * /, &amp;arg2);
    }

The ioctl AMDGPU_WAIT_CS without previously submitted job could be assumed that
the error should be returned, but the following commit 1decbf6bb0b4dc56c9da6c5e57b994ebfc2be3aa
modified the logic and allowed to have sched_rq equal to NULL.

As a result when there is no job the ioctl AMDGPU_WAIT_CS returns success.
The change fixes null-ptr-deref in init entity and the stack below demonstrates
the error condition:

[  +0.000007] BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000028
[  +0.007086] #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
[  +0.005234] #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
[  +0.005232] PGD 0 P4D 0
[  +0.002501] Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN NOPTI
[  +0.005034] CPU: 10 PID: 9229 Comm: amd_basic Tainted: G    B   W    L     6.7.0+ #4
[  +0.007797] Hardware name: ASUS System Product Name/ROG STRIX B550-F GAMING (WI-FI), BIOS 1401 12/03/2020
[  +0.009798] RIP: 0010:drm_sched_entity_init+0x2d3/0x420 [gpu_sched]
[  +0.006426] Code: 80 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 e8 1a 81 82 e0 49 89 9c 24 c0 00 00 00 4c 89 ef e8 4a 80 82 e0 49 8b 5d 00 48 8d 7b 28 e8 3d 80 82 e0 &lt;48&gt; 83 7b 28 00 0f 84 28 01 00 00 4d 8d ac 24 98 00 00 00 49 8d 5c
[  +0.019094] RSP: 0018:ffffc90014c1fa40 EFLAGS: 00010282
[  +0.005237] RAX: 0000000000000001 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: ffffffff8113f3fa
[  +0.007326] RDX: fffffbfff0a7889d RSI: 0000000000000008 RDI: ffffffff853c44e0
[  +0.007264] RBP: ffffc90014c1fa80 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: fffffbfff0a7889c
[  +0.007266] R10: ffffffff853c44e7 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: ffff8881a719b010
[  +0.007263] R13: ffff88810d412748 R14: 0000000000000002 R15: 0000000000000000
[  +0.007264] FS:  00007ffff7045540(0000) GS:ffff8883cc900000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[  +0.008236] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[  +0.005851] CR2: 0000000000000028 CR3: 000000011912e000 CR4: 0000000000350ef0
[  +0.007175] Call Trace:
[  +0.002561]  &lt;TASK&gt;
[  +0.002141]  ? show_regs+0x6a/0x80
[  +0.003473]  ? __die+0x25/0x70
[  +0.003124]  ? page_fault_oops+0x214/0x720
[  +0.004179]  ? preempt_count_sub+0x18/0xc0
[  +0.004093]  ? __pfx_page_fault_oops+0x10/0x10
[  +0.004590]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.004000]  ? vprintk_default+0x1d/0x30
[  +0.004063]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.004087]  ? vprintk+0x5c/0x90
[  +0.003296]  ? drm_sched_entity_init+0x2d3/0x420 [gpu_sched]
[  +0.005807]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.004090]  ? _printk+0xb3/0xe0
[  +0.003293]  ? __pfx__printk+0x10/0x10
[  +0.003735]  ? asm_sysvec_apic_timer_interrupt+0x1b/0x20
[  +0.005482]  ? do_user_addr_fault+0x345/0x770
[  +0.004361]  ? exc_page_fault+0x64/0xf0
[  +0.003972]  ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x27/0x30
[  +0.004271]  ? add_taint+0x2a/0xa0
[  +0.003476]  ? drm_sched_entity_init+0x2d3/0x420 [gpu_sched]
[  +0.005812]  amdgpu_ctx_get_entity+0x3f9/0x770 [amdgpu]
[  +0.009530]  ? finish_task_switch.isra.0+0x129/0x470
[  +0.005068]  ? __pfx_amdgpu_ctx_get_entity+0x10/0x10 [amdgpu]
[  +0.010063]  ? __kasan_check_write+0x14/0x20
[  +0.004356]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.004001]  ? mutex_unlock+0x81/0xd0
[  +0.003802]  ? srso_return_thunk+0x5/0x5f
[  +0.004096]  amdgpu_cs_wait_ioctl+0xf6/0x270 [amdgpu]
[  +0.009355]  ? __pfx_
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:19:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1504 | The SecuPress Free  WordPress Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and includin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1504</link><description>The SecuPress Free  WordPress Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.5.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the secupress_blackhole_ban_ip() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to block a user's IP via a forged request granted they can trick the user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:39:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2791 | The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2791</link><description>The Metform Elementor Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2924 | The Creative Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2924</link><description>The Creative Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:39:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1274 | My Calendar &amp;lt; 3.4.24 - Authenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1274</link><description>The My Calendar WordPress plugin before 3.4.24 does not sanitise and escape some parameters, which could allow users with a role as low as Subscriber to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks (depending on the permissions set by the admin)</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:25:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2369 | Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt; 3.1.7 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2369</link><description>The Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.1.7 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25187 | Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in 71cms v1.0.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25187</link><description>Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in 71cms v1.0.0, allows remote unauthenticated attackers to obtain sensitive information via getweather.html.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20842 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in handling apdu of libsec-ril prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20842</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in handling apdu of libsec-ril prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20843 | Out-of-bound write vulnerability in command parsing implementation of libIfaaCa prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20843</link><description>Out-of-bound write vulnerability in command parsing implementation of libIfaaCa prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20844 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while parsing remaining codewords in libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20844</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while parsing remaining codewords in libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20845 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while releasing memory in libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20845</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while releasing memory in libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20846 | Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while decoding hcr of libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20846</link><description>Out-of-bounds write vulnerability while decoding hcr of libsavsac.so prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20847 | Improper Access Control vulnerability in StorageManagerService prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read sdcard informa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20847</link><description>Improper Access Control vulnerability in StorageManagerService prior to SMR Apr-2024 Release 1 allows local attackers to read sdcard information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20848 | Out-of-bound Write vulnerability in text parsing implementation of libsdffextractor prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20848</link><description>Out-of-bound Write vulnerability in text parsing implementation of libsdffextractor prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20849 | Out-of-bound Write vulnerability in chunk parsing implementation of libsdffextractor prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20849</link><description>Out-of-bound Write vulnerability in chunk parsing implementation of libsdffextractor prior to SMR Apr-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20850 | Use of Implicit Intent for Sensitive Communication in Samsung Pay prior to version 5.4.99 allows local attackers to access information of Sa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20850</link><description>Use of Implicit Intent for Sensitive Communication in Samsung Pay prior to version 5.4.99 allows local attackers to access information of Samsung Pay.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20851 | Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Data Store prior to version 5.3.00.4 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20851</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Data Store prior to version 5.3.00.4 allows local attackers to launch arbitrary activity with Samsung Data Store privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20852 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.13.22 allows local attackers to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20852</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in SmartThings prior to version 1.8.13.22 allows local attackers to access testing configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20853 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in ThemeStore prior to 5.3.05.2 allows local attackers to write arbitrar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20853</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in ThemeStore prior to 5.3.05.2 allows local attackers to write arbitrary files to sandbox of ThemeStore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20854 | Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in Samsung Camera prior to versions 12.1.0.31 in Android 12, 13.1.02.07 in Androi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20854</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient privileges vulnerability in Samsung Camera prior to versions 12.1.0.31 in Android 12, 13.1.02.07 in Android 13, and 14.0.01.06 in Android 14 allows local attackers to access image data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:08:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3160 | Intelbras HDCVI 1016 HTTP GET Request cap.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3160</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Intelbras MHDX 1004, MHDX 1008, MHDX 1016, MHDX 5016, HDCVI 1008 and HDCVI 1016 up to 20240401. This affects an unknown part of the file /cap.js of the component HTTP GET Request Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier VDB-258933 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor explains that they do not classify the information shown as sensitive and therefore there is no vulnerability which is about to harm the user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3148 | DedeCMS makehtml_archives_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3148</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in DedeCMS 5.7.112. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file dede/makehtml_archives_action.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258923. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3146 | DedeCMS makehtml_rss_action.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3146</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in DedeCMS 5.7. This affects an unknown part of the file /src/dede/makehtml_rss_action.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258921 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3147 | DedeCMS makehtml_map.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3147</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in DedeCMS 5.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /src/dede/makehtml_map.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258922 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3144 | DedeCMS makehtml_spec.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3144</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/makehtml_spec.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258919. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3145 | DedeCMS makehtml_js_action.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3145</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /src/dede/makehtml_js_action.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258920. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3137 | Improper Privilege Management in uvdesk/community-skeleton</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3137</link><description>Improper Privilege Management in uvdesk/community-skeleton</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3142 | Clavister E10/E80 Setting cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Clavister E10 and E80 up to 20240323 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258917 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3143 | DedeCMS member_rank.php cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3143</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS 5.7. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /src/dede/member_rank.php. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258918 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:48:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27334 | Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27334</link><description>Kofax Power PDF JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files.
The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21978.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27333 | Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27333</link><description>Kofax Power PDF GIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of Kofax Power PDF. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of GIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-21976.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3140 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3140</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument middlename leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258915.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3141 | Clavister E10/E80 Misc Settings Page MiscSettings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3141</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Clavister E10 and E80 up to 20240323 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /?Page=Node&amp;OBJ=/System/AdvancedSettings/DeviceSettings/MiscSettings of the component Misc Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument WatchdogTimerTime/BufFloodRebootTime/MaxPipeUsers/AVCache Lifetime/HTTPipeliningMaxReq/Reassembly MaxConnections/Reassembly MaxProcessingMem/ScrSaveTime leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258916. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3139 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System save_users improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3139</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is the function save_users of the file /classes/Users.php?f=save. The manipulation of the argument id leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258914 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 22:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3138 | francoisjacquet RosarioSIS Add Portal Note cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3138</link><description>** DISPUTED ** A vulnerability was found in francoisjacquet RosarioSIS 11.5.1. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Add Portal Note. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258911. NOTE: The vendor explains that the PDF is opened by the browser app in a sandbox, so no data from the website should be accessible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 22:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27327 | PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27327</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor PDF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of PDF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a write  past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22277.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27328 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27328</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22280.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27329 | PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27329</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22285.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27330 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27330</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22286.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27331 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27331</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22287.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27332 | PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27332</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor JPG File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of JPG files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22288.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0637 | Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0637</link><description>Centreon updateDirectory SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateDirectory function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22294.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1179 | TP-Link Omada ER605 DHCPv6 Client Options Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1179</link><description>TP-Link Omada ER605 DHCPv6 Client Options Stack-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of TP-Link Omada ER605 routers. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the handling of DHCP options. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a fixed-length stack-based buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of root. Was ZDI-CAN-22420.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1863 | Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1863</link><description>Sante PACS Server Token Endpoint SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Sante PACS Server. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the processing of HTTP requests on port 3000. When parsing the token parameter, the process does not properly validate a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of NETWORK SERVICE. Was ZDI-CAN-21539.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23115 | Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23115</link><description>Centreon updateGroups SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateGroups function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22295.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23116 | Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23116</link><description>Centreon updateLCARelation SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateLCARelation function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22296.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23117 | Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23117</link><description>Centreon updateContactServiceCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactServiceCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22297.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23118 | Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23118</link><description>Centreon updateContactHostCommands SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateContactHostCommands function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22298.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23119 | Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23119</link><description>Centreon insertGraphTemplate SQL Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Centreon. Authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the insertGraphTemplate function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to construct SQL queries. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the service account. Was ZDI-CAN-22339.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27323 | PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27323</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor Updater Improper Certificate Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the update functionality. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of the certificate presented by the server. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Was ZDI-CAN-22224.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27324 | PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27324</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor TIF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of TIF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22270.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27325 | PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27325</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor EMF File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of EMF files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22275.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27326 | PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27326</link><description>PDF-XChange Editor XPS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of PDF-XChange Editor. User interaction is required to exploit this vulnerability in that the target must visit a malicious page or open a malicious file.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of XPS files. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in a read past the end of an allocated object. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process. Was ZDI-CAN-22276.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:51:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3165 | Database Credential Exposure in the Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3165</link><description>System-&gt;Maintenance-&gt; Log Files in dotCMS dashboard is providing the username/password for database connections in the log output. Nevertheless, this is a moderate issue as it requires a backend admin as well as that dbs are locked down by environment. 

OWASP Top 10 - A05) Insecure Design

OWASP Top 10 - A05) Security Misconfiguration

OWASP Top 10 - A09) Security Logging and Monitoring Failure</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3164 | In dotCMS dashboard, the Tools and Log Files tabs under System  Maintenance Portlet, which is and always has been an Admin portlet, is acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3164</link><description>In dotCMS dashboard, the Tools and Log Files tabs under System  Maintenance Portlet, which is and always has been an Admin portlet, is accessible to anyone with that portlet and not just to CMS Admins. Users that get site admin but not a system admin, should not have access to the System Maintenance  Tools portlet. This would share database username and password under Log Files and download DB Dump and other dotCMS Content under Tools. Nothing in the System  Maintenance should be displayed for users with site admin role. Only system admins must have access to System Maintenance.

OWASP Top 10 - A01) Broken Access Control

OWASP Top 10 - A04) Insecure Design</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51570 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51570</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the RMI interface, which listens on TCP port 41009 by default. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in deserialization of untrusted data. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21012.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51571 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro SocketService Missing Authentication Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51571</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro SocketService Missing Authentication Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the SocketService module, which listens on UDP port 41222 by default. The issue results from the lack of authentication prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21162.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51572 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro getMacAddressByIp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51572</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro getMacAddressByIp Command Injection Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the getMacAddressByIP function. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied string before using it to execute a system call. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-21163.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51573 | Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro updateManagerPassword Exposed Dangerous Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51573</link><description>Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro updateManagerPassword Exposed Dangerous Function Authentication Bypass Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to bypass authentication on affected installations of Voltronic Power ViewPower Pro. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the updateManagerPassword function. The issue results from the exposure of a dangerous function. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-21203.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29433 | A deserialization vulnerability in the FASTJSON component of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29433</link><description>A deserialization vulnerability in the FASTJSON component of Alldata v0.4.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via supplying crafted data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29435 | An issue discovered in Alldata v0.4.6 allows attacker to run arbitrary commands via the processId parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29435</link><description>An issue discovered in Alldata v0.4.6 allows attacker to run arbitrary commands via the processId parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:10:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48906 | Stack Overflow vulnerability in Btstack 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted input to the char_for_nibb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48906</link><description>Stack Overflow vulnerability in Btstack 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to cause a denial of service via crafted input to the char_for_nibble function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 19:28:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3135 | Cross Site Request Forgery to denial of service or credit loss in LocalAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3135</link><description>The web server lacked CSRF tokens allowing an attacker to host malicious JavaScript on a host that when visited by a LocalAI user, could allow the attacker to fill disk space to deny service or abuse credits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 18:54:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28232 | Username Enumeration in CasaOS via bypass of CVE-2024-24766</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28232</link><description>Go package IceWhaleTech/CasaOS-UserService provides user management functionalities to CasaOS. The Casa OS Login page has disclosed the username enumeration vulnerability in the login page which was patched in version 0.4.7. This issue in CVE-2024-28232 has been patched in version 0.4.8 but that version has not yet been uploaded to Go's package manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3131 | SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Computer Laboratory Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_category. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-258874 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25574 | Delta Electronics DIAEnergie SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25574</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability exists in GetDIAE_usListParameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3129 | SourceCodester Image Accordion Gallery App add-image.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Image Accordion Gallery App 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/add-image.php. The manipulation of the argument image_name leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258873 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30858 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_fire_wall.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30858</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_fire_wall.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30859 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupSSLCert.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30859</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupSSLCert.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30861 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/configguide/ipsec_guide_1.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30861</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/configguide/ipsec_guide_1.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30860 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/export_excel_user.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30860</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/export_excel_user.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30862 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30862</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/index.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30863 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/history.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30863</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/history.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30867 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_virtual_site_info.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30867</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_virtual_site_info.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28547 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in SPS Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28547</link><description>Memory corruption in SPS Application while requesting for public key in sorter TA.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33023 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in SPS-Applications</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33023</link><description>Memory corruption while processing finish_sign command to pass a rsp buffer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33099 | Improper Input Validation in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33099</link><description>Transient DOS while processing SMS container of non-standard size received in DL NAS transport in NR.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33100 | Improper input validation in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33100</link><description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS Transport message when message ID is not defined in the 3GPP specification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33101 | Incorrect Type Conversion or Cast in Multi-Mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33101</link><description>Transient DOS while processing DL NAS TRANSPORT message with payload length 0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33111 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33111</link><description>Information disclosure when VI calibration state set by ADSP is greater than MAX_FBSP_STATE in the response payload to AFE calibration command.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33115 | Buffer Over-read in Trusted Execution Environment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33115</link><description>Memory corruption while processing buffer initialization, when trusted report for certain report types are generated.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43515 | Buffer copy without checking size of input (Classic buffer overflow) in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43515</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running kernel address sanitizers (syzkaller) on tmecom with DEBUG_FS enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21452 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21452</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding an ASN.1 OER message containing a SEQUENCE of unknown extensions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21453 | Improper Input Validation in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21453</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding message of size that exceeds the available system memory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21454 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Automotive Telematics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21454</link><description>Transient DOS while decoding the ToBeSignedMessage in Automotive Telematics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21463 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21463</link><description>Memory corruption while processing Codec2 during v13k decoder pitch synthesis.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21468 | Use After Free in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21468</link><description>Memory corruption when there is failed unmap operation in GPU.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21470 | Integer Overflow to Buffer Overflow in Graphics Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21470</link><description>Memory corruption while allocating memory for graphics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21472 | Use After Free in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21472</link><description>Memory corruption in Kernel while handling GPU operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21473 | Improper Input Validation in WIN SON</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21473</link><description>Memory corruption while redirecting log file to any file location with any file name.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30864 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupTimePolicy.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30864</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/config_ISCGroupTimePolicy.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30865 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_user_login.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30865</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/edit_user_login.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30866 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/menu.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30866</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /3g/menu.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26655 | Fix memory leak in posix_clock_open()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26655</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Fix memory leak in posix_clock_open()

If the clk ops.open() function returns an error, we don't release the
pccontext we allocated for this clock.

Re-organize the code slightly to make it all more obvious.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3128 | Replify-Messenger Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3128</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Replify-Messenger 1.0 on Android. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-258869 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early and responded very quickly. He does not intend to maintain the app anymore and will revoke the availability in the Google Play Store.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31099 | WordPress Phlox Core Elements plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31099</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Averta Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme.This issue affects Shortcodes and extra features for Phlox theme: from n/a through 2.15.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3125 | Zebra ZTC GK420d Alert Setup Page settings cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3125</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Zebra ZTC GK420d 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /settings of the component Alert Setup Page. The manipulation of the argument Address leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258868. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30868 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/add_getlogin.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30868</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/add_getlogin.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30870 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/address_interpret.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30870</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /admin/address_interpret.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30871 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/applyhardware.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30871</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /WebPages/applyhardware.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30872 | netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /include/authrp.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30872</link><description>netentsec NS-ASG 6.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via /include/authrp.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3124 | fridgecow smartalarm Backup File androidmanifest.xml backup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3124</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in fridgecow smartalarm 1.8.1 on Android. This affects an unknown part of the file androidmanifest.xml of the component Backup File Handler. The manipulation leads to exposure of backup file to an unauthorized control sphere. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258867.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4966 | sequentech admin-console Election Description cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4966</link><description>A vulnerability was found in sequentech admin-console up to 6.1.7 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Election Description Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 7.0.0-beta.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 0043a6b1e6e0f5abc9557e73f9ffc524fc5d609d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-258782 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 12:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6154 | Local privilege escalation in Bitdefender Total Security (VA-11168)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6154</link><description>A configuration setting issue in seccenter.exe as used in Bitdefender Total Security, Bitdefender Internet Security, Bitdefender Antivirus Plus, Bitdefender Antivirus Free allows an attacker to change the product's expected behavior and potentially load a third-party library upon execution. This issue affects Total Security: 27.0.25.114; Internet Security: 27.0.25.114; Antivirus Plus: 27.0.25.114; Antivirus Free: 27.0.25.114.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 10:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3130 |  Insecure Data Storage leading to sensitive Information disclosure.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3130</link><description>Hard-coded Credentialsin CoolKit eWeLlink app are before 5.4.x on Android and IOS allows local attacker tounauthorized access to sensitive data via Decryption algorithm and key obtained after decompiling app</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 09:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25080 | WebMail in Axigen 10.x before 10.3.3.62 allows XSS via the image attachment viewer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25080</link><description>WebMail in Axigen 10.x before 10.3.3.62 allows XSS via the image attachment viewer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26653 | usb: misc: ljca: Fix double free in error handling path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26653</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: misc: ljca: Fix double free in error handling path

When auxiliary_device_add() returns error and then calls
auxiliary_device_uninit(), callback function ljca_auxdev_release
calls kfree(auxdev-&gt;dev.platform_data) to free the parameter data
of the function ljca_new_client_device. The callers of
ljca_new_client_device shouldn't call kfree() again
in the error handling path to free the platform data.

Fix this by cleaning up the redundant kfree() in all callers and
adding kfree() the passed in platform_data on errors which happen
before auxiliary_device_init() succeeds .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26654 | ALSA: sh: aica: reorder cleanup operations to avoid UAF bugs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26654</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: sh: aica: reorder cleanup operations to avoid UAF bugs

The dreamcastcard-&gt;timer could schedule the spu_dma_work and the
spu_dma_work could also arm the dreamcastcard-&gt;timer.

When the snd_pcm_substream is closing, the aica_channel will be
deallocated. But it could still be dereferenced in the worker
thread. The reason is that del_timer() will return directly
regardless of whether the timer handler is running or not and
the worker could be rescheduled in the timer handler. As a result,
the UAF bug will happen. The racy situation is shown below:

      (Thread 1)                 |      (Thread 2)
snd_aicapcm_pcm_close()          |
 ...                             |  run_spu_dma() //worker
                                 |    mod_timer()
  flush_work()                   |
  del_timer()                    |  aica_period_elapsed() //timer
  kfree(dreamcastcard-&gt;channel)  |    schedule_work()
                                 |  run_spu_dma() //worker
  ...                            |    dreamcastcard-&gt;channel-&gt; //USE

In order to mitigate this bug and other possible corner cases,
call mod_timer() conditionally in run_spu_dma(), then implement
PCM sync_stop op to cancel both the timer and worker. The sync_stop
op will be called from PCM core appropriately when needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15038 | NUUO NVRmini 2 deletefile.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15038</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in NUUO NVRmini 2 up to 3.0.8. Affected is an unknown function of the file /deletefile.php. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-258780.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:42:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1526 | Hubbub Lite &amp;lt; 1.33.1 - Unauthenticated Password Protected Posts Access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1526</link><description>The Hubbub Lite  WordPress plugin before 1.33.1 does not ensure that user have access to password protected post before displaying its content in a meta tag.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2262 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Filter Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2262</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not have CSRF check in its bulk action, which could allow attackers to make logged in users delete arbitrary filters via CSRF attack, granted they know the related filter slugs</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2263 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2263</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2278 | WooCommerce Product Filter &amp;lt; 1.4.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2278</link><description>Themify  WordPress plugin before 1.4.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its Filters settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20039 | In modem protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20039</link><description>In modem protocol, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01240012; Issue ID: MSV-1215.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20040 | In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20040</link><description>In wlan firmware, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08360153 (for MT6XXX chipsets) / WCNCR00363530 (for MT79XX chipsets); Issue ID: MSV-979.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20041 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20041</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541746; Issue ID: ALPS08541746.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20042 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20042</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541780; Issue ID: ALPS08541780.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20043 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20043</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541781; Issue ID: ALPS08541781.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20044 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20044</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541784; Issue ID: ALPS08541784.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20045 | In audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect calculation of buffer size. This could lead to local information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20045</link><description>In audio, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect calculation of buffer size. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08024748; Issue ID: ALPS08029526.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20046 | In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20046</link><description>In battery, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08485622; Issue ID: ALPS08485622.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20047 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20047</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08587865; Issue ID: ALPS08486807.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20048 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20048</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541769; Issue ID: ALPS08541769.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20049 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20049</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541765; Issue ID: ALPS08541765.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20050 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20050</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541757.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20051 | In flashc, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20051</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible system crash due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local denial of service with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541758.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20052 | In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20052</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible information disclosure due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541761.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20053 | In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20053</link><description>In flashc, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an uncaught exception. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08541757; Issue ID: ALPS08541764.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20054 | In gnss, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20054</link><description>In gnss, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08580200; Issue ID: ALPS08580200.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20055 | In imgsys, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with Sy...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20055</link><description>In imgsys, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation Patch ID: ALPS08518692; Issue ID: MSV-1012.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31033 | JJWT (aka Java JWT) through 0.12.5 ignores certain characters and thus a user might falsely conclude that they have a strong key. The impact...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31033</link><description>JJWT (aka Java JWT) through 0.12.5 ignores certain characters and thus a user might falsely conclude that they have a strong key. The impacted code is the setSigningKey() method within the DefaultJwtParser class and the signWith() method within the DefaultJwtBuilder class. NOTE: the vendor disputes this because the "ignores" behavior cannot occur (in any version) unless there is a user error in how JJWT is used, and because the version that was actually tested must have been more than six years out of date.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 02:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28895 | 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for Android v2.3.1 to v3.161.1 and 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for iOS v3.2.2 to v4.109.0 contain a cross-site scripting vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28895</link><description>'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for Android v2.3.1 to v3.161.1 and 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App for iOS v3.2.2 to v4.109.0 contain a cross-site scripting vulnerability. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the WebView of 'Yahoo! JAPAN' App via other app installed on the user's device.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:53:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>