<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:47:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-4924 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System user_void_transaction.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4924</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user_void_transaction.php. The manipulation of the argument order_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27566 | Path traversal vulnerability exists in a-blog cms versions prior to Ver. 3.1.43 and versions prior to Ver. 3.0.47. This is an issue with ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27566</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability exists in a-blog cms versions prior to Ver. 3.1.43 and versions prior to Ver. 3.0.47. This is an issue with insufficient path validation in the backup feature, and exploitation requires the administrator privilege. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote authenticated attacker with the administrator privilege may obtain or delete any file on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32999 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms versions prior to Ver. 3.1.43 and prior to Ver. 3.0.47. This issue exists in a speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32999</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in a-blog cms versions prior to Ver. 3.1.43 and prior to Ver. 3.0.47. This issue exists in a specific field in the entry editing screen, and exploitation requires contributor or higher level privileges.  If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who is logging in to the product.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36560 | Server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in a-blog cms multiple versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36560</link><description>Server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in a-blog cms multiple versions. If this vulnerability is exploited, a remote unauthenticated attacker may gain access to sensitive information by sending a specially crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41429 | a-blog cms multiple versions neutralize logs improperly. If this vulnerability is exploited with CVE-2025-36560, a remote unauthenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41429</link><description>a-blog cms multiple versions neutralize logs improperly. If this vulnerability is exploited with CVE-2025-36560, a remote unauthenticated attacker may hijack a legitimate user's session.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4923 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System user_delivery_update.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4923</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user_delivery_update.php. The manipulation of the argument uploaded_file_cancelled leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:26:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47752 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6ComFile!MakeItemGlidZahyou function. Opening specially crafted V...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47752</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6ComFile!MakeItemGlidZahyou function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47753 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!CDrawSLine::GetRectArea function. Opening specially craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47753</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!CDrawSLine::GetRectArea function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47754 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!Conv_Macro_Data function. Opening specially crafted V7 o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47754</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!Conv_Macro_Data function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47755 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!VS4_SaveEnvFile function. Opening specially crafted V7 o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47755</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!VS4_SaveEnvFile function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47756 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!CGamenDataRom::set_mr400_strc function. Opening speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47756</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6EditData!CGamenDataRom::set_mr400_strc function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47757 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6MemInIF.dll!set_plc_type_default function. Opening specially craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47757</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds read in VS6MemInIF.dll!set_plc_type_default function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47758 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6File!CTxSubFile::get_ProgramFile_name function. Opening ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47758</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6File!CTxSubFile::get_ProgramFile_name function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47759 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6ComFile!CV7BaseMap::WriteV7DataToRom function. Opening s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47759</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6ComFile!CV7BaseMap::WriteV7DataToRom function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47760 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default function. Opening speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47760</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with stack-based buffer overflow in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47749 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with free of pointer not at start of buffer in VS6EditData.dll!CWinFontInf::WinFontMsgCheck fun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47749</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with free of pointer not at start of buffer in VS6EditData.dll!CWinFontInf::WinFontMsgCheck function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47750 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default function. Opening specially crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47750</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6MemInIF!set_temp_type_default function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47751 | V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6EditData!CDataRomErrorCheck::MacroCommandCheck function. Opening...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47751</link><description>V-SFT v6.2.5.0 and earlier contains an issue with out-of-bounds write in VS6EditData!CDataRomErrorCheck::MacroCommandCheck function. Opening specially crafted V7 or V8 files may lead to crash, information disclosure, and arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4917 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System new-autoortaxi-entry-form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4917</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/new-autoortaxi-entry-form.php. The manipulation of the argument drivername leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37891 | ALSA: ump: Fix buffer overflow at UMP SysEx message conversion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37891</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: ump: Fix buffer overflow at UMP SysEx message conversion

The conversion function from MIDI 1.0 to UMP packet contains an
internal buffer to keep the incoming MIDI bytes, and its size is 4, as
it was supposed to be the max size for a MIDI1 UMP packet data.
However, the implementation overlooked that SysEx is handled in a
different format, and it can be up to 6 bytes, as found in
do_convert_to_ump().  It leads eventually to a buffer overflow, and
may corrupt the memory when a longer SysEx message is received.

The fix is simply to extend the buffer size to 6 to fit with the SysEx
UMP message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46801 | Pgpool-II provided by PgPool Global Development Group contains an authentication bypass by primary weakness vulnerability. if the vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46801</link><description>Pgpool-II provided by PgPool Global Development Group contains an authentication bypass by primary weakness vulnerability. if the vulnerability is exploited, an attacker may be able to log in to the system as an arbitrary user, allowing them to read or tamper with data in the database, and/or disable the database.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4916 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4916</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:22:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4915 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System auto-taxi-entry-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4915</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/auto-taxi-entry-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument price leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:53:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1625 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt; 1.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via Counter Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1625</link><description>The Qi Blocks WordPress plugin before 1.4 does not validate and escape some of its Counter block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1626 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt; 1.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS vi Countdown Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1626</link><description>The Qi Blocks WordPress plugin before 1.4 does not validate and escape some of its Countdown block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1627 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt; 1.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS via ToC Block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1627</link><description>The Qi Blocks WordPress plugin before 1.4 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2524 | Ninja Forms &amp;lt; 3.10.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2524</link><description>The Ninja Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.10.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2560 | Ninja Forms &amp;lt; 3.10.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2560</link><description>The Ninja Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.10.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2561 | Ninja Forms &amp;lt; 3.10.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2561</link><description>The Ninja Forms  WordPress plugin before 3.10.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4914 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4914</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4477 | TeamT5 ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware - Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4477</link><description>The ThreatSonar Anti-Ransomware from TeamT5 has a Privilege Escalation vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with intermediate privileges to escalate their privileges to highest administrator level through a specific API.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4913 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4913</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:46:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4912 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Image File update_student.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4912</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/core/update_student.php of the component Image File Handler. The manipulation of the argument old_photo leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4911 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System view-foreigner-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4911</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/view-foreigner-ticket.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2892 | All in One SEO Pack &amp;lt;= 4.8.1.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Meta Description and Canonical URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2892</link><description>The All in One SEO – Powerful SEO Plugin to Boost SEO Rankings &amp; Increase Traffic plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the post Meta Description and Canonical URL parameters in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4910 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System edit-animal-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4910</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/edit-animal-details.php. The manipulation of the argument aname leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4909 | SourceCodester Client Database Management System exposure of information through directory listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4909</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Client Database Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code. The manipulation leads to exposure of information through directory listing. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4907 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4907</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4908 | PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System expense-datewise-reports-detailed.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4908</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Daily Expense Tracker System 1.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /expense-datewise-reports-detailed.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4906 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4906</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23122 | In Node.js, the `ReadFileUtf8` internal binding leaks memory due to a corrupted pointer in `uv_fs_s.file`: a UTF-16 path buffer is allocated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23122</link><description>In Node.js, the `ReadFileUtf8` internal binding leaks memory due to a corrupted pointer in `uv_fs_s.file`: a UTF-16 path buffer is allocated but subsequently overwritten when the file descriptor is set. This results in an unrecoverable memory leak on every call. Repeated use can cause unbounded memory growth, leading to a denial of service.

Impact:
* This vulnerability affects APIs relying on `ReadFileUtf8` on Node.js release lines: v20 and v22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23123 | A malicious actor with access to the management network could execute a remote code execution (RCE) by exploiting a heap buffer overflow vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23123</link><description>A malicious actor with access to the management network could execute a remote code execution (RCE) by exploiting a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the UniFi Protect Cameras (Version 4.75.43 and earlier) firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23164 | A misconfigured access token mechanism in the Unifi Protect Application (Version 5.3.41 and earlier) could permit the recipient of a "Share ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23164</link><description>A misconfigured access token mechanism in the Unifi Protect Application (Version 5.3.41 and earlier) could permit the recipient of a "Share Livestream" link to maintain access to the corresponding livestream subsequent to such link becoming disabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23165 | In Node.js, the `ReadFileUtf8` internal binding leaks memory due to a corrupted pointer in `uv_fs_s.file`: a UTF-16 path buffer is allocated...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23165</link><description>In Node.js, the `ReadFileUtf8` internal binding leaks memory due to a corrupted pointer in `uv_fs_s.file`: a UTF-16 path buffer is allocated but subsequently overwritten when the file descriptor is set. This results in an unrecoverable memory leak on every call. Repeated use can cause unbounded memory growth, leading to a denial of service.

Impact:
* This vulnerability affects APIs relying on `ReadFileUtf8` on Node.js release lines: v20 and v22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23166 | The C++ method SignTraits::DeriveBits() may incorrectly call ThrowException() based on user-supplied inputs when executing in a background t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23166</link><description>The C++ method SignTraits::DeriveBits() may incorrectly call ThrowException() based on user-supplied inputs when executing in a background thread, crashing the Node.js process. Such cryptographic operations are commonly applied to untrusted inputs. Thus, this mechanism potentially allows an adversary to remotely crash a Node.js runtime.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23167 | A flaw in Node.js 20's HTTP parser allows improper termination of HTTP/1 headers using `\r\n\rX` instead of the required `\r\n\r\n`.
This in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23167</link><description>A flaw in Node.js 20's HTTP parser allows improper termination of HTTP/1 headers using `\r\n\rX` instead of the required `\r\n\r\n`.
This inconsistency enables request smuggling, allowing attackers to bypass proxy-based access controls and submit unauthorized requests.

The issue was resolved by upgrading `llhttp` to version 9, which enforces correct header termination.

Impact:
* This vulnerability affects only Node.js 20.x users prior to the `llhttp` v9 upgrade.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4905 | iop-apl-uw basestation3 QC.py load_qc_pickl deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4905</link><description>A vulnerability was found in iop-apl-uw basestation3 up to 3.0.4 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function load_qc_pickl of the file basestation3/QC.py. The manipulation of the argument qc_file leads to deserialization. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The code maintainer tagged the issue as closed. But there is no new commit nor release in the GitHub repository available so far.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4904 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 webgl.data sub_41F0FC information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4904</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125) and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function sub_41F0FC of the file /H5/webgl.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4903 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 webgl.asp sub_41F4F0 unverified password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4903</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). This affects the function sub_41F4F0 of the file /H5/webgl.asp?tggl_port=0&amp;amp;remote_management=0&amp;amp;http_passwd=game&amp;amp;exec_service=admin-restart. The manipulation leads to unverified password change. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4902 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 versionupdate.data sub_48F4F0 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4902</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). Affected by this issue is the function sub_48F4F0 of the file /H5/versionupdate.data. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 01:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4901 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 HTTP Endpoint state_view.data sub_41E304 information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4901</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in D-Link DI-7003GV2 24.04.18D1 R(68125). Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_41E304 of the file /H5/state_view.data of the component HTTP Endpoint. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack can only be done within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4900 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System payment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4900</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/payment.php. The manipulation of the argument cid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4899 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System transaction_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4899</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /pages/transaction_update.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 22:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4898 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Logo File update_system.php unlink path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4898</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function unlink of the file update_system.php of the component Logo File Handler. The manipulation of the argument old_logo leads to path traversal. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 22:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4897 | Tenda A15 HTTP POST Request multimodalAdd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4897</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.09/15.13.07.13. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/multimodalAdd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 21:40:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4896 | Tenda AC10 UserCongratulationsExec buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4896</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/UserCongratulationsExec. The manipulation of the argument getuid leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 21:07:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4895 | SourceCodester Doctors Appointment System delete-session.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4895</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Doctors Appointment System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete-session.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4894 | calmkart Django-sso-server crypto.py gen_rsa_keys inadequate encryption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4894</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in calmkart Django-sso-server up to 057247929a94ffc358788a37ab99e391379a4d15. This vulnerability affects the function gen_rsa_keys of the file common/crypto.py. The manipulation leads to inadequate encryption strength. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4893 | jammy928 CoinExchange_CryptoExchange_Java File Upload Endpoint UploadFileUtil.java uploadLocalImage path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4893</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in jammy928 CoinExchange_CryptoExchange_Java up to 8adf508b996020d3efbeeb2473d7235bd01436fa. This affects the function uploadLocalImage of the file /CoinExchange_CryptoExchange_Java-master/00_framework/core/src/main/java/com/bizzan/bitrade/util/UploadFileUtil.java of the component File Upload Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4892 | code-projects Police Station Management System Delete Record source.cpp remove stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4892</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Police Station Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function criminal::remove of the file source.cpp of the component Delete Record. The manipulation of the argument No leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:14:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4891 | code-projects Police Station Management System Display Record source.cpp display buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4891</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Police Station Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function criminal::display of the file source.cpp of the component Display Record. The manipulation of the argument N leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4890 | code-projects Tourism Management System Login User LoginUser stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4890</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Tourism Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function LoginUser of the component Login User. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4889 | code-projects Tourism Management System User Registration AddUser buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4889</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Tourism Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function AddUser of the component User Registration. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:39:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4888 | code-projects Pharmacy Management System Add Order Details take_order buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4888</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Pharmacy Management System 1.0. This affects the function medicineType::take_order of the component Add Order Details. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4887 | SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4887</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Online Student Clearance System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4886 | itsourcecode Sales and Inventory System product_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4886</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/product_update.php. The manipulation of the argument serial leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4885 | itsourcecode Sales and Inventory System product_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4885</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Sales and Inventory System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pages/product_add.php. The manipulation of the argument serial leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 15:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4884 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System assign_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4884</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/assign_save.php. The manipulation of the argument team leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 15:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4883 | D-Link DI-8100 Connection Limit Page ctxz.asp ctxz_asp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4883</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8100 16.07.26A1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function ctxz_asp of the file /ctxz.asp of the component Connection Limit Page. The manipulation of the argument def/defTcp/defUdp/defIcmp/defOther leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48219 | O2 UK through 2025-05-17 allows subscribers to determine the Cell ID of other subscribers by initiating an IMS (IP Multimedia Subsystem) cal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48219</link><description>O2 UK through 2025-05-17 allows subscribers to determine the Cell ID of other subscribers by initiating an IMS (IP Multimedia Subsystem) call and then reading the utran-cell-id-3gpp field of a Cellular-Network-Info SIP header, aka an ECI (E-UTRAN Cell Identity) leak. The Cell ID might be usable to identify a cell location via crowdsourced data, and might correspond to a small physical area (e.g., if the called party is in a city centre). Removal of the Cellular-Network-Info header is mentioned in section 4.4.19 of ETSI TS 124 229.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4882 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System team_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4882</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/team_update.php. The manipulation of the argument team leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:17:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4881 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System user_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4881</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/user_save.php. The manipulation of the argument username/name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4880 | PHPGurukul News Portal aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4880</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4875 | Campcodes Online Shopping Portal forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4875</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Shopping Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:56:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4874 | PHPGurukul News Portal Project contactus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4874</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul News Portal Project 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/contactus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4873 | PHPGurukul News Portal Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4873</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul News Portal 4.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4872 | FreeFloat FTP Server CCC Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4872</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component CCC Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4871 | PCMan FTP Server REST Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4871</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component REST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4870 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System menu_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4870</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/menu_save.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4869 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System member_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4869</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/member_update.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 09:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4868 | merikbest ecommerce-spring-reactjs File Upload Endpoint admin path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4868</link><description>A vulnerability was found in merikbest ecommerce-spring-reactjs up to 464e610bb11cc2619cf6ce8212ccc2d1fd4277fd. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/v1/admin/ of the component File Upload Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 09:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4867 | Tenda A15 ArpNerworkSet formArpNerworkSet denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4867</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A15 15.13.07.13. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formArpNerworkSet of the file /goform/ArpNerworkSet. The manipulation leads to denial of service. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 08:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4866 | weibocom rill-flow Management Console code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4866</link><description>A vulnerability was found in weibocom rill-flow 0.1.18. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component Management Console. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 08:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4865 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System member_save.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4865</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/member_save.php. The manipulation of the argument last leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4864 | itsourcecode Restaurant Management System finished.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4864</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itsourcecode Restaurant Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/finished.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 07:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4863 | Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal studentLogin.action sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4863</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Advaya Softech GEMS ERP Portal 2.1. This affects an unknown part of the file /studentLogin/studentLogin.action. The manipulation of the argument userId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4862 | PHPGurukul Directory Management System searchdata.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4862</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PHPGurukul Directory Management System 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /searchdata.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 06:24:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4861 | PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4861</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Beauty Parlour Management System 1.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument contactnumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3715 | Bold Page Builder &amp;lt;= 5.3.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;data-text&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3715</link><description>The Bold Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the data-text parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.3.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4860 | D-Link DAP-2695 Static Pool Settings Page adv_dhcps.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4860</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. Affected is an unknown function of the file /adv_dhcps.php of the component Static Pool Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument f_mac leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:17:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4859 | D-Link DAP-2695 MAC Bypass Settings Page adv_macbypass.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4859</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /adv_macbypass.php of the component MAC Bypass Settings Page. The manipulation of the argument f_mac leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4858 | D-Link DAP-2695 ARP Spoofing Prevention Page adv_arpspoofing.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4858</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DAP-2695 120b36r137_ALL_en_20210528. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /adv_arpspoofing.php of the component ARP Spoofing Prevention Page. The manipulation of the argument harp_mac leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:04:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4852 | TOTOLINK A3002R VPN Page cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4852</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in TOTOLINK A3002R 2.1.1-B20230720.1011. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component VPN Page. The manipulation of the argument Comment leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 04:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4851 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi setUploadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4851</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. This vulnerability affects the function setUploadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument FileName leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4849 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4849</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function CloudACMunualUpdateUserdata of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument url leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4850 | TOTOLINK N300RH cstecgi.cgi setUnloadUserData command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4850</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK N300RH 6.1c.1390_B20191101. This affects the function setUnloadUserData of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument plugin_name leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:44:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4848 | FreeFloat FTP Server RECV Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4848</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component RECV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4847 | FreeFloat FTP Server MLS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4847</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component MLS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4846 | FreeFloat FTP Server MPUT Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4846</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component MPUT Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4845 | FreeFloat FTP Server TRACE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4845</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component TRACE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4844 | FreeFloat FTP Server CD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4844</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component CD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 01:25:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4843 | D-Link DCS-932L udev SubUPnPCSInit stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function SubUPnPCSInit of the file /sbin/udev. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4842 | D-Link DCS-932L ucp isUCPCameraNameChanged stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function isUCPCameraNameChanged of the file /sbin/ucp. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4841 | D-Link DCS-932L gpio sub_404780 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4841</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_404780 of the file /bin/gpio. The manipulation of the argument CameraName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 22:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4839 | itwanger paicoding CrossUtil.java cross-domain policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4839</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in itwanger paicoding 1.0.0/1.0.1/1.0.2/1.0.3 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /paicoding-core/src/main/java/com/github/paicoding/forum/core/util/CrossUtil.java. The manipulation leads to permissive cross-domain policy with untrusted domains. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4838 | kanwangzjm Funiture Login LoginServlet.java doPost redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4838</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in kanwangzjm Funiture up to 71ca0fb0658b3d839d9e049ac36429207f05329b. Affected is the function doPost of the file /funiture-master/src/main/java/com/app/mvc/acl/servlet/LoginServlet.java of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument ret leads to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4918 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 11...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4918</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4919 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4919</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability affects Firefox ESR &lt; 115.23.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4920 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4920</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript `Promise` object. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0.4 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4921 | An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4921</link><description>An attacker was able to perform an out-of-bounds read or write on a JavaScript object by confusing array index sizes. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 138.0.4 and Firefox ESR &lt; 128.10.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4837 | projectworlds Student Project Allocation System make_group_sql.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4837</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in projectworlds Student Project Allocation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /make_group_sql.php. The manipulation of the argument mem1/mem2/mem3 leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4836 | Projectworlds Life Insurance Management System deleteAgent.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4836</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Projectworlds Life Insurance Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /deleteAgent.php. The manipulation of the argument agent_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4835 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWlanRedirect buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4835</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formWlanRedirect of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument redirect-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4834 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSetLg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4834</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSetLg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47948 | Cocotais Bot has builtin .echo command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47948</link><description>Cocotais Bot is a QQ official robot framework based on qq-bot-sdk. Starting in version 1.5.0-test2-hotfix and prior to version 1.6.2, command echoing feature in the framework allows users to indirectly trigger privileged behavior by injecting special platform tags. Specifically, an unauthorized user can use the `/echo ` command to cause the bot to send a message that mentions all members in the chat, bypassing any permission controls. This can lead to spam, disruption, or abuse of notification systems. Version 1.6.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47945 | Donetick Has Weak Default JWT Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47945</link><description>Donetick an open-source app for managing tasks and chores. Prior to version 0.1.44, the application uses JSON Web Tokens (JWT) for authentication, but the signing secret has a weak default value. While the responsibility is left to the system administrator to change it, this approach is inadequate. The vulnerability is proven by existence of the issue in the live version as well. This issue can result in full account takeover of any user. Version 0.1.44 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4833 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formNtp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4833</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formNtp of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:41:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4832 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formDosCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4832</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formDosCfg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4831 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSiteSurveyProfile buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4831</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formSiteSurveyProfile of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:41:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33103 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33103</link><description>IBM i 7.2, 7.3, 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 product IBM TCP/IP Connectivity Utilities for i contains a privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with command line access to the host operating system can elevate privileges to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47931 | LibreNMS stored Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in poller group name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47931</link><description>LibreNMS is PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring software. LibreNMS v25.4.0 and prior suffers from a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in the `group name` parameter of the `http://localhost/poller/groups` form. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into web pages viewed by other users. LibreNMS v25.5.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47273 | setuptools has a path traversal vulnerability in PackageIndex.download that leads to Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47273</link><description>setuptools is a package that allows users to download, build, install, upgrade, and uninstall Python packages. A path traversal vulnerability in `PackageIndex` is present in setuptools prior to version 78.1.1. An attacker would be allowed to write files to arbitrary locations on the filesystem with the permissions of the process running the Python code, which could escalate to remote code execution depending on the context. Version 78.1.1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4830 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSysCmd buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4830</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formSysCmd of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4829 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formStats sub_40BE30 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4829</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_40BE30 of the file /boafrm/formStats of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4827 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formSaveConfig buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4827</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formSaveConfig of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48187 | RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48187</link><description>RAGFlow through 0.18.1 allows account takeover because it is possible to conduct successful brute-force attacks against email verification codes to perform arbitrary account registration, login, and password reset. Codes are six digits and there is no rate limiting.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:03:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4101 | MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions &amp;lt;= 4.2.22 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Post Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4101</link><description>The MultiVendorX – WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solutions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a misconfigured capability check on the 'delete_fpm_product' function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.22. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary posts, pages, attachments, and products. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.2.22.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13613 | Wise Chat &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13613</link><description>The Wise Chat plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.3 via the 'uploads' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads directory which can contain file attachments included in chat messages. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4669 | Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 10.11.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpbc Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4669</link><description>The WP Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpbc shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 10.11.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3527 | EventON - WordPress Virtual Event Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.9.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3527</link><description>The EventON Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check in the 'assets/lib/settings/settings.js' file in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 4.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3888 | Jupiterx Core &amp;lt;= 4.8.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Inline SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3888</link><description>The Jupiter X Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the page with the included SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4826 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWirelessTbl buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4826</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formWirelessTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 11:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4825 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formDMZ buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4825</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formDMZ of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4824 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formWsc buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4824</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. This affects an unknown part of the file /boafrm/formWsc of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 10:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4823 | TOTOLINK A702R/A3002R/A3002RU HTTP POST Request formReflashClientTbl submit-url buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4823</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK A702R, A3002R and A3002RU 3.0.0-B20230809.1615. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function submit-url of the file /boafrm/formReflashClientTbl of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4610 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via wpmem_user_memberships Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4610</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's wpmem_user_memberships shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 09:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4190 | CSV Mass Importer &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Admin+ Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4190</link><description>The CSV Mass Importer WordPress plugin through 1.2 does not properly validate uploaded files, allowing high privilege users such as admin to upload arbitrary files on the server even when they should not be allowed to (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4819 | y_project RuoYi Offline Logout batchForceLogout improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4819</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in y_project RuoYi 4.8.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /monitor/online/batchForceLogout of the component Offline Logout. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 06:18:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3812 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.6.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3812</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the qcld_openai_delete_training_file() function in all versions up to, and including, 13.6.2. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4389 | Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator &amp;lt;= 2.6.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4389</link><description>The Crawlomatic Multipage Scraper Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the crawlomatic_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4391 | Echo RSS Feed Post Generator &amp;lt;= 5.4.8.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4391</link><description>The Echo RSS Feed Post Generator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the echo_generate_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.8.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:42:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4818 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-doctor.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4818</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/delete-doctor.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 05:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4817 | Sourcecodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter delete-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4817</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sourcecodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/delete-appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:18:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4189 | Audio Comments Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4189</link><description>The Audio Comments Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'audio-comments/audior-settings.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4194 | AlT Monitoring &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4194</link><description>The AlT Monitoring plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ALT_Monitoring_edit' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4816 | SourceCodester Doctor&amp;#x27;s Appointment System GET Parameter appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4816</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Doctor's Appointment System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/appointment.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4815 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4815</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_update.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4814 | Campcodes Sales and Inventory System supplier_add.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4814</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Sales and Inventory System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /pages/supplier_add.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47893 | GPU DDK - OOB read and write of the shared KMD/FW memory heap (VZ/TEE setups)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47893</link><description>Kernel software installed and running inside a Guest VM may exploit memory shared with the GPU Firmware to read and/or write data outside the Guest's virtualised GPU memory.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1706 | GPU DDK - Improper locking when accessing the pvr_exp_fence  object</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1706</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to trigger use-after-free kernel exceptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 02:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>