<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:36:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-15162 | Tenda WH450 RouteStatic stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15162</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/RouteStatic. Executing manipulation of the argument page can lead to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15161 | Tenda WH450 PPTPUserSetting stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/PPTPUserSetting. Performing manipulation of the argument delno results in stack-based buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15160 | Tenda WH450 PPTPServer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda WH450 1.0.0.18. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/PPTPServer. Such manipulation of the argument ip1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:48:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15156 | omec-project UPF PFCP Session Establishment Request messages_session.go handleSessionEstablishmentRequest null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15156</link><description>A flaw has been found in omec-project UPF up to 2.1.3-dev. This affects the function handleSessionEstablishmentRequest of the file /pfcpiface/pfcpiface/messages_session.go of the component PFCP Session Establishment Request Handler. This manipulation causes null pointer dereference. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15155 | floooh sokol sokol_gfx.h _sg_pipeline_desc_defaults stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15155</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in floooh sokol up to 16cbcc864012898793cd2bc57f802499a264ea40. The impacted element is the function _sg_pipeline_desc_defaults in the library sokol_gfx.h. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack requires a local approach. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The patch is identified as 5d11344150973f15e16d3ec4ee7550a73fb995e0. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:44:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15154 | PbootCMS Header handle.php get_user_ip less trusted source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15154</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PbootCMS up to 3.2.12. The affected element is the function get_user_ip of the file core/function/handle.php of the component Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument X-Forwarded-For leads to use of less trusted source. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15153 | PbootCMS SQLite Database pbootcms.db file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15153</link><description>A weakness has been identified in PbootCMS up to 3.2.12. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /data/pbootcms.db of the component SQLite Database. Executing manipulation can lead to files or directories accessible. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Modifying the configuration settings is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:46:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15152 | h-moses moga-mall PmsProductController.java addProduct unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15152</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in h-moses moga-mall up to 392d631a5ef15962a9bddeeb9f1269b9085473fa. This vulnerability affects the function addProduct of the file src/main/java/com/ms/product/controller/PmsProductController.java. Such manipulation of the argument objectName leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15151 | TaleLin Lin-CMS Tests Folder config.py password in configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15151</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in TaleLin Lin-CMS up to 0.6.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /tests/config.py of the component Tests Folder. This manipulation of the argument username/password causes password in configuration file. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:42:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15150 | PX4 PX4-Autopilot mavlink_log_handler.cpp log_entry_from_id stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15150</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PX4 PX4-Autopilot up to 1.16.0. Affected by this issue is the function MavlinkLogHandler::state_listing/MavlinkLogHandler::log_entry_from_id of the file src/modules/mavlink/mavlink_log_handler.cpp. The manipulation results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is only possible with local access. The patch is identified as 338595edd1d235efd885fd5e9f45e7f9dcf4013d. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15149 | rawchen ecms Add New Product updateProductServlet.java updateProductServlet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15149</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in rawchen ecms up to b59d7feaa9094234e8aa6c8c6b290621ca575ded. Affected by this vulnerability is the function updateProductServlet of the file src/servlet/product/updateProductServlet.java of the component Add New Product Page. The manipulation of the argument productName leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15148 | CmsEasy Backend Template Management template_admin.php savetemp_action code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15148</link><description>A flaw has been found in CmsEasy up to 7.7.7. Affected is the function savetemp_action in the library /lib/admin/template_admin.php of the component Backend Template Management Page. Executing manipulation of the argument content/tempdata can lead to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15146 | SohuTV CacheCloud UserManageController.java doUserList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15146</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This impacts the function doUserList of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/UserManageController.java. Performing manipulation results in cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15145 | SohuTV CacheCloud TotalManageController.java doTotalList cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15145</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in SohuTV CacheCloud up to 3.2.0. This affects the function doTotalList of the file src/main/java/com/sohu/cache/web/controller/TotalManageController.java. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15144 | dayrui XunRuiCMS JSONP Callback Init.php dr_exit_msg cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15144</link><description>A weakness has been identified in dayrui XunRuiCMS up to 4.7.1. The impacted element is the function dr_show_error/dr_exit_msg of the file /dayrui/Fcms/Init.php of the component JSONP Callback Handler. This manipulation of the argument callback causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68973 | In GnuPG through 2.4.8, armor_filter in g10/armor.c has two increments of an index variable where one is intended, leading to an out-of-boun...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68973</link><description>In GnuPG through 2.4.8, armor_filter in g10/armor.c has two increments of an index variable where one is intended, leading to an out-of-bounds write for crafted input.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15143 | EyouCMS Backend Template Management FilemanagerLogic.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15143</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in EyouCMS up to 1.7.6. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /application/admin/logic/FilemanagerLogic.php of the component Backend Template Management. The manipulation of the argument content results in sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15142 | 9786 phpok3w show.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15142</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in 9786 phpok3w up to 901d96a06809fb28b17f3a4362c59e70411c933c. Impacted is an unknown function of the file show.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:46:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15141 | Halo Configuration actuator information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15141</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Halo up to 2.21.10. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /actuator of the component Configuration Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:18:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15140 | saiftheboss7 onlinemcqexam quesadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in saiftheboss7 onlinemcqexam up to 0e56806132971e49721db3ef01868098c7b42ada. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/quesadd.php. Performing manipulation of the argument ans1/ans2 results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15139 | TRENDnet TEW-822DRE formWsc sub_43ACF4  command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15139</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TRENDnet TEW-822DRE 1.00B21/1.01B06. This affects the function sub_43ACF4  of the file /boafrm/formWsc. Such manipulation of the argument peerPin leads to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:12:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15138 | prasathmani TinyFileManager tinyfilemanager.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15138</link><description>A flaw has been found in prasathmani TinyFileManager up to 2.6. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file tinyfilemanager.php. This manipulation of the argument fullpath causes path traversal. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15137 | TRENDnet TEW-800MB NTPSyncWithHost.cgi sub_F934  command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15137</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in TRENDnet TEW-800MB 1.0.1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_F934  of the file NTPSyncWithHost.cgi. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15136 | TRENDnet TEW-800MB Management wizardset do_setWizard_asp command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15136</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in TRENDnet TEW-800MB 1.0.1.0. Affected is the function do_setWizard_asp of the file /goform/wizardset of the component Management Interface. The manipulation of the argument WizardConfigured leads to command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15135 | joey-zhou xiaozhi-esp32-server-java Cookie AuthenticationInterceptor.java tryAuthenticateWithCookies improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15135</link><description>A weakness has been identified in joey-zhou xiaozhi-esp32-server-java up to 3.0.0. This impacts the function tryAuthenticateWithCookies of the file AuthenticationInterceptor.java of the component Cookie Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. Upgrading to version 4.0.0 will fix this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15134 | yourmaileyes MOOC Submission MainController.java subreview cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15134</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in yourmaileyes MOOC up to 1.17. This affects the function subreview of the file mooc/controller/MainController.java of the component Submission Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument review results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15133 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request close zfilev2_api_CloseSafe command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15133</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. The impacted element is the function zfilev2_api_CloseSafe of the file /v2/file/safe/close of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. Such manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 11:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15132 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request open zfilev2_api_open command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15132</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. The affected element is the function zfilev2_api_open of the file /v2/file/safe/open of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. This manipulation causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:41:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15131 | ZSPACE Z4Pro+ HTTP POST Request status zfilev2_api_SafeStatus command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15131</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ZSPACE Z4Pro+ 1.0.0440024. Impacted is the function zfilev2_api_SafeStatus of the file /v2/file/safe/status of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation results in command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15130 | shanyu SyCms Administrative Panel FileManageController.class.php addPost code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in shanyu SyCms up to a242ef2d194e8bb249dc175e7c49f2c1673ec921. This issue affects the function addPost of the file Application/Admin/Controller/FileManageController.class.php of the component Administrative Panel. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product adopts a rolling release strategy to maintain continuous delivery The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15129 | ChenJinchuang Lin-CMS-TP5 File Upload LocalUploader.php upload code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15129</link><description>A flaw has been found in ChenJinchuang Lin-CMS-TP5 up to 0.3.3. This vulnerability affects the function Upload of the file application/lib/file/LocalUploader.php of the component File Upload Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument File can lead to code injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15128 | ZKTeco BioTime Endpoint safe_setting credentials storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15128</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in ZKTeco BioTime up to 9.0.3/9.0.4/9.5.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /base/safe_setting/ of the component Endpoint. Performing manipulation of the argument backup_encryption_password_decrypt/export_encryption_password_decrypt results in unprotected storage of credentials. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15127 | FantasticLBP Hotels_Server Room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15127</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in FantasticLBP Hotels_Server up to 67b44df162fab26df209bd5d5d542875fcbec1d0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /controller/api/Room.php. Such manipulation of the argument hotelId leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product operates on a rolling release basis, ensuring continuous delivery. Consequently, there are no version details for either affected or updated releases. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15126 | JeecgBoot getPositionUserList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15126</link><description>A weakness has been identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getPositionUserList of the file /sys/position/getPositionUserList. This manipulation of the argument positionId causes improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15125 | JeecgBoot queryDepartPermission improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15125</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Affected is the function queryDepartPermission of the file /sys/permission/queryDepartPermission. The manipulation of the argument departId results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 07:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15124 | JeecgBoot list getParameterMap improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15124</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This impacts the function getParameterMap of the file /sys/sysDepartPermission/list. The manipulation of the argument departId leads to improper authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is said to be difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:54:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15123 | JeecgBoot datarule improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15123</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /sys/sysDepartPermission/datarule/. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The attack requires a high level of complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15122 | JeecgBoot datarule loadDatarule improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15122</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The impacted element is the function loadDatarule of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/datarule/. Performing manipulation of the argument departId/roleId results in improper authorization. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15121 | JeecgBoot getDeptRoleByUserId information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15121</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. The affected element is the function getDeptRoleByUserId of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/getDeptRoleByUserId. Such manipulation of the argument departId leads to information disclosure. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15120 | JeecgBoot getDeptRoleList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15120</link><description>A flaw has been found in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. Impacted is the function getDeptRoleList of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/getDeptRoleList. This manipulation of the argument departId causes improper authorization. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. A high degree of complexity is needed for the attack. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15119 | JeecgBoot list queryPageList improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15119</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in JeecgBoot up to 3.9.0. This issue affects the function queryPageList of the file /sys/sysDepartRole/list. The manipulation of the argument deptId results in improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. A high complexity level is associated with this attack. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15118 | macrozheng mall Member Endpoint update improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15118</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /member/address/update/ of the component Member Endpoint. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15116 | OpenCart Single-Use Coupon race condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15116</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in OpenCart up to 4.1.0.3. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Single-Use Coupon Handler. Performing manipulation results in race condition. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15117 | Dromara Sa-Token SaJdkSerializer.java ObjectInputStream.readObject deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15117</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Dromara Sa-Token up to 1.44.0. This affects the function ObjectInputStream.readObject of the file SaJdkSerializer.java. Executing manipulation can lead to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is indicated that the exploitability is difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68972 | In GnuPG through 2.4.8, if a signed message has \f at the end of a plaintext line, an adversary can construct a modified message that places...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68972</link><description>In GnuPG through 2.4.8, if a signed message has \f at the end of a plaintext line, an adversary can construct a modified message that places additional text after the signed material, such that signature verification of the modified message succeeds (although an "invalid armor" message is printed during verification). This is related to use of \f as a marker to denote truncation of a long plaintext line.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 23:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15110 | jackq XCMS Backend ProductImageController.class.php upload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15110</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in jackq XCMS up to 3fab5342cc509945a7ce1b8ec39d19f701b89261. Affected is the function Upload of the file Admin/Home/Controller/ProductImageController.class.php of the component Backend. Such manipulation of the argument File leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:24:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14177 | Information Leak of Memory in getimagesize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14177</link><description>In PHP versions:8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1, the getimagesize() function may leak uninitialized heap memory into the APPn segments (e.g., APP1) when reading images in multi-chunk mode (such as via php://filter). This occurs due to a bug in php_read_stream_all_chunks() that overwrites the buffer without advancing the pointer, leaving tail bytes uninitialized. This may lead to information disclosure of sensitive heap data and affect the confidentiality of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14178 | Heap buffer overflow in array_merge()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14178</link><description>In PHP versions:8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1, a heap buffer overflow occurs in array_merge() when the total element count of packed arrays exceeds 32-bit limits or HT_MAX_SIZE, due to an integer overflow in the precomputation of element counts using zend_hash_num_elements(). This may lead to memory corruption or crashes and affect the integrity and availability of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14180 | NULL Pointer Dereference in PDO quoting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14180</link><description>In PHP versions 8.1.* before 8.1.34, 8.2.* before 8.2.30, 8.3.* before 8.3.29, 8.4.* before 8.4.16, 8.5.* before 8.5.1 when using the PDO PostgreSQL driver with PDO::ATTR_EMULATE_PREPARES enabled, an invalid character sequence (such as \x99) in a prepared statement parameter may cause the quoting function PQescapeStringConn to return NULL, leading to a null pointer dereference in pdo_parse_params() function. This may lead to crashes (segmentation fault) and affect the availability of the target server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 19:29:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15109 | jackq XCMS upload.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15109</link><description>A flaw has been found in jackq XCMS up to 3fab5342cc509945a7ce1b8ec39d19f701b89261. This impacts an unknown function of the file Public/javascripts/admin/plupload-2.1.2/examples/upload.php. This manipulation causes unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15108 | PandaXGO PandaX JWT Secret config.yml hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15108</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in PandaXGO PandaX up to fb8ff40f7ce5dfebdf66306c6d85625061faf7e5. This affects an unknown function of the file config.yml of the component JWT Secret Handler. The manipulation of the argument key results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack may be performed from remote. This attack is characterized by high complexity. The exploitability is reported as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used. This product utilizes a rolling release system for continuous delivery, and as such, version information for affected or updated releases is not disclosed. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54322 | Xspeeder SXZOS through 2025-12-26 allows root remote code execution via base64-encoded Python code in the chkid parameter to vLogin.py. The ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54322</link><description>Xspeeder SXZOS through 2025-12-26 allows root remote code execution via base64-encoded Python code in the chkid parameter to vLogin.py. The title and oIP parameters are also used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:57:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15107 | actiontech sqle JWT Secret jwt.go hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15107</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in actiontech sqle up to 4.2511.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file sqle/utils/jwt.go of the component JWT Secret Handler. The manipulation of the argument JWTSecretKey leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report and is planning to fix this flaw in an upcoming release.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15106 | getmaxun Authentication Endpoint auth.ts router.get improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15106</link><description>A weakness has been identified in getmaxun maxun up to 0.0.28. The affected element is the function router.get of the file server/src/routes/auth.ts of the component Authentication Endpoint. Executing manipulation can lead to improper authorization. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15105 | getmaxun auth.ts hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15105</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in getmaxun maxun up to 0.0.28. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /getmaxun/maxun/blob/develop/server/src/routes/auth.ts. Performing manipulation of the argument api_key results in use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:23:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59946 | NanoMQ has a Use After Free vulnerability via sub info list</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59946</link><description>NanoMQ MQTT Broker (NanoMQ) is an Edge Messaging Platform. Prior to version 0.24.2, there is a classical data racing issue about sub info list which could result in heap use after free crash. This issue has been patched in version 0.24.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68927 | Improper Neutralization of  HTML Tags in a Web Page in libredesk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68927</link><description>Libredesk is a self-hosted customer support desk. Prior to version 0.8.6-beta, LibreDesk is vulnerable to stored HTML injection in the contact notes feature. When adding notes via POST /api/v1/contacts/{id}/notes, the backend automatically wraps user input in &lt;p&gt; tags. However, by intercepting the request and removing the &lt;p&gt; tag, an attacker can inject arbitrary HTML elements such as forms and images, which are then stored and rendered without proper sanitization. This can lead to phishing, CSRF-style forced actions, and UI redress attacks. This issue has been patched in version 0.8.6-beta.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68948 | SiYuan: Information Disclosure and Authentication Bypass via Hardcoded Session Secret</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68948</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. In versions 3.5.1 and prior, the SiYuan Note application utilizes a hardcoded cryptographic secret for its session store. This unsafe practice renders the session encryption ineffective. Since the sensitive AccessAuthCode is stored within the session cookie, an attacker who intercepts or obtains a user's encrypted session cookie (e.g., via session hijacking) can locally decrypt it using the public key. Once decrypted, the attacker can retrieve the AccessAuthCode in plain text and use it to authenticate or take over the session.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68952 | 1-click Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in Eigent</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68952</link><description>Eigent is a multi-agent Workforce. In version 0.0.60, a 1-click Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability has been identified in Eigent. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim's machine or server through a specific interaction (1-click). This issue has been patched in version 0.0.61.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68473 | ESF-IDF Has Out-of-Bounds Read in ESP32 Bluetooth SDP Result Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68473</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In versions 5.5.1, 5.4.3, 5.3.4, 5.2.6, 5.1.6, and earlier, in the ESP-IDF Bluetooth host stack (BlueDroid), the function bta_dm_sdp_result() used a fixed-size array uuid_list[32][MAX_UUID_SIZE] to store discovered service UUIDs during the SDP (Service Discovery Protocol) process. On modern Bluetooth devices, it is possible for the number of available services to exceed this fixed limit (32). In such cases, if more than 32 services are discovered, subsequent writes to uuid_list could exceed the bounds of the array, resulting in a potential out-of-bounds write condition.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68474 | ESF-IDF Has Out-of-Bounds Write in ESP32 Bluetooth AVRCP Vendor Command Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68474</link><description>ESF-IDF is the Espressif Internet of Things (IOT) Development Framework. In versions 5.5.1, 5.4.3, 5.3.4, 5.2.6, 5.1.6, and earlier, in the avrc_vendor_msg() function of the ESP-IDF BlueDroid AVRCP stack, the allocated buffer size was validated using AVRC_MIN_CMD_LEN (20 bytes). However, the actual fixed header data written before the vendor payload exceeds this value. This totals 29 bytes written before p_msg-&gt;p_vendor_data is copied. Using the old AVRC_MIN_CMD_LEN could allow an out-of-bounds write if vendor_len approaches the buffer limit. For commands where vendor_len is large, the original buffer allocation may be insufficient, causing writes beyond the allocated memory. This can lead to memory corruption, crashes, or other undefined behavior. The overflow could be larger when assertions are disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68148 | FreshRSS globally denies access to feed via proxy modifying to 429 Retry-After</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68148</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. From version 1.27.0 to before 1.28.0, An attacker could globally deny access to feeds via proxy modifying to 429 Retry-After for a large list of feeds on given instance, making it unusable for majority of users. This issue has been patched in version 1.28.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68932 | FreshRSS has weak cryptographic randomness in remember-me token and nonce generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68932</link><description>FreshRSS is a free, self-hostable RSS aggregator. Prior to version 1.28.0, FreshRSS uses cryptographically weak random number generators (mt_rand() and uniqid()) to generate remember-me authentication tokens and challenge-response nonces. This allows attackers to predict valid session tokens, leading to account takeover through persistent session hijacking. The remember-me tokens provide permanent authentication and are the sole credential for "keep me logged in" functionality. This issue has been patched in version 1.28.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66203 | StreamVault is Vulnerable to Authenticated Remote Code Execution (RCE) via ytdlpargs Configuration Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66203</link><description>StreamVault is a video download integration solution. Prior to version 251126, a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in the stream-vault application (SpiritApplication). The application allows administrators to configure yt-dlp arguments via the /admin/api/saveConfig endpoint without sufficient validation. These arguments are stored globally and subsequently used in YtDlpUtil.java when constructing the command line to execute yt-dlp. This issue has been patched in version 251126.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:48:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67729 | lmdeploy vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution via Insecure Deserialization in torch.load()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67729</link><description>LMDeploy is a toolkit for compressing, deploying, and serving LLMs. Prior to version 0.11.1, an insecure deserialization vulnerability exists in lmdeploy where torch.load() is called without the weights_only=True parameter when loading model checkpoint files. This allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code on the victim's machine when they load a malicious .bin or .pt model file. This issue has been patched in version 0.11.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68697 | Self-hosted n8n has Legacy Code node that enables arbitrary file read/write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68697</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to version 2.0.0, in self-hosted n8n instances where the Code node runs in legacy (non-task-runner) JavaScript execution mode, authenticated users with workflow editing access can invoke internal helper functions from within the Code node. This allows a workflow editor to perform actions on the n8n host with the same privileges as the n8n process, including: reading files from the host filesystem (subject to any file-access restrictions configured on the instance and OS/container permissions), and writing files to the host filesystem (subject to the same restrictions). This issue has been patched in version 2.0.0. Workarounds for this issue involve limiting file operations by setting N8N_RESTRICT_FILE_ACCESS_TO to a dedicated directory (e.g., ~/.n8n-files) and ensure it contains no sensitive data, keeping N8N_BLOCK_FILE_ACCESS_TO_N8N_FILES=true (default) to block access to .n8n and user-defined config files, and disabling high-risk nodes (including the Code node) using NODES_EXCLUDE if workflow editors are not fully trusted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61914 | n8n&amp;#x27;s Possible Stored XSS in &amp;quot;Respond to Webhook&amp;quot; Node May Execute Outside iframe Sandbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61914</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. Prior to version 1.114.0, a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability may occur in n8n when using the “Respond to Webhook” node. When this node responds with HTML content containing executable scripts, the payload may execute directly in the top-level window, rather than within the expected sandbox introduced in version 1.103.0. This behavior can enable a malicious actor with workflow creation permissions to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the n8n editor interface. This issue has been patched in version 1.114.0. Workarounds for this issue involve restricting workflow creation and modification privileges to trusted users only, avoiding use of untrusted HTML responses in the “Respond to Webhook” node, and using an external reverse proxy or HTML sanitizer to filter responses that include executable scripts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:54:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68668 | n8n Vulnerable to Arbitrary Command Execution in Pyodide based Python Code Node</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68668</link><description>n8n is an open source workflow automation platform. From version 1.0.0 to before 2.0.0, a sandbox bypass vulnerability exists in the Python Code Node that uses Pyodide. An authenticated user with permission to create or modify workflows can exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands on the host system running n8n, using the same privileges as the n8n process. This issue has been patched in version 2.0.0. Workarounds for this issue involve disabling the Code Node by setting the environment variable NODES_EXCLUDE: "[\"n8n-nodes-base.code\"]", disabling Python support in the Code node by setting the environment variable N8N_PYTHON_ENABLED=false, which was introduced in n8n version 1.104.0, and configuring n8n to use the task runner based Python sandbox via the N8N_RUNNERS_ENABLED and N8N_NATIVE_PYTHON_RUNNER environment variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:54:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44065 | Time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability in Cloudlog v2.6.15 at the endpoint /index.php/logbookadvanced/search in the qsoresults paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44065</link><description>Time-based blind SQL Injection vulnerability in Cloudlog v2.6.15 at the endpoint /index.php/logbookadvanced/search in the qsoresults parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42718 | A path traversal vulnerability in Croogo CMS 4.0.7 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a specially crafted path in the 'edit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42718</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in Croogo CMS 4.0.7 allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files via a specially crafted path in the 'edit-file' parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:34:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66737 | Yealink T21P_E2 Phone 52.84.0.15 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. A remote normal privileged attacker can read arbitrary files via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66737</link><description>Yealink T21P_E2 Phone 52.84.0.15 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. A remote normal privileged attacker can read arbitrary files via a crafted request result read function of the diagnostic component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66738 | An issue in Yealink T21P_E2 Phone 52.84.0.15 allows a remote normal privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66738</link><description>An issue in Yealink T21P_E2 Phone 52.84.0.15 allows a remote normal privileged attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted request the ping function of the diagnostic component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:34:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13158 | apidoc-core - prototype pollution in api_group.js, api_param_title.js, api_use.js, and api_permission.js worker</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13158</link><description>Prototype pollution vulnerability in apidoc-core versions 0.2.0 and all subsequent versions allows remote attackers to modify JavaScript object prototypes via malformed data structures, including the “define” property processed by the application, potentially leading to denial of service or unintended behavior in applications relying on the integrity of prototype chains. This affects the preProcess() function in api_group.js, api_param_title.js, api_use.js, and api_permission.js worker modules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57403 | Cola Dnslog v1.3.2 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. When a DNS query for a TXT record is processed, the application concatenates the re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57403</link><description>Cola Dnslog v1.3.2 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal. When a DNS query for a TXT record is processed, the application concatenates the requested URL (or a portion of it) directly with a base path using os.path.join. This bypass allows directory traversal or absolute path injection, leading to the potential exposure of sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:34:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29720 | An issue in Terra Informatica Software, Inc Sciter v.4.4.7.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the adopt component...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29720</link><description>An issue in Terra Informatica Software, Inc Sciter v.4.4.7.0 allows a local attacker to obtain sensitive information via the adopt component of the Sciter video rendering function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67014 | Incorrect access control in DEV Systemtechnik GmbH DEV 7113 RF over Fiber Distribution System 32-0078 H.01 allows unauthenticated attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67014</link><description>Incorrect access control in DEV Systemtechnik GmbH DEV 7113 RF over Fiber Distribution System 32-0078 H.01 allows unauthenticated attackers to access an administrative endpoint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67013 | The web management interface in ETL Systems Ltd DEXTRA Series ' Digital L-Band Distribution System v1.8 does not implement Cross-Site Reques...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67013</link><description>The web management interface in ETL Systems Ltd DEXTRA Series ' Digital L-Band Distribution System v1.8 does not implement Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protection mechanisms (no tokens, no Origin/Referer validation) on critical configuration endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67015 | Incorrect access control in Comtech EF Data CDM-625 / CDM-625A Advanced Satellite Modem with firmware v2.5.1 allows attackers to change the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67015</link><description>Incorrect access control in Comtech EF Data CDM-625 / CDM-625A Advanced Satellite Modem with firmware v2.5.1 allows attackers to change the Administrator password and escalate privileges via sending a crafted POST request to /Forms/admin_access_1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:27:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25341 | A vulnerability exists in the libxmljs 1.0.11 when parsing a specially crafted XML document. Accessing the internal _ref property on entity_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25341</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the libxmljs 1.0.11 when parsing a specially crafted XML document. Accessing the internal _ref property on entity_ref and entity_decl nodes causes a segmentation fault, potentially leading to a denial-of-service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:27:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66947 | SQL injection vulnerability in krishanmuraiji SMS v.1.0, within the /studentms/admin/edit-class-detail.php via the editid GET parameter. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66947</link><description>SQL injection vulnerability in krishanmuraiji SMS v.1.0, within the /studentms/admin/edit-class-detail.php via the editid GET parameter. An attacker can trigger controlled delays using SQL SLEEP() to infer database contents. Successful exploitation may lead to full database compromise, especially within an administrative module.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67349 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in FluentCMS 1.2.3. After logging in as an admin and navigating to the "Add Page" ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67349</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in FluentCMS 1.2.3. After logging in as an admin and navigating to the "Add Page" function, the application fails to properly sanitize input in the  section, allowing remote attackers to inject arbitrary script tags.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-65885 | An issue was discovered in the Delight Custom Firmware (CFW) for Nokia Symbian Belle devices on Nokia 808 (Delight v1.8), Nokia N8 (Delight ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-65885</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Delight Custom Firmware (CFW) for Nokia Symbian Belle devices on Nokia 808 (Delight v1.8), Nokia N8 (Delight v6.7), Nokia E7 (Delight v1.3), Nokia C7 (Delight v6.7), Nokia 700 (Delight v1.2), Nokia 701 (Delight v1.1), Nokia 603 (Delight v1.0), Nokia 500 (Delight v1.2), Nokia E6 (Delight v1.0), Nokia Oro (Delight v1.0), and Vertu Constellation T (Delight v1.0) allowing local attackers to inject startup scripts via crafted .txt files in the :\Data directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36230 | XSS in IBM Aspera Faspex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36230</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5 5.0.0 through 5.0.14.1 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64645 | Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) in IBM Concert Software.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64645</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 could allow a local user to escalate their privileges due to a race condition of a symbolic link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36228 | Incorrect Execution-Assigned Permissions in IBM Aspera Faspex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36228</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5 5.0.0 through 5.0.14.1 may allow inconsistent permissions between the user interface and backend API allowed users to access features that appeared disabled, potentially leading to misuse.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36229 | Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere in IBM Aspera Faspex</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36229</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5 5.0.0 through 5.0.14.1 could allow authenticated users to enumerate sensitive information of data due by enumerating package identifiers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36192 | Missing Authorization with the DS8900F and DS8A00 Hardware Management Console</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36192</link><description>IBM DS8A00( R10.1) 10.10.106.0 and IBM DS8A00 ( R10.0) 10.1.3.010.2.45.0 and IBM DS8900F ( R9.4) 89.40.83.089.42.18.089.44.5.0 IBM System Storage DS8000 could allow a local user with authorized CCW update permissions to delete or corrupt backups due to missing authorization in IBM Safeguarded Copy / GDPS Logical corruption protection mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:14:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13915 | Authentication bypass in IBM API Connect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13915</link><description>IBM API Connect 10.0.8.0 through 10.0.8.5, and 10.0.11.0 could allow a remote attacker to bypass authentication mechanisms and gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14687 | Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security in IBM Db2 Intelligence Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14687</link><description>IBM Db2 Intelligence Center 1.1.0, 1.1.1, 1.1.2 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to client-side enforcement of sever side security mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12771 | IBM Concert Software Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12771</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1721 | BM Concert Software Improper Clearing of Heap Memory Before Release.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1721</link><description>IBM Concert 1.0.0 through 2.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information from allocated memory due to improper clearing of heap memory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67450 | Due to insecure library loading in the Eaton UPS Companion software executable, an attacker with access to the software package

 could perf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67450</link><description>Due to insecure library loading in the Eaton UPS Companion software executable, an attacker with access to the software package

 could perform arbitrary code execution . This security issue has been fixed in the latest version of EUC which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:23:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59887 | Improper authentication of library files in the Eaton UPS Companion software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59887</link><description>Improper authentication of library files in the Eaton UPS Companion software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker with the access to the software package.  This security issue has been fixed in the latest version of EUC which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59888 | Improper quotation in search paths in the Eaton UPS Companion software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59888</link><description>Improper quotation in search paths in the Eaton UPS Companion software installer could lead to arbitrary code execution of an attacker with the access to the 

file system.  This security issue has been fixed in the latest version of EUC which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:58:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62578 | DVP-12SE - Modbus/TCP Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62578</link><description>DVP-12SE - Modbus/TCP Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52601 | Hardcoding sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52601</link><description>Cybersecurity Nozomi Networks Labs, a specialized security company focused on Industrial Control Systems (ICS) and OT/IoT security, has discovered a vulnerability in Device Manager that a hardcoded encryption key for sensitive information. An attacker can use key to decrypt sensitive information. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8075 | Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8075</link><description>Cybersecurity Nozomi Networks Labs, a specialized security company focused on Industrial Control Systems (ICS) and OT/IoT security, has discovered that validation of incoming XML format request messages is inadequate. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to XSS on the user's browser. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52598 | Insufficient certificate validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52598</link><description>Cybersecurity Nozomi Networks Labs, a specialized security company focused on Industrial Control Systems (ICS) and OT/IoT security, has found a flaw that camera's client service does not perform certificate validation. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52599 | Inadequate account permissions management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52599</link><description>Cybersecurity Nozomi Networks Labs, a specialized security company focused on Industrial Control Systems (ICS) and OT/IoT security, has discovered Inadequate of permission management for camera guest account. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52600 | Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52600</link><description>Cybersecurity Nozomi Networks Labs, a specialized security company focused on Industrial Control Systems (ICS) and OT/IoT security, has discovered a vulnerability in camera video analytics that Improper input validation. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute specific commands on the user's host PC.The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68946 | In Gitea before 1.20.1, a forbidden URL scheme such as javascript: can be used for a link, aka XSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68946</link><description>In Gitea before 1.20.1, a forbidden URL scheme such as javascript: can be used for a link, aka XSS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15099 | simstudioai sim CRON Secret internal.ts improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15099</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in simstudioai sim up to 0.5.27. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file apps/sim/lib/auth/internal.ts of the component CRON Secret Handler. The manipulation of the argument INTERNAL_API_SECRET leads to improper authentication. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The identifier of the patch is e359dc2946b12ed5e45a0ec9c95ecf91bd18502a. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:11:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68945 | In Gitea before 1.21.2, an anonymous user can visit a private user's project.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68945</link><description>In Gitea before 1.21.2, an anonymous user can visit a private user's project.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68943 | Gitea before 1.21.8 inadvertently discloses users' login times by allowing (for example) the lastlogintime explore/users sort order.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68943</link><description>Gitea before 1.21.8 inadvertently discloses users' login times by allowing (for example) the lastlogintime explore/users sort order.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68944 | Gitea before 1.22.2 sometimes mishandles the propagation of token scope for access control within one of its own package registries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68944</link><description>Gitea before 1.22.2 sometimes mishandles the propagation of token scope for access control within one of its own package registries.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 04:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15098 | YunaiV yudao-cloud Business Process Management BpmSyncHttpRequestTrigger server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15098</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in YunaiV yudao-cloud up to 2025.11. This affects the function BpmHttpCallbackTrigger/BpmSyncHttpRequestTrigger of the component Business Process Management. Executing manipulation of the argument url/header/body can lead to server-side request forgery. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68942 | Gitea before 1.22.2 allows XSS because the search input box (for creating tags and branches) is v-html instead of v-text.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68942</link><description>Gitea before 1.22.2 allows XSS because the search input box (for creating tags and branches) is v-html instead of v-text.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15095 | postmanlabs httpbin core.py cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15095</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in postmanlabs httpbin up to 0.6.1. This affects an unknown function of the file httpbin-master/httpbin/core.py. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15097 | Alteryx Server status improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15097</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Alteryx Server. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /gallery/api/status/. Performing manipulation results in improper authentication. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. Upgrading to version 2023.1.1.13.486, 2023.2.1.10.293, 2024.1.1.9.236, 2024.2.1.6.125 and 2025.1.1.1.31 can resolve this issue. Upgrading the affected component is recommended.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68939 | Gitea before 1.23.0 allows attackers to add attachments with forbidden file extensions by editing an attachment name via an attachment API.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68939</link><description>Gitea before 1.23.0 allows attackers to add attachments with forbidden file extensions by editing an attachment name via an attachment API.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68940 | In Gitea before 1.22.5, branch deletion permissions are not adequately enforced after merging a pull request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68940</link><description>In Gitea before 1.22.5, branch deletion permissions are not adequately enforced after merging a pull request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68941 | Gitea before 1.22.3 mishandles access to a private resource upon receiving an API token with scope limited to public resources.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68941</link><description>Gitea before 1.22.3 mishandles access to a private resource upon receiving an API token with scope limited to public resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15094 | sunkaifei FlyCMS User Login UserController.java userLogin cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15094</link><description>A weakness has been identified in sunkaifei FlyCMS up to abbaa5a8daefb146ad4d61027035026b052cb414. The impacted element is the function userLogin of the file src/main/java/com/flycms/web/front/UserController.java of the component User Login. Executing manipulation of the argument redirectUrl can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68938 | Gitea before 1.25.2 mishandles authorization for deletion of releases.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68938</link><description>Gitea before 1.25.2 mishandles authorization for deletion of releases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15093 | sunkaifei FlyCMS Admin Login IndexAdminController.java cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15093</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in sunkaifei FlyCMS up to abbaa5a8daefb146ad4d61027035026b052cb414. The affected element is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/com/flycms/web/system/IndexAdminController.java of the component Admin Login. Performing manipulation of the argument redirectUrl results in cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15092 | UTT 进取 512W ConfigExceptMSN strcpy buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15092</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in UTT 进取 512W up to 1.7.7-171114. Impacted is the function strcpy of the file /goform/ConfigExceptMSN. Such manipulation of the argument remark leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 01:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>