<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:25:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-1932 | Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Appointment Status Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1932</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin – Bookr plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the update-appointment REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the status of any appointment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:25:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2469 | Versions of the package directorytree/imapengine before 1.22.3 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2469</link><description>Versions of the package directorytree/imapengine before 1.22.3 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') via the id() function in ImapConnection.php due to improperly escaping user input before including it in IMAP ID commands. This allows attackers to read or delete victim's emails, terminate the victim's session or execute any valid IMAP command on victim's mailbox by including quote characters " or CRLF sequences \r\n in the input.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0692 | BlueSnap Payment Gateway for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Order Status Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0692</link><description>The BlueSnap Payment Gateway for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.0. This is due to the plugin relying on WooCommerce's `WC_Geolocation::get_ip_address()` function to validate IPN requests, which trusts user-controllable headers like X-Real-IP and X-Forwarded-For to determine the client IP address. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass IP allowlist restrictions by spoofing a whitelisted BlueSnap IP address and send forged IPN (Instant Payment Notification) data to manipulate order statuses (mark orders as paid, failed, refunded, or on-hold) without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1164 | Easy Voice Mail &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;message&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1164</link><description>The Easy Voice Mail plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘message’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1754 | personal-authors-category &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1754</link><description>The personal-authors-category plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the URL path in all versions up to, and including, 0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1904 | Simple Wp colorfull Accordion &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;title&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1904</link><description>The Simple Wp colorfull Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter in the 'accordion' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1912 | Citations tools &amp;lt;= 0.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;code&amp;#x27; Shortcode Attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1912</link><description>The Citations tools plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'code' parameter in the 'ctdoi' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1983 | SEATT: Simple Event Attendance &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Event Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1983</link><description>The SEATT: Simple Event Attendance plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on the event deletion functionality. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary events via a forged request granted they can trick an administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2027 | AMP Enhancer &amp;lt;= 1.0.49 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via AMP Custom CSS Setting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2027</link><description>The AMP Enhancer – Compatibility Layer for Official AMP Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the AMP Custom CSS setting in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.49 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2144 | Magic Login Mail or QR Code &amp;lt;= 2.05 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Insecure QR Code File Storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2144</link><description>The Magic Login Mail or QR Code plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.05. This is due to the plugin storing the magic login QR code image with a predictable, static filename (QR_Code.png) in the publicly accessible WordPress uploads directory during the email sending process. The file is only deleted after wp_mail() completes, creating an exploitable race condition window. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to trigger a login link request for any user, including administrators, and then exploit the race condition between QR code file creation and deletion to obtain the login URL encoded in the QR code, thereby gaining unauthorized access to the targeted user's account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13681 | BFG Tools – Extension Zipper &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Path Traversal via &amp;#x27;first_file&amp;#x27; Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13681</link><description>The BFG Tools – Extension Zipper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7. This is due to insufficient input validation on the user-supplied `first_file` parameter in the `zip()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files and directories outside the intended `/wp-content/plugins/` directory, which can contain sensitive information such as wp-config.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13973 | StickEasy Protected Contact Form &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Unauthenticated Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13973</link><description>The StickEasy Protected Contact Form plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2. The plugin stores spam detection logs at a predictable publicly accessible location (wp-content/uploads/stickeasy-protected-contact-form/spcf-log.txt). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download the log file and access sensitive information including visitor IP addresses, email addresses, and comment snippets from contact form submissions that were flagged as spam.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14067 | Easy Form Builder &amp;lt;= 3.9.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Form Response Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14067</link><description>The Easy Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on multiple AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve sensitive form response data, including messages, admin replies, and user information due to a logic error in the authorization check that uses AND (&amp;&amp;) instead of OR (||).</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14608 | WP Last Modified Info &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Author+) Post Metadata Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14608</link><description>The WP Last Modified Info plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.5. This is due to the plugin not validating a user's access to a post before modifying its metadata in the 'bulk_save' AJAX action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to update the last modified metadata and lock the modification date of arbitrary posts, including those created by Administrators via the 'post_ids' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:55:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24853 | Caido has an insufficient patch for DNS rebind leading to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24853</link><description>Caido is a web security auditing toolkit. Prior to 0.55.0, Caido blocks non whitelisted domains to reach out through the 8080 port, and shows Host/IP is not allowed to connect to Caido on all endpoints. But this is bypassable by injecting a X-Forwarded-Host: 127.0.0.1:8080 header. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.55.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69633 | A SQL Injection vulnerability in the Advanced Popup Creator (advancedpopupcreator) module for PrestaShop 1.1.26 through 1.2.6 (Fixed in vers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69633</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability in the Advanced Popup Creator (advancedpopupcreator) module for PrestaShop 1.1.26 through 1.2.6 (Fixed in version 1.2.7) allows remote unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary SQL queries via the fromController parameter in the popup controller. The parameter is passed unsanitized to SQL queries in classes/AdvancedPopup.php (getPopups() and updateVisits() functions).</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70957 | A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability was discovered in the TON Lite Server before v2024.09. The vulnerability arises from the handling of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70957</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability was discovered in the TON Lite Server before v2024.09. The vulnerability arises from the handling of external arguments passed to locally executed "get methods." An attacker can inject a constructed Continuation object (an internal TVM type) that is normally restricted within the VM. When the TVM executes this malicious continuation, it consumes excessive CPU resources while accruing disproportionately low virtual gas costs. This "free" computation allows an attacker to monopolize the Lite Server's processing power, significantly reducing its throughput and causing a denial of service for legitimate users acting through the gateway.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26273 | Known affected by Account Takeover via Password Reset Token Leakage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26273</link><description>Known is a social publishing platform. Prior to 1.6.3, a Critical Broken Authentication vulnerability exists in Known 1.6.2 and earlier. The application leaks the password reset token within a hidden HTML input field on the password reset page. This allows any unauthenticated attacker to retrieve the reset token for any user by simply querying the user's email, leading to full Account Takeover (ATO) without requiring access to the victim's email inbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15157 | Starfish Review Generation &amp;amp; Marketing for WordPress &amp;lt;= 3.1.19 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update via srm_restore_options_defaults</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15157</link><description>The Starfish Review Generation &amp; Marketing for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'srm_restore_options_defaults' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70866 | LavaLite CMS 10.1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An authenticated user with low-level privileges (User role) can directly acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70866</link><description>LavaLite CMS 10.1.0 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. An authenticated user with low-level privileges (User role) can directly access the admin backend by logging in through /admin/login. The vulnerability exists because the admin and user authentication guards share the same user provider without role-based access control verification.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70954 | A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability exists in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) within the TON Blockchain before v2025.06. The issue is loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70954</link><description>A Null Pointer Dereference vulnerability exists in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) within the TON Blockchain before v2025.06. The issue is located in the execution logic of the INMSGPARAM instruction, where the program fails to validate if a specific pointer is null before accessing it. By sending a malicious transaction or smart contract, an attacker can trigger this null pointer dereference, causing the validator node process to crash (segmentation fault). This results in a Denial of Service (DoS) affecting the availability of the entire blockchain network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70955 | A Stack Overflow vulnerability was discovered in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) before v2024.10. The vulnerability stems from the improper ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70955</link><description>A Stack Overflow vulnerability was discovered in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) before v2024.10. The vulnerability stems from the improper handling of vmstate and continuation jump instructions, which allow for continuous dynamic tail calls. An attacker can exploit this by crafting a smart contract with deeply nested jump logic. Even within permissible gas limits, this nested execution exhausts the host process's stack space, causing the validator node to crash. This results in a Denial of Service (DoS) for the TON blockchain network.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1841 | PixelYourSite &amp;lt;= 11.2.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1841</link><description>The PixelYourSite – Your smart PIXEL (TAG) &amp; API Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pysTrafficSource' parameter and the 'pys_landing_page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 11.2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1844 | PixelYourSite PRO &amp;lt;= 12.4.0.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1844</link><description>The PixelYourSite PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'pysTrafficSource' parameter and the 'pys_landing_page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 12.4.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70956 | A State Pollution vulnerability was discovered in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) before v2025.04. The issue exists in the RUNVM instruction l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70956</link><description>A State Pollution vulnerability was discovered in the TON Virtual Machine (TVM) before v2025.04. The issue exists in the RUNVM instruction logic (VmState::run_child_vm), which is responsible for initializing child virtual machines. The operation moves critical resources (specifically libraries and log) from the parent state to a new child state in a non-atomic manner. If an Out-of-Gas (OOG) exception occurs after resources are moved but before the state transition is finalized, the parent VM retains a corrupted state where these resources are emptied/invalid. Because RUNVM supports gas isolation, the parent VM continues execution with this corrupted state, leading to unexpected behavior or denial of service within the contract's context.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26333 | Calero VeraSMART &amp;lt; 2022 R1 .NET Remoting Arbitrary File Read Leading to ViewState RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26333</link><description>Calero VeraSMART versions prior to 2022 R1 expose an unauthenticated .NET Remoting HTTP service on TCP port 8001. The service publishes default ObjectURIs (including EndeavorServer.rem and RemoteFileReceiver.rem) and permits the use of SOAP and binary formatters with TypeFilterLevel set to Full. An unauthenticated remote attacker can invoke the exposed remoting endpoints to perform arbitrary file read and write operations via the WebClient class. This allows retrieval of sensitive files such as WebRoot\\web.config, which may disclose IIS machineKey validation and decryption keys. An attacker can use these keys to generate a malicious ASP.NET ViewState payload and achieve remote code execution within the IIS application context. Additionally, supplying a UNC path can trigger outbound SMB authentication from the service account, potentially exposing NTLMv2 hashes for relay or offline cracking.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26334 | Calero VeraSMART &amp;lt; 2026 R1 Hardcoded Static AES Keys Allow Decryption of Service Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26334</link><description>Calero VeraSMART versions prior to 2026 R1 contain hardcoded static AES encryption keys within Veramark.Framework.dll (Veramark.Core.Config class). These keys are used to encrypt the password of the service account stored in C:\\VeraSMART Data\\app.settings. An attacker with local access to the system can extract the hardcoded keys from the Veramark.Framework.dll module and decrypt the stored credentials. The recovered credentials can then be used to authenticate to the Windows host, potentially resulting in local privilege escalation depending on the privileges of the configured service account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26335 | Calero VeraSMART &amp;lt; 2022 R1 Static IIS Machine Keys Enable ViewState RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26335</link><description>Calero VeraSMART versions prior to 2022 R1 use static ASP.NET/IIS machineKey values configured for the VeraSMART web application and stored in C:\\Program Files (x86)\\Veramark\\VeraSMART\\WebRoot\\web.config. An attacker who obtains these keys can craft a valid ASP.NET ViewState payload that passes integrity validation and is accepted by the application, resulting in server-side deserialization and remote code execution in the context of the IIS application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26269 | Vim has a Netbeans specialKeys Stack Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26269</link><description>Vim is an open source, command line text editor. Prior to 9.1.2148, a stack buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Vim's NetBeans integration when processing the specialKeys command, affecting Vim builds that enable and use the NetBeans feature. The Stack buffer overflow exists in special_keys() (in src/netbeans.c). The while (*tok) loop writes two bytes per iteration into a 64-byte stack buffer (keybuf) with no bounds check. A malicious NetBeans server can overflow keybuf with a single specialKeys command. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.2148.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:49:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26190 | Milvus Allows Unauthenticated Access to Restful API on Metrics Port (9091) Leads to Critical System Compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26190</link><description>Milvus is an open-source vector database built for generative AI applications. Prior to 2.5.27 and 2.6.10, Milvus exposes TCP port 9091 by default, which enables authentication bypasses. The /expr debug endpoint uses a weak, predictable default authentication token derived from etcd.rootPath (default: by-dev), enabling arbitrary expression evaluation. The full REST API (/api/v1/*) is registered on the metrics/management port without any authentication, allowing unauthenticated access to all business operations including data manipulation and credential management. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.27 and 2.6.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26208 | ADB Explorer Vulnerable to Remote Code Execution via Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26208</link><description>ADB Explorer is a fluent UI for ADB on Windows. Prior to Beta 0.9.26020, ADB Explorer is vulnerable to Insecure Deserialization leading to Remote Code Execution. The application attempts to deserialize the App.txt settings file using Newtonsoft.Json with TypeNameHandling set to Objects. This allows an attacker to supply a crafted JSON file containing a gadget chain (e.g., ObjectDataProvider) to execute arbitrary code when the application launches and subsequently saves its settings. This vulnerability is fixed in Beta 0.9.26020.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25964 | Tandoor Recipes Affected by Authenticated Local File Disclosure (LFD) via Recipe Import leads to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25964</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. Prior to 2.5.1, a Path Traversal vulnerability in the RecipeImport workflow of Tandoor Recipes allows authenticated users with import permissions to read arbitrary files on the server. This vulnerability stems from a lack of input validation in the file_path parameter and insufficient checks in the Local storage backend, enabling an attacker to bypass storage directory restrictions and access sensitive system files (e.g., /etc/passwd) or application configuration files (e.g., settings.py), potentially leading to full system compromise. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25991 | Tandoor Recipes affected by Blind SSRF with Internal Network Access via Recipe Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25991</link><description>Tandoor Recipes is an application for managing recipes, planning meals, and building shopping lists. Prior to 2.5.1, there is a Blind Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in the Cookmate recipe import feature of Tandoor Recipes. The application fails to validate the destination URL after following HTTP redirects, allowing any authenticated user (including standard users without administrative privileges) to force the server to connect to arbitrary internal or external resources. The vulnerability lies in cookbook/integration/cookmate.py, within the Cookmate integration class. This vulnerability can be leveraged to scan internal network ports, access cloud instance metadata (e.g., AWS/GCP Metadata Service), or disclose the server's real IP address. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26187 | lakeFS vulnerable to path traversal in local block adapter allow cross-namespace and sibling directory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26187</link><description>lakeFS is an open-source tool that transforms object storage into a Git-like repositories. Prior to 1.77.0, the local block adapter (pkg/block/local/adapter.go) allows authenticated users to read and write files outside their designated storage boundaries. The verifyRelPath function used strings.HasPrefix() to verify that requested paths fall within the configured storage directory. This check was insufficient because it validated only the path prefix without requiring a path separator, allowing access to sibling directories with similar names. Also, the adapter verified that resolved paths stayed within the adapter's base path, but did not verify that object identifiers stayed within their designated storage namespace. This allowed attackers to use path traversal sequences in the object identifier to access files in other namespaces. Fixed in version v1.77.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2441 | Use after free in CSS in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.75 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2441</link><description>Use after free in CSS in Google Chrome prior to 145.0.7632.75 allowed a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code inside a sandbox via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21878 | BACnet Stack Improperly Limits Pathnames to a Restricted Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21878</link><description>BACnet Stack is a BACnet open source protocol stack C library for embedded systems. Prior to 1.5.0.rc3, a vulnerability has been discovered in BACnet Stack's file writing functionality where there is no validation of user-provided file paths, allowing attackers to write files to arbitrary directories. This affects apps/readfile/main.c and ports/posix/bacfile-posix.c. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.0.rc3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26264 | BACnet Stack WriteProperty decoding length underflow leads to OOB read and crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26264</link><description>BACnet Stack is a BACnet open source protocol stack C library for embedded systems. Prior to 1.5.0rc4 and 1.4.3rc2, a malformed WriteProperty request can trigger a length underflow in the BACnet stack, leading to an out‑of‑bounds read and a crash (DoS). The issue is in wp.c within wp_decode_service_request. When decoding the optional priority context tag, the code passes apdu_len - apdu_size to bacnet_unsigned_context_decode without validating that apdu_size &lt;= apdu_len. If a truncated APDU reaches this path, apdu_len - apdu_size underflows, resulting in a large size being used for decoding and an out‑of‑bounds read. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.0rc4 and 1.4.3rc2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:04:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21870 | The BACnet Protocol Stack library has an Off-by-one Stack-based Buffer Overflow in tokenizer_string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21870</link><description>BACnet Protocol Stack library provides a BACnet application layer, network layer and media access (MAC) layer communications services. In 1.4.2, 1.5.0.rc2, and earlier, an off-by-one stack-based buffer overflow in the ubasic interpreter causes a crash (SIGABRT) when processing string literals longer than the buffer limit. The tokenizer_string function in src/bacnet/basic/program/ubasic/tokenizer.c incorrectly handles null termination for maximum-length strings. It writes a null byte to dest[40] when the buffer size is only 40 (indices 0-39), triggering a stack overflow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:02:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69770 | A zip slip vulnerability in the /DesignTools/SkinList.aspx endpoint of MojoPortal CMS v2.9.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary command...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69770</link><description>A zip slip vulnerability in the /DesignTools/SkinList.aspx endpoint of MojoPortal CMS v2.9.0.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via uploading a crafted zip file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66676 | An issue in IObit Unlocker v1.3.0.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66676</link><description>An issue in IObit Unlocker v1.3.0.11 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1790 | Local privilege escalation in Genetec Sipelia Plugin. An authenticated low-privileged Windows user could exploit this vulnerability to gain ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1790</link><description>Local privilege escalation in Genetec Sipelia Plugin. An authenticated low-privileged Windows user could exploit this vulnerability to gain elevated privileges on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26268 | Cursor sandbox escape via Git hooks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26268</link><description>Cursor is a code editor built for programming with AI. Sandbox escape via writing .git configuration was possible in versions prior to 2.5. A malicious agent (ie prompt injection) could write to improperly protected .git settings, including git hooks, which may cause out-of-sandbox RCE next time they are triggered. No user interaction was required as Git executes these commands automatically. Fixed in version 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26226 | beautiful-mermaid &amp;lt; 0.1.3 SVG Attribute Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26226</link><description>beautiful-mermaid versions prior to 0.1.3 contain an SVG attribute injection issue that can lead to cross-site scripting (XSS) when rendering attacker-controlled Mermaid diagrams. User-controlled values from Mermaid style and classDef directives are interpolated into SVG attribute values without proper escaping, allowing crafted input to break out of an attribute context and inject arbitrary SVG elements/attributes into the rendered output. When the generated SVG is embedded in a web page, this can result in script execution in the context of the embedding origin.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:25:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70121 | An array index out of bounds vulnerability in the AMF component of free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70121</link><description>An array index out of bounds vulnerability in the AMF component of free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted 5GS Mobile Identity in a NAS Registration Request message. The issue occurs in the GetSUCI method (NAS_MobileIdentity5GS.go) when accessing index 5 of a 5-element array, leading to a runtime panic and AMF crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70122 | A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the UPF component of free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70122</link><description>A heap buffer overflow vulnerability in the UPF component of free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a crafted PFCP Session Modification Request. The issue occurs in the SDFFilterFields.UnmarshalBinary function (sdf-filter.go) when processing a declared length that exceeds the actual buffer capacity, leading to a runtime panic and UPF crash.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70123 | An improper input validation and protocol compliance vulnerability in free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70123</link><description>An improper input validation and protocol compliance vulnerability in free5GC v4.0.1 allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service. The UPF incorrectly accepts a malformed PFCP Association Setup Request, violating 3GPP TS 29.244. This places the UPF in an inconsistent state where a subsequent valid PFCP Session Establishment Request triggers a cascading failure, disrupting the SMF connection and causing service degradation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2026 | Improper Access Control Allows Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2026</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified where weak file permissions in the Nessus Agent directory on Windows hosts could allow unauthorized access, potentially permitting Denial of Service (DoS) attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70091 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Customers function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70091</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Customers function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Phone Number parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70093 | An issue in OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via returning a crafted AJAX response.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70093</link><description>An issue in OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via returning a crafted AJAX response.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70095 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the item management and sales invoice function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70095</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the item management and sales invoice function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70094 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Generate Item Barcode function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70094</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Generate Item Barcode function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Item Category parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26221 | Hyland OnBase Timer Services Unauthenticated .NET Remoting RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26221</link><description>Hyland OnBase contains an unauthenticated .NET Remoting exposure in the OnBase Workflow Timer Service (Hyland.Core.Workflow.NTService.exe) and is also reported by the vendor to impact the Workview Timer Service (an impacted version range is undefined). An attacker who can reach the service can send crafted .NET Remoting requests to default HTTP channel endpoints on TCP/8900 (e.g., TimerServiceAPI.rem and TimerServiceEvents.rem for Workflow) to trigger unsafe object unmarshalling, enabling arbitrary file read/write. By writing attacker-controlled content into web-accessible locations or chaining with other OnBase features, this can lead to remote code execution. The same primitive can be abused by supplying a UNC path to coerce outbound NTLM authentication (SMB coercion) to an attacker-controlled host.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1578 | HP App – Potential Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1578</link><description>HP App for Android is potentially vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) when using an outdated version of the application via mobile devices. HP is releasing updates to mitigate these potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25531 | Kanboard TaskCreationController::duplicateProjects() endpoint does not validate user permissions for target projects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25531</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Prior to 1.2.50, The fix for CVE-2023-33968 is incomplete. The TaskCreationController::duplicateProjects() endpoint does not validate user permissions for target projects, allowing authenticated users to duplicate tasks into projects they cannot access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.50.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23111 | netfilter: nf_tables: fix inverted genmask check in nft_map_catchall_activate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23111</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_tables: fix inverted genmask check in nft_map_catchall_activate()

nft_map_catchall_activate() has an inverted element activity check
compared to its non-catchall counterpart nft_mapelem_activate() and
compared to what is logically required.

nft_map_catchall_activate() is called from the abort path to re-activate
catchall map elements that were deactivated during a failed transaction.
It should skip elements that are already active (they don't need
re-activation) and process elements that are inactive (they need to be
restored). Instead, the current code does the opposite: it skips inactive
elements and processes active ones.

Compare the non-catchall activate callback, which is correct:

  nft_mapelem_activate():
    if (nft_set_elem_active(ext, iter-&gt;genmask))
        return 0;   /* skip active, process inactive */

With the buggy catchall version:

  nft_map_catchall_activate():
    if (!nft_set_elem_active(ext, genmask))
        continue;   /* skip inactive, process active */

The consequence is that when a DELSET operation is aborted,
nft_setelem_data_activate() is never called for the catchall element.
For NFT_GOTO verdict elements, this means nft_data_hold() is never
called to restore the chain-&gt;use reference count. Each abort cycle
permanently decrements chain-&gt;use. Once chain-&gt;use reaches zero,
DELCHAIN succeeds and frees the chain while catchall verdict elements
still reference it, resulting in a use-after-free.

This is exploitable for local privilege escalation from an unprivileged
user via user namespaces + nftables on distributions that enable
CONFIG_USER_NS and CONFIG_NF_TABLES.

Fix by removing the negation so the check matches nft_mapelem_activate():
skip active elements, process inactive ones.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23112 | nvmet-tcp: add bounds checks in nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23112</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet-tcp: add bounds checks in nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec

nvmet_tcp_build_pdu_iovec() could walk past cmd-&gt;req.sg when a PDU
length or offset exceeds sg_cnt and then use bogus sg-&gt;length/offset
values, leading to _copy_to_iter() GPF/KASAN. Guard sg_idx, remaining
entries, and sg-&gt;length/offset before building the bvec.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14349 | Business Logic Error in Universal Software&amp;#x27;s FlexCity/Kiosk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14349</link><description>Privilege Defined With Unsafe Actions, Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in Universal Software Inc. FlexCity/Kiosk allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs, Privilege Escalation.This issue affects FlexCity/Kiosk: from 1.0 before 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1618 | Admin Account Takeover in Universal Sotware&amp;#x27;s FlexCity/Kiosk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1618</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Universal Software Inc. FlexCity/Kiosk allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects FlexCity/Kiosk: from 1.0 before 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1619 | IDOR in Universal Sotware&amp;#x27;s FlexCity/Kiosk</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1619</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Universal Software Inc. FlexCity/Kiosk allows Exploitation of Trusted Identifiers.This issue affects FlexCity/Kiosk: from 1.0 before 1.0.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2443 | Libsoup: out-of-bounds read in libsoup handle_partial_get() leading to heap information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2443</link><description>A flaw was identified in libsoup, a widely used HTTP library in GNOME-based systems. When processing specially crafted HTTP Range headers, the library may improperly validate requested byte ranges. In certain build configurations, this could allow a remote attacker to access portions of server memory beyond the intended response. Exploitation requires a vulnerable configuration and access to a server using the embedded SoupServer component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33042 | Apache Avro Java SDK: Code injection on Java generated code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33042</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Apache Avro Java SDK when generating specific records from untrusted Avro schemas.

This issue affects Apache Avro Java SDK: all versions through 1.11.4 and version 1.12.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.12.1 or 1.11.5, which fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-20796 | Time-of-check time-of-use vulnerability in common teams API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-20796</link><description>Mattermost versions 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9 fail to properly validate channel membership at the time of data retrieval which allows a deactivated user to learn team names they should not have access to via a race condition in the /common_teams API endpoint.. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00549</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22892 | Insufficient Authorization in Mattermost Jira Plugin Allows Unauthorized Access to Post Attachments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22892</link><description>Mattermost versions 11.1.x &lt;= 11.1.2, 10.11.x &lt;= 10.11.9, 11.2.x &lt;= 11.2.1 fail to validate user permissions when creating Jira issues from Mattermost posts, which allows an authenticated attacker with access to the Jira plugin to read post content and attachments from channels they do not have access to via the /create-issue API endpoint by providing the post ID of an inaccessible post.. Mattermost Advisory ID: MMSA-2025-00550</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0872 | Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in Thales SafeNet Agent for Windows Logon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0872</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation vulnerability in Thales SafeNet Agent for Windows Logon on Windows allows Signature Spoofing by Improper Validation.This issue affects SafeNet Agent for Windows Logon: 4.0.0, 4.1.1, 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15520 | RegistrationMagic &amp;lt;= 6.0.7.2 - Subscriber+ Sensitive Data Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15520</link><description>The RegistrationMagic  WordPress plugin before 6.0.7.2 checks nonces but not capabilities, allowing for the disclosure of some sensitive data to subscribers and above.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 07:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48021 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48021</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciously crafted packets, Vnet/IP software stack process may be terminated.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48022 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48022</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciously crafted packets, Vnet/IP software stack process may be terminated.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:14:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48023 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48023</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciously crafted packets, Vnet/IP software stack process may be terminated.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1924 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receive malicious...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1924</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receive maliciously crafted packets, a DoS attack may cause Vnet/IP communication functions to stop or arbitrary programs to be executed.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48019 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48019</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciously crafted packets, Vnet/IP software stack process may be terminated.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48020 | A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48020</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vnet/IP Interface Package provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.
If affected product receives maliciously crafted packets, Vnet/IP software stack process may be terminated.
The affected products and versions are as follows: Vnet/IP Interface Package (for CENTUM VP R6 VP6C3300, CENTUM VP R7 VP7C3300) R1.07.00 or earlier</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25108 | FileZen contains an OS command injection vulnerability. When FileZen Antivirus Check Option is enabled, a logged-in user may send a speciall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25108</link><description>FileZen contains an OS command injection vulnerability. When FileZen Antivirus Check Option is enabled, a logged-in user may send a specially crafted HTTP request to execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:13:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1721 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in AI Playground site</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1721</link><description>Summary

A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was discovered in the AI Playground's OAuth callback handler. The `error_description` query parameter was directly interpolated into an HTML script tag without proper escaping, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of the victim's session.




Root cause

The OAuth callback handler in `site/ai-playground/src/server.ts` directly interpolated the `authError` value, sourced from the `error_description` query parameter,  into an inline `</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9292 | Permissive Web Security Policy Allows Cross-Origin Access Control Bypass on Omada Cloud Controllers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9292</link><description>A permissive web security configuration may allow cross-origin restrictions enforced by modern browsers to be bypassed under specific circumstances.  Exploitation requires the presence of an existing client-side injection vulnerability and user access to the affected web interface.  Successful exploitation could allow unauthorized disclosure of sensitive information. Fixed in updated Omada Cloud Controller service versions deployed automatically by TP‑Link. No user action is required.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9293 | Insufficient Certificate Validation in Multiple Mobile Applications Allows Man in the Middle Interception</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9293</link><description>A vulnerability in the certificate validation logic may allow applications to accept untrusted or improperly validated server identities during TLS communication. An attacker in a privileged network position may be able to intercept or modify traffic if they can position themselves within the communication channel.  Successful exploitation may compromise confidentiality, integrity, and availability of application data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21961 | Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in PCIe® Link could allow an attacker with access to a guest virtual...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21961</link><description>Improper restriction of operations within the bounds of a memory buffer in PCIe® Link could allow an attacker with access to a guest virtual machine to potentially perform a denial of service attack against the host resulting in loss of availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40905 | WWW::OAuth 1.000 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40905</link><description>WWW::OAuth 1.000 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25318 | AVS Audio Converter 9.1.2.600 - Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25318</link><description>AVS Audio Converter 9.1.2.600 contains a stack overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by manipulating the output folder text input. Attackers can craft a malicious payload that overwrites stack memory and triggers a bind shell on port 9999 when the 'Browse' button is clicked.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25319 | Domain Quester Pro 6.02 - Stack Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25319</link><description>Domain Quester Pro 6.02 contains a stack overflow vulnerability that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting Structured Exception Handler (SEH) registers. Attackers can craft a malicious payload targeting the 'Domain Name Keywords' input field to trigger an access violation and execute a bind shell on port 9999.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25320 | elearning-script 1.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25320</link><description>E Learning Script 1.0 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows attackers to access the dashboard without valid credentials by manipulating login parameters. Attackers can exploit the /login.php file by sending a specific payload '=''or' to bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access to the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25321 | FTP Navigator 8.03 - Stack Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25321</link><description>FTP Navigator 8.03 contains a stack overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting Structured Exception Handler (SEH) registers. Attackers can craft a malicious payload that triggers a buffer overflow when pasted into the Custom Command textbox, enabling remote code execution and launching the calculator as proof of concept.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25322 | Heatmiser Netmonitor 3.03 - Hardcoded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25322</link><description>Heatmiser Netmonitor 3.03 contains a hardcoded credentials vulnerability in the networkSetup.htm page with predictable admin login credentials. Attackers can access the device by using the hard-coded username 'admin' and password 'admin' in the hidden form input fields.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25323 | Heatmiser Netmonitor 3.03 - HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25323</link><description>Heatmiser Netmonitor v3.03 contains an HTML injection vulnerability in the outputSetup.htm page that allows attackers to inject malicious HTML code through the outputtitle parameter. Attackers can craft specially formatted POST requests to the outputtitle parameter to execute arbitrary HTML and potentially manipulate the web interface's displayed content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25324 | RICOH Web Image Monitor 1.09 - HTML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25324</link><description>RICOH Web Image Monitor 1.09 contains an HTML injection vulnerability in the address configuration CGI script that allows attackers to inject malicious HTML code. Attackers can exploit the entryNameIn and entryDisplayNameIn parameters to insert arbitrary HTML content, potentially enabling cross-site scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25325 | Thrive Smart Home 1.1 - &amp;#x27;Smart Home&amp;#x27; Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25325</link><description>Thrive Smart Home 1.1 contains an SQL injection vulnerability in the checklogin.php endpoint that allows unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication by manipulating the 'user' POST parameter. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code like ' or 1=1# to manipulate login queries and gain unauthorized access to the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25327 | Prime95 Version 29.8 build 6 - Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25327</link><description>Prime95 version 29.8 build 6 contains a buffer overflow vulnerability in the user ID input field that allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code. Attackers can craft a malicious payload and paste it into the PrimeNet user ID and proxy host fields to trigger a bind shell on port 3110.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25328 | XnConvert 1.82 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25328</link><description>XnConvert 1.82 contains a denial of service vulnerability in its registration code input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can generate a 9000-byte buffer of repeated characters and paste it into the registration code field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25329 | FTP Navigator 8.03 -  &amp;#x27;Custom Command&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25329</link><description>FTP Navigator 8.03 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by overwriting Structured Exception Handler (SEH) with malicious input. Attackers can generate a payload of 4108 'A' characters followed by 4 'B' characters and 40 'C' characters to trigger a program crash when pasted into the custom command input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25330 | SurfOffline Professional 2.2.0.103 - &amp;#x27;Project Name&amp;#x27; Denial of Service (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25330</link><description>SurfOffline Professional 2.2.0.103 contains a structured exception handler (SEH) overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to crash the application by manipulating the project name input. Attackers can generate a malicious payload of 382 'A' characters followed by specific byte sequences to trigger a denial of service condition and overwrite SEH registers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25331 | AVS Audio Converter 9.1 - &amp;#x27;Exit folder&amp;#x27; Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25331</link><description>AVS Audio Converter 9.1 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability that allows local attackers to overwrite CPU registers by manipulating the 'Exit folder' input field. Attackers can craft a specially designed text file with 264 bytes of padding followed by register overwrite values to compromise the application and potentially execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25332 | FTP Commander Pro 8.03 - Local Stack Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25332</link><description>FTP Commander Pro 8.03 contains a local stack overflow vulnerability that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by overwriting the EIP register through a custom command input. Attackers can craft a malicious payload of 4108 bytes to overwrite memory and execute shellcode, demonstrating remote code execution potential.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25333 | Bullwark Momentum Series JAWS 1.0 - &amp;#x27;Momentum Series JAWS&amp;#x27; Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25333</link><description>Bullwark Momentum Series JAWS 1.0 contains a directory traversal vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to access system files by manipulating HTTP request paths. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by sending crafted GET requests with multiple '../' sequences to read sensitive files like /etc/passwd outside the web root directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25334 | Product Key Explorer 4.2.0.0 - &amp;#x27;Name&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25334</link><description>Product Key Explorer 4.2.0.0 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows local attackers to crash the application by overflowing the registration name input field. Attackers can create a specially crafted text file with repeated characters to trigger a buffer overflow when pasted into the registration name field, causing the application to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25335 | PRO-7070 Hazır Profesyonel Web Sitesi 1.0 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25335</link><description>PRO-7070 Hazır Profesyonel Web Sitesi version 1.0 contains an authentication bypass vulnerability in the administration panel login page. Attackers can bypass authentication by using '=' 'or' as both username and password to gain unauthorized access to the administrative interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25336 | SpotAuditor 5.3.2 - &amp;#x27;Base64&amp;#x27; Local Buffer Overflow (SEH)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25336</link><description>SpotAuditor 5.3.2 contains a local buffer overflow vulnerability in the Base64 Encrypted Password tool that allows attackers to execute arbitrary code by crafting a malicious payload. Attackers can generate a specially crafted Base64 encoded payload to trigger a Structured Exception Handler (SEH) overwrite and execute shellcode on the vulnerable system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25337 | OwnCloud 8.1.8 - Username Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25337</link><description>OwnCloud 8.1.8 contains a username enumeration vulnerability that allows remote attackers to discover user accounts by manipulating the share.php endpoint. Attackers can send crafted GET requests to /index.php/core/ajax/share.php with a wildcard search parameter to retrieve comprehensive user information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25338 | Dokuwiki 2018-04-22b - Username Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25338</link><description>DokuWiki 2018-04-22b contains a username enumeration vulnerability in its password reset functionality that allows attackers to identify valid user accounts. Attackers can submit different usernames to the password reset endpoint and distinguish between existing and non-existing accounts by analyzing the server's error response messages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25339 | GHIA CamIP 1.2 for iOS - &amp;#x27;Password&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25339</link><description>GHIA CamIP 1.2 for iOS contains a denial of service vulnerability in the password input field that allows attackers to crash the application. Attackers can paste a 33-character buffer of repeated characters into the password field to trigger an application crash on iOS devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25340 | SpotAuditor 5.3.2 - &amp;#x27;Base64&amp;#x27; Denial Of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25340</link><description>SpotAuditor 5.3.2 contains a denial of service vulnerability in its Base64 decryption feature that allows attackers to crash the application by supplying an oversized buffer. Attackers can generate a malformed input file with 2000 repeated characters to trigger an application crash when pasted into the Base64 Encrypted Password field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25341 | iNetTools for iOS 8.20 - &amp;#x27;Whois&amp;#x27; Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25341</link><description>iNetTools for iOS 8.20 contains a denial of service vulnerability in the Whois feature that allows attackers to crash the application by manipulating input. Attackers can paste a specially crafted 98-character buffer into the Domain Name field to trigger an application crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25342 | Centova Cast 3.2.12 - Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25342</link><description>Centova Cast 3.2.12 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows attackers to overwhelm the system by repeatedly calling the database export API endpoint. Attackers can trigger 100% CPU load by sending multiple concurrent requests to the /api.php endpoint with crafted parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-37167 | ClamAV ClamBC &amp;lt;= 0.102.0 - &amp;#x27;ClamBC&amp;#x27; Executable Regular Expression Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-37167</link><description>ClamAV ClamBC bytecode interpreter contains a vulnerability in function name processing that allows attackers to manipulate bytecode function names. Attackers can exploit the weak input validation in function name encoding to potentially execute malicious bytecode or cause unexpected behavior in the ClamAV engine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26188 | Solspace Freeform plugin affected by Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in Freeform Craft Plugin CP UI (builder/integrations)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26188</link><description>Solspace Freeform plugin for Craft CMS 5.x is a super flexible form-building tool. An authenticated, low-privilege user (able to create/edit forms) can inject arbitrary HTML/JS into the Craft Control Panel (CP) builder and integrations views. User-controlled form labels and integration metadata are rendered with dangerouslySetInnerHTML without sanitization, leading to stored XSS that executes when any admin views the builder/integration screens. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:18:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70092 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Item Kits function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70092</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Item Kits function of OpenSourcePOS v3.4.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the Item Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26068 | emp3r0r Agent-Controlled Metadata to Operator RCE (tmux Command Injection)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26068</link><description>emp3r0r is a stealth-focused C2 designed by Linux users for Linux environments. Prior to 3.21.1, untrusted agent metadata (Transport, Hostname) is accepted during check-in and later interpolated into tmux shell command strings executed via /bin/sh -c. This enables command injection and remote code execution on the operator host. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.21.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26185 | Directus Affected by User Enumeration via Password Reset Timing Attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26185</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Before 11.14.1, a timing-based user enumeration vulnerability exists in the password reset functionality. When an invalid reset_url parameter is provided, the response time differs by approximately 500ms between existing and non-existing users, enabling reliable user enumeration. This vulnerability is fixed in 11.14.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26224 | Intego Log Reporter TOCTOU Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26224</link><description>Intego Log Reporter, a macOS diagnostic utility bundled with Intego security products that collects system and application logs for support analysis, contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A root-executed diagnostic script creates and writes files in /tmp without enforcing secure directory handling, introducing a time-of-check to time-of-use (TOCTOU) race condition. A local unprivileged user can exploit a symlink-based race condition to cause arbitrary file writes to privileged system locations, resulting in privilege escalation to root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26225 | Intego Personal Backup Task File Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26225</link><description>Intego Personal Backup, a macOS backup utility that allows users to create scheduled backups and bootable system clones, contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. Backup task definitions are stored in a location writable by non-privileged users while being processed with elevated privileges. By crafting a malicious serialized task file, a local attacker can trigger arbitrary file writes to sensitive system locations, leading to privilege escalation to root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 22:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14282 | privilege escalation via unix domain socket forwardings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14282</link><description>A flaw was found in Dropbear. When running in multi-user mode and authenticating users, the dropbear ssh server does the socket forwardings requested by the remote client as root, only switching to the logged-in user upon spawning a shell or performing some operations like reading the user's files. With the recent ability of also using unix domain sockets as the forwarding destination any user able to log in via ssh can connect to any unix socket with the root's credentials, bypassing both file system restrictions and any SO_PEERCRED / SO_PASSCRED checks performed by the peer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70845 | lty628 aidigu v1.9.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) exists in the /setting/ page where the "intro" field is not properly saniti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70845</link><description>lty628 aidigu v1.9.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) exists in the /setting/ page where the "intro" field is not properly sanitized or escaped.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26075 | Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) in FastGPT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26075</link><description>FastGPT is an AI Agent building platform. Due to the fact that FastGPT's web page acquisition nodes, HTTP nodes, etc. need to initiate data acquisition requests from the server, there are certain security issues. In addition to implementing internal network isolation in the deployment environment, this optimization has added stricter internal network address detection. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.14.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26076 | ntpd-rs affected by excessive CPU load from malformed packets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26076</link><description>ntpd-rs is a full-featured implementation of the Network Time Protocol. Prior to 1.7.1, an attacker can remotely induce moderate increases (2-4 times above normal) in cpu usage. When having NTS enabled on an ntpd-rs server, an attacker can create malformed NTS packets that take significantly more effort for the server to respond to by requesting a large number of cookies. This can lead to degraded server performance even when a server could otherwise handle the load. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1358 | Airleader Master Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1358</link><description>Airleader Master versions 6.381 and prior allow for file uploads without
 restriction to multiple webpages running maximum privileges. This could
 allow an unauthenticated user to potentially obtain remote code 
execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25828 | grub-btrfs through 2026-01-31 (on Arch Linux and derivative distributions) allows initramfs OS command injection because it does not sanitiz...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25828</link><description>grub-btrfs through 2026-01-31 (on Arch Linux and derivative distributions) allows initramfs OS command injection because it does not sanitize the $root parameter to resolve_device().</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26069 | Scraparr Readarr Integration exposes sensitive values as metric labels.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26069</link><description>Scraparr is a Prometheus Exporter for various components of the *arr Suite. From 3.0.0-beta to before 3.0.2, when the Readarr integration was enabled, the exporter exposed the configured Readarr API key as the alias metric label value. Users were affected only if all of the following conditions are met, Readarr scraping feature was enabled and no alias configured, the exporter’s /metrics endpoint was accessible to external or unauthorized users, and the Readarr instance is externally accessible. If the /metrics endpoint was publicly accessible, the Readarr API key could have been disclosed via exported metrics data. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26055 | Unauthenticated Admission Webhook Endpoints in Yoke ATC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26055</link><description>Yoke is a Helm-inspired infrastructure-as-code (IaC) package deployer. In 0.19.0 and earlier, a vulnerability exists in the Air Traffic Controller (ATC) component of Yoke. The ATC webhook endpoints lack proper authentication mechanisms, allowing any pod within the cluster network to directly send AdmissionReview requests to the webhook, bypassing Kubernetes API Server authentication. This enables attackers to trigger WASM module execution in the ATC controller context without proper authorization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26056 | Arbitrary WASM Code Execution via AnnotationOverrideFlight Injection in Yoke ATC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26056</link><description>Yoke is a Helm-inspired infrastructure-as-code (IaC) package deployer. In 0.19.0 and earlier, a vulnerability exists in the Air Traffic Controller (ATC) component of Yoke. It allows users with CR create/update permissions to execute arbitrary WASM code in the ATC controller context by injecting a malicious URL through the overrides.yoke.cd/flight annotation. The ATC controller downloads and executes the WASM module without proper URL validation, enabling attackers to create arbitrary Kubernetes resources or potentially escalate privileges to cluster-admin level.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26011 | Critical Heap Out-of-bounds Access in `pf_cluster_stats()` via Malicious /initialpose Covariance -- Potential Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26011</link><description>navigation2 is a ROS 2 Navigation Framework and System. In 1.3.11 and earlier, a critical heap out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in Nav2 AMCL's particle filter clustering logic. By publishing a single crafted geometry_msgs/PoseWithCovarianceStamped message with extreme covariance values to the /initialpose topic, an unauthenticated attacker on the same ROS 2 DDS domain can trigger a negative index write (set-&gt;clusters[-1]) into heap memory preceding the allocated buffer. In Release builds, the sole boundary check (assert) is compiled out, leaving zero runtime protection. This primitive allows controlled corruption of the heap chunk metadata(at least the size of the heap chunk where the set-&gt;clusters is in is controllable by the attacker), potentially leading to further exploitation. At minimum, it provides a reliable single-packet denial of service that kills localization and halts all navigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26020 | AutoGPT Affected by Remote Code Execution via Dynamic Module Import in Block Loading (__import__)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26020</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents that automate complex workflows. Prior to 0.6.48, an authenticated user could achieve Remote Code Execution (RCE) on the backend server by embedding a disabled block inside a graph. The BlockInstallationBlock — a development tool capable of writing and importing arbitrary Python code — was marked disabled=True, but graph validation did not enforce this flag. This allowed any authenticated user to bypass the restriction by including the block as a node in a graph, rather than calling the block's execution endpoint directly (which did enforce the flag). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.48.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26000 | XWiki Platform affected by click-jacking through CSS injection in comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26000</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. Prior to 17.9.0, 17.4.6, and 16.10.13, it's possible using comments to inject CSS that would transform the full wiki in a link area leading to a malicious page. This vulnerability is fixed in 17.9.0, 17.4.6, and 16.10.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26005 | ClipBucket v5 enables internal network scans via an SSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26005</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Prior to 5.5.3 - #45, in Clip Bucket V5, The Remote Play allows creating video entries that reference external video URLs without uploading the video files to the server. However, by specifying an internal network host in the video URL, an SSRF can be triggered, causing GET requests to be sent to internal servers. An attacker can exploit this to scan the internal network. Even a regular (non-privileged) user can carry out the attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0619 | Integer Wraparound DoS in Silicon Labs Matter Implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0619</link><description>A reachable infinite loop via an integer wraparound is present in Silicon Labs' Matter SDK which allows an attacker to trigger a denial of service. A hard reset is required to recover the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25996 | Inspektor Gadget uses unsanitized ANSI Escape Sequences In `columns` Output Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25996</link><description>Inspektor Gadget is a set of tools and framework for data collection and system inspection on Kubernetes clusters and Linux hosts using eBPF. String fields from eBPF events in columns output mode are rendered to the terminal without any sanitization of control characters or ANSI escape sequences. Therefore, a maliciously forged – partially or completely – event payload, coming from an observed container, might inject the escape sequences into the terminal of ig operators, with various effects. The columns output mode is the default when running ig run interactively.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25933 | Arduino App Lab has Improper Data Validation in Internal Terminal Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25933</link><description>Arduino App Lab is a cross-platform IDE for developing Arduino Apps. Prior to 0.4.0, a vulnerability was identified in the Terminal component of the arduino-app-lab application. The issue stems from insufficient sanitization and validation of input data received from connected hardware devices, specifically in the _info.Serial and _info.Address metadata fields. The problem occurs during device information handling. When a board is connected, the application collects identifying attributes to establish a terminal session. Because strict validation is not enforced for the Serial and Address parameters, an attacker with control over the connected hardware can supply specially crafted strings containing shell metacharacters. The exploitation requires direct physical access to a previously tampered board. When the host system processes these fields, any injected payload is executed with the privileges of the user running arduino-app-lab. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25949 | Traefik: TCP readTimeout bypass via STARTTLS on Postgres</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25949</link><description>Traefik is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. Prior to 3.6.8, there is a potential vulnerability in Traefik managing STARTTLS requests. An unauthenticated client can bypass Traefik entrypoint respondingTimeouts.readTimeout by sending the 8-byte Postgres SSLRequest (STARTTLS) prelude and then stalling, causing connections to remain open indefinitely, leading to a denial of service. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25767 | LavinMQ has incomplete shovel configuration validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25767</link><description>LavinMQ is a high-performance message queue &amp; streaming server. Before 2.6.8, an authenticated user, with the “Policymaker” tag, could create shovels bypassing access controls. an authenticated user with the "Policymaker" management tag could exploit it to read messages from vhosts they are not authorized to access or publish messages to vhosts they are not authorized to access. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25768 | LavinMQ is missing vhost access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25768</link><description>LavinMQ is a high-performance message queue &amp; streaming server. Before 2.6.6, an authenticated user could access metadata in the broker they should not have access to. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.6.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67432 | A stack overflow in the ZBarcode_Encode function of Monkeybread Software MBS DynaPDF Plugin v21.3.1.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67432</link><description>A stack overflow in the ZBarcode_Encode function of Monkeybread Software MBS DynaPDF Plugin v21.3.1.1 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-67433 | A heap buffer overflow in the processRequest function of Open TFTP Server MultiThreaded v1.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-67433</link><description>A heap buffer overflow in the processRequest function of Open TFTP Server MultiThreaded v1.7 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted DATA packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70314 | webfsd 1.21 is vulnerable to a Buffer Overflow via a crafted request. This is due to the filename variable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70314</link><description>webfsd 1.21 is vulnerable to a Buffer Overflow via a crafted request. This is due to the filename variable</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25227 | authentik affected by Remote Code Execution via Context Key Injection in PropertyMapping Test Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25227</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. From 2021.3.1 to before 2025.8.6, 2025.10.4, and 2025.12.4, when using delegated permissions, a User that has the permission Can view * Property Mapping or Can view Expression Policy is able to execute arbitrary code within the authentik server container through the test endpoint, which is intended to preview how a property mapping/policy works. authentik 2025.8.6, 2025.10.4, and 2025.12.4 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25748 | authentik has a forward authentication bypass with broken cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25748</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. Prior to 2025.10.4 and 2025.12.4, with a malformed cookie it was possible to bypass authentication when using forward authentication in the authentik Proxy Provider when used in conjunction with Traefik or Caddy as reverse proxy. When a malicious cookie was used, none of the authentik-specific X-Authentik-* headers were set which depending on application can grant access to an attacker. authentik 2025.10.4 and 2025.12.4 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25922 | authentik has a Signature Verification Bypass via SAML Assertion Wrapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25922</link><description>authentik is an open-source identity provider. Prior to 2025.8.6, 2025.10.4, and 2025.12.4, when using a SAML Source that has the option Verify Assertion Signature under Verification Certificate enabled and not Verify Response Signature, or does not have the Encryption Certificate setting under Advanced Protocol settings configured, it was possible for an attacker to inject a malicious assertion before the signed assertion that authentik would use instead. authentik 2025.8.6, 2025.10.4, and 2025.12.4 fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25343 | NextVPN 4.10 - Insecure File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25343</link><description>NextVPN 4.10 contains an insecure file permissions vulnerability that allows local users to modify executable files with full access rights. Attackers can replace system executables with malicious files to gain SYSTEM or Administrator privileges through unauthorized file modification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25344 | MobileGo 8.5.0 - Insecure File Permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25344</link><description>Wondershare MobileGo 8.5.0 contains an insecure file permissions vulnerability that allows local users to modify executable files in the application directory. Attackers can replace the original MobileGo.exe with a malicious executable to create a new user account and add it to the Administrators group with full system access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25345 | RTK IIS Codec Service 6.4.10041.133 - &amp;#x27;RtkI2SCodec&amp;#x27; Unquote Service Path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25345</link><description>Realtek IIS Codec Service 6.4.10041.133 contains an unquoted service path vulnerability that allows local attackers to potentially execute arbitrary code. Attackers can exploit the unquoted path in the service configuration to inject malicious executables and escalate privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25346 | thesystem 1.0 - &amp;#x27;server_name&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25346</link><description>TheSystem 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication by manipulating the 'server_name' parameter. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code like ' or '1=1 to retrieve unauthorized database records and potentially access sensitive system information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25347 | thesystem App 1.0 - &amp;#x27;username&amp;#x27; SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25347</link><description>thesystem App 1.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability that allows attackers to bypass authentication by manipulating the username parameter. Attackers can inject malicious SQL code like ' or '1=1 to the username field to gain unauthorized access to user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25348 | CBAS-Web 19.0.0 - &amp;#x27;id&amp;#x27; Boolean-based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25348</link><description>Computrols CBAS-Web 19.0.0 contains a boolean-based blind SQL injection vulnerability in the 'id' parameter that allows authenticated attackers to manipulate database queries. Attackers can exploit the vulnerability by crafting boolean-based SQL injection payloads in the 'id' parameter of the servers endpoint to extract or infer database information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24044 | ESS Community Helm Chart has a weak server key generation method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24044</link><description>Element Server Suite Community Edition (ESS Community) deploys a Matrix stack using the provided Helm charts and Kubernetes distribution. The ESS Community Helm Chart secrets initialization hook (using matrix-tools container before 0.5.7) is using an insecure Matrix server key generation method, allowing network attackers to potentially recreate the same key pair, allowing them to impersonate the victim server. The secret is generated by the secrets initialization hook, in the ESS Community Helm Chart values, if both initSecrets.enabled is not set to false and synapse.signingKey is not defined. Given a server key in Matrix authenticates both requests originating from and events constructed on a given server, this potentially impacts confidentiality, integrity and availability of rooms which have a vulnerable server present as a member. The confidentiality of past conversations in end-to-end encrypted rooms is not impacted. The key generation issue was fixed in matrix-tools 0.5.7, released as part of ESS Community Helm Chart 25.12.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24894 | FrankenPHP leaks session data between requests in worker mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24894</link><description>FrankenPHP is a modern application server for PHP. Prior to 1.11.2, when running FrankenPHP in worker mode, the $_SESSION superglobal is not correctly reset between requests. This allows a subsequent request processed by the same worker to access the $_SESSION data of the previous request (potentially belonging to a different user) before session_start() is called. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24895 | FrankenPHP affected by Path Confusion via Unicode casing in CGI path splitting allows execution of arbitrary files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24895</link><description>FrankenPHP is a modern application server for PHP. Prior to 1.11.2, FrankenPHP’s CGI path splitting logic improperly handles Unicode characters during case conversion. The logic computes the split index (for finding .php) on a lowercased copy of the request path but applies that byte index to the original path. Because strings.ToLower() in Go can increase the byte length of certain UTF-8 characters (e.g., Ⱥ expands when lowercased), the computed index may not align with the correct position in the original string. This results in an incorrect SCRIPT_NAME and SCRIPT_FILENAME, potentially causing FrankenPHP to execute a file other than the one intended by the URI. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.11.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22821 | mreporting affected by a SQLI on date change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22821</link><description>mreporting is the more reporting GLPI plugin. Prior to 1.9.4, there is a possible SQL injection on date change. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26218 | newbee-mall Default Seeded Administrator Credentials Allow Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26218</link><description>newbee-mall includes pre-seeded administrator accounts in its database initialization script. These accounts are provisioned with a predictable default password. Deployments that initialize or reset the database using the provided schema and fail to change the default administrative credentials may allow unauthenticated attackers to log in as an administrator and gain full administrative control of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26219 | newbee-mall Unsalted MD5 Password Hashing Enables Offline Credential Cracking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26219</link><description>newbee-mall stores and verifies user passwords using an unsalted MD5 hashing algorithm. The implementation does not incorporate per-user salts or computational cost controls, enabling attackers who obtain password hashes through database exposure, backup leakage, or other compromise vectors to rapidly recover plaintext credentials via offline attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21434 | webtransport-go affected by Memory Exhaustion Attack due to Missing Length Check in WT_CLOSE_SESSION Capsule</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21434</link><description>webtransport-go is an implementation of the WebTransport protocol. From 0.3.0 to 0.9.0, an attacker can cause excessive memory consumption in webtransport-go's session implementation by sending a WT_CLOSE_SESSION capsule containing an excessively large Application Error Message. The implementation does not enforce the draft-mandated limit of 1024 bytes on this field, allowing a peer to send an arbitrarily large message payload that is fully read and stored in memory. This allows an attacker to consume an arbitrary amount of memory. The attacker must transmit the full payload to achieve the memory consumption, but the lack of any upper bound makes large-scale attacks feasible given sufficient bandwidth. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21435 | webtransport-go CloseWithError can block indefinitely</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21435</link><description>webtransport-go is an implementation of the WebTransport protocol. Prior to v0.10.0, an attacker can cause a denial of service in webtransport-go by preventing or indefinitely delaying WebTransport session closure. A malicious peer can withhold QUIC flow control credit on the CONNECT stream, blocking transmission of the WT_CLOSE_SESSION capsule and causing the close operation to hang. This vulnerability is fixed in v0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21438 | webtransport-go affected by a Memory Exhaustion Attack due to Missing Cleanup of Streams Map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21438</link><description>webtransport-go is an implementation of the WebTransport protocol. Prior to 0.10.0, an attacker can cause unbounded memory consumption repeatedly creating and closing many WebTransport streams. Closed streams were not removed from an internal session map, preventing garbage collection of their resources. This vulnerability is fixed in v0.10.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31323 | Type confusion in the AMD Secure Processor (ASP) could allow an attacker to pass a malformed argument to the External Global Memory Intercon...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31323</link><description>Type confusion in the AMD Secure Processor (ASP) could allow an attacker to pass a malformed argument to the External Global Memory Interconnect Trusted Agent (XGMI TA) leading to a memory safety violation potentially resulting in loss of confidentiality, integrity, or availability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54519 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in Doc Nav could allow a local attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54519</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in Doc Nav could allow a local attacker to achieve privilege escalation, potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20601 | Improper input validation within RAS TA Driver can allow a local attacker to access out-of-bounds memory, potentially resulting in a denial-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20601</link><description>Improper input validation within RAS TA Driver can allow a local attacker to access out-of-bounds memory, potentially resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36319 | Debug code left active in AMD's Video Decoder Engine Firmware (VCN FW) could allow a attacker to submit a maliciously crafted command causin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36319</link><description>Debug code left active in AMD's Video Decoder Engine Firmware (VCN FW) could allow a attacker to submit a maliciously crafted command causing the VCN FW to perform read/writes HW registers, potentially impacting confidentiality, integrity and availabilability of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20601 | Improper input validation within RAS TA Driver can allow a local attacker to access out-of-bounds memory, potentially resulting in a denial-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20601</link><description>Improper input validation within RAS TA Driver can allow a local attacker to access out-of-bounds memory, potentially resulting in a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36319 | Debug code left active in AMD's Video Decoder Engine Firmware (VCN FW) could allow a attacker to submit a maliciously crafted command causin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36319</link><description>Debug code left active in AMD's Video Decoder Engine Firmware (VCN FW) could allow a attacker to submit a maliciously crafted command causing the VCN FW to perform read/writes HW registers, potentially impacting confidentiality, integrity and availabilability of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52533 | Improper Access Control in an on-chip debug interface could allow a privileged attacker to enable a debug interface and potentially compromi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52533</link><description>Improper Access Control in an on-chip debug interface could allow a privileged attacker to enable a debug interface and potentially compromise data confidentiality or integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63421 | An issue in filosoft Comerc.32 Commercial Invoicing v.16.0.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the comeinst.exe file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63421</link><description>An issue in filosoft Comerc.32 Commercial Invoicing v.16.0.0.3 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the comeinst.exe file</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69806 | p2r3 bareiron commit: 8e4d4020d contains an Out-of-bounds Read, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to get relative information le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69806</link><description>p2r3 bareiron commit: 8e4d4020d contains an Out-of-bounds Read, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to get relative information leakage via a packet sent to the server</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69807 | p2r3 Bareiron commit: 8e4d4020d is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause a denial of service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69807</link><description>p2r3 Bareiron commit: 8e4d4020d is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow, which allows unauthenticated remote attackers to cause a denial of service via a packet sent to the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70981 | CordysCRM 1.4.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the employee list query interface (/user/list) via the departmentIds parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70981</link><description>CordysCRM 1.4.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the employee list query interface (/user/list) via the departmentIds parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54756 | BrightSign Players Use of Default Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54756</link><description>BrightSign players running BrightSign OS series 4 prior to v8.5.53.1 or 
series 5 prior to v9.0.166 use a default password that is guessable with
 knowledge of the device information. The latest release fixes this 
issue for new installations; users of old installations are encouraged 
to change all default passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61879 | In Infoblox NIOS through 9.0.7, a High-Privileged User Can Trigger an Arbitrary File Write via the Account Creation Mechanism.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61879</link><description>In Infoblox NIOS through 9.0.7, a High-Privileged User Can Trigger an Arbitrary File Write via the Account Creation Mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55210 | FreePBX API has a Privilege Escalation Error in GraphQL Allowing Authenticated Users to Access Additional Scopes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55210</link><description>FreePBX is an open-source web-based graphical user interface (GUI) that manages Asterisk. Prior to 17.0.5 and 16.0.17, FreePBX module api (PBX API) is vulnerable to privilege escalation by authenticated users with REST/GraphQL API access. This vulnerability allows an attacker to forge a valid JWT with full access to the REST and GraphQL APIs on a FreePBX that they've already connected to, possibly as a lower privileged user. The JWT is signed using the api-oauth.key private key. An attacker can generate their own token if they possess this key (e.g., by accessing an affected instance), and specify any scopes they wish (e.g., rest, gql), bypassing traditional authorization checks. However, FreePBX enforces that the jti (JWT ID) claim must exist in the database (api_access_tokens table in the asterisk MySQL database) in order for the token to be accepted. Therefore, the attacker must know a jti value that already exists on the target instance. This vulnerability is fixed in 17.0.5 and 16.0.17.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61880 | In Infoblox NIOS through 9.0.7, insecure deserialization can result in remote code execution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61880</link><description>In Infoblox NIOS through 9.0.7, insecure deserialization can result in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56647 | npm @farmfe/core before 1.7.6 is Missing Origin Validation in WebSocket. The development (hot module reloading) server does not validate ori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56647</link><description>npm @farmfe/core before 1.7.6 is Missing Origin Validation in WebSocket. The development (hot module reloading) server does not validate origin when connecting to a WebSocket client. This allows attackers to surveil developers running Farm who visit their webpage and steal source code that is leaked by the WebSocket server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69752 | An issue in the "My Details" user profile functionality of Ideagen Q-Pulse 7.1.0.32 allows an authenticated user to view other users' profil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69752</link><description>An issue in the "My Details" user profile functionality of Ideagen Q-Pulse 7.1.0.32 allows an authenticated user to view other users' profile information by modifying the objectKey HTTP parameter in the My Details page URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70886 | An issue in halo v.2.22.4 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted payload to the public comment submi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70886</link><description>An issue in halo v.2.22.4 and before allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted payload to the public comment submission endpoint</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26216 | Crawl4AI &amp;lt; 0.8.0 Docker API Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Hooks Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26216</link><description>Crawl4AI versions prior to 0.8.0 contain a remote code execution vulnerability in the Docker API deployment. The /crawl endpoint accepts a hooks parameter containing Python code that is executed using exec(). The __import__ builtin was included in the allowed builtins, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to import arbitrary modules and execute system commands. Successful exploitation allows full server compromise, including arbitrary command execution, file read and write access, sensitive data exfiltration, and lateral movement within internal networks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26217 | Crawl4AI &amp;lt; 0.8.0 Docker API Local File Inclusion via file URL Handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26217</link><description>Crawl4AI versions prior to 0.8.0 contain a local file inclusion vulnerability in the Docker API deployment. The /execute_js, /screenshot, /pdf, and /html endpoints accept file:// URLs, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read arbitrary files from the server filesystem. An attacker can access sensitive files such as /etc/passwd, /etc/shadow, application configuration files, and environment variables via /proc/self/environ, potentially exposing credentials, API keys, and internal application structure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-69634 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Dolibarr ERP &amp; CRM v.22.0.9 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the notes field ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-69634</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Dolibarr ERP &amp; CRM v.22.0.9 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the notes field in perms.php</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26214 | Xiaomi Galaxy FDS Android SDK &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 TLS Hostname Verification Disabled Enables MITM</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26214</link><description>Galaxy FDS Android SDK (XiaoMi/galaxy-fds-sdk-android) version 3.0.8 and prior disable TLS hostname verification when HTTPS is enabled (the default configuration). In GalaxyFDSClientImpl.createHttpClient(), the SDK configures Apache HttpClient with SSLSocketFactory.ALLOW_ALL_HOSTNAME_VERIFIER, which accepts any valid TLS certificate regardless of hostname mismatch. Because HTTPS is enabled by default in FDSClientConfiguration, all applications using the SDK with default settings are affected. This vulnerability allows a man-in-the-middle attacker to intercept and modify SDK communications to Xiaomi FDS cloud storage endpoints, potentially exposing authentication credentials, file contents, and API responses. The XiaoMi/galaxy-fds-sdk-android open source project has reached end-of-life status.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31313 | An unintended proxy or intermediary in the AMD power management firmware (PMFW) could allow a privileged attacker to send malformed messages...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31313</link><description>An unintended proxy or intermediary in the AMD power management firmware (PMFW) could allow a privileged attacker to send malformed messages to the system management unit (SMU) potentially resulting in arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:42:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1104 | FastDup – Fastest WordPress Migration &amp;amp; Duplicator &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Backup Creation and Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1104</link><description>The FastDup – Fastest WordPress Migration &amp; Duplicator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized backup creation and download due to a missing capability check on REST API endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to create and download full-site backup archives containing the entire WordPress installation, including database exports and configuration files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14014 | Insecure File Upload in NTN Informatics&amp;#x27; Smart Panel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14014</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NTN Information Processing Services Computer Software Hardware Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Smart Panel allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Smart Panel: before 20251215.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1320 | Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking &amp;lt;= 4.9.8 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via X-Forwarded-For Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1320</link><description>The Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'X-Forwarded-For' HTTP header in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10969 | SQLi in Farktor Software&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10969</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Farktor Software E-Commerce Services Inc. E-Commerce Package allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects E-Commerce Package: through 27112025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13002 | XSS in Farktor Software&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13002</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Farktor Software E-Commerce Services Inc. E-Commerce Package allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects E-Commerce Package: through 27112025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13004 | IDOR in Farktor Software&amp;#x27;s E-Commerce Package</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13004</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Farktor Software E-Commerce Services Inc. E-Commerce Package allows Manipulating User-Controlled Variables.This issue affects E-Commerce Package: through 27112025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2003 | PostgreSQL oidvector discloses a few bytes of memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2003</link><description>Improper validation of type "oidvector" in PostgreSQL allows a database user to disclose a few bytes of server memory.  We have not ruled out viability of attacks that arrange for presence of confidential information in disclosed bytes, but they seem unlikely.  Versions before PostgreSQL 18.2, 17.8, 16.12, 15.16, and 14.21 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2004 | PostgreSQL intarray missing validation of type of input to selectivity estimator executes arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2004</link><description>Missing validation of type of input in PostgreSQL intarray extension selectivity estimator function allows an object creator to execute arbitrary code as the operating system user running the database.  Versions before PostgreSQL 18.2, 17.8, 16.12, 15.16, and 14.21 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2005 | PostgreSQL pgcrypto heap buffer overflow executes arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2005</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in PostgreSQL pgcrypto allows a ciphertext provider to execute arbitrary code as the operating system user running the database.  Versions before PostgreSQL 18.2, 17.8, 16.12, 15.16, and 14.21 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2006 | PostgreSQL missing validation of multibyte character length executes arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2006</link><description>Missing validation of multibyte character length in PostgreSQL text manipulation allows a database user to issue crafted queries that achieve a buffer overrun.  That suffices to execute arbitrary code as the operating system user running the database.  Versions before PostgreSQL 18.2, 17.8, 16.12, 15.16, and 14.21 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:53:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2007 | PostgreSQL pg_trgm heap buffer overflow writes pattern onto server memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2007</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in PostgreSQL pg_trgm allows a database user to achieve unknown impacts via a crafted input string.  The attacker has limited control over the byte patterns to be written, but we have not ruled out the viability of attacks that lead to privilege escalation.  PostgreSQL 18.1 and 18.0 are affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1316 | Customer Reviews for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.97.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via media[].href Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1316</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'media[].href' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.97.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers (if 'Enable for Guests' is enabled) to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1671 | Activity Log for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure via Log File</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1671</link><description>The Activity Log for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the winter_activity_log_action() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view potentially sensitive information (e.g., the password of a higher level user, such as an administrator) contained in the exposed log files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 13:54:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15574 | Insecure Credential Generation for Solax Power Pocket WiFi models MQTT Cloud Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15574</link><description>When connecting to the Solax Cloud MQTT server the username is the "registration number", which is the 10 character string printed on the SolaX Power Pocket device / the QR code on the device. The password is derived from the "registration number" using a proprietary XOR/transposition algorithm. Attackers with the knowledge of the registration numbers can connect to the MQTT server and impersonate the dongle / inverters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15575 | Missing Firmware Authenticity Checks in Solax Power Pocket WiFi models</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15575</link><description>The firmware update functionality does not verify the authenticity of the supplied firmware update files. This allows attackers to flash malicious firmware update files on the device. Initial analysis of the firmware update functionality does not show any cryptographic checks (e.g. digital signature checks) on the supplied firmware update files. Furthermore, ESP32 security features such as secure boot are not used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:52:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15573 | Missing Certificate Validation for Solax Power Pocket WiFi models MQTT Cloud Connection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15573</link><description>The affected devices do not validate the server certificate when connecting to the SolaX Cloud MQTTS server hosted in the Alibaba Cloud (mqtt001.solaxcloud.com, TCP 8883). This allows attackers in a man-in-the-middle position to act as the legitimate MQTT server and issue arbitrary commands to devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2276 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in the Wix web application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2276</link><description>Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Wix web application, where the endpoint ' https://manage.wix.com/account/account-settings ', responsible for uploading SVG images, does not properly sanitize the content. An authenticated attacker could upload an SVG file containing embedded JavaScript code, which is stored and subsequently executed when other users view the image. Exploiting this vulnerability allows arbitrary code to be executed in the context of the victim's browser, which could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information or the abuse of the affected user's session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 11:05:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1356 | Converter for Media – Optimize images | Convert WebP &amp;amp; AVIF &amp;lt;= 6.5.1 - Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery via src</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1356</link><description>The Converter for Media – Optimize images | Convert WebP &amp; AVIF plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.5.1 via the PassthruLoader::load_image_source function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 10:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41117 | XSS in Grafana Explore stack trace</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41117</link><description>Stack traces in Grafana's Explore Traces view can be rendered as raw HTML, and thus inject malicious JavaScript in the browser. This would require malicious JavaScript to be entered into the stack trace field.

Only datasources with the Jaeger HTTP API appear to be affected; Jaeger gRPC and Tempo do not appear affected whatsoever.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21722 | Public Dashboards time range restriction on annotations can be bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21722</link><description>Public dashboards with annotations enabled did not limit their annotation timerange to the locked timerange of the public dashboard. This means one could read the entire history of annotations visible on the specific dashboard, even those outside the locked timerange.

This did not leak any annotations that would not otherwise be visible on the public dashboard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:12:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15577 | Valmet DNA Web server arbitrary file read access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15577</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this vulnerability by manipulating URL to achieve arbitrary file read access.This issue affects Valmet DNA Web Tools: C2022 and older.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14892 | Prime Listing Manager &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14892</link><description>The Prime Listing Manager WordPress plugin through 1.1 allows an attacker to gain administrative access without having any kind of account on the targeted site and perform unauthorized actions due to a hardcoded secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:45:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2327 | Versions of the package markdown-it from 13.0.0 and before 14.1.1 are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) due to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2327</link><description>Versions of the package markdown-it from 13.0.0 and before 14.1.1 are vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) due to the use of the regex /\*+$/ in the linkify function. An attacker can supply a long sequence of * characters followed by a non-matching character, which triggers excessive backtracking and may lead to a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25676 | The installer of M-Track Duo HD version 1.0.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25676</link><description>The installer of M-Track Duo HD version 1.0.0 contains an issue with the DLL search path, which may lead to insecurely loading Dynamic Link Libraries. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2391 | qs&amp;#x27;s arrayLimit bypass in comma parsing allows denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2391</link><description>### Summary
The `arrayLimit` option in qs does not enforce limits for comma-separated values when `comma: true` is enabled, allowing attackers to cause denial-of-service via memory exhaustion. This is a bypass of the array limit enforcement, similar to the bracket notation bypass addressed in GHSA-6rw7-vpxm-498p (CVE-2025-15284).

### Details
When the `comma` option is set to `true` (not the default, but configurable in applications), qs allows parsing comma-separated strings as arrays (e.g., `?param=a,b,c` becomes `['a', 'b', 'c']`). However, the limit check for `arrayLimit` (default: 20) and the optional throwOnLimitExceeded occur after the comma-handling logic in `parseArrayValue`, enabling a bypass. This permits creation of arbitrarily large arrays from a single parameter, leading to excessive memory allocation.

**Vulnerable code** (lib/parse.js: lines ~40-50):
```js
if (val &amp;&amp; typeof val === 'string' &amp;&amp; options.comma &amp;&amp; val.indexOf(',') &gt; -1) {
    return val.split(',');
}

if (options.throwOnLimitExceeded &amp;&amp; currentArrayLength &gt;= options.arrayLimit) {
    throw new RangeError('Array limit exceeded. Only ' + options.arrayLimit + ' element' + (options.arrayLimit === 1 ? '' : 's') + ' allowed in an array.');
}

return val;
```
The `split(',')` returns the array immediately, skipping the subsequent limit check. Downstream merging via `utils.combine` does not prevent allocation, even if it marks overflows for sparse arrays.This discrepancy allows attackers to send a single parameter with millions of commas (e.g., `?param=,,,,,,,,...`), allocating massive arrays in memory without triggering limits. It bypasses the intent of `arrayLimit`, which is enforced correctly for indexed (`a[0]=`) and bracket (`a[]=`) notations (the latter fixed in v6.14.1 per GHSA-6rw7-vpxm-498p).

### PoC
**Test 1 - Basic bypass:**
```
npm install qs
```

```js
const qs = require('qs');

const payload = 'a=' + ','.repeat(25);  // 26 elements after split (bypasses arrayLimit: 5)
const options = { comma: true, arrayLimit: 5, throwOnLimitExceeded: true };

try {
  const result = qs.parse(payload, options);
  console.log(result.a.length);  // Outputs: 26 (bypass successful)
} catch (e) {
  console.log('Limit enforced:', e.message);  // Not thrown
}
```
**Configuration:**
- `comma: true`
- `arrayLimit: 5`
- `throwOnLimitExceeded: true`

Expected: Throws "Array limit exceeded" error.
Actual: Parses successfully, creating an array of length 26.


### Impact
Denial of Service (DoS) via memory exhaustion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 05:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1537 | LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events &amp;lt;= 5.2.6 - Missing Authorization to Booking Details Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1537</link><description>The LatePoint – Calendar Booking Plugin for Appointments and Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the load_step() function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view booking information including customer names, email addresses, phone numbers, appointment times, and service details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26234 | JUNG Smart Visu Server - Improper Neutralization of HTTP Headers for Scripting Syntax</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26234</link><description>JUNG Smart Visu Server 1.1.1050 contains a request header manipulation vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to override request URLs by injecting arbitrary values in the X-Forwarded-Host header. Attackers can manipulate proxied requests to generate tainted responses, enabling cache poisoning, potential phishing, and redirecting users to malicious domains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-26235 | JUNG Smart Visu Server 1.1.1050 - &amp;#x27;JUNG Smart Visu Server&amp;#x27; Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-26235</link><description>JUNG Smart Visu Server 1.1.1050 contains a denial of service vulnerability that allows unauthenticated attackers to remotely shutdown or reboot the server. Attackers can send a single POST request to trigger the server reboot without requiring any authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0969 | Arbitrary code execution in React server-side rendering of untrusted MDX content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0969</link><description>The serialize function used to compile MDX in next-mdx-remote is vulnerable to arbitrary code execution due to insufficient sanitization of MDX content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23856 | Dell iDRAC Service Module (iSM) for Windows, versions prior to 6.0.3.1, and Dell iDRAC Service Module (iSM) for Linux, versions prior to 5.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23856</link><description>Dell iDRAC Service Module (iSM) for Windows, versions prior to 6.0.3.1, and Dell iDRAC Service Module (iSM) for Linux, versions prior to 5.4.1.1, contain an Improper Access Control vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23857 | Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework, versions 23.12.00 through 24.12.00, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23857</link><description>Dell Update Package (DUP) Framework, versions 23.12.00 through 24.12.00, contains an Improper Handling of Insufficient Permissions or Privileges vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1729 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 6.0.12 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1729</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.12. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them through the 'sb_login_user_with_otp_fun' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as arbitrary users, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 02:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>