<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-9094 | code-projects Blood Bank System o-.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9094</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/blood/update/o-.php. The manipulation of the argument bloodname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43996 | WordPress ElementsKit Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43996</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in ElementsKit ElementsKit Pro allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects ElementsKit Pro: from n/a through 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44048 | WordPress Product Carousel Slider &amp;amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.10 - Authenticated Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44048</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in wpWax Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Product Carousel Slider &amp; Grid Ultimate for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.9.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45453 | WordPress Maintenance Redirect  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - IP Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45453</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Peter Hardy-vanDoorn Maintenance Redirect allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Maintenance Redirect: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9092 | SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh Registration Form add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add.php of the component Registration Form. The manipulation of the argument full_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9093 | SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh GET Parameter del.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9093</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Profile Registration without Reload Refresh 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file del.php of the component GET Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument list leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43989 | WordPress Justified Image Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.1 - Unauthenticated Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43989</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Firsh Justified Image Grid allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Justified Image Grid: from n/a through 4.6.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9091 | code-projects Student Record System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9091</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument regno leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 01:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9089 | SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System update_loan_record.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9089</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file update_loan_record.php. The manipulation of the argument amount leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9090 | SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System search_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9090</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Modern Loan Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file search_member.php. The manipulation of the argument searchMember leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9087 | code-projects Vehicle Management edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9087</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit1.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9088 | SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9088</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Telecom Billing Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function login. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9086 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System filter.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9086</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /filter.php. The manipulation of the argument from/to leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory only mentions the parameter "from" to be affected. But it must be assumed that parameter "to" is affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 21:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40703 | IBM Cognos Analytics information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40703</link><description>IBM Cognos Analytics 11.2.0, 11.2.1, 11.2.2, 11.2.3, 11.2.4, 12.0.0, 12.0.1, 12.0.2, 12.0.3, and IBM Cognos Analytics Reports for iOS 11.0.0.7 could allow a local attacker to obtain sensitive information in the form of an API key.  An attacker could use this information to launch further attacks against affected applications.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 12:57:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9084 | code-projects Blood Bank System bbms.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9084</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file bbms.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname/age/bloodgroup/city/phno/gender as part of String leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 09:14:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9083 | SourceCodester Employee Management System add-admin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9083</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Employee Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/add-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument txtfullname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:35:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9082 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop User Creation Users.phpf=save improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9082</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Users.phpf=save of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation of the argument type with the input 1 leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 08:19:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9085 | code-projects Restaurant Reservation System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9085</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Restaurant Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.php. The manipulation of the argument date leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The initial researcher advisory mentions sid as affected paramater which is incorrect.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 07:56:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9081 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop view_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9081</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file view_category.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 07:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9080 | code-projects Student Record System pincode-verification.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9080</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pincode-verification.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9079 | code-projects Student Record System marks.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9079</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /marks.php. The manipulation of the argument coursename leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 04:41:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9078 | code-projects Student Record System course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9078</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Student Record System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /course.php. The manipulation of the argument coursename leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47226 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in NetBox 4.1.0 within the "Configuration History" feature of the "Admin" panel via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47226</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in NetBox 4.1.0 within the "Configuration History" feature of the "Admin" panel via a /core/config-revisions/ Add action. An authenticated user can inject arbitrary JavaScript or HTML into the "Top banner" field.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9077 | dingfangzu Order Checkout order.js cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9077</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in dingfangzu up to 29d67d9044f6f93378e6eb6ff92272217ff7225c. Affected is an unknown function of the file scripts/order.js of the component Order Checkout. The manipulation of the argument address-name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product is using a rolling release to provide continious delivery. Therefore, no version details for affected nor updated releases are available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47221 | CheckUser in ScadaServerEngine/MainLogic.cs in Rapid SCADA through 5.8.4 allows an empty password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47221</link><description>CheckUser in ScadaServerEngine/MainLogic.cs in Rapid SCADA through 5.8.4 allows an empty password.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47218 | An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows bypassing authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47218</link><description>An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows bypassing authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47219 | An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows shell command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47219</link><description>An issue was discovered in vesoft NebulaGraph through 3.8.0. It allows shell command injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47220 | An issue was discovered in the WEBrick toolkit through 1.8.1 for Ruby. It allows HTTP request smuggling by providing both a Content-Length h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47220</link><description>An issue was discovered in the WEBrick toolkit through 1.8.1 for Ruby. It allows HTTP request smuggling by providing both a Content-Length header and a Transfer-Encoding header, e.g., "GET /admin HTTP/1.1\r\n" inside of a "POST /user HTTP/1.1\r\n" request. NOTE: the supplier's position is "Webrick should not be used in production."</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9076 | DedeCMS article_string_mix.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9076</link><description>A vulnerability was found in DedeCMS up to 5.7.115. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file article_string_mix.php. The manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 01:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9075 | Stirling-Tools Stirling-PDF Markdown-to-PDF cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9075</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Stirling-Tools Stirling-PDF up to 0.28.3. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Markdown-to-PDF. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 23:13:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47210 | Gladys Assistant before 4.45.1 allows Privilege Escalation (a user changing their own role) because req.body.role can be used in updateMySel...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47210</link><description>Gladys Assistant before 4.45.1 allows Privilege Escalation (a user changing their own role) because req.body.role can be used in updateMySelf in server/api/controllers/user.controller.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 22:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42323 | Apache HertzBeat: RCE by snakeYaml deser load malicious xml</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42323</link><description>SnakeYaml Deser Load Malicious xml rce vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat (incubating). 

This vulnerability can only be exploited by authorized attackers.
This issue affects Apache HertzBeat (incubating): before 1.6.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.6.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8680 | MailChimp for Wordpress &amp;lt;= 4.9.16 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8680</link><description>The MC4WP: Mailchimp for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.9.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 08:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9048 | y_project RuoYi Backend User Import SysUserServiceImpl.java SysUserServiceImpl cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9048</link><description>A vulnerability was found in y_project RuoYi up to 4.7.9. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function SysUserServiceImpl of the file ruoyi-system/src/main/java/com/ruoyi/system/service/impl/SysUserServiceImpl.java of the component Backend User Import. The manipulation of the argument loginName leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named 9b68013b2af87b9c809c4637299abd929bc73510. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 08:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6787 | MXview One Series vulnerable to Time-of-check Time-of-use (TOCTOU) Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6787</link><description>This vulnerability occurs when an attacker exploits a race condition between the time a file is checked and the time it is used (TOCTOU). By exploiting this race condition, an attacker can write arbitrary files to the system. This could allow the attacker to execute malicious code and potentially cause file losses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6785 | MXview One and MXview One Central Manger Series store cleartext credentials in a local file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6785</link><description>The configuration file stores credentials in cleartext. An attacker with local access rights can read or modify the configuration file, potentially resulting in the service being abused due to sensitive information exposure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6786 | MXview One Series vulnerable to Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6786</link><description>The vulnerability allows an attacker to craft MQTT messages that include relative path traversal sequences, enabling them to read arbitrary files on the system. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information, such as configuration files and JWT signing secrets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 04:21:59 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>