<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:07:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-0196 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System plist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0196</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/plist.php. The manipulation of the argument cat leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:07:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-35365 | FFmpeg version n6.1.1 has a double-free vulnerability in the fftools/ffmpeg_mux_init.c component of FFmpeg, specifically within the new_stre...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-35365</link><description>FFmpeg version n6.1.1 has a double-free vulnerability in the fftools/ffmpeg_mux_init.c component of FFmpeg, specifically within the new_stream_audio function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36613 | FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the DXA demuxer of the libavformat library allowing for an integer overflow, potentially resulting in a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36613</link><description>FFmpeg n6.1.1 has a vulnerability in the DXA demuxer of the libavformat library allowing for an integer overflow, potentially resulting in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or other undefined behavior.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0195 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System del_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0195</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/del_product.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56410 | PhpSpreadsheet has Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in custom properties</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56410</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in custom properties. The HTML page is generated without clearing custom properties. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56411 | PhpSpreadsheet has Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability of the hyperlink base in the HTML page header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56411</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability of the hyperlink base in the HTML page header. The HTML page is formed without sanitizing the hyperlink base. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56412 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to bypass of the XSS sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56412</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to bypass of the cross-site scripting sanitizer using the javascript protocol and special characters. An attacker can use special characters, so that the library processes the javascript protocol with special characters and generates an HTML link. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56366 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected  XSS in the Accounting.php file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56366</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the `Accounting.php` file. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Wizards/NumberFormat/Accounting.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56409 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected XSS in Currency.php file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56409</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the `Currency.php` file. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Wizards/NumberFormat/Currency.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56365 | PhpSpreadsheet vulnerable to unauthorized reflected XSS in the constructor of the Downloader class</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56365</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 are vulnerable to unauthorized reflected cross-site scripting in the constructor of the `Downloader` class. Using the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/download.php` script, an attacker can perform a cross-site scripting attack. Versions  3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21610 | Trix allows Cross-site Scripting via `javascript:` url in a link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21610</link><description>Trix is a what-you-see-is-what-you-get rich text editor for everyday writing. Versions prior to 2.1.12 are vulnerable to cross-site scripting when pasting malicious code in the link field. An attacker could trick the user to copy&amp;amp;paste a malicious `javascript:` URL as a link that would execute arbitrary JavaScript code within the context of the user's session, potentially leading to unauthorized actions being performed or sensitive information being disclosed. Users should upgrade to Trix editor version 2.1.12 or later to receive a patch. In addition to upgrading, affected users can disallow browsers that don't support a Content Security Policy (CSP) as a workaround for this and other cross-site scripting vulnerabilities. Set CSP policies such as script-src 'self' to ensure that only scripts hosted on the same origin are executed, and explicitly prohibit inline scripts using script-src-elem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21609 | SiYuan has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21609</link><description>SiYuan is self-hosted, open source personal knowledge management software. SiYuan Note version 3.1.18 has an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability. The vulnerability exists in the `POST /api/history/getDocHistoryContent` endpoint. An attacker can craft a payload to exploit this vulnerability, resulting in the deletion of arbitrary files on the server. Commit d9887aeec1b27073bec66299a9a4181dc42969f3 fixes this vulnerability and is expected to be available in version 3.1.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56513 | Karmada PULL Mode Cluster Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56513</link><description>Karmada is a Kubernetes management system that allows users to run cloud-native applications across multiple Kubernetes clusters and clouds. Prior to version 1.12.0, the PULL mode clusters registered with the `karmadactl register` command have excessive privileges to access control plane resources. By abusing these permissions, an attacker able to authenticate as the karmada-agent to a karmada cluster would be able to obtain administrative privileges over the entire federation system including all registered member clusters. Since Karmada v1.12.0, command `karmadactl register` restricts the access permissions of pull mode member clusters to control plane resources. This way, an attacker able to authenticate as the karmada-agent cannot control other member clusters in Karmada. As a workaround, one may restrict the access permissions of pull mode member clusters to control plane resources according to Karmada Component Permissions Docs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56514 | Karmada Tar Slips in CRDs archive extraction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56514</link><description>Karmada is a Kubernetes management system that allows users to run cloud-native applications across multiple Kubernetes clusters and clouds. Prior to version 1.12.0, both in karmadactl and karmada-operator, it is possible to supply a filesystem path, or an HTTP(s) URL to retrieve the custom resource definitions(CRDs) needed by Karmada. The CRDs are downloaded as a gzipped tarfile and are vulnerable to a TarSlip vulnerability. An attacker able to supply a malicious CRD file into a Karmada initialization could write arbitrary files in arbitrary paths of the filesystem. From Karmada version 1.12.0, when processing custom CRDs files, CRDs archive verification is utilized to enhance file system robustness. A workaround is available. Someone who needs to set flag `--crd` to customize the CRD files required for Karmada initialization when using `karmadactl init` to set up Karmada can manually inspect the CRD files to check whether they contain sequences such as `../` that would alter file paths, to determine if they potentially include malicious files. When using karmada-operator to set up Karmada, one must upgrade one's karmada-operator to one of the fixed versions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55507 | An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the delete_e.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55507</link><description>An issue in CodeAstro Complaint Management System v.1.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the delete_e.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56408 | Phpspreadsheet allows unauthorized Reflected XSS in `Convert-Online.php` file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56408</link><description>PhpSpreadsheet is a PHP library for reading and writing spreadsheet files. Versions prior to 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 have is no sanitization in the `/vendor/phpoffice/phpspreadsheet/samples/Engineering/Convert-Online.php` file, which leads to the possibility of a cross-site scripting attack. Versions 3.7.0, 2.3.5, 2.1.6, and 1.29.7 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56324 | GoCD vulnerable to XXE injection via abuse of pipeline XML &amp;quot;snippet&amp;quot; editing by group admins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56324</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions prior to 24.4.0 can allow GoCD "group admins" to abuse ability to edit the raw XML configuration for groups they administer to trigger XML External Entity (XXE) injection on the GoCD server. Theoretically, the XXE vulnerability can result in additional attacks such as SSRF, information disclosure from the GoCD server, and directory traversal, although these additional attacks have not been explicitly demonstrated as exploitable. This issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. Some workarounds are available. One may temporarily block access to  `/go/*/pipelines/snippet` routes from an external reverse proxy or WAF if one's "group admin" users do not need the functionality to edit the XML of pipelines directly (rather than using the UI, or using a configuration repository). One may also prevent external access from one's GoCD server to arbitrary locations using some kind of environment egress control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:10:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56322 | GoCD vulnerable to XXE injection via abuse of unused XML configuration repository functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56322</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions 16.7.0 through 24.4.0 (inclusive) can allow GoCD admins to abuse a hidden/unused configuration repository (pipelines as code) feature to allow XML External Entity (XXE) injection on the GoCD Server which will be executed when GoCD periodically scans configuration repositories for pipeline updates, or is triggered by an administrator or config repo admin. In practice the impact of this vulnerability is limited, in most cases without combining with another vulnerability, as only GoCD (super) admins have the ability to abuse this vulnerability. Typically a malicious GoCD admin can cause much larger damage than that they can do with XXE injection. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. As a workaround, prevent external access from the GoCD server to arbitrary locations using some kind of environment egress control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:55:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56321 | GoCD before 24.5.0 can allow malicious GoCD admins to abuse backup configuration to gain additional host access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56321</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions 18.9.0 through 24.4.0 (inclusive) can allow GoCD admins to abuse the backup configuration "post-backup script" feature to potentially execute arbitrary scripts on the hosting server or container as GoCD's user, rather than pre-configured scripts. In practice the impact of this vulnerability is limited, as in most configurations a user who can log into the GoCD UI as an admin also has host administration permissions for the host/container that GoCD runs on, in order to manage artifact storage and other service-level configuration options. Additionally, since a GoCD admin has ability to configure and schedule pipelines tasks on all GoCD agents available to the server, the fundamental functionality of GoCD allows co-ordinated task execution similar to that of post-backup-scripts. However in restricted environments where the host administration is separated from the role of a GoCD admin, this may be unexpected. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. Post-backup scripts can no longer be executed from within certain sensitive locations on the GoCD server. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56320 | GoCD before 24.5.0 is vulnerable to admin privilege escalation by a malicious internal/existing authenticated user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56320</link><description>GoCD is a continuous deliver server. GoCD versions prior to 24.5.0 are vulnerable to admin privilege escalation due to improper authorization of access to the admin "Configuration XML" UI feature, and its associated API. A malicious insider/existing authenticated GoCD user with an existing GoCD user account could abuse this vulnerability to access information intended only for GoCD admins, or to escalate their privileges to that of a GoCD admin in a persistent manner. it is not possible for this vulnerability to be abused prior to authentication/login. The issue is fixed in GoCD 24.5.0. GoCD users who are not able to immediate upgrade can mitigate this issue by using a reverse proxy, WAF or similar to externally block access paths with a `/go/rails/` prefix. Blocking this route causes no loss of functionality. If it is not possible to upgrade or block the above route, consider reducing the GoCD user base to more trusted set of users, including temporarily disabling use of plugins such as the guest-login-plugin, which allow limited anonymous access as a regular user account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48814 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Silverpeas 6.4.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ViewType parameter of the f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48814</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Silverpeas 6.4.1 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the ViewType parameter of the findbywhereclause function</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41780 | IBM Jazz Foundation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41780</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1.0 could 

could allow a physical user to obtain sensitive information due to not masking passwords during entry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55078 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /adminUser/updateImg of WukongCRM-11.0-JAVA v11.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55078</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the component /adminUser/updateImg of WukongCRM-11.0-JAVA v11.3.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5591 | IBM Jazz Foundation information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5591</link><description>IBM Jazz Foundation 7.0.2, 7.0.3, and 7.1.0 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:47:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9140 | Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a critical vulnerability, CVE-2024-9140. This vulne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9140</link><description>Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a critical vulnerability, CVE-2024-9140. This vulnerability allows OS command injection due to improperly restricted commands, potentially enabling attackers to execute arbitrary code. This poses a significant risk to the system’s security and functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12132 | WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website &amp;lt;= 2.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12132</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.4 due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create jobs for companies that are unaffiliated with the attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9138 | Privilege Escalation in Cellular Router, Secure Router, and Network Security Appliances</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9138</link><description>Moxa’s cellular routers, secure routers, and network security appliances are affected by a high-severity vulnerability, CVE-2024-9138. This vulnerability involves hard-coded credentials, enabling an authenticated user to escalate privileges and gain root-level access to the system, posing a significant security risk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22275 | iTerm2 3.5.6 through 3.5.10 before 3.5.11 sometimes allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from terminal commands by readin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22275</link><description>iTerm2 3.5.6 through 3.5.10 before 3.5.11 sometimes allows remote attackers to obtain sensitive information from terminal commands by reading the /tmp/framer.txt file. This can occur for certain it2ssh and SSH Integration configurations, during remote logins to hosts that have a common Python installation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 05:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11624 | there is a possible to add apps to bypass VPN due to Undeclared Permission . This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11624</link><description>there is a possible to add apps to bypass VPN due to Undeclared Permission . This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47032 | In construct_transaction_from_cmd of lwis_ioctl.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47032</link><description>In construct_transaction_from_cmd of lwis_ioctl.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53833 | In prepare_response_locked of  lwis_transaction.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53833</link><description>In prepare_response_locked of  lwis_transaction.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53834 | In sms_DisplayHexDumpOfPrivacyBuffer of sms_Utilities.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53834</link><description>In sms_DisplayHexDumpOfPrivacyBuffer of sms_Utilities.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53835 | there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53835</link><description>there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53836 | In wbrc_bt_dev_write of wb_regon_coordinator.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53836</link><description>In wbrc_bt_dev_write of wb_regon_coordinator.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53837 | In prepare_response of lwis_periodic_io.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53837</link><description>In prepare_response of lwis_periodic_io.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53838 | In Exynos_parsing_user_data_registered_itu_t_t35 of VendorVideoAPI.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53838</link><description>In Exynos_parsing_user_data_registered_itu_t_t35 of VendorVideoAPI.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53839 | In GetCellInfoList() of protocolnetadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53839</link><description>In GetCellInfoList() of protocolnetadapter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with baseband firmware compromise required. User Interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53840 | there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53840</link><description>there is a possible biometric bypass due to an unusual root cause. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53841 | In startListeningForDeviceStateChanges, there is a possible Permission Bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53841</link><description>In startListeningForDeviceStateChanges, there is a possible Permission Bypass due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53842 | In cc_SendCcImsInfoIndMsg of cc_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53842</link><description>In cc_SendCcImsInfoIndMsg of cc_MmConManagement.c, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 03:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0176 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System add_cart.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /user/add_cart.php. The manipulation of the argument id/qty leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 02:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0175 | code-projects Online Shop view.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Shop 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view.php. The manipulation of the argument name/details leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0174 | code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System Parameter search_result2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0174</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Point of Sales and Inventory Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/search_result2.php of the component Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument search leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43077 | In DevmemValidateFlags of devicemem_server.c , there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43077</link><description>In DevmemValidateFlags of devicemem_server.c , there is a possible out of bounds write due to memory corruption. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43097 | In resizeToAtLeast of SkRegion.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43097</link><description>In resizeToAtLeast of SkRegion.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43762 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way to avoid unbinding of a service from the system due to a logic error in the code. This could ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43762</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way to avoid unbinding of a service from the system due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43764 | In onPrimaryClipChanged of ClipboardListener.java, there is a possible way to partially bypass lock screen. This could lead to local escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43764</link><description>In onPrimaryClipChanged of ClipboardListener.java, there is a possible way to partially bypass lock screen. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43767 | In prepare_to_draw_into_mask of SkBlurMaskFilterImpl.cpp, there is a possible heap overflow due to improper input validation. This could lea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43767</link><description>In prepare_to_draw_into_mask of SkBlurMaskFilterImpl.cpp, there is a possible heap overflow due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43768 | In skia_alloc_func of SkDeflate.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43768</link><description>In skia_alloc_func of SkDeflate.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43769 | In isPackageDeviceAdmin of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible edge case which could prevent the uninstallation of CloudDpc due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43769</link><description>In isPackageDeviceAdmin of PackageManagerService.java, there is a possible edge case which could prevent the uninstallation of CloudDpc due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 01:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8447 | Narayana: deadlock via multiple join requests sent to lra coordinator</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8447</link><description>A security issue was discovered in the LRA Coordinator component of Narayana. When Cancel is called in LRA, an execution time of approximately 2 seconds occurs. If Join is called with the same LRA ID within that timeframe, the application may crash or hang indefinitely, leading to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 20:28:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48197 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Audiocodes MP-202b v.4.4.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the login page of the w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48197</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Audiocodes MP-202b v.4.4.3 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the login page of the web interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56199 | phpMyFAQ Vulnerable to Stored HTML Injection at FAQ</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56199</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application. Starting no later than version 3.2.10 and prior to version 4.0.2, an attacker can inject malicious HTML content into the FAQ editor at `http[:]//localhost/admin/index[.]php?action=editentry`, resulting in a complete disruption of the FAQ page's user interface. By injecting malformed HTML elements styled to cover the entire screen, an attacker can render the page unusable. This injection manipulates the page structure by introducing overlapping buttons, images, and iframes, breaking the intended layout and functionality. Exploiting this issue can lead to Denial of Service for legitimate users, damage to the user experience, and potential abuse in phishing or defacement attacks. Version 4.0.2 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0173 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop view_order.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0173</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /orders/view_order.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11716 | While assignment of a user to a team (bracket) in CTFd  should be possible only once, at the registration, a flaw in logic implementation al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11716</link><description>While assignment of a user to a team (bracket) in CTFd  should be possible only once, at the registration, a flaw in logic implementation allows an authenticated user to reset it's bracket and then pick a new one, joining another team while a competition is already ongoing.
This issue impacts releases from 3.7.0 up to 3.7.4 and was addressed by  pull request 2636 https://github.com/CTFd/CTFd/pull/2636  included in 3.7.5 release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 16:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11717 | Tokens in CTFd used for account activation and password resetting can be used interchangeably for these operations. When used, they are sent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11717</link><description>Tokens in CTFd used for account activation and password resetting can be used interchangeably for these operations. When used, they are sent to the server as a GET parameter and they are not single use, which means, that during token expiration time an on-path attacker might reuse such a token to change user's password and take over the account. Moreover, the tokens also include base64 encoded user email.

This issue impacts releases up to 3.7.4 and was addressed by  pull request 2679 https://github.com/CTFd/CTFd/pull/2679  included in 3.7.5 release.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 16:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12907 | XSS in Kentico 7</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12907</link><description>Kentico CMS in version 7 is vulnerable to a Reflected XSS attacks through manipulation of  a specific GET request parameter sent to /CMSMessages/AccessDenied.aspx endpoint.
Notably, support for this version of Kentico ended in 2016. Version 8 was tested as well and does not contain this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9950 | Abuse of Unauthenticated Compliance Recheck in SecureConnector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9950</link><description>A vulnerability in Forescout SecureConnector v11.3.07.0109 on Windows allows 

unauthenticated user to modify compliance scripts due to insecure temporary directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55540 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55540</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39169.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55541 | Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to missing origin validation in postMessage. The following products are affected: Acroni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55541</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability due to missing origin validation in postMessage. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, Windows) before build 39169.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55542 | Local privilege escalation due to excessive permissions assigned to Tray Monitor service. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55542</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to excessive permissions assigned to Tray Monitor service. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 39169, Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 35895.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56413 | Missing session invalidation after user deletion. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39169...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56413</link><description>Missing session invalidation after user deletion. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39169.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56414 | Web installer integrity check used weak hash algorithm. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56414</link><description>Web installer integrity check used weak hash algorithm. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39169.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0172 | code-projects Chat System deleteroom.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0172</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Chat System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/deleteroom.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:39:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55543 | Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55543</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to DLL hijacking vulnerability. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39169.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45811 | WordPress Post Teaser plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.5 - Auth. Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45811</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WeyHan Ng Post Teaser.This issue affects Post Teaser: from n/a through 4.1.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47601 | WordPress WP Table Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47601</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JoomUnited WP Table Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Table Manager: from n/a through 3.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23672 | WordPress GiveWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.25.1 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23672</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Liquid Web / StellarWP GiveWP.This issue affects GiveWP: from n/a through 2.25.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45830 | WordPress Analytify - Google Analytics Dashboard plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.3 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45830</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Analytify.This issue affects Analytify: from n/a through 4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32240 | WordPress Woodmart theme &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32240</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xtemos WoodMart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WoodMart: from n/a through 7.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39994 | WordPress ARMember Premium plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.2 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39994</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Repute InfoSystems ARMember Premium allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ARMember Premium: from n/a through 5.9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40327 | WordPress Putler Connector for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.12.0 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40327</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Putler / Storeapps Putler Connector for WooCommerce.This issue affects Putler Connector for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0171 | code-projects Chat System deleteuser.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0171</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Chat System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/deleteuser.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45272 | WordPress 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.73 - Notice Dismissal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45272</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 10Web 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects 10Web Map Builder for Google Maps: from n/a through 1.0.73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:59:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45633 | WordPress IMPress Listings plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45633</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in IDX IMPress Listings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects IMPress Listings: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41995 | WordPress Photo Gallery – Image Gallery by Ape Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.8 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Galleryape Gallery Images Ape allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gallery Images Ape: from n/a through 2.2.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-49035 | media: s5p_cec: limit msg.len to CEC_MAX_MSG_SIZE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-49035</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: s5p_cec: limit msg.len to CEC_MAX_MSG_SIZE

I expect that the hardware will have limited this to 16, but just in
case it hasn't, check for this corner case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56137 | MaxKB RCE vulnerability in function library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56137</link><description>MaxKB, which stands for Max Knowledge Base, is an open source knowledge base question-answering system based on a large language model and retrieval-augmented generation (RAG). Prior to version 1.9.0, a remote command execution vulnerability exists in the module of function library. The vulnerability allow privileged‌ users to execute OS command in custom scripts. The vulnerability has been fixed in v1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43476 | WordPress Subscribe to Category Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 is vulnerable to Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43476</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Daniel Söderström / Sidney van de Stouwe Subscribe to Category allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Subscribe to Category: from n/a through 2.7.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47778 | WordPress LuckyWP Scripts Control plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47778</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LuckyWP LuckyWP Scripts Control allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LuckyWP Scripts Control: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47807 | WordPress 10WebAnalytics plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47807</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 10Web 10WebAnalytics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects 10WebAnalytics: from n/a through 1.2.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48739 | WordPress Porto Theme Functionality plugin &amp;lt; 2.12.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48739</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Porto Theme Porto Theme - Functionality allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Porto Theme - Functionality: from n/a before 2.12.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48758 | WordPress JetEngine plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48758</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Crocoblock JetEngine allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JetEngine: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49385 | Sensitive information disclosure due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (Windows) befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49385</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (Windows) before build 41736.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55538 | Sensitive information disclosure due to missing authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before build...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55538</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to missing authentication. The following products are affected: Acronis True Image (macOS) before build 41725, Acronis True Image (Windows) before build 41736.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13111 | Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System JWT Token SysUserControl improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13111</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System 1.9.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file src/main/java/com/yf/exam/modules/sys/user/controller/SysUserControl of the component JWT Token Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:09:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37237 | WordPress FS Poster plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37237</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FS-code FS Poster allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects FS Poster: from n/a through 6.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37241 | WordPress WP Job Manager Resume Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37241</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic WP Job Manager - Resume Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Job Manager - Resume Manager: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13110 | Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System Exam Answer PaperController.java， information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13110</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System 1.9.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file src/main/java/com/yf/exam/modules/paper/controller/PaperController.java， of the component Exam Answer Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37438 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash plugin &amp;lt; 4.1.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37438</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit Pro for LearnDash: from n/a before 4.1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37452 | WordPress Schema Lite theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37452</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MyThemeShop Schema Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Schema Lite: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37925 | WordPress BuddyBoss Theme theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.61 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37925</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BUDDYBOSS LLC BuddyBoss Theme allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects BuddyBoss Theme: from n/a through 2.4.61.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37931 | WordPress Point theme &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37931</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Creativthemes Point allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Point: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38731 | WordPress i-amaze theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38731</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marsian i-amaze allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects i-amaze: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38732 | WordPress Patricia Blog theme &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38732</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in VolThemes Patricia Blog allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Patricia Blog: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13109 | Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System doc.html improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13109</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Beijing Yunfan Internet Technology Yunfan Learning Examination System 1.9.2. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doc.html. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38764 | WordPress i-transform theme &amp;lt;= 3.0.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38764</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marsian allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects i-transform: from n/a through 3.0.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:22:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38778 | WordPress WP Fast Total Search &amp;lt;= 1.69.234 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38778</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Epsiloncool WP Fast Total Search.This issue affects WP Fast Total Search: from n/a through 1.69.234.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39623 | WordPress ListingPro theme &amp;lt;= 2.9.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39623</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CridioStudio ListingPro allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ListingPro: from n/a through 2.9.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:22:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13108 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 form2NetSniper.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13108</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/form2NetSniper.cgi. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56014 | WordPress Olivia Theme &amp;lt;= 0.9.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56014</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Markyis Cool Olivia allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Olivia: from n/a through 0.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56257 | WordPress Coins MarketCap plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56257</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CoolPlugins Coins MarketCap allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Coins MarketCap: from n/a through 5.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56268 | WordPress Post Grid Elementor Addon plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.18 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56268</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WP Hait Post Grid Elementor Addon allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Post Grid Elementor Addon: from n/a through 2.0.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44258 | WordPress Schema App Structured Data plugin &amp;lt;= 1.23.1 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44258</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Schema App Schema App Structured Data allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Schema App Structured Data: from n/a through 1.23.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44988 | WordPress WP Custom Admin Interface plugin &amp;lt;= 7.32 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44988</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Martin Gibson WP Custom Admin Interface allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Custom Admin Interface: from n/a through 7.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45002 | WordPress WP User Frontend plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45002</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in weDevs WP User Frontend allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP User Frontend: from n/a through 3.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45045 | WordPress WP Custom Widget area plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45045</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kishor Khambu WP Custom Widget area allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Custom Widget area: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45061 | WordPress WP Job Openings plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45061</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AWSM Innovations WP Job Openings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Job Openings: from n/a through 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45101 | WordPress Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.36.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45101</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CusRev Customer Reviews for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Customer Reviews for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.36.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45104 | WordPress BetterLinks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45104</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper BetterLinks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects BetterLinks: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45110 | WordPress Bold Timeline Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45110</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BoldThemes Bold Timeline Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Bold Timeline Lite: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45271 | WordPress ProductX – Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45271</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WowStore Team ProductX – Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ProductX – Gutenberg WooCommerce Blocks: from n/a through 2.7.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45275 | WordPress Contact Form builder with drag &amp;amp; drop plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.28 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45275</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kali Forms Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop - Kali Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop - Kali Forms: from n/a through 2.3.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45631 | WordPress Gallery – Image and Video Gallery with Thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45631</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpdevart Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45636 | WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Migration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45636</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee WordPress Backup &amp; Migration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WordPress Backup &amp; Migration: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45649 | WordPress Appointment Hour Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45649</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CodePeople Appointment Hour Booking allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Appointment Hour Booking: from n/a through 1.4.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45760 | WordPress wpDiscuz plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45760</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in gVectors Team wpDiscuz allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects wpDiscuz: from n/a through 7.6.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45765 | WordPress WP ERP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45765</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in weDevs WP ERP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP ERP: from n/a through 1.12.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45766 | WordPress Poll Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45766</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Poll Maker Team Poll Maker allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Poll Maker: from n/a through 4.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45828 | WordPress RumbleTalk Live Group Chat plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45828</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RumbleTalk Ltd RumbleTalk Live Group Chat allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects RumbleTalk Live Group Chat: from n/a through 6.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46073 | WordPress DX Delete Attached Media plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability + CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46073</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in nofearinc DX Delete Attached Media allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects DX Delete Attached Media: from n/a through 2.0.5.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46079 | WordPress Ashe Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46079</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Royal Ashe Extra allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ashe Extra: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46080 | WordPress ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46080</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Farhan Noor ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ApplyOnline – Application Form Builder and Manager: from n/a through 2.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46082 | WordPress Broken Link Checker | Finder plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46082</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cyberlord92 Broken Link Checker | Finder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Broken Link Checker | Finder: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46083 | WordPress Kali Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.27 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46083</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Kali Forms Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop - Kali Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Contact Form builder with drag &amp; drop - Kali Forms: from n/a through 2.3.27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46188 | WordPress Freesoul Deactivate Plugins plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46188</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jose Mortellaro Freesoul Deactivate Plugins – Plugin manager and cleanup allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Freesoul Deactivate Plugins – Plugin manager and cleanup: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46195 | WordPress Headline Analyzer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46195</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CoSchedule Headline Analyzer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Headline Analyzer: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46196 | WordPress Social proof testimonials and reviews by Repuso plugin &amp;lt;= 4.97 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46196</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Repuso Social proof testimonials and reviews by Repuso allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Social proof testimonials and reviews by Repuso: from n/a through 4.97.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46203 | WordPress Just Custom Fields plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46203</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JustCoded / Alex Prokopenko Just Custom Fields allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Just Custom Fields: from n/a through 3.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46206 | WordPress MW WP Form plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46206</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in websoudan MW WP Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects MW WP Form: from n/a through 4.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46309 | WordPress wpDiscuz plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46309</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in gVectors Team wpDiscuz allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects wpDiscuz: from n/a through 7.6.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46605 | WordPress Convertful – Your Ultimate On-Site Conversion Tool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46605</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ruslan Suhar Convertful – Your Ultimate On-Site Conversion Tool allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Convertful – Your Ultimate On-Site Conversion Tool: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46606 | WordPress AtomChat plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46606</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AtomChat AtomChat allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AtomChat: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46607 | WordPress WP iCal Availability plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46607</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP iCal Availability WP iCal Availability allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP iCal Availability: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46608 | WordPress DoLogin Security plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.1 - Multiple Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46608</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDO DoLogin Security allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects DoLogin Security: from n/a through 3.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46609 | WordPress FeedFocal plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46609</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FeedFocal FeedFocal allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FeedFocal: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46610 | WordPress Quill Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46610</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in quillforms.com Quill Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Quill Forms: from n/a through 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46611 | WordPress YOP Poll plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.28 - Vote Manipulation Due to Broken Captcha Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46611</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness vulnerability in yourownprogrammer YOP Poll allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects YOP Poll: from n/a through 6.5.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46612 | WordPress Mediabay plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46612</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in codedrafty Mediabay allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Mediabay: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46616 | WordPress Draw Attention plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46616</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NSquared Draw Attention allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Draw Attention: from n/a through 2.0.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46628 | WordPress WP Word Count plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46628</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RedLettuce Plugins WP Word Count allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Word Count: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46631 | WordPress Product Recommendation Quiz for eCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46631</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RevenueHunt Product Recommendation Quiz for eCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Product Recommendation Quiz for eCommerce: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46632 | WordPress My Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46632</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in David Cramer My Shortcodes allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects My Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46633 | WordPress WP Glossary plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46633</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in TCBarrett Glossary allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Glossary: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46635 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46635</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46637 | WordPress Generate Dummy Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46637</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Saurav Sharma Generate Dummy Posts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Generate Dummy Posts: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46639 | WordPress kk Star Ratings plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46639</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FeedbackWP kk Star Ratings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects kk Star Ratings: from n/a through 5.4.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46644 | WordPress WordPress CTA plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46644</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP CTA PRO WordPress CTA allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WordPress CTA: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47179 | WordPress WooODT Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Arbitrary Site Option Update vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47179</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ByConsole WooODT Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooODT Lite: from n/a through 2.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47180 | WordPress Finale Lite – Sales Countdown Timer &amp;amp; Discount for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47180</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in XLPlugins Finale Lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Finale Lite: from n/a through 2.16.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47183 | WordPress GiveWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.33.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47183</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GiveWP GiveWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GiveWP: from n/a through 2.33.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47187 | WordPress Animated Rotating Words plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47187</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Labib Ahmed Animated Rotating Words allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Animated Rotating Words: from n/a through 5.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47188 | WordPress Simple Job Board plugin &amp;lt;= 2.10.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47188</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PressTigers Simple Job Board allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple Job Board: from n/a through 2.10.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47224 | WordPress WP Travel plugin &amp;lt;= 7.8.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47224</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Travel WP Travel allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Travel: from n/a through 7.8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47225 | WordPress Short URL plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47225</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in KaizenCoders Short URL allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Short URL: from n/a through 1.6.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47241 | WordPress CoCart – Headless ecommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.11.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47241</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CoCart Headless, LLC CoCart – Headless ecommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CoCart – Headless ecommerce: from n/a through 3.11.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47515 | WordPress Seers | GDPR &amp;amp; CCPA Cookie Consent &amp;amp; Compliance plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47515</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Seers Seers allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Seers: from n/a through 8.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47523 | WordPress Auto Tag Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47523</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ecreate Infotech Auto Tag Creator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Auto Tag Creator: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47557 | WordPress Visitor Traffic Real Time Statistics plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47557</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wp-buy Visitors Traffic Real Time Statistics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Visitors Traffic Real Time Statistics: from n/a through 7.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47647 | WordPress BadgeOS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.1.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47647</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LearningTimes BadgeOS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects BadgeOS: from n/a through 3.7.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47648 | WordPress EazyDocs plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47648</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in spider-themes EazyDocs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects EazyDocs: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47661 | WordPress Dragfy Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47661</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dragfy Dragfy Addons for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Dragfy Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47689 | WordPress Animator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.10 - Unauthenticated Plugin Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47689</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Toast Plugins Animator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Animator: from n/a through 3.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47692 | WordPress Flo Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.41 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47692</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Flothemes Flo Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Flo Forms: from n/a through 1.0.41.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47693 | WordPress Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47693</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themefic Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7 allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ultimate Addons for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13107 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 ACL form2LocalAclEditcfg.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13107</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/form2LocalAclEditcfg.cgi of the component ACL Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37093 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37093</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in StylemixThemes MasterStudy LMS allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37102 | WordPress Vilva theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37102</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blossom Themes Vilva allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Vilva: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37103 | WordPress Education Zone theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37103</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Education Zone allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Education Zone: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37104 | WordPress Chic Lite theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37104</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Chic Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Chic Lite: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37235 | WordPress Groundhogg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37235</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Groundhogg Inc. Groundhogg allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Groundhogg: from n/a through 3.4.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37236 | WordPress Loco Translate plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37236</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tim Whitlock Loco Translate allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Loco Translate: from n/a through 2.6.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37238 | WordPress WPAdverts – Classifieds plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37238</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Greg Winiarski WPAdverts – Classifieds Plugin allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WPAdverts – Classifieds Plugin: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37240 | WordPress Falang multilanguage for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.51 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37240</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Faboba Falang multilanguage allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Falang multilanguage: from n/a through 1.3.51.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37242 | WordPress Newspack Newsletters plugin &amp;lt;= 2.13.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37242</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Automattic Newspack Newsletters allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Newspack Newsletters: from n/a through 2.13.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37243 | WordPress Vandana Lite theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37243</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blossom Themes Vandana Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Vandana Lite: from n/a through 1.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37272 | WordPress Travel Monster theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37272</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Travel Engine Travel Monster allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Travel Monster: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37274 | WordPress WP Mobile Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37274</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Freshlight Lab WP Mobile Menu allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects WP Mobile Menu: from n/a through 2.8.4.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37412 | WordPress Blossom Shop theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37412</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Blossom Themes Blossom Shop allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Blossom Shop: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37413 | WordPress Preschool and Kindergarten theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37413</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Preschool and Kindergarten allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Preschool and Kindergarten: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37417 | WordPress Coachify theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37417</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Coachify Coachify allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Coachify: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37421 | WordPress JobScout theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37421</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme JobScout allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects JobScout: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37426 | WordPress Elegant Pink theme 1.3.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37426</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Elegant Pink allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Elegant Pink: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37431 | WordPress Mesmerize theme &amp;lt;= 1.6.120 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37431</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Horea Radu Mesmerize allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Mesmerize: from n/a through 1.6.120.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37435 | WordPress Perfect Portfolio theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37435</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Perfect Portfolio allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Perfect Portfolio: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37441 | WordPress NewsMash theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.34 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37441</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DesertThemes NewsMash allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects NewsMash: from n/a through 1.0.34.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37448 | WordPress OnePress theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37448</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FameThemes OnePress allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects OnePress: from n/a through 2.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37450 | WordPress Benevolent theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37450</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Benevolent allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Benevolent: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37451 | WordPress Travel Agency theme &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37451</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Travel Agency allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Travel Agency: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37458 | WordPress Highlight theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.29 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37458</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ExtendThemes Highlight allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Highlight: from n/a through 1.0.29.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37467 | WordPress Hestia theme &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37467</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeIsle Hestia allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Hestia: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37469 | WordPress Blocksy theme &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37469</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CreativeThemes Blocksy allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37473 | WordPress Trendy News theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.15 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37473</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BlazeThemes Trendy News allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Trendy News: from n/a through 1.0.15.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37478 | WordPress Ashe theme &amp;lt;= 2.233 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37478</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Royal Ashe allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Ashe: from n/a through 2.233.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37490 | WordPress Bard theme &amp;lt;= 2.210 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37490</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Royal Bard allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Bard: from n/a through 2.210.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37491 | WordPress Rife Free theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.18 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37491</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Apollo13Themes Rife Free allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Rife Free: from n/a through 2.4.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37493 | WordPress Posterity theme &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37493</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SKT Themes Posterity allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Posterity: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37503 | WordPress Lawyer Landing Page theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37503</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Lawyer Landing Page allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Lawyer Landing Page: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37508 | WordPress Construction Landing Page theme &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37508</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Construction Landing Page allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Construction Landing Page: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37511 | WordPress Swift Performance Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.6.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37511</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SWTE Swift Performance Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Swift Performance Lite: from n/a through 2.3.6.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37518 | WordPress The Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 6.5.1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37518</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in The Events Calendar The Events Calendar allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects The Events Calendar: from n/a through 6.5.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37540 | WordPress Leaky Paywall plugin &amp;lt;= 4.21.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37540</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Leaky Paywall Leaky Paywall allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Leaky Paywall: from n/a through 4.21.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37543 | WordPress Ultimate Auction plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37543</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Nitesh Singh Ultimate Auction  allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Ultimate Auction : from n/a through 4.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37937 | WordPress Rara Business theme &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37937</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Rara Theme Rara Business allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Rara Business: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38691 | WordPress Metorik plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38691</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Metorik Metorik – Reports &amp; Email Automation for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Metorik – Reports &amp; Email Automation for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38729 | WordPress MBE eShip plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38729</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MBE Worldwide S.p.A. MBE eShip allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects MBE eShip: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38751 | WordPress  AdsforWP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.28 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38751</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Magazine3 Google Adsense &amp; Banner Ads by AdsforWP allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Google Adsense &amp; Banner Ads by AdsforWP: from n/a through 1.9.28.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38753 | WordPress Animated Rotating Words Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38753</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Labib Ahmed Animated Rotating Words allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Animated Rotating Words: from n/a through 5.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38754 | WordPress Tagbox plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38754</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tagbox Taggbox allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Taggbox: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38762 | WordPress Event Tickets and Registration plugin &amp;lt;= 5.11.0.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38762</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in The Events Calendar Event Tickets allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Event Tickets: from n/a through 5.11.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38763 | WordPress Popularis Verse theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38763</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Themes4WP Popularis Verse allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Popularis Verse: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38765 | WordPress Oceanic theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.48 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38765</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Freelancelot Oceanic allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Oceanic: from n/a through 1.0.48.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38766 | WordPress Matomo Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38766</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Matomo Matomo Analytics allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Matomo Analytics: from n/a through 5.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38789 | WordPress Telegram Bot &amp;amp; Channel plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38789</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Marco Milesi Telegram Bot &amp; Channel allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Telegram Bot &amp; Channel: from n/a through 3.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38790 | WordPress Smartsupp plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38790</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Smartsupp Smartsupp – live chat, chatbots, AI and lead generation allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Smartsupp – live chat, chatbots, AI and lead generation: from n/a through 3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43927 | WordPress Email Address Encoder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.23 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43927</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Till Krüss Email Address Encoder allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Email Address Encoder: from n/a through 1.0.23.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56018 | WordPress BU Section Editing Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56018</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Boston University (IS&amp;amp;T) BU Section Editing allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects BU Section Editing: from n/a through 0.9.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56022 | WordPress Preloader by WordPress Monsters plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56022</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WordPress Monsters Preloader by WordPress Monsters allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Preloader by WordPress Monsters: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56023 | WordPress WP eCommerce Quickpay plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56023</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Perfect Solution WP eCommerce Quickpay allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP eCommerce Quickpay: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56024 | WordPress Custom Dashboard Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56024</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DuoGeek Custom Dashboard Widget allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Custom Dashboard Widget: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56025 | WordPress AdWork Media EZ Content Locker plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56025</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AdWorkMedia.com AdWork Media EZ Content Locker allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects AdWork Media EZ Content Locker: from n/a through 3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56026 | WordPress Simple Proxy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56026</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Greg Priday Simple Proxy allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Proxy: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56236 | WordPress Hestia Nginx Cache plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56236</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jakob Bouchard Hestia Nginx Cache allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Hestia Nginx Cache: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56237 | WordPress Contest Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 24.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56237</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Contest Gallery Contest Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Contest Gallery: from n/a through 24.0.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56238 | WordPress Floating Action Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56238</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in QunatumCloud Floating Action Buttons allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Floating Action Buttons: from n/a through 0.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56239 | WordPress Themify Audio Dock plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Themify Themify Audio Dock allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Themify Audio Dock: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56240 | WordPress Pronamic Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pronamic Pronamic Google Maps allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Pronamic Google Maps: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56241 | WordPress WPKoi Templates for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56241</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPKoi WPKoi Templates for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WPKoi Templates for Elementor: from n/a through 3.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56242 | WordPress Arconix Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56242</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Arconix Shortcodes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Arconix Shortcodes: from n/a through 2.1.14.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56243 | WordPress WPSSO Core plugin &amp;lt;= 18.18.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56243</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Morisset WPSSO Core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WPSSO Core: from n/a through 18.18.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56244 | WordPress Ashe Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.92 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56244</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Royal Ashe Extra allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ashe Extra: from n/a through 1.2.92.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56245 | WordPress Premium Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.42 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leap13 Premium Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Premium Blocks – Gutenberg Blocks for WordPress: from n/a through 2.1.42.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56246 | WordPress Nexter Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in POSIMYTH Nexter Blocks allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Nexter Blocks: from n/a through 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56247 | WordPress WP Post Author plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56247</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in AF themes WP Post Author allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Post Author: from n/a through 3.8.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56248 | WordPress WPMasterToolKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.1 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56248</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Webdeclic WPMasterToolKit allows Path Traversal.This issue affects WPMasterToolKit: from n/a through 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56249 | WordPress WPMasterToolKit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.13.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56249</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Webdeclic WPMasterToolKit allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects WPMasterToolKit: from n/a through 1.13.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56250 | WordPress Just Writing Statistics plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56250</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in GregRoss Just Writing Statistics allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Just Writing Statistics: from n/a through 4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56251 | WordPress Event Espresso plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.28.decaf - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56251</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Event Espresso Event Espresso 4 Decaf allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Event Espresso 4 Decaf: from n/a through 5.0.28.decaf.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56252 | WordPress Enter Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56252</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeLooks Enter Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Enter Addons: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56253 | WordPress Data Tables Generator by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.36 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56253</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in supsystic.com Data Tables Generator by Supsystic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Data Tables Generator by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.10.36.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56254 | WordPress Move Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56254</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in moveaddons Move Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Move Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56255 | WordPress AyeCode Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56255</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AyeCode AyeCode Connect allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects AyeCode Connect: from n/a through 1.3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56258 | WordPress Magazine Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56258</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPBlockArt Magazine Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Magazine Blocks: from n/a through 1.3.20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56259 | WordPress GeoDirectory plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.84 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56259</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AyeCode - WP Business Directory Plugins GeoDirectory allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GeoDirectory: from n/a through 2.3.84.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56260 | WordPress ShopElement plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in StorePlugin ShopElement allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ShopElement: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56261 | WordPress Project Showcase plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GS Plugins Project Showcase allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Project Showcase: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56262 | WordPress GS Coaches plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56262</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GS Plugins GS Coaches allows Stored XSS.This issue affects GS Coaches: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56263 | WordPress GS Shots for Dribbble plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56263</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GS Plugins GS Shots for Dribbble allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects GS Shots for Dribbble: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56264 | WordPress ACF City Selector plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.0 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56264</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Beee ACF City Selector allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects ACF City Selector: from n/a through 1.14.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56266 | WordPress MP3 Audio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56266</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sonaar Music MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar: from n/a through 5.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56267 | WordPress Interactive UK Map plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.8 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56267</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fla-shop.com Interactive UK Map allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Interactive UK Map: from n/a through 3.4.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56302 | WordPress ConvertCalculator for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56302</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ConvertCalculator ConvertCalculator for WordPress allows Stored XSS.This issue affects ConvertCalculator for WordPress: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13106 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 IP QoS form2IPQoSTcAdd access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13106</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/form2IPQoSTcAdd of the component IP QoS Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 11:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13105 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 DHCPD Setting form2Dhcpd.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13105</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/form2Dhcpd.cgi of the component DHCPD Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 11:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13104 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 WiFi Settings form2AdvanceSetup.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13104</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/form2AdvanceSetup.cgi of the component WiFi Settings Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 10:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13103 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 Virtual Service form2AddVrtsrv.cgi access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13103</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/form2AddVrtsrv.cgi of the component Virtual Service Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13102 | D-Link DIR-816 A2 DDNS Service access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13102</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in D-Link DIR-816 A2 1.10CNB05_R1B011D88210. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/DDNS of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56019 | WordPress Inline Footnotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56019</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Gavin Rehkemper Inline Footnotes allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Inline Footnotes: from n/a through 2.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56027 | WordPress Leads CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.13 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56027</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BizSwoop a CPF Concepts, LLC Brand Leads CRM allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Leads CRM: from n/a through 2.0.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56028 | WordPress Lemonade Social Networks Autoposter Pinterest plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56028</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Lemonade Coding Studio Lemonade Social Networks Autoposter Pinterest allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Lemonade Social Networks Autoposter Pinterest: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56029 | WordPress Easy Language Switcher plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56029</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dreamwinner Easy Language Switcher allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Easy Language Switcher: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56030 | WordPress 10CentMail plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.50 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56030</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 10CentMail allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects 10CentMail: from n/a through 2.1.50.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56032 | WordPress FV Descriptions plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56032</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Foliovision FV Descriptions allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FV Descriptions: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56033 | WordPress FAQs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56033</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 FAQs allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FAQs: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13062 | An unintended entry point vulnerability has been identified in certain router models, which may allow for arbitrary command execution.
Refer...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13062</link><description>An unintended entry point vulnerability has been identified in certain router models, which may allow for arbitrary command execution.
Refer to the ' 01/02/2025 ASUS Router AiCloud vulnerability' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56034 | WordPress Services updates for customers plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56034</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Irshad Services updates for customers allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Services updates for customers: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56035 | WordPress Upload Scanner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56035</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kurt Payne Upload Scanner allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Upload Scanner: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56036 | WordPress odPhotogallery plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56036</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ondrej Donek odPhotogallery allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects odPhotogallery: from n/a through 0.5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56037 | WordPress User Referral plugin &amp;lt;= 8.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56037</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Md Maruf Adnan Sami User Referral allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects User Referral: from n/a through 8.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56038 | WordPress SendSMS Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56038</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SendSMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SendSMS: from n/a through 1.2.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56060 | WordPress HTML Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56060</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HTML Forms allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects HTML Forms: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56069 | WordPress WP SuperBackup plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56069</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Azzaroco WP SuperBackup allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP SuperBackup: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:27:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12912 | An improper input insertion vulnerability in AiCloud on certain router models may lead to arbitrary command execution.
Refer to the '01/02/2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12912</link><description>An improper input insertion vulnerability in AiCloud on certain router models may lead to arbitrary command execution.
Refer to the '01/02/2025 ASUS Router AiCloud vulnerability' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13093 | code-projects Job Recruitment Seeker Profile _call_main_search_ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13093</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /_parse/_call_main_search_ajax.php of the component Seeker Profile Handler. The manipulation of the argument s1 leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 09:09:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13092 | code-projects Job Recruitment Job Post search_ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13092</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /_parse/_call_job/search_ajax.php of the component Job Post Handler. The manipulation of the argument n leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 08:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11184 | WP Enabled SVG &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Author+ Stored XSS via SVG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11184</link><description>The wp-enable-svg WordPress plugin through 0.7 does not sanitize SVG files when uploaded, allowing for authors and above to upload SVGs containing malicious scripts</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11357 | Goodlayers Core &amp;lt; 2.0.10 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11357</link><description>The goodlayers-core WordPress plugin before 2.0.10 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12595 | AHAthat Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Reflected XSS via REQUEST_URI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12595</link><description>The AHAthat Plugin WordPress plugin through 1.6 does not escape the $_SERVER['REQUEST_URI'] parameter before outputting it back in an attribute, which could lead to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in old web browsers</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 06:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2002-20002 | The Net::EasyTCP package before 0.15 for Perl always uses Perl's builtin rand(), which is not a strong random number generator, for cryptogr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2002-20002</link><description>The Net::EasyTCP package before 0.15 for Perl always uses Perl's builtin rand(), which is not a strong random number generator, for cryptographic keys.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 05:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56830 | The Net::EasyTCP package 0.15 through 0.26 for Perl uses Perl's builtin rand() if no strong randomization module is present.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56830</link><description>The Net::EasyTCP package 0.15 through 0.26 for Perl uses Perl's builtin rand() if no strong randomization module is present.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 05:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56829 | Huang Yaoshi Pharmaceutical Management Software through 16.0 allows arbitrary file upload via a .asp filename in the fileName element of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56829</link><description>Huang Yaoshi Pharmaceutical Management Software through 16.0 allows arbitrary file upload via a .asp filename in the fileName element of the UploadFile element in a SOAP request to /XSDService.asmx.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 04:11:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22214 | Landray EIS 2001 through 2006 allows Message/fi_message_receiver.aspx?replyid= SQL injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22214</link><description>Landray EIS 2001 through 2006 allows Message/fi_message_receiver.aspx?replyid= SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 04:11:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0168 | code-projects Job Recruitment _feedback_system.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0168</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Job Recruitment 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /_parse/_feedback_system.php. The manipulation of the argument person leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 13:40:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11846 | Travel Tour &amp;lt; 5.2.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11846</link><description>The  does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>