<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:54:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-5117 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5117</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.6.0 in which users were unaware that files uploaded to comments on confidential issues and epics of public projects could be accessed without authentication via a direct link to the uploaded file URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47102 | IBM AIX denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47102</link><description>IBM AIX 7.2, 7.3, VIOS 3.1, and 4.1

could allow a non-privileged local user to exploit a vulnerability in the AIX perfstat kernel extension to cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52535 | Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.6.1 and prior and Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.0 and prior, contain a symboli...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52535</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs versions 4.6.1 and prior and Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs versions 4.5.0 and prior, contain a symbolic link (symlink) attack vulnerability in the software remediation component. A low-privileged authenticated user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, gaining privileges escalation, leading to arbitrary deletion of files and folders from the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:47:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39725 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39725</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser. This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39727 | IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights tabnabbing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39727</link><description>IBM Engineering Lifecycle Optimization - Engineering Insights 7.0.2 and 7.0.3 uses a web link with untrusted references to an external site. A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to expose sensitive information or perform unauthorized actions on the victims’ web browser.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8950 | SQLi in Arne Informatics&amp;#x27; Piramit Automation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8950</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Arne Informatics Piramit Automation allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Piramit Automation: before 27.09.2024.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 12:55:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52046 | Apache MINA: MINA applications using unbounded deserialization may allow RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52046</link><description>The ObjectSerializationDecoder in Apache MINA uses Java’s native deserialization protocol to process
incoming serialized data but lacks the necessary security checks and defenses. This vulnerability allows
attackers to exploit the deserialization process by sending specially crafted malicious serialized data,
potentially leading to remote code execution (RCE) attacks.



					


				


			


		


	
This issue affects MINA core versions 2.0.X, 2.1.X and 2.2.X, and will be fixed by the releases 2.0.27, 2.1.10 and 2.2.4.





It's also important to note that an application using MINA core library will only be affected if the IoBuffer#getObject() method is called, and this specific method is potentially called when adding a ProtocolCodecFilter instance using the ObjectSerializationCodecFactory class in the filter chain. If your application is specifically using those classes, you have to upgrade to the latest version of MINA core library.




Upgrading will  not be enough: you also need to explicitly allow the classes the decoder will accept in the ObjectSerializationDecoder instance, using one of the three new methods:




    /**

     * Accept class names where the supplied ClassNameMatcher matches for

     * deserialization, unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param classNameMatcher the matcher to use

     */

    public void accept(ClassNameMatcher classNameMatcher)




    /**

     * Accept class names that match the supplied pattern for

     * deserialization, unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param pattern standard Java regexp

     */

    public void accept(Pattern pattern) 





    /**

     * Accept the wildcard specified classes for deserialization,

     * unless they are otherwise rejected.

     *

     * @param patterns Wildcard file name patterns as defined by

     *                  {@link org.apache.commons.io.FilenameUtils#wildcardMatch(String, String) FilenameUtils.wildcardMatch}

     */

    public void accept(String... patterns)







By default, the decoder will reject *all* classes that will be present in the incoming data.







Note: The FtpServer, SSHd and Vysper sub-project are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10862 | NEX-Forms &amp;lt;= 8.7.13 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10862</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search_params' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 8.7.13 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This can be exploited via CSRF due to a lack of nonce validation on the get_table_records AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11281 | WooCommerce Point of Sale &amp;lt;= 6.1.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Privilege Escalation via Arbitrary User Email Change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11281</link><description>The WooCommerce Point of Sale plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.0. This is due to insufficient validation on the 'logged_in_user_id' value when option values are empty and the ability for attackers to change the email of arbitrary user accounts. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the email of arbitrary user accounts, including administrators, and reset their password to gain access to the account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12335 | Avada Builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Protected Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12335</link><description>The Avada (Fusion) Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.12 via the handle_clone_post() function and the 'fusion_blog' shortcode and due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10858 | Jetpack 13.0-14.0 - Unauthenticated DOM-XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10858</link><description>The Jetpack  WordPress plugin before 14.1 does not properly checks the postmessage origin in its 13.x versions, allowing it to be bypassed and leading to DOM-XSS. The issue only affects websites hosted on WordPress.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 06:16:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12428 | WP Data Access – App, Table, Form and Chart Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.22 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12428</link><description>The WP Data Access – App, Table, Form and Chart Builder plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'order[user_login][dir]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.5.22 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 04:35:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12636 | Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp;amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12636</link><description>The Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'create_popup_delete_process' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete popups via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12032 | Tourfic – Ultimate Hotel Booking, Travel Booking &amp;amp; Apartment Booking WordPress Plugin | WooCommerce Booking &amp;lt;= 2.15.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12032</link><description>The Tourfic – Ultimate Hotel Booking, Travel Booking &amp; Apartment Booking WordPress Plugin | WooCommerce Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'enquiry_id' parameter of the 'tf_enquiry_reply_email_callback' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.15.3 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12190 | Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp;amp; Custom Contact Form builder &amp;lt;=  2.17.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Form Submission Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12190</link><description>The Contact Form by Bit Form: Multi Step Form, Calculation Contact Form, Payment Contact Form &amp; Custom Contact Form builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the bitform-form-entry-edit endpoint in all versions up to, and including,  2.17.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view all form submissions from other users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12272 | WP Travel Engine – Elementor Widgets | Create Travel Booking Website Using WordPress and Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12272</link><description>The WP Travel Engine – Elementor Widgets | Create Travel Booking Website Using WordPress and Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.7 via several widgets. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12413 | MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 2.0.00 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12413</link><description>The MarketKing — Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to missing capability checks on several functions like 'marketking_delete_team_member', 'marketkingrejectuser', 'marketking_save_profile_settings', and many more in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.00. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete users, update settings, approve users, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1609 | OPPO Store APP has a WebView component privilege escalation vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1609</link><description>In OPPOStore iOS App, there's a possible escalation of privilege due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 03:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-2483 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-2483</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 19:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-21505 | In the linux kernel, if IMA appraisal is used with the "ima_appraise=log" boot param, lockdown can be defeated with kexec on any machine whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-21505</link><description>In the linux kernel, if IMA appraisal is used with the "ima_appraise=log" boot param, lockdown can be defeated with kexec on any machine when Secure Boot is disabled or unavailable. IMA prevents setting "ima_appraise=log" from the boot param when Secure Boot is enabled, but this does not cover cases where lockdown is used without Secure Boot. CVSS 3.1 Base Score 6.7 (Confidentiality, Integrity, Availability impacts). CVSS Vector: (CVSS:3.1/AV:L/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H).</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 18:54:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12744 | SQL Injection in the Amazon Redshift JDBC Driver affecting v2.1.0.31</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12744</link><description>A SQL injection in the Amazon Redshift JDBC Driver in v2.1.0.31 allows a user to gain escalated privileges via the getSchemas, getTables, or getColumns Metadata APIs. Users should upgrade to the driver version 2.1.0.32 or revert to driver version 2.1.0.30.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 16:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12745 | SQL Injection in the Amazon Redshift Python Connector affecting v2.1.4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12745</link><description>A SQL injection in the Amazon Redshift Python Connector v2.1.4 allows a user to gain escalated privileges via the get_schemas, get_tables, or get_columns Metadata APIs. Users are recommended to upgrade to the driver version 2.1.5 or revert to driver version 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 16:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12746 | SQL Injection in the Amazon Redshift ODBC Driver affecting v2.1.5.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12746</link><description>A SQL injection in the Amazon Redshift ODBC Driver v2.1.5.0 (Windows or Linux) allows a user to gain escalated privileges via the SQLTables or SQLColumns Metadata APIs. Users are recommended to upgrade to the driver version 2.1.6.0 or revert to driver version 2.1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 16:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43441 | Apache HugeGraph-Server: Fixed JWT Token(Secret)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43441</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Assumed-Immutable Data vulnerability in Apache HugeGraph-Server.

This issue affects Apache HugeGraph-Server: from 1.0.0 before 1.5.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.5.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53145 | um: Fix potential integer overflow during physmem setup</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53145</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

um: Fix potential integer overflow during physmem setup

This issue happens when the real map size is greater than LONG_MAX,
which can be easily triggered on UML/i386.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53146 | NFSD: Prevent a potential integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53146</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

NFSD: Prevent a potential integer overflow

If the tag length is &gt;= U32_MAX - 3 then the "length + 4" addition
can result in an integer overflow. Address this by splitting the
decoding into several steps so that decode_cb_compound4res() does
not have to perform arithmetic on the unsafe length value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53147 | exfat: fix out-of-bounds access of directory entries</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53147</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

exfat: fix out-of-bounds access of directory entries

In the case of the directory size is greater than or equal to
the cluster size, if start_clu becomes an EOF cluster(an invalid
cluster) due to file system corruption, then the directory entry
where ei-&gt;hint_femp.eidx hint is outside the directory, resulting
in an out-of-bounds access, which may cause further file system
corruption.

This commit adds a check for start_clu, if it is an invalid cluster,
the file or directory will be treated as empty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53148 | comedi: Flush partial mappings in error case</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53148</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: Flush partial mappings in error case

If some remap_pfn_range() calls succeeded before one failed, we still have
buffer pages mapped into the userspace page tables when we drop the buffer
reference with comedi_buf_map_put(bm). The userspace mappings are only
cleaned up later in the mmap error path.

Fix it by explicitly flushing all mappings in our VMA on the error path.

See commit 79a61cc3fc04 ("mm: avoid leaving partial pfn mappings around in
error case").</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53149 | usb: typec: ucsi: glink: fix off-by-one in connector_status</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53149</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: typec: ucsi: glink: fix off-by-one in connector_status

UCSI connector's indices start from 1 up to 3, PMIC_GLINK_MAX_PORTS.
Correct the condition in the pmic_glink_ucsi_connector_status()
callback, fixing Type-C orientation reporting for the third USB-C
connector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53150 | ALSA: usb-audio: Fix out of bounds reads when finding clock sources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53150</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ALSA: usb-audio: Fix out of bounds reads when finding clock sources

The current USB-audio driver code doesn't check bLength of each
descriptor at traversing for clock descriptors.  That is, when a
device provides a bogus descriptor with a shorter bLength, the driver
might hit out-of-bounds reads.

For addressing it, this patch adds sanity checks to the validator
functions for the clock descriptor traversal.  When the descriptor
length is shorter than expected, it's skipped in the loop.

For the clock source and clock multiplier descriptors, we can just
check bLength against the sizeof() of each descriptor type.
OTOH, the clock selector descriptor of UAC2 and UAC3 has an array
of bNrInPins elements and two more fields at its tail, hence those
have to be checked in addition to the sizeof() check.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53151 | svcrdma: Address an integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53151</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

svcrdma: Address an integer overflow

Dan Carpenter reports:
&gt; Commit 78147ca8b4a9 ("svcrdma: Add a "parsed chunk list" data
&gt; structure") from Jun 22, 2020 (linux-next), leads to the following
&gt; Smatch static checker warning:
&gt;
&gt;	net/sunrpc/xprtrdma/svc_rdma_recvfrom.c:498 xdr_check_write_chunk()
&gt;	warn: potential user controlled sizeof overflow 'segcount * 4 * 4'
&gt;
&gt; net/sunrpc/xprtrdma/svc_rdma_recvfrom.c
&gt;     488 static bool xdr_check_write_chunk(struct svc_rdma_recv_ctxt *rctxt)
&gt;     489 {
&gt;     490         u32 segcount;
&gt;     491         __be32 *p;
&gt;     492
&gt;     493         if (xdr_stream_decode_u32(&amp;amp;rctxt-&gt;rc_stream, &amp;amp;segcount))
&gt;                                                               ^^^^^^^^
&gt;
&gt;     494                 return false;
&gt;     495
&gt;     496         /* A bogus segcount causes this buffer overflow check to fail. */
&gt;     497         p = xdr_inline_decode(&amp;amp;rctxt-&gt;rc_stream,
&gt; --&gt; 498                               segcount * rpcrdma_segment_maxsz * sizeof(*p));
&gt;
&gt;
&gt; segcount is an untrusted u32.  On 32bit systems anything &gt;= SIZE_MAX / 16 will
&gt; have an integer overflow and some those values will be accepted by
&gt; xdr_inline_decode().</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53152 | PCI: tegra194: Move controller cleanups to pex_ep_event_pex_rst_deassert()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53152</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: tegra194: Move controller cleanups to pex_ep_event_pex_rst_deassert()

Currently, the endpoint cleanup function dw_pcie_ep_cleanup() and EPF
deinit notify function pci_epc_deinit_notify() are called during the
execution of pex_ep_event_pex_rst_assert() i.e., when the host has asserted
PERST#. But quickly after this step, refclk will also be disabled by the
host.

All of the tegra194 endpoint SoCs supported as of now depend on the refclk
from the host for keeping the controller operational. Due to this
limitation, any access to the hardware registers in the absence of refclk
will result in a whole endpoint crash. Unfortunately, most of the
controller cleanups require accessing the hardware registers (like eDMA
cleanup performed in dw_pcie_ep_cleanup(), etc...). So these cleanup
functions can cause the crash in the endpoint SoC once host asserts PERST#.

One way to address this issue is by generating the refclk in the endpoint
itself and not depending on the host. But that is not always possible as
some of the endpoint designs do require the endpoint to consume refclk from
the host.

Thus, fix this crash by moving the controller cleanups to the start of
the pex_ep_event_pex_rst_deassert() function. This function is called
whenever the host has deasserted PERST# and it is guaranteed that the
refclk would be active at this point. So at the start of this function
(after enabling resources) the controller cleanup can be performed. Once
finished, rest of the code execution for PERST# deassert can continue as
usual.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53153 | PCI: qcom-ep: Move controller cleanups to qcom_pcie_perst_deassert()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53153</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

PCI: qcom-ep: Move controller cleanups to qcom_pcie_perst_deassert()

Currently, the endpoint cleanup function dw_pcie_ep_cleanup() and EPF
deinit notify function pci_epc_deinit_notify() are called during the
execution of qcom_pcie_perst_assert() i.e., when the host has asserted
PERST#. But quickly after this step, refclk will also be disabled by the
host.

All of the Qcom endpoint SoCs supported as of now depend on the refclk from
the host for keeping the controller operational. Due to this limitation,
any access to the hardware registers in the absence of refclk will result
in a whole endpoint crash. Unfortunately, most of the controller cleanups
require accessing the hardware registers (like eDMA cleanup performed in
dw_pcie_ep_cleanup(), powering down MHI EPF etc...). So these cleanup
functions are currently causing the crash in the endpoint SoC once host
asserts PERST#.

One way to address this issue is by generating the refclk in the endpoint
itself and not depending on the host. But that is not always possible as
some of the endpoint designs do require the endpoint to consume refclk from
the host (as I was told by the Qcom engineers).

Thus, fix this crash by moving the controller cleanups to the start of
the qcom_pcie_perst_deassert() function. qcom_pcie_perst_deassert() is
called whenever the host has deasserted PERST# and it is guaranteed that
the refclk would be active at this point. So at the start of this function
(after enabling resources), the controller cleanup can be performed. Once
finished, rest of the code execution for PERST# deassert can continue as
usual.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53154 | clk: clk-apple-nco: Add NULL check in applnco_probe</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53154</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

clk: clk-apple-nco: Add NULL check in applnco_probe

Add NULL check in applnco_probe, to handle kernel NULL pointer
dereference error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53155 | ocfs2: fix uninitialized value in ocfs2_file_read_iter()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53155</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ocfs2: fix uninitialized value in ocfs2_file_read_iter()

Syzbot has reported the following KMSAN splat:

BUG: KMSAN: uninit-value in ocfs2_file_read_iter+0x9a4/0xf80
 ocfs2_file_read_iter+0x9a4/0xf80
 __io_read+0x8d4/0x20f0
 io_read+0x3e/0xf0
 io_issue_sqe+0x42b/0x22c0
 io_wq_submit_work+0xaf9/0xdc0
 io_worker_handle_work+0xd13/0x2110
 io_wq_worker+0x447/0x1410
 ret_from_fork+0x6f/0x90
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30

Uninit was created at:
 __alloc_pages_noprof+0x9a7/0xe00
 alloc_pages_mpol_noprof+0x299/0x990
 alloc_pages_noprof+0x1bf/0x1e0
 allocate_slab+0x33a/0x1250
 ___slab_alloc+0x12ef/0x35e0
 kmem_cache_alloc_bulk_noprof+0x486/0x1330
 __io_alloc_req_refill+0x84/0x560
 io_submit_sqes+0x172f/0x2f30
 __se_sys_io_uring_enter+0x406/0x41c0
 __x64_sys_io_uring_enter+0x11f/0x1a0
 x64_sys_call+0x2b54/0x3ba0
 do_syscall_64+0xcd/0x1e0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

Since an instance of 'struct kiocb' may be passed from the block layer
with 'private' field uninitialized, introduce 'ocfs2_iocb_init_rw_locked()'
and use it from where 'ocfs2_dio_end_io()' might take care, i.e. in
'ocfs2_file_read_iter()' and 'ocfs2_file_write_iter()'.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53156 | wifi: ath9k: add range check for conn_rsp_epid in htc_connect_service()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53156</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

wifi: ath9k: add range check for conn_rsp_epid in htc_connect_service()

I found the following bug in my fuzzer:

  UBSAN: array-index-out-of-bounds in drivers/net/wireless/ath/ath9k/htc_hst.c:26:51
  index 255 is out of range for type 'htc_endpoint [22]'
  CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 8 Comm: kworker/0:0 Not tainted 6.11.0-rc6-dirty #14
  Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
  Workqueue: events request_firmware_work_func
  Call Trace:
   
   dump_stack_lvl+0x180/0x1b0
   __ubsan_handle_out_of_bounds+0xd4/0x130
   htc_issue_send.constprop.0+0x20c/0x230
   ? _raw_spin_unlock_irqrestore+0x3c/0x70
   ath9k_wmi_cmd+0x41d/0x610
   ? mark_held_locks+0x9f/0xe0
   ...

Since this bug has been confirmed to be caused by insufficient verification
of conn_rsp_epid, I think it would be appropriate to add a range check for
conn_rsp_epid to htc_connect_service() to prevent the bug from occurring.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53157 | firmware: arm_scpi: Check the DVFS OPP count returned by the firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53157</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: arm_scpi: Check the DVFS OPP count returned by the firmware

Fix a kernel crash with the below call trace when the SCPI firmware
returns OPP count of zero.

dvfs_info.opp_count may be zero on some platforms during the reboot
test, and the kernel will crash after dereferencing the pointer to
kcalloc(info-&gt;count, sizeof(*opp), GFP_KERNEL).

  |  Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000028
  |  Mem abort info:
  |    ESR = 0x96000004
  |    Exception class = DABT (current EL), IL = 32 bits
  |    SET = 0, FnV = 0
  |    EA = 0, S1PTW = 0
  |  Data abort info:
  |    ISV = 0, ISS = 0x00000004
  |    CM = 0, WnR = 0
  |  user pgtable: 4k pages, 48-bit VAs, pgdp = 00000000faefa08c
  |  [0000000000000028] pgd=0000000000000000
  |  Internal error: Oops: 96000004 [#1] SMP
  |  scpi-hwmon: probe of PHYT000D:00 failed with error -110
  |  Process systemd-udevd (pid: 1701, stack limit = 0x00000000aaede86c)
  |  CPU: 2 PID: 1701 Comm: systemd-udevd Not tainted 4.19.90+ #1
  |  Hardware name: PHYTIUM LTD Phytium FT2000/4/Phytium FT2000/4, BIOS
  |  pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO)
  |  pc : scpi_dvfs_recalc_rate+0x40/0x58 [clk_scpi]
  |  lr : clk_register+0x438/0x720
  |  Call trace:
  |   scpi_dvfs_recalc_rate+0x40/0x58 [clk_scpi]
  |   devm_clk_hw_register+0x50/0xa0
  |   scpi_clk_ops_init.isra.2+0xa0/0x138 [clk_scpi]
  |   scpi_clocks_probe+0x528/0x70c [clk_scpi]
  |   platform_drv_probe+0x58/0xa8
  |   really_probe+0x260/0x3d0
  |   driver_probe_device+0x12c/0x148
  |   device_driver_attach+0x74/0x98
  |   __driver_attach+0xb4/0xe8
  |   bus_for_each_dev+0x88/0xe0
  |   driver_attach+0x30/0x40
  |   bus_add_driver+0x178/0x2b0
  |   driver_register+0x64/0x118
  |   __platform_driver_register+0x54/0x60
  |   scpi_clocks_driver_init+0x24/0x1000 [clk_scpi]
  |   do_one_initcall+0x54/0x220
  |   do_init_module+0x54/0x1c8
  |   load_module+0x14a4/0x1668
  |   __se_sys_finit_module+0xf8/0x110
  |   __arm64_sys_finit_module+0x24/0x30
  |   el0_svc_common+0x78/0x170
  |   el0_svc_handler+0x38/0x78
  |   el0_svc+0x8/0x340
  |  Code: 937d7c00 a94153f3 a8c27bfd f9400421 (b8606820)
  |  ---[ end trace 06feb22469d89fa8 ]---
  |  Kernel panic - not syncing: Fatal exception
  |  SMP: stopping secondary CPUs
  |  Kernel Offset: disabled
  |  CPU features: 0x10,a0002008
  |  Memory Limit: none</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53158 | soc: qcom: geni-se: fix array underflow in geni_se_clk_tbl_get()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53158</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

soc: qcom: geni-se: fix array underflow in geni_se_clk_tbl_get()

This loop is supposed to break if the frequency returned from
clk_round_rate() is the same as on the previous iteration.  However,
that check doesn't make sense on the first iteration through the loop.
It leads to reading before the start of these-&gt;clk_perf_tbl[] array.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53159 | hwmon: (nct6775-core) Fix overflows seen when writing limit attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53159</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hwmon: (nct6775-core) Fix overflows seen when writing limit attributes

DIV_ROUND_CLOSEST() after kstrtoul() results in an overflow if a large
number such as 18446744073709551615 is provided by the user.
Fix it by reordering clamp_val() and DIV_ROUND_CLOSEST() operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53160 | rcu/kvfree: Fix data-race in __mod_timer / kvfree_call_rcu</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53160</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

rcu/kvfree: Fix data-race in __mod_timer / kvfree_call_rcu

KCSAN reports a data race when access the krcp-&gt;monitor_work.timer.expires
variable in the schedule_delayed_monitor_work() function:


BUG: KCSAN: data-race in __mod_timer / kvfree_call_rcu

read to 0xffff888237d1cce8 of 8 bytes by task 10149 on cpu 1:
 schedule_delayed_monitor_work kernel/rcu/tree.c:3520 [inline]
 kvfree_call_rcu+0x3b8/0x510 kernel/rcu/tree.c:3839
 trie_update_elem+0x47c/0x620 kernel/bpf/lpm_trie.c:441
 bpf_map_update_value+0x324/0x350 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:203
 generic_map_update_batch+0x401/0x520 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:1849
 bpf_map_do_batch+0x28c/0x3f0 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5143
 __sys_bpf+0x2e5/0x7a0
 __do_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5741 [inline]
 __se_sys_bpf kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5739 [inline]
 __x64_sys_bpf+0x43/0x50 kernel/bpf/syscall.c:5739
 x64_sys_call+0x2625/0x2d60 arch/x86/include/generated/asm/syscalls_64.h:322
 do_syscall_x64 arch/x86/entry/common.c:52 [inline]
 do_syscall_64+0xc9/0x1c0 arch/x86/entry/common.c:83
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x77/0x7f

write to 0xffff888237d1cce8 of 8 bytes by task 56 on cpu 0:
 __mod_timer+0x578/0x7f0 kernel/time/timer.c:1173
 add_timer_global+0x51/0x70 kernel/time/timer.c:1330
 __queue_delayed_work+0x127/0x1a0 kernel/workqueue.c:2523
 queue_delayed_work_on+0xdf/0x190 kernel/workqueue.c:2552
 queue_delayed_work include/linux/workqueue.h:677 [inline]
 schedule_delayed_monitor_work kernel/rcu/tree.c:3525 [inline]
 kfree_rcu_monitor+0x5e8/0x660 kernel/rcu/tree.c:3643
 process_one_work kernel/workqueue.c:3229 [inline]
 process_scheduled_works+0x483/0x9a0 kernel/workqueue.c:3310
 worker_thread+0x51d/0x6f0 kernel/workqueue.c:3391
 kthread+0x1d1/0x210 kernel/kthread.c:389
 ret_from_fork+0x4b/0x60 arch/x86/kernel/process.c:147
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30 arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:244

Reported by Kernel Concurrency Sanitizer on:
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 56 Comm: kworker/u8:4 Not tainted 6.12.0-rc2-syzkaller-00050-g5b7c893ed5ed #0
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 09/13/2024
Workqueue: events_unbound kfree_rcu_monitor


kfree_rcu_monitor() rearms the work if a "krcp" has to be still
offloaded and this is done without holding krcp-&gt;lock, whereas
the kvfree_call_rcu() holds it.

Fix it by acquiring the "krcp-&gt;lock" for kfree_rcu_monitor() so
both functions do not race anymore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53161 | EDAC/bluefield: Fix potential integer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53161</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

EDAC/bluefield: Fix potential integer overflow

The 64-bit argument for the "get DIMM info" SMC call consists of mem_ctrl_idx
left-shifted 16 bits and OR-ed with DIMM index.  With mem_ctrl_idx defined as
32-bits wide the left-shift operation truncates the upper 16 bits of
information during the calculation of the SMC argument.

The mem_ctrl_idx stack variable must be defined as 64-bits wide to prevent any
potential integer overflow, i.e. loss of data from upper 16 bits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53162 | crypto: qat/qat_4xxx - fix off by one in uof_get_name()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53162</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: qat/qat_4xxx - fix off by one in uof_get_name()

The fw_objs[] array has "num_objs" elements so the &gt; needs to be &gt;= to
prevent an out of bounds read.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53163 | crypto: qat/qat_420xx - fix off by one in uof_get_name()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53163</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

crypto: qat/qat_420xx - fix off by one in uof_get_name()

This is called from uof_get_name_420xx() where "num_objs" is the
ARRAY_SIZE() of fw_objs[].  The &gt; needs to be &gt;= to prevent an out of
bounds access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10584 | DirectoryPress &amp;lt;= 3.6.16 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10584</link><description>The DirectoryPress – Business Directory And Classified Ad Listing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file. When DirectoryPress Frontend is installed, this can be exploited by unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10856 | Booking Calendar WpDevArt &amp;lt;= 3.2.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10856</link><description>The Booking Calendar WpDevArt plugin is vulnerable to time-based, blind SQL injection via the `id` parameter in the “wpdevart_booking_calendar” shortcode in versions up to, and including, 3.2.19 due to insufficient escaping on the user-supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. The vulnerability requires the “delete_prev_date” theme option being enabled. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access or above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing query that can be used to extract sensitive information such as passwords from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11726 | Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.21 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11726</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar Plugin and Scheduling Plugin – BookingPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'category' parameter of the 'bookingpress_form' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.21 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12268 | Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.9.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12268</link><description>The Responsive Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'responsive-block-editor-addons/portfolio' block in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12031 | Advanced Floating Content &amp;lt;= 3.8.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12031</link><description>The Advanced Floating Content plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'floating_content_duplicate_post' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.8.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12103 | Content No Cache: prevent specific content from being cached &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Unauthenticated Private Content Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12103</link><description>The Content No Cache: prevent specific content from being cached plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.2 via the eos_dyn_get_content action due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12850 | Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 &amp;lt;= 2.32 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12850</link><description>The Database Backup and check Tables Automated With Scheduler 2024 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.32 via the database_backup_ajax_download() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to read the contents of arbitrary files on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12881 | PlugVersions – Easily rollback to previous versions of your plugins &amp;lt;= 0.0.7 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12881</link><description>The PlugVersions – Easily rollback to previous versions of your plugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to a missing capability check on the eos_plugin_reviews_restore_version() function in all versions up to, and including, 0.0.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create arbitrary files leveraging files included locally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53240 | xen/netfront: fix crash when removing device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53240</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xen/netfront: fix crash when removing device

When removing a netfront device directly after a suspend/resume cycle
it might happen that the queues have not been setup again, causing a
crash during the attempt to stop the queues another time.

Fix that by checking the queues are existing before trying to stop
them.

This is XSA-465 / CVE-2024-53240.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53241 | x86/xen: don&amp;#x27;t do PV iret hypercall through hypercall page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53241</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

x86/xen: don't do PV iret hypercall through hypercall page

Instead of jumping to the Xen hypercall page for doing the iret
hypercall, directly code the required sequence in xen-asm.S.

This is done in preparation of no longer using hypercall page at all,
as it has shown to cause problems with speculation mitigations.

This is part of XSA-466 / CVE-2024-53241.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8721 | Tracking Code Manager &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8721</link><description>The Tracking Code Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the tracking code field in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11896 | Text Prompter – Unlimited chatgpt text prompts for openai tasks &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11896</link><description>The Text Prompter – Unlimited chatgpt text prompts for openai tasks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'text_prompter' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 08:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12468 | WP Datepicker &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12468</link><description>The WP Datepicker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wpdp_get_selected_datepicker' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 08:24:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12814 | Loan Comparison &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12814</link><description>The Loan Comparison plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'loancomparison' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 07:09:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12096 | Exhibit to WP Gallery &amp;lt;= 0.0.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12096</link><description>The Exhibit to WP Gallery WordPress plugin through 0.0.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 06:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41882 | Stack based buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41882</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the NVR. An attacker can cause a stack overflow by entering large data into URL parameters, which will result in a system reboot. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41883 | Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41883</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the 

NVR

. An attacker enters a special value for a specific URL parameter, resulting in a NULL pointer reference and a reboot of the NVR. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:42:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41884 | Null Pointer Dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41884</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the NVR. If an attacker does not enter any value for a specific URL parameter, NULL pointer references will occur and the NVR will reboot. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41885 | Hardcoding sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41885</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the NVR. The seed string for the encrypt key was hardcoding. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11885 | NinjaTeam Chat for Telegram &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11885</link><description>The NinjaTeam Chat for Telegram plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'njtele_button shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12034 | Advanced Google reCAPTCHA &amp;lt;= 1.25 - Brute Force Protection IP Unblock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12034</link><description>The Advanced Google reCAPTCHA plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP unblocking in all versions up to, and including, 1.25. This is due to the plugin not utilizing a strong unique key when generating an unblock request. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to unblock their IP after being locked out due to too many bad password attempts</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12100 | Bitcoin Lightning Publisher for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12100</link><description>The Bitcoin Lightning Publisher for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12210 | Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.4.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Logo Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12210</link><description>The Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'wcdn_remove_shoplogo' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to remove the shop's logo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12405 | Export Customers Data &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12405</link><description>The Export Customers Data plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 't' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12594 | ALL In One Custom Login Page &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+)Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12594</link><description>The Custom Login Page Styler – Login Protected Private Site , Change wp-admin login url , WordPress login logo , Temporary admin login access , Rename login , Login customizer, Hide wp-login – Limit Login Attempts – Locked Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'lps_generate_temp_access_url' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to login as other users such as subscribers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12622 | WordPress Simple Shopping Cart &amp;lt;= 5.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12622</link><description>The WordPress Simple Shopping Cart plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_cart_button' and 'wp_cart_display_product' shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 5.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41886 | Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41886</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the NVR. An attacker could inject malformed data into url input parameters to reboot the NVR. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41887 | Arbitrary File Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41887</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the NVR. An attacker can create an NVR log file in a directory one level higher on the system, which can be used to corrupt files in the directory. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 05:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12266 | ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12266</link><description>The ELEX WooCommerce Dynamic Pricing and Discounts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the elex_dp_export_rules() and elex_dp_import_rules() functions in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import and export product rules along with obtaining phpinfo() data</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12507 | Optio Dentistry &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12507</link><description>The Optio Dentistry plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'optio-lightbox' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12518 | shMapper by Teplitsa &amp;lt;= 1.4.18 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12518</link><description>The ShMapper by Teplitsa plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'shmMap' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.18 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12617 | WC Price History for Omnibus &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12617</link><description>The WC Price History for Omnibus plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view and modify history data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12710 | WP-Appbox &amp;lt;= 4.5.3 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12710</link><description>The WP-Appbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12582 | Skupper: skupper-cli: flawed authentication method may lead to arbitrary file read or denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12582</link><description>A flaw was found in the skupper console,  a read-only interface that renders cluster network, traffic details, and metrics for a network application that a user sets up across a hybrid multi-cloud environment. When the default authentication method is used, a random password is generated for the "admin" user and is persisted in either a Kubernetes secret or a podman volume in a plaintext file. This authentication method can be manipulated by an attacker, leading to the reading of any user-readable file in the container filesystem, directly impacting data confidentiality. Additionally, the attacker may induce skupper to read extremely large files into memory, resulting in resource exhaustion and a denial of service attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 03:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47515 | Pagure: generate_archive() follows symbolic links in temporary clones</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47515</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Pagure. Support of symbolic links during repository archiving of repositories allows the disclosure of local files. This flaw allows a malicious user to take advantage of the Pagure instance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 03:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9427 | Koji: escape html tag characters in the query string</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9427</link><description>A vulnerability in Koji was found. An unsanitized input allows for an XSS attack. Javascript code from a malicious link could be reflected in the resulting web page. It is not expected to be able to submit an action or make a change in Koji due to existing XSS protections in the code</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25106 | webuidesigning NebulaX Theme Legacy.php nebula_send_to_hubspot sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25106</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in webuidesigning NebulaX Theme up to 5.0 on WordPress. This issue affects the function nebula_send_to_hubspot of the file libs/Legacy/Legacy.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The patch is named 41230a81db0f671c570c2644bc2f80565ca83c5a. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 23:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53961 | ColdFusion | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) (CWE-22)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53961</link><description>ColdFusion versions 2023.11, 2021.17 and earlier are affected by an Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability that could lead to arbitrary file system read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to access files or directories that are outside of the restricted directory set by the application. This could lead to the disclosure of sensitive information or the manipulation of system data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 20:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56362 | Navidrome Stores JWT Secret in Plaintext in navidrome.db</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56362</link><description>Navidrome is an open source web-based music collection server and streamer. Navidrome stores the JWT secret in plaintext in the navidrome.db database file under the property table. This practice introduces a security risk because anyone with access to the database file can retrieve the secret. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.54.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56363 | APTRS has SSTI vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56363</link><description>APTRS (Automated Penetration Testing Reporting System) is a Python and Django-based automated reporting tool designed for penetration testers and security organizations. In 1.0, there is a vulnerability in the web application's handling of user-supplied input that is incorporated into a Jinja2 template. Specifically, when user input is improperly sanitized or validated, an attacker can inject Jinja2 syntax into the template, causing the server to execute arbitrary code. For example, an attacker might be able to inject expressions like {{ config }}, {{ self.class.mro[1].subclasses() }}, or more dangerous payloads that trigger execution of arbitrary Python code. The vulnerability can be reproduced by submitting crafted input to all the template fields handled by ckeditor, that are passed directly to a Jinja2 template. If the input is rendered without sufficient sanitization, it results in the execution of malicious Jinja2 code on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53275 | GHSL-2024-091: DNS rebinding attack in home-gallery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53275</link><description>Home-Gallery.org is a self-hosted open-source web gallery to browse personal photos and videos. In 1.15.0 and earlier, the default setup of home-gallery is vulnerable to DNS rebinding. Home-gallery is set up without TLS and user authentication by default, leaving it vulnerable to DNS rebinding. In this attack, an attacker will ask a user to visit their website. The attacker website will then change the DNS records of their domain from their IP address to the internal IP address of the home-gallery instance. To tell which IP addresses are valid, we can rebind a subdomain to each IP address we want to check, and see if there is a response. Once potential candidates have been found, the attacker can launch the attack by reading the response of the web server after the IP address has changed. When the attacker domain is fetched, the response will be from the home-gallery instance, not the attacker website, because the IP address has been changed. Due to a lack of authentication, home-gallery photos can then be extracted by the attacker website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53276 | GHSL-2024-092: Open CORS policy in home-gallery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53276</link><description>Home-Gallery.org is a self-hosted open-source web gallery to browse personal photos and videos. In 1.15.0 and earlier, an open CORS policy in app.js may allow an attacker to view the images of home-gallery when it is using the default settings. The following express middleware allows any website to make a cross site request to home-gallery, thus allowing them to read any endpoint on home-gallery. Home-gallery is mostly safe from cross-site requests due to most of its pages requiring JavaScript, and cross-site requests such as fetch() do not render javascript. If an attacker is able to get the path of the preview images which are randomized, an attacker will be able to view such a photo. If any static files or endpoints are introduced in the future that contain sensitive information, they will be accessible to an attacker website.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40896 | In libxml2 2.11 before 2.11.9, 2.12 before 2.12.9, and 2.13 before 2.13.3, the SAX parser can produce events for external entities even if c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40896</link><description>In libxml2 2.11 before 2.11.9, 2.12 before 2.12.9, and 2.13 before 2.13.3, the SAX parser can produce events for external entities even if custom SAX handlers try to override entity content (by setting "checked"). This makes classic XXE attacks possible.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56364 | Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in SimpleXLSXEx::readThemeColors, SimpleXLSXEx::getColorValue and SimpleXLSX::toHTMLEx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56364</link><description>SimpleXLSX is software for parsing and retrieving data from Excel XLSx files. Starting in 1.0.12 and ending in 1.1.13, when calling the extended toHTMLEx method, it is possible to execute arbitrary JavaScript code. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.1.13.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56326 | Jinja has a sandbox breakout through indirect reference to format method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56326</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. Prior to 3.1.5, An oversight in how the Jinja sandboxed environment detects calls to str.format allows an attacker that controls the content of a template to execute arbitrary Python code. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker needs to control the content of a template. Whether that is the case depends on the type of application using Jinja. This vulnerability impacts users of applications which execute untrusted templates. Jinja's sandbox does catch calls to str.format and ensures they don't escape the sandbox. However, it's possible to store a reference to a malicious string's format method, then pass that to a filter that calls it. No such filters are built-in to Jinja, but could be present through custom filters in an application. After the fix, such indirect calls are also handled by the sandbox. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56201 | Jinja has a sandbox breakout through malicious filenames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56201</link><description>Jinja is an extensible templating engine. Prior to 3.1.5, a bug in the Jinja compiler allows an attacker that controls both the content and filename of a template to execute arbitrary Python code, regardless of if Jinja's sandbox is used. To exploit the vulnerability, an attacker needs to control both the filename and the contents of a template. Whether that is the case depends on the type of application using Jinja. This vulnerability impacts users of applications which execute untrusted templates where the template author can also choose the template filename. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45387 | Apache Traffic Control: SQL Injection in Traffic Ops endpoint PUT deliveryservice_request_comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45387</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability in Traffic Ops in Apache Traffic Control &lt;= 8.0.1, &gt;= 8.0.0 allows a privileged user with role "admin", "federation", "operations", "portal", or "steering" to execute arbitrary SQL against the database by sending a specially-crafted PUT request.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version Apache Traffic Control 8.0.2 if you run an affected version of Traffic Ops.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23945 | Apache Hive, Apache Spark, Apache Spark: CookieSigner exposes the correct signature when message verification fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23945</link><description>Signing cookies is an application security feature that adds a digital signature to cookie data to verify its authenticity and integrity. The signature helps prevent malicious actors from modifying the cookie value, which can lead to security vulnerabilities and exploitation. Apache Hive’s service component accidentally exposes the signed cookie to the end user when there is a mismatch in signature between the current and expected cookie. Exposing the correct cookie signature can lead to further exploitation.

The vulnerable CookieSigner logic was introduced in Apache Hive by HIVE-9710 (1.2.0) and in Apache Spark by SPARK-14987 (2.0.0). The affected components are the following:
* org.apache.hive:hive-service
* org.apache.spark:spark-hive-thriftserver_2.11
* org.apache.spark:spark-hive-thriftserver_2.12</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54148 | Gogs has a Path Traversal in file editing UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54148</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. A malicious user is able to commit and edit a crafted symlink file to a repository to gain SSH access to the server. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55947 | Gogs has a Path Traversal in file update API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55947</link><description>Gogs is an open source self-hosted Git service. A malicious user is able to write a file to an arbitrary path on the server to gain SSH access to the server. The vulnerability is fixed in 0.13.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53256 | Rizin has a command injection via RzBinInfo bclass due legacy code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53256</link><description>Rizin is a UNIX-like reverse engineering framework and command-line toolset. `rizin.c` still had an old snippet of code which suffered a command injection due the usage of `rz_core_cmdf` to invoke the command `m` which was removed in v0.1.x. A malicious binary defining `bclass` (part of RzBinInfo) is executed if `rclass` (part of RzBinInfo) is set to `fs`; the vulnerability can be exploited by any bin format where `bclass` and `rclass` are user defined. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55539 | Weak algorithm used to sign RPM package. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux) before build 39185.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55539</link><description>Weak algorithm used to sign RPM package. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux) before build 39185.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12903 | Incorrect default permissions in Biamp Evoko Home</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12903</link><description>Incorrect default permissions vulnerability in Evoko Home, affecting version 2.4.2 to 2.7.4. A non-admin user could exploit weak file and folder permissions to escalate privileges, execute arbitrary code and maintain persistence on the compromised machine. It has been identified that full control permissions exist on the ‘Everyone’ group (i.e. any user who has local access to the operating system regardless of their privileges).</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 13:02:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12902 | Global Wisdom Software ANCHOR - Undocumented Privileged Account</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12902</link><description>ANCHOR from Global Wisdom Software is an integrated product running on a Windows virtual machine. The underlying Windows OS of the product contains high-privilege service accounts. If these accounts use default passwords, attackers could remotely log in to the virtual machine using the default credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 10:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11230 | Elementor Header &amp;amp; Footer Builder &amp;lt;= 1.6.46 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Page Title Widget</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11230</link><description>The Elementor Header &amp; Footer Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘size’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.46 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 04:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12901 | FoxCMS API Endpoint Site.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12901</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in FoxCMS up to 1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /app/api/controller/Site.php of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument password leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 02:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12900 | FoxCMS Configuration File installdb.php code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12900</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FoxCMS up to 1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /install/installdb.php of the component Configuration File Handler. The manipulation of the argument database password leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 02:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12899 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System course_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12899</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/course_action.php. The manipulation of the argument course_code leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45721 | home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the HOST name configuration sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45721</link><description>home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the HOST name configuration screen. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46873 | Multiple SHARP routers leave the hidden debug function enabled. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by a remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46873</link><description>Multiple SHARP routers leave the hidden debug function enabled. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47864 | home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the hidden debug function. A remote ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47864</link><description>home 5G HR02, Wi-Fi STATION SH-52B, and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the hidden debug function. A remote unauthenticated attacker may get the web console of the product down.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52321 | Multiple SHARP routers contain an improper authentication vulnerability in the configuration backup function. The product's backup files con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52321</link><description>Multiple SHARP routers contain an improper authentication vulnerability in the configuration backup function. The product's backup files containing sensitive information may be retrieved by a remote unauthenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54082 | home 5G HR02 and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the configuration restore function. An arbitrary OS c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54082</link><description>home 5G HR02 and Wi-Fi STATION SH-54C contain an OS command injection vulnerability in the configuration restore function. An arbitrary OS command may be executed with the root privilege by an administrative user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12898 | 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System faculty_action.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12898</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects Attendance Tracking Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/faculty_action.php. The manipulation of the argument faculty_course_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>