<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-2320 | 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt User submit improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2320</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 274056675 springboot-openai-chatgpt e84f6f5 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function submit of the file /api/blade-user/submit of the component User Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:15:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2295 | Potential iSCSI R2T PDU Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2295</link><description>EDK2 contains a vulnerability in BIOS where a user may cause an Integer Overflow or Wraparound by network means. A successful exploitation of this vulnerability may lead to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2309 | HDF5 Type Conversion Logic H5T__bit_copy heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2309</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in HDF5 1.14.6 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function H5T__bit_copy of the component Type Conversion Logic. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2310 | HDF5 Metadata Attribute Decoder H5MM_strndup heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2310</link><description>A vulnerability was found in HDF5 1.14.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function H5MM_strndup of the component Metadata Attribute Decoder. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2308 | HDF5 Scale-Offset Filter H5Z__scaleoffset_decompress_one_byte heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2308</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in HDF5 1.14.6. This affects the function H5Z__scaleoffset_decompress_one_byte of the component Scale-Offset Filter. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor was contacted early about a batch of vulnerabilities. His response was "reject" without further explanation. We have not received an elaboration even after asking politely for further details. Currently we assume that the vendor wants to "dispute" the entries which is why they are flagged as such until further details become available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 20:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29782 | WeGIA Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Stored in endpoint `adicionar_tipo_docs_atendido.php` parameter `tipo`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29782</link><description>WeGIA is Web manager for charitable institutions A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability was identified in the `adicionar_tipo_docs_atendido.php` endpoint in versions of the WeGIA application prior to 3.2.17. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into the `tipo` parameter. The injected scripts are stored on the server and executed automatically whenever the affected page is accessed by users, posing a significant security risk. Version 3.2.17 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:23:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29771 | HtmlSanitizer vulnerable to XSS when used with contentEditable</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29771</link><description>HtmlSanitizer is a client-side HTML Sanitizer. Versions prior to 2.0.3 have a cross-site scripting vulnerability when the sanitizer is used with a `contentEditable` element to set the elements `innerHTML` to a sanitized string produced by the package. If the code is particularly crafted to abuse the code beautifier, that runs AFTER sanitation. The issue is patched in version 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 19:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12019 | Arbitrary File Read via Document API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12019</link><description>The API used to interact with documents in the application contains a flaw that allows an authenticated attacker to read the contents of files on the underlying operating system. An account with ‘read’ and ‘download’ privileges on at least one existing document in the application is required to exploit the vulnerability. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to read the contents of any file available within the privileges of the system user running the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12020 | Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12020</link><description>There is a reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) within JSP files used to control application appearance. An unauthenticated attacker could deceive a user into clicking a crafted link to trigger the vulnerability. Stealing the session cookie is not possible due to cookie security flags, however the XSS may be used to induce a victim to perform on-site requests without their knowledge.

This vulnerability only affects LogicalDOC Enterprise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12245 | Blind SQL Injection in Logout</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12245</link><description>Logout functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54449 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Arbitrary File Write In Document API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54449</link><description>The API used to interact with documents in the application contains two endpoints with a flaw that allows an authenticated attacker to write a file with controlled contents to an arbitrary location on the underlying file system. This can be used to facilitate RCE. An account with ‘read’ and ‘write’ privileges on at least one existing document in the application is required to exploit the vulnerability. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to run commands of their choosing on the underlying operating system of the web server running LogicalDOC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54447 | Blind SQLi in Saved Search</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54447</link><description>Saved search functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by authenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54448 | Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Automation Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54448</link><description>The Automation Scripting functionality can be exploited by attackers to run arbitrary system commands on the underlying operating system. An account with administrator privileges or that has been explicitly granted access to use Automation Scripting is needed to carry out the attack. Exploitation of this vulnerability would allow an attacker to run commands of their choosing on the underlying operating system of the web server running LogicalDOC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54446 | Blind SQLi in Document History</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54446</link><description>Document history functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by authenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54445 | Blind SQLi in Login</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54445</link><description>Login functionality contains a blind SQL injection that can be exploited by unauthenticated attackers. Using a time-based blind SQLi technique the attacker can disclose all database contents. Account takeover is a potential outcome depending on the presence or lack thereof entries in certain database tables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29409 | File Upload vulnerability in nestjs nest v.10.3.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content-Type header.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29409</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in nestjs nest v.10.3.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content-Type header.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:48:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29780 | Post-Quantum Secure Feldman&amp;#x27;s Verifiable Secret Sharing has Timing Side-Channels in Matrix Operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29780</link><description>Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing provides a Python implementation of Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. In versions 0.7.6b0 and prior, the `feldman_vss` library contains timing side-channel vulnerabilities in its matrix operations, specifically within the `_find_secure_pivot` function and potentially other parts of `_secure_matrix_solve`. These vulnerabilities are due to Python's execution model, which does not guarantee constant-time execution. An attacker with the ability to measure the execution time of these functions (e.g., through repeated calls with carefully crafted inputs) could potentially recover secret information used in the Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. The `_find_secure_pivot` function, used during Gaussian elimination in `_secure_matrix_solve`, attempts to find a non-zero pivot element. However, the conditional statement `if matrix[row][col] != 0 and row_random &lt; min_value:` has execution time that depends on the value of `matrix[row][col]`. This timing difference can be exploited by an attacker. The `constant_time_compare` function in this file also does not provide a constant-time guarantee. The Python implementation of matrix operations in the _find_secure_pivot and _secure_matrix_solve functions cannot guarantee constant-time execution, potentially leaking information about secret polynomial coefficients. An attacker with the ability to make precise timing measurements of these operations could potentially extract secret information through statistical analysis of execution times, though practical exploitation would require significant expertise and controlled execution environments. Successful exploitation of these timing side-channels could allow an attacker to recover secret keys or other sensitive information protected by the VSS scheme. This could lead to a complete compromise of the shared secret. As of time of publication, no patched versions of Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing exist, but other mitigations are available. As acknowledged in the library's documentation, these vulnerabilities cannot be adequately addressed in pure Python. In the short term, consider using this library only in environments where timing measurements by attackers are infeasible. In the medium term, implement your own wrappers around critical operations using constant-time libraries in languages like Rust, Go, or C. In the long term, wait for the planned Rust implementation mentioned in the library documentation that will properly address these issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26312 | SendQuick Entera devices before 11HF5 are vulnerable to CAPTCHA bypass via the captcha parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26312</link><description>SendQuick Entera devices before 11HF5 are vulnerable to CAPTCHA bypass via the captcha parameter</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29779 | Post-Quantum Secure Feldman&amp;#x27;s Verifiable Secret Sharing has Inadequate Fault Injection Countermeasures in `secure_redundant_execution`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29779</link><description>Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing provides a Python implementation of Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing (VSS) scheme. In versions 0.7.6b0 and prior, the `secure_redundant_execution` function in feldman_vss.py attempts to mitigate fault injection attacks by executing a function multiple times and comparing results. However, several critical weaknesses exist. Python's execution environment cannot guarantee true isolation between redundant executions, the constant-time comparison implementation in Python is subject to timing variations, the randomized execution order and timing provide insufficient protection against sophisticated fault attacks, and the error handling may leak timing information about partial execution results. These limitations make the protection ineffective against targeted fault injection attacks, especially from attackers with physical access to the hardware. A successful fault injection attack could allow an attacker to bypass the redundancy check mechanisms, extract secret polynomial coefficients during share generation or verification, force the acceptance of invalid shares during verification, and/or manipulate the commitment verification process to accept fraudulent commitments. This undermines the core security guarantees of the Verifiable Secret Sharing scheme. As of time of publication, no patched versions of Post-Quantum Secure Feldman's Verifiable Secret Sharing exist, but other mitigations are available. Long-term remediation requires reimplementing the security-critical functions in a lower-level language like Rust. Short-term mitigations include deploying the software in environments with physical security controls, increasing the redundancy count (from 5 to a higher number) by modifying the source code, adding external verification of cryptographic operations when possible, considering using hardware security modules (HSMs) for key operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29775 | xml-crypto Vulnerable to XML Signature Verification Bypass via DigestValue Comment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29775</link><description>xml-crypto is an XML digital signature and encryption library for Node.js. An attacker may be able to exploit a vulnerability in versions prior to 6.0.1, 3.2.1, and 2.1.6 to bypass authentication or authorization mechanisms in systems that rely on xml-crypto for verifying signed XML documents. The vulnerability allows an attacker to modify a valid signed XML message in a way that still passes signature verification checks. For example, it could be used to alter critical identity or access control attributes, enabling an attacker to escalate privileges or impersonate another user. Users of versions 6.0.0 and prior should upgrade to version 6.0.1 to receive a fix. Those who are still using v2.x or v3.x should upgrade to patched versions 2.1.6 or 3.2.1, respectively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29384 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanMTU parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29384</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanMTU parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29385 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the cloneType parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29385</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the cloneType parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29386 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the mac parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to rem...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29386</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the mac parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29387 | In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanSpeed parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29387</link><description>In Tenda AC9 v1.0 V15.03.05.14_multi, the wanSpeed parameter of /goform/AdvSetMacMtuWan has a stack overflow vulnerability, which can lead to remote arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29774 | xml-crypto Vulnerable to XML Signature Verification Bypass via Multiple SignedInfo References</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29774</link><description>xml-crypto is an XML digital signature and encryption library for Node.js. An attacker may be able to exploit a vulnerability in versions prior to 6.0.1, 3.2.1, and 2.1.6 to bypass authentication or authorization mechanisms in systems that rely on xml-crypto for verifying signed XML documents. The vulnerability allows an attacker to modify a valid signed XML message in a way that still passes signature verification checks. For example, it could be used to alter critical identity or access control attributes, enabling an attacker with a valid account to escalate privileges or impersonate another user. Users of versions 6.0.0 and prior should upgrade to version 6.0.1 to receive a fix. Those who are still using v2.x or v3.x should upgrade to patched versions 2.1.6 or 3.2.1, respectively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27606 | Element Android PIN autologout bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27606</link><description>Element Android is an Android Matrix Client provided by Element. Element Android up to version 1.6.32 can, under certain circumstances, fail to logout the user if they input the wrong PIN more than the configured amount of times. An attacker with physical access to a device can exploit this to guess the PIN. Version 1.6.34 solves the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55594 | An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least vesrions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55594</link><description>An improper handling of syntactically invalid structure in Fortinet FortiWeb at least vesrions 7.4.0 through 7.4.6 and 7.2.0 through 7.2.10 and 7.0.0 through 7.0.10 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via HTTP/S crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1888 | Reflected Cross Site Scripting in Aperio Eslide Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1888</link><description>The Leica Web Viewer within the Aperio Eslide Manager Application is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting (XSS). An authenticated user can access the slides within a project and injecting malicious JavaScript into the "memo" field. The memo field has a hover over action that will display a Microsoft Tool Tip which a user can use to quickly view the memo associated with the slide and execute the JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-29059 | An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiWeb version 7.0.1 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-29059</link><description>An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiWeb version 7.0.1 and below, 6.4.2 and below, 6.3.20 and below, 6.2.7 and below may allow a privileged attacker to execute SQL commands over the log database via specifically crafted strings parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33300 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiNAC 7.2.1 and earlier, 9.4.3 and earl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33300</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiNAC 7.2.1 and earlier, 9.4.3 and earlier allows attacker a limited, unauthorized file access via specifically crafted request in inter-server  communication port.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45588 | An external control of file name or path vulnerability [CWE-73] in  FortiClientMac version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.10 and below install...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45588</link><description>An external control of file name or path vulnerability [CWE-73] in  FortiClientMac version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.10 and below installer may allow a local attacker to execute arbitrary code or commands via writing a malicious configuration file in /tmp before starting the installation process.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48785 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiNAC-F version 7.2.4 and below may allow a remote and unauthenticated atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48785</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiNAC-F version 7.2.4 and below may allow a remote and unauthenticated attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack on the HTTPS communication channel between the FortiOS device, an inventory, and FortiNAC-F.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40585 | An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerabilities [CWE-532] in FortiManager version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40585</link><description>An insertion of sensitive information into log file vulnerabilities [CWE-532] in FortiManager version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.4.12 and below, version 6.2.11 and below and FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.0, version 7.2.3 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.4.12 and below, version 6.2.11 and below eventlog may allow any low privileged user with access to event log section to retrieve certificate private key and encrypted password logged as system log.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25871 | An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25871</link><description>An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:55:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25873 | Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Open Panel OpenAdmin v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Change Root...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25873</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery vulnerability in Open Panel OpenAdmin v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Change Root Password function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25872 | An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25872</link><description>An issue in Open Panel v.0.3.4 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the Fix Permissions function</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40590 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiPortal version 7.4.0, version 7.2.4 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40590</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability [CWE-295] in FortiPortal version 7.4.0, version 7.2.4 and below, version 7.0.8 and below, version 6.0.15 and below when connecting to a FortiManager device, a FortiAnalyzer device, or an SMTP server may allow an unauthenticated attacker in a Man-in-the-Middle position to intercept on and tamper with the encrypted communication channel established between the FortiPortal and those endpoints.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46662 | A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46662</link><description>A improper neutralization of special elements used in a command ('command injection') in Fortinet FortiManager versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3, FortiManager Cloud versions 7.4.1 through 7.4.3 allows attacker to escalation of privilege via specifically crafted packets</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47573 | An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiNDR version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.1 and below, versio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47573</link><description>An improper validation of integrity check value vulnerability [CWE-354] in FortiNDR version 7.4.2 and below, version 7.2.1 and below, version 7.1.1 and below, version 7.0.6 and below may allow an authenticated attacker with at least Read/Write permission on system maintenance to install a corrupted firmware image.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45638 | IBM QRadar EDR information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45638</link><description>IBM Security QRadar 3.12 EDR stores user credentials in plain text which can be read by a local privileged user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:56:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45643 | IBM QRadar EDR information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45643</link><description>IBM Security QRadar 3.12 EDR uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt sensitive credential information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:49:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52927 | netfilter: allow exp not to be removed in nf_ct_find_expectation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52927</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: allow exp not to be removed in nf_ct_find_expectation

Currently nf_conntrack_in() calling nf_ct_find_expectation() will
remove the exp from the hash table. However, in some scenario, we
expect the exp not to be removed when the created ct will not be
confirmed, like in OVS and TC conntrack in the following patches.

This patch allows exp not to be removed by setting IPS_CONFIRMED
in the status of the tmpl.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29029 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formSetSpeedWan function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29029</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formSetSpeedWan function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29030 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29030</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29031 | Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the fromAddressNat function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29031</link><description>Tenda AC6 v15.03.05.16 was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the fromAddressNat function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29032 | Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.19(6318) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29032</link><description>Tenda AC9 v15.03.05.19(6318) was discovered to contain a buffer overflow via the formWifiWpsOOB function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:49:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2268 | HP LaserJet MFP M232-M237 Printer Series - Potential Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2268</link><description>The HP LaserJet MFP M232-M237 Printer Series may be vulnerable to a denial of service attack when a specially crafted request message is sent via Internet Printing Protocol (IPP).</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:43:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29776 | Azle calling `setTimer` causes infinite loop of timers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29776</link><description>Azle is a WebAssembly runtime for TypeScript and JavaScript on ICP. Calling `setTimer` in Azle versions `0.27.0`, `0.28.0`, and `0.29.0` causes an immediate infinite loop of timers to be executed on the canister, each timer attempting to clean up the global state of the previous timer. The infinite loop will occur with any valid invocation of `setTimer`. The problem has been fixed as of Azle version `0.30.0`. As a workaround, if a canister is caught in this infinite loop after calling `setTimer`, the canister can be upgraded and the timers will all be cleared, thus ending the loop.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2000 | Qiskit SDK code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2000</link><description>A maliciously crafted QPY file can potential execute arbitrary-code embedded in the payload without privilege escalation when deserialising QPY formats &lt; 13. A python process calling Qiskit 0.18.0 through 1.4.1's `qiskit.qpy.load()` function could potentially execute any arbitrary Python code embedded in the correct place in the binary file as part of specially constructed payload.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26626 | GLPI Inventory Plugin vulnerable to reflective Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26626</link><description>The GLPI Inventory Plugin handles various types of tasks for GLPI agents for the GLPI asset and IT management software package. Versions prior to 1.5.0 are vulnerable to reflective cross-site scripting, which may lead to executing javascript code. Version 1.5.0 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27593 | RCE due to Device Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27593</link><description>The product can be used to distribute malicious code using SDD Device Drivers due to missing download verification checks, leading to code execution on target systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27594 | Unencrypted transmission of password hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27594</link><description>The device uses an unencrypted, proprietary protocol for communication. Through this protocol, configuration data is transmitted and device authentication is performed. An attacker can thereby intercept the authentication hash and use it to log into the device using a pass-the-hash attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27595 | Weak hashing alghrythm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27595</link><description>The device uses a weak hashing alghorithm to create the password hash. Hence, a matching password can be easily calculated by an attacker. This impacts the security and the integrity of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2304 | Camaleon CMS Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2304</link><description>A Privilege Escalation through a Mass Assignment exists in Camaleon CMS

When a user wishes to change his password, the 'updated_ajax' method of the UsersController is called. The vulnerability stems from the use of the dangerous permit! method, which allows all parameters to pass through without any filtering.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 12:54:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12810 | JobCareer | Job Board Responsive WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12810</link><description>The JobCareer | Job Board Responsive WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access, modification, and loss of data due to a missing capability checks on multiple functions in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files, generate backups, restore backups, update theme options, and reset theme options to default settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13771 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authentication Bypass via Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13771</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to a lack of user validation before changing a password. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the password of arbitrary users, including administrators, if the attacker knows the username of the victim.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13772 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authentication Bypass via Non-Randomized Password for SSO Accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13772</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to a lack of randomization of a password created during Single Sign-On via Google or Facebook. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change the password of arbitrary Candidate-level users if the attacker knows the username assigned to the victim during account creation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13773 | Civi - Job Board &amp;amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13773</link><description>The Civi - Job Board &amp; Freelance Marketplace WordPress Theme plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4 via hard-coded credentials. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including LinkedIn client and secret keys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2232 | Realteo - Real Estate Plugin by Purethemes &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authentication Bypass via &amp;#x27;do_register_user&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2232</link><description>The Realteo - Real Estate Plugin by Purethemes plugin for WordPress, used by the Findeo Theme, is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8. This is due to insufficient role restrictions in the 'do_register_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register an account with the Administrator role.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26006 | An improper neutralization of input during web page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.7 and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26006</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page Generation vulnerability [CWE-79] in FortiOS version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.7 and below, version 7.0.13 and below and FortiProxy version 7.4.3 and below, version 7.2.9 and below, version 7.0.16 and below web SSL VPN UI may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to perform a Cross-Site Scripting attack via a malicious samba server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 09:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8176 | Libexpat: expat: improper restriction of xml entity expansion depth in libexpat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8176</link><description>A stack overflow vulnerability exists in the libexpat library due to the way it handles recursive entity expansion in XML documents. When parsing an XML document with deeply nested entity references, libexpat can be forced to recurse indefinitely, exhausting the stack space and causing a crash. This issue could lead to denial of service (DoS) or, in some cases, exploitable memory corruption, depending on the environment and library usage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1507 | ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics &amp;lt;= 3.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Feature Deactivation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1507</link><description>The ShareThis Dashboard for Google Analytics plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the handle_actions() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disable all features.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 08:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13321 | AnalyticsWP &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13321</link><description>The AnalyticsWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'custom_sql' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient authorization checks on the handle_get_stats() function.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13407 | Omnipress &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13407</link><description>The Omnipress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4 via the megamenu block due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1526 | DethemeKit for Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1526</link><description>The DethemeKit for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the De Product Display Widget (countdown feature) in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 07:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13824 | CiyaShop - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 4.19.0 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13824</link><description>The CiyaShop - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 4.19.0 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'add_ciyashop_wishlist' and 'ciyashop_get_compare' functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2221 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Unauthenticated Time-Based SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2221</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘user_phone’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13376 | Industrial &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13376</link><description>The Industrial theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the _ajax_get_total_content_import_items() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13913 | InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp;amp; Migration &amp;lt;= 0.1.0.83 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13913</link><description>The InstaWP Connect – 1-click WP Staging &amp; Migration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.0.83. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the '/migrate/templates/main.php' file. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0952 | Eco Nature - Environment &amp;amp; Ecology WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0952</link><description>The Eco Nature - Environment &amp; Ecology WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'cmsmasters_hide_admin_notice' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'hide' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1764 | LoginPress &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1764</link><description>The LoginPress | wp-login Custom Login Page Customizer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.1. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'custom_plugin_set_option' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site. The 'WPBRIGADE_SDK__DEV_MODE' constant must be set to 'true' to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2103 | SoundRise Music &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2103</link><description>The SoundRise Music plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on theironMusic_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.11. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2289 | Zegen - Church WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Options Updates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2289</link><description>The Zegen - Church WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on several AJAX endpoints in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to import, export, and update theme options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 05:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11283 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Authentication Bypass to Candidate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11283</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to wp_ajax_google_api_login_callback function not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access arbitrary candidate accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11284 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11284</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 6.9. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their password through the account_settings_save_callback() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's passwords, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11285 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Email Update/Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11285</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email via the account_settings_callback() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11286 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11286</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 7.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to authenticating them through the cs_parse_request() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to to log in to any user's account, including administrators.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0955 | VidoRev Extensions &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.9.9.9.5 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Youtube Video Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0955</link><description>The VidoRev Extensions plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'vidorev_import_single_video' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.9.9.9.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to import arbitrary youtube videos.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1285 | Resido - Real Estate WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.6 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery and API Key Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1285</link><description>The Resido - Real Estate WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the delete_api_key and save_api_key AJAX actions in all versions up to, and including, 3.6. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to issue requests to internal services and update API key details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1528 | Search and filter pro &amp;lt;= 2.5.19 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Meta Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1528</link><description>The Search &amp; Filter Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'get_meta_values' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.19. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read the values of arbitrary post meta.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2056 | WP Ghost &amp;lt;= 5.4.01 - Unauthenticated Limited File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2056</link><description>The WP Ghost (Hide My WP Ghost) – Security &amp; Firewall plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.01 via the showFile function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read the contents of specific file types on the server, which can contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2166 | CM FAQ  – Simplify support with an intuitive FAQ management tool &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2166</link><description>The CM FAQ  – Simplify support with an intuitive FAQ management tool plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of remove_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 04:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26163 | CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the CPF parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26163</link><description>CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the CPF parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30022 | CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the DATANASC parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30022</link><description>CM Soluces Informatica Ltda Auto Atendimento 1.x.x was discovered to contain a SQL injection via the DATANASC parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 03:05:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55549 | xsltGetInheritedNsList in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free issue related to exclusion of result prefixes.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55549</link><description>xsltGetInheritedNsList in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free issue related to exclusion of result prefixes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24855 | numbers.c in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free because, in nested XPath evaluations, an XPath context node can be modified but neve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24855</link><description>numbers.c in libxslt before 1.1.43 has a use-after-free because, in nested XPath evaluations, an XPath context node can be modified but never restored. This is related to xsltNumberFormatGetValue, xsltEvalXPathPredicate, xsltEvalXPathStringNs, and xsltComputeSortResultInternal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55060 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component index.php of Rafed CMS Website v1.44 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55060</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component index.php of Rafed CMS Website v1.44 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27496 | Snowflake JDBC Driver client-side encryption key in DEBUG logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27496</link><description>Snowflake, a platform for using artificial intelligence in the context of cloud computing, has a vulnerability in the Snowflake JDBC driver ("Driver") in versions 3.0.13 through 3.23.0 of the driver. When the logging level was set to DEBUG, the Driver would log locally the client-side encryption master key of the target stage during the execution of GET/PUT commands. This key by itself does not grant access to any sensitive data without additional access authorizations,  and is not logged server-side by Snowflake. Snowflake fixed the issue in version 3.23.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2229 | Philips Intellispace Cardiovascular (ISCV) Use of Weak Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2229</link><description>A token is created using the username, current date/time, and a fixed 
AES-128 encryption key, which is the same across all installations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2230 | Philips Intellispace Cardiovascular (ISCV) Improper Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2230</link><description>A flaw exists in the Windows login flow where an AuthContext token can 
be exploited for replay attacks and authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25363 | An authenticated stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Plugin People Enterprise Mail Handler for Jira Data Center (JEMH) be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25363</link><description>An authenticated stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in The Plugin People Enterprise Mail Handler for Jira Data Center (JEMH) before v4.1.69-dc allows attackers with Administrator privileges to execute arbitrary Javascript in context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the HTML field of a template.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25598 | Incorrect access control in the scheduled tasks console of Inova Logic CUSTOMER MONITOR (CM) v3.1.757.1 allows attackers to escalate privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25598</link><description>Incorrect access control in the scheduled tasks console of Inova Logic CUSTOMER MONITOR (CM) v3.1.757.1 allows attackers to escalate privileges via placing a crafted executable into a scheduled task.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:59:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30143 | A path traversal vulnerability in HCL AppScan Traffic Recorder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30143</link><description>HCL AppScan Traffic Recorder fails to adequately neutralize special characters within the filename, potentially allowing it to resolve to a location beyond the restricted directory. Potential exploits can completely disrupt or takeover the application or the computer where the application is running.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24053 | Microsoft Dataverse Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24053</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:27:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53406 | Espressif Esp idf v5.3.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions resulting in Authentication bypass. In the reconnection phase, the device reu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53406</link><description>Espressif Esp idf v5.3.0 is vulnerable to Insecure Permissions resulting in Authentication bypass. In the reconnection phase, the device reuses the session key from a previous connection session, creating an opportunity for attackers to execute security bypass attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29768 | Vim vulnerable to potential data loss with zip.vim and special crafted zip files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29768</link><description>Vim, a text editor, is vulnerable to potential data loss with zip.vim and special crafted zip files in versions prior to 9.1.1198. The impact is medium because a user must be made to view such an archive with Vim and then press 'x' on such a strange filename. The issue has been fixed as of Vim patch v9.1.1198.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29773 | Froxlor allows Multiple Accounts to Share the Same Email Address Leading to Potential Privilege Escalation or Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29773</link><description>Froxlor is open-source server administration software. A vulnerability in versions prior to 2.2.6 allows users (such as resellers or customers) to create accounts with the same email address as an existing account. This creates potential issues with account identification and security. This vulnerability can be exploited by authenticated users (e.g., reseller, customer) who can create accounts with the same email address that has already been used by another account, such as the admin. The attack vector is email-based, as the system does not prevent multiple accounts from registering the same email address, leading to possible conflicts and security issues. Version 2.2.6 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2081 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 are vulnerable to an attacker impersona...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2081</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 are vulnerable to an attacker impersonating the web application service and mislead victim clients.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27107 | Integrated Scripting vulnerable to arbitrary code execution via Java reflection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27107</link><description>Integrated Scripting is a tool for creating scripts for handling complex operations in Integrated Dynamics. Minecraft users who use Integrated Scripting prior to versions 1.21.1-1.0.17, 1.21.4-1.0.9-254, 1.20.1-1.0.13, and 1.19.2-1.0.10 may be vulnerable to arbitrary code execution. By using Java reflection on a thrown exception object it's possible to escape the JavaScript sandbox for IntegratedScripting's Variable Cards, and leverage that to construct arbitrary Java classes and invoke arbitrary Java methods.
This vulnerability allows for execution of arbitrary Java methods, and by extension arbitrary native code e.g. from `java.lang.Runtime.exec`, on the Minecraft server by any player with the ability to create and use an IntegratedScripting Variable Card. Versions 1.21.1-1.0.17, 1.21.4-1.0.9-254, 1.20.1-1.0.13, and 1.19.2-1.0.10 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2079 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain a hard coded secret key. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2079</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain a hard coded secret key. This could allow an attacker to generate valid JWT (JSON Web Token) sessions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2080 | Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain an exposed web management servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2080</link><description>Optigo Networks Visual BACnet Capture Tool and Optigo Visual Networks Capture Tool version 3.1.2rc11 contain an exposed web management service that could allow an attacker to bypass authentication measures and gain controls over utilities within the products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12858 | Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 Heap-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12858</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 Version 2.1.0.16 and prior lacks proper 
validation of the length of user-supplied data prior to copying it to a 
fixed-length heap-based buffer. If a target visits a malicious page or 
opens a malicious file an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to 
execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1427 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1427</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1428 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1428</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPART file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1429 | MODEL File Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1429</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1430 | SLDPRT File Parsing Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1430</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Memory Corruption vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1431 | SLDPRT File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1431</link><description>A maliciously crafted SLDPRT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability.  A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1432 | 3DM File Parsing Use-After-Free Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1432</link><description>A maliciously crafted 3DM file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Use-After-Free vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1433 | MODEL File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1433</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1649 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1649</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1650 | CATPRODUCT File Parsing Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1650</link><description>A maliciously crafted CATPRODUCT file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Uninitialized Variable vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1651 | MODEL File Parsing Heap-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1651</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force a Heap-Based Overflow vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1652 | MODEL File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1652</link><description>A maliciously crafted MODEL file, when parsed through Autodesk AutoCAD, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27138 | DataEase has an improper authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27138</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, there is a flaw in the authentication in the io.dataease.auth.filter.TokenFilter class, which may cause the risk of unauthorized access. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9042 | This CVE affects only Windows worker nodes. Your worker node is vulnerable to this issue if it is running one of the affected versions liste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9042</link><description>This CVE affects only Windows worker nodes. Your worker node is vulnerable to this issue if it is running one of the affected versions listed below.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1767 | This CVE only affects Kubernetes clusters that utilize the in-tree gitRepo volume to clone git repositories from other pods within the same ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1767</link><description>This CVE only affects Kubernetes clusters that utilize the in-tree gitRepo volume to clone git repositories from other pods within the same node. Since the in-tree gitRepo volume feature has been deprecated and will not receive security updates upstream, any cluster still using this feature remains vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24974 | DataEase Mysql JDBC Connection Parameters Not Being Verified Leads to Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24974</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, authenticated users can read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27103 | Dataease Mysql JDBC Connection Parameters Not Being Verified Leads to Arbitrary File Read Vulnerability​</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27103</link><description>DataEase is an open source business intelligence and data visualization tool. Prior to version 2.10.6, a bypass for the patch for CVE-2024-55953 allows authenticated users to read and deserialize arbitrary files through the background JDBC connection. The vulnerability has been fixed in v2.10.6. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2284 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Access of Uninitialized Pointer DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2284</link><description>A denial-of-service vulnerability exists in the "GetWebLoginCredentials" function in "Sante PACS Server.exe".</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2263 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Stack-based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2263</link><description>During login to the web server in "Sante PACS Server.exe", OpenSSL function EVP_DecryptUpdate is called to decrypt the username and password. A fixed 0x80-byte stack-based buffer is passed to the function as the output buffer. A stack-based buffer overflow exists if a long encrypted username or password is supplied by an unauthenticated remote attacker.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2264 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server Path Traversal Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2264</link><description>A Path Traversal Information Disclosure vulnerability exists in "Sante PACS Server.exe". An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit it to download arbitrary files on the disk drive where the application is installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2265 | Santesoft Sante PACS Server HTTP.db SHA1 Hash Truncation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2265</link><description>The password of a web user in "Sante PACS Server.exe" is zero-padded to 0x2000 bytes, SHA1-hashed, base64-encoded, and stored in the USER table in the SQLite database HTTP.db. However, the number of hash bytes encoded and stored is truncated if the hash contains a zero byte</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28011 | A SQL Injection was found in loginsystem/change-password.php in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System v3.3 allows ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28011</link><description>A SQL Injection was found in loginsystem/change-password.php in PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System v3.3 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via the currentpassword POST request parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28010 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in MODX prior to 3.1.0. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to uploa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28010</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in MODX prior to 3.1.0. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to upload SVG files containing malicious JavaScript code as profile images, which gets executed in victims' browsers when viewing the profile image.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28015 | A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28015</link><description>A HTML Injection vulnerability was found in loginsystem/edit-profile.php of the PHPGurukul User Registration &amp; Login and User Management System V3.3. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary HTML code via the fname, lname, and contact parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:25:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57062 | An issue in SoundCloud IOS application v.7.65.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the sess...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57062</link><description>An issue in SoundCloud IOS application v.7.65.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges and obtain sensitive information via the session handling component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25625 | FS Inc S3150 8T2F Switch s3150-8t2f-switch-fsos-220d_118101 has a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the web management inte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25625</link><description>FS Inc S3150 8T2F Switch s3150-8t2f-switch-fsos-220d_118101 has a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the web management interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 15:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55198 | User Enumeration via Discrepancies in Error Messages in the Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 password recovery functionality which allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55198</link><description>User Enumeration via Discrepancies in Error Messages in the Celk Sistemas Celk Saude v.3.1.252.1 password recovery functionality which allows a remote attacker to enumerate users through discrepancies in the responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22880 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zadarma Zadarma extension v.1.0.11 allows a remote attacker to execute a arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22880</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Zadarma Zadarma extension v.1.0.11 allows a remote attacker to execute a arbitrary code via a crafted script to the webchat component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29357 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the startIp and endIp parameters at /goform/SetPptpServ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29357</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the startIp and endIp parameters at /goform/SetPptpServerCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57348 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PecanProject pecan v.1.7.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the crafted payload ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57348</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in PecanProject pecan v.1.7.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the crafted payload to the hostname, sitegroupid, lat, lon and sitename parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29358 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the firewallEn parameter at /goform/SetFirewallCfg. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29358</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the firewallEn parameter at /goform/SetFirewallCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29359 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter at /goform/saveParentControlInfo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29359</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the deviceId parameter at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29360 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the time and timeZone parameters at /goform/SetSysTimeC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29360</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the time and timeZone parameters at /goform/SetSysTimeCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28803 | Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Italtel S.p.A. i-MCS NFV v.12.1.0-20211215 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28803</link><description>Cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Italtel S.p.A. i-MCS NFV v.12.1.0-20211215 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML into HTTP/POST parameter</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29361 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29361</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29362 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/setPptpUserList. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29362</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow via the list parameter at /goform/setPptpUserList. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:51:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29363 | Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to buffer overflow via the schedStartTime and schedEndTime parameters at /gofo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29363</link><description>Tenda RX3 US_RX3V1.0br_V16.03.13.11_multi_TDE01 is vulnerable to buffer overflow via the schedStartTime and schedEndTime parameters at /goform/saveParentControlInfo. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted packet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2278 | Improper access control in temporary access requests and checkout requests endpoints in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2278</link><description>Improper access control in temporary access requests and checkout requests endpoints in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to access information about these requests via a known request ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2280 | Improper access control in web extension restriction feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to byp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2280</link><description>Improper access control in web extension restriction feature in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the browser extension restriction feature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10942 | All in One WP Migration &amp;lt;= 7.89 - Unauthenticated PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10942</link><description>The All-in-One WP Migration and Backup plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in all versions up to, and including, 7.89 via deserialization of untrusted input in the 'replace_serialized_values' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code. An administrator must export and restore a backup in order to trigger the exploit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1635 | Exposure of sensitive information in hub data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1635</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in hub data source export feature in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows allows a user exporting a hub data source to include his authenticated session in the export due to faulty business logic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1636 | Exposure of sensitive information in My Personnal Credentials password history component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1636</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information in My Personnal Credentials password history component in Devolutions Remote Desktop Manager 2024.3.29 and earlier on Windows allows an authenticated user to inadvertently leak the My Personnal Credentials in a shared vault via the clear history feature due to faulty business logic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2277 | Exposure of password in web-based SSH authentication component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows a user to unadvertently le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2277</link><description>Exposure of password in web-based SSH authentication component in Devolutions Server 2024.3.13 and earlier allows a user to unadvertently leak his SSH password due to missing password masking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21104 | Dell NetWorker, 19.11.0.3 and below versions, contain(s) an Open Redirect Vulnerability in NMC. An unauthenticated attacker with remoter acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21104</link><description>Dell NetWorker, 19.11.0.3 and below versions, contain(s) an Open Redirect Vulnerability in NMC. An unauthenticated attacker with remoter access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a targeted application user being redirected to arbitrary web URLs. The vulnerability could be leveraged by attackers to conduct phishing attacks that cause users to divulge sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29996 | Authentication Bypass Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29996</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper implementation of OTP verification mechanism in its API based login. A remote attacker with valid credentials could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API request URL/payload. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability could allow the attacker to bypass Two-Factor Authentication (2FA) for other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29997 | Improper Access Control Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29997</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper authorization checks on certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API request URL to gain unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29998 | No Rate Limiting Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29998</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to missing rate limiting on OTP requests in an API endpoint. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending multiple OTP request through vulnerable API endpoint which could lead to the OTP bombing/flooding on the targeted system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:30:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29994 | Improper Authentication Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29994</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to improper authentication check at the API endpoint. An unauthenticated remote attacker with a valid login ID could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating API input parameters through API request URL/payload leading to unauthorized access to other user accounts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29995 | Account Takeover Vulnerability in CAP back office application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29995</link><description>This vulnerability exists in the CAP back office application due to a weak password-reset mechanism implemented at API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker with a valid login ID could exploit this vulnerability through vulnerable API endpoint which could lead to account takeover of targeted users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25175 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap V2401 (All versions &lt; V2401.0003), Simcenter Femap V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0002)....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25175</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap V2401 (All versions &lt; V2401.0003), Simcenter Femap V2406 (All versions &lt; V2406.0002). The affected application contains a memory corruption vulnerability while  parsing specially crafted .NEU files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process. (ZDI-CAN-25443)</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 09:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1785 | Download Manager &amp;lt;= 3.3.08 - Authenticated (Author+) Path Traversal to Limited File Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1785</link><description>The Download Manager plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.08 via the 'wpdm_newfile' action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to overwrite select file types outside of the originally intended directory, which may cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:37:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1119 | Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.8.5 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1119</link><description>The Appointment Booking Calendar — Simply Schedule Appointments Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.8.5. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 07:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2271 | IDOR in Issuetrak NewAuditID parameter via Inv_PopTrakXShow.asp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2271</link><description>A vulnerability exists in Issuetrak v17.2.2 and prior that allows a low-privileged user to access audit results of other users by exploiting an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in the Issuetrak audit component. The vulnerability enables unauthorized access to sensitive information, including user details, network and hardware information, installed programs, running processes, drives, and printers. Due to improper access controls, an attacker can retrieve audit data belonging to other users, potentially leading to unauthorized data exposure, privacy violations, and security risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13884 | Limit Bio &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13884</link><description>The Limit Bio WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13885 | WP E Customers &amp;lt;= 0.0.1 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13885</link><description>The WP e-Customers Beta WordPress plugin through 0.0.1 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13891 | Schedule &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13891</link><description>The Schedule WordPress plugin through 1.0.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7296 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7296</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 16.5 prior to 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2  which allowed a user with a custom permission to approve pending membership requests beyond the maximum number of allowed users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1257 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1257</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting with 12.3 before 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2. A vulnerability in certain GitLab instances could allow an attacker to cause a denial of service condition by manipulating specific API inputs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1401 | WP Click Info &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1401</link><description>The WP Click Info WordPress plugin through 2.7.4 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1436 | Limit Bio &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1436</link><description>The Limit Bio WordPress plugin through 1.0 does not have CSRF check when updating its settings, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1486 | WoWPth &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1486</link><description>The WoWPth WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1487 | WoWPth &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1487</link><description>The WoWPth WordPress plugin through 2.0 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 06:21:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12380 | Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12380</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 11.5 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2. Certain user inputs in repository mirroring settings could potentially expose sensitive authentication information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13054 | Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13054</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 17.7.7, 17.8 prior to 17.8.5, and 17.9 prior to 17.9.2. where a denial of service vulnerability could allow an attacker to cause a system reboot under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8402 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command (&amp;#x27;Command Injection&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8402</link><description>An issue was discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 17.2 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2. An input validation issue in the Google Cloud IAM integration feature could have enabled a Maintainer to introduce malicious code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0652 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0652</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting from 16.9 before 17.7.7, all versions starting from 17.8 before 17.8.5, all versions starting from 17.9 before 17.9.2 could allow unauthorized users to access confidential information intended for internal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36843 | The implementation of EdDSA in EdDSA-Java (aka ed25519-java) through 0.3.0 exhibits signature malleability and does not satisfy the SUF-CMA ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36843</link><description>The implementation of EdDSA in EdDSA-Java (aka ed25519-java) through 0.3.0 exhibits signature malleability and does not satisfy the SUF-CMA (Strong Existential Unforgeability under Chosen Message Attacks) property. This allows attackers to create new valid signatures different from previous signatures for a known message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1503 | WP Recipe Maker &amp;lt;= 9.8.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1503</link><description>The WP Recipe Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Roundup Recipe Name field in all versions up to, and including, 9.8.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1561 | AppPresser – Mobile App Framework &amp;lt;= 4.4.10 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1561</link><description>The AppPresser – Mobile App Framework plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages when logging is enabled that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2104 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Publication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2104</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized post publication due to insufficient validation on the pagelayer_save_content() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to bypass post moderation and publish posts to the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13887 | Business Directory Plugin - Easy Listing Directories for WordPress &amp;lt;= 6.4.14 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Listing Arbitrary Image Addition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13887</link><description>The Business Directory Plugin – Easy Listing Directories for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 6.4.14 via the 'ajax_listing_submit_image_upload' function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add arbitrary images to listings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2250 | WordPress Report Brute Force Attacks and Login Protection ReportAttacks Plugins &amp;lt;= 2.32 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2250</link><description>The WordPress Report Brute Force Attacks and Login Protection ReportAttacks Plugins plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'orderby' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.32 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 03:44:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13703 | CRM and Lead Management by vcita &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Susbcriber+) Widget Toggle</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13703</link><description>The CRM and Lead Management by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the vcita_ajax_toggle_ae() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to enable and disable plugin widgets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1559 | CC-IMG-Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1559</link><description>The CC-IMG-Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'img' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2106 | Arielbrailovsky-Viralad &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2106</link><description>The ArielBrailovsky-ViralAd plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'text' and 'id' parameters of the limpia() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This only appears to be exploitable on very old versions of WordPress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2107 | Arielbrailovsky-Viralad &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2107</link><description>The ArielBrailovsky-ViralAd plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the printResultAndDie() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database. This only appears to be exploitable on very old versions of WordPress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 02:38:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25292 | Ruby SAML vulnerable to SAML authentication bypass due to namespace handling (parser differential)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25292</link><description>ruby-saml provides security assertion markup language (SAML) single sign-on (SSO) for Ruby. An authentication bypass vulnerability was found in ruby-saml prior to versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0 due to a parser differential. ReXML and Nokogiri parse XML differently, the parsers can generate entirely different document structures from the same XML input. That allows an attacker to be able to execute a Signature Wrapping attack. This issue may lead to authentication bypass. Versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 21:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25291 | ruby-saml vulnerable to SAML authentication bypass due to DOCTYPE handling (parser differential)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25291</link><description>ruby-saml provides security assertion markup language (SAML) single sign-on (SSO) for Ruby. An authentication bypass vulnerability was found in ruby-saml prior to versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0 due to a parser differential. ReXML and Nokogiri parse XML differently; the parsers can generate entirely different document structures from the same XML input. That allows an attacker to be able to execute a Signature Wrapping attack. This issue may lead to authentication bypass. Versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25293 | ruby-saml vulnerable to Remote Denial of Service (DoS) with compressed SAML responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25293</link><description>ruby-saml provides security assertion markup language (SAML) single sign-on (SSO) for Ruby. Prior to versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0, ruby-saml is susceptible to remote Denial of Service (DoS) with compressed SAML responses. ruby-saml uses zlib to decompress SAML responses in case they're compressed. It is possible to bypass the message size check with a compressed assertion since the message size is checked before inflation and not after. This issue may lead to remote Denial of Service (DoS). Versions 1.12.4 and 1.18.0 fix the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26290 | Authenticated Remote Command Injection affecting Avid NEXIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26290</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Avid Avid NEXIS E-series on Linux, Avid Avid NEXIS F-series on Linux, Avid Avid NEXIS PRO+ on Linux, Avid System Director Appliance (SDA+) on Linux allows code execution on underlying operating system with root permissions.This issue affects Avid NEXIS E-series: before 2024.6.0; Avid NEXIS F-series: before 2024.6.0; Avid NEXIS PRO+: before 2024.6.0; System Director Appliance (SDA+): before 2024.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:55:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25975 | An issue in parse-git-config v.3.0.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the expandKeys function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25975</link><description>An issue in parse-git-config v.3.0.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the expandKeys function</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0115 | PAN-OS: Authenticated Admin File Read Vulnerability in PAN-OS CLI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0115</link><description>A vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an authenticated admin on the PAN-OS CLI to read arbitrary files.

This issue does not affect Cloud NGFW or Prisma Access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0116 | PAN-OS: Firewall Denial of Service (DoS) Using a Specially Crafted LLDP Frame</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0116</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software causes the firewall to unexpectedly reboot when processing a specially crafted LLDP frame sent by an unauthenticated adjacent attacker. Repeated attempts to initiate this condition causes the firewall to enter maintenance mode.

This issue does not apply to Cloud NGFWs or Prisma Access software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0117 | GlobalProtect App: Local Privilege Escalation (PE) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0117</link><description>A reliance on untrusted input for a security decision in the GlobalProtect app on Windows devices potentially enables a locally authenticated non-administrative Windows user to escalate their privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.

GlobalProtect App on Linux, iOS, Android, Chrome OS and GlobalProtect UWP App are not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:45:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0118 | GlobalProtect App: Execution of Unsafe ActiveX Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0118</link><description>A vulnerability in the Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect app on Windows allows a remote attacker to run ActiveX controls within the context of an authenticated Windows user. This enables the attacker to run commands as if they are a legitimate authenticated user. However, to exploit this vulnerability, the authenticated user must navigate to a malicious page during the GlobalProtect SAML login process on a Windows device.

This issue does not apply to the GlobalProtect app on other (non-Windows) platforms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22870 | HTTP Proxy bypass using IPv6 Zone IDs in golang.org/x/net</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22870</link><description>Matching of hosts against proxy patterns can improperly treat an IPv6 zone ID as a hostname component. For example, when the NO_PROXY environment variable is set to "*.example.com", a request to "[::1%25.example.com]:80` will incorrectly match and not be proxied.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0114 | PAN-OS: Denial of Service (DoS) in GlobalProtect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0114</link><description>A Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables an unauthenticated attacker to render the service unavailable by sending a large number of specially crafted packets over a period of time. This issue affects both the GlobalProtect portal and the GlobalProtect gateway.

This issue does not apply to Cloud NGFWs or Prisma Access software.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27407 | Remote code execution when loading a crafted GraphQL schema</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27407</link><description>graphql-ruby is a Ruby implementation of GraphQL. Starting in version 1.11.5 and prior to versions 1.11.8, 1.12.25, 1.13.24, 2.0.32, 2.1.14, 2.2.17, and 2.3.21, loading a malicious schema definition in `GraphQL::Schema.from_introspection` (or `GraphQL::Schema::Loader.load`) can result in remote code execution. Any system which loads a schema by JSON from an untrusted source is vulnerable, including those that use GraphQL::Client to load external schemas via GraphQL introspection. Versions 1.11.8, 1.12.25, 1.13.24, 2.0.32, 2.1.14, 2.2.17, and 2.3.21 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:27:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34398 | An issue was discovered in BMC Remedy Mid Tier 7.6.04. The web application allows stored HTML Injection by authenticated remote attackers.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34398</link><description>An issue was discovered in BMC Remedy Mid Tier 7.6.04. The web application allows stored HTML Injection by authenticated remote attackers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25774 | An issue was discovered in Open5GS v2.7.2. When a UE switches between two gNBs and sends a handover request at a specific time, it may cause...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25774</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open5GS v2.7.2. When a UE switches between two gNBs and sends a handover request at a specific time, it may cause an exception in the AMF's internal state machine, leading to an AMF crash and resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:08:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25683 | AlekSIS-Core is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Unauthenticated users can access all PDF files. This affects AlekSIS-Core 3.0, 3.1, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25683</link><description>AlekSIS-Core is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Unauthenticated users can access all PDF files. This affects AlekSIS-Core 3.0, 3.1, 3.1.1, 3.1.2, 3.1.3, 3.1.4, 3.1.5, 3.1.6, 3.2.0 and 3.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27017 | Apache NiFi: Potential Insertion of MongoDB Password in Provenance Record</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27017</link><description>Apache NiFi 1.13.0 through 2.2.0 includes the username and password used to authenticate with MongoDB in the NiFi provenance events that MongoDB components generate during processing. An authorized user with read access to the provenance events of those processors may see the credentials information. Upgrading to Apache NiFi 2.3.0 is the recommended mitigation, which removes the credentials from provenance event records.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20115 | Cisco IOS XR Software Border Gateway Protocol Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20115</link><description>A vulnerability in confederation implementation for the Border Gateway Protocol (BGP)&amp;nbsp;in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to a memory corruption that occurs when a BGP update is created with an AS_CONFED_SEQUENCE attribute that has 255 autonomous system numbers (AS numbers). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted BGP update message, or the network could be designed in such a manner that the AS_CONFED_SEQUENCE attribute grows to 255 AS numbers or more. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause memory corruption, which may cause the BGP process to restart, resulting in a DoS condition. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker must control a BGP confederation speaker within the same autonomous system as the victim, or the network must be designed in such a manner that the AS_CONFED_SEQUENCE attribute grows to 255 AS numbers or more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20138 | Cisco IOS XR Software CLI Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20138</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands as root on the underlying operating system of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient validation of user arguments that are passed to specific CLI commands. An attacker with a low-privileged account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted commands at the prompt. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to elevate privileges to root and execute arbitrary commands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20141 | Cisco IOS XR Software Release 7.9.2 Denial of Service Vulnerabillity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20141</link><description>A vulnerability in the handling of specific packets that are punted from a line card to a route processor in Cisco IOS XR Software Release 7.9.2 could allow an unauthenticated, adjacent attacker to cause control plane traffic to stop working on multiple Cisco IOS XR platforms.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of packets that are punted to the route processor. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending traffic, which must be handled by the Linux stack on the route processor, to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause control plane traffic to stop working, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20142 | Cisco IOS XR Software for ASR 9000 Series Routers L2VPN Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20142</link><description>A vulnerability in the IPv4 access control list (ACL) feature and quality of service (QoS) policy feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers, ASR 9902 Compact High-Performance Routers, and ASR 9903 Compact High-Performance Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a line card to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of malformed IPv4 packets that are received on line cards where the interface has either an IPv4 ACL or QoS policy applied. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IPv4 packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause network processor errors, resulting in a reset or shutdown of the network process. Traffic over that line card would be lost while the line card reloads.
Note: This vulnerability has predominantly been observed in Layer 2 VPN (L2VPN) environments where an IPv4 ACL or QoS policy has been applied to the bridge virtual interface. Layer 3 configurations where the interface has either an IPv4 ACL or QoS policy applied are also affected, though the vulnerability has not been observed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20143 | Cisco IOS XR Software Secure Boot Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20143</link><description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker with high privileges to bypass the Secure Boot functionality and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient verification of modules in the software load process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the loaded binaries to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the booting process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass the requirement to run Cisco-signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.
Note: This vulnerability affects Cisco IOS XR Software, not the Secure Boot feature.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20144 | Cisco IOS XR Software Access Control List Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20144</link><description>A vulnerability in the hybrid access control list (ACL) processing of IPv4 packets in Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.

This vulnerability is due to incorrect handling of packets when a specific configuration of the hybrid ACL exists. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass a configured ACL on the affected device.
For more information, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20145 | Cisco IOS XR Software Access Control List Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20145</link><description>A vulnerability in the access control list (ACL) processing in the egress direction of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to bypass a configured ACL.

This vulnerability exists because certain packets are handled incorrectly when they are received on an ingress interface on one line card and destined out of an egress interface on another line card where the egress ACL is configured. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by attempting to send traffic through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to bypass an egress ACL on the affected device.
For more information about this vulnerability, see the  section of this advisory.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20146 | Cisco IOS XR Software for ASR 9000 Series Routers Layer 3 Multicast Routing Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20146</link><description>A vulnerability in the Layer 3 multicast feature of Cisco IOS XR Software for Cisco ASR 9000 Series Aggregation Services Routers, ASR 9902 Compact High-Performance Routers, and ASR 9903 Compact High-Performance Routers could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a line card to reset, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to the incorrect handling of malformed IPv4 multicast packets that are received on line cards where the interface has either an IPv4 access control list (ACL) or a QoS policy applied. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted IPv4 multicast packets through an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to cause line card exceptions or a hard reset. Traffic over that line card would be lost while the line card reloads.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20177 | Cisco IOS XR Software Image Verification Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20177</link><description>A vulnerability in the boot process of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an authenticated, local attacker to bypass Cisco IOS XR image signature verification and load unverified software on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have root-system privileges on the affected device.

This vulnerability is due to incomplete validation of files in the boot verification process. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating the system configuration options to bypass some of the integrity checks that are performed during the boot process. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to control the boot configuration, which could enable them to bypass the requirement to run Cisco-signed images or alter the security properties of the running system.
Note: Because exploitation of this vulnerability could result in the attacker bypassing Cisco image verification, Cisco has raised the Security Impact Rating (SIR) of this advisory from Medium to High.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20209 | Cisco IOS XR Software Internet Key Exchange Version 2 Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20209</link><description>A vulnerability in the Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2) function of Cisco IOS XR Software could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to prevent an affected device from processing any control plane UDP packets.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to improper handling of malformed IKEv2 packets. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending malformed IKEv2 packets to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to prevent the affected device from processing any control plane UDP packets, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:26:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27867 | Apache Felix HTTP Webconsole Plugin: XSS in HTTP Webconsole Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27867</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Apache Felix HTTP Webconsole Plugin.

This issue affects Apache Felix HTTP Webconsole Plugin: from Version 1.X through 1.2.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.2.2, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0813 | CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause an Authentication Bypass when an
unauthorized user without permission...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0813</link><description>CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause an Authentication Bypass when an
unauthorized user without permission rights has physical access to the EPAS-UI computer and is able to
reboot the workstation and interrupt the normal boot process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1960 | CWE-1188: Initialization of a Resource with an Insecure Default vulnerability exists that could cause an
attacker to execute unauthorized co...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1960</link><description>CWE-1188: Initialization of a Resource with an Insecure Default vulnerability exists that could cause an
attacker to execute unauthorized commands when a system’s default password credentials have not been
changed on first use. The default username is not displayed correctly in the WebHMI interface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25567 | SoftEther VPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in Internat.c via the UniToStrForSingleChars function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25567</link><description>SoftEther VPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in Internat.c via the UniToStrForSingleChars function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25568 | SoftEtherVPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Use after Free in the Command.c file via the CheckNetworkAcceptThread function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25568</link><description>SoftEtherVPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Use after Free in the Command.c file via the CheckNetworkAcceptThread function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0883 | vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Service Manager.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0883</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script in an Error Message Web Page vulnerability in OpenText™ Service Manager. 

The vulnerability could reveal sensitive information retained by the browser.

This issue affects Service Manager: 9.70, 9.71, 9.72, 9.80.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0884 | Privilege Escalation vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText™ Service Manager.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0884</link><description>Unquoted Search Path or Element vulnerability in OpenText™ Service Manager. 

The vulnerability could allow a user to gain SYSTEM privileges through Privilege Escalation.

This issue affects Service Manager: 9.70, 9.71, 9.72.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1683 | 1E Nomad Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1683</link><description>Improper Link Resolution Before File Access in the Nomad module of the 1E Client prior to versions 25.3, allows an attacker with local unprivileged access on a Windows system to delete arbitrary files on the device by abusing symbolic links.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1984 | Local Privilege Escalation on Xerox® Desktop Print Experience® v8.5</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1984</link><description>Xerox Desktop Print Experience application contains a Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerability, which allows a low-privileged user to gain SYSTEM-level access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25565 | SoftEther VPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the Command.c file via the PtMakeCert and PtMakeCert2048 functions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25565</link><description>SoftEther VPN 5.02.5187 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the Command.c file via the PtMakeCert and PtMakeCert2048 functions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25566 | Memory Leak vulnerability in SoftEtherVPN 5.02.5187 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the UnixMemoryAlloc function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25566</link><description>Memory Leak vulnerability in SoftEtherVPN 5.02.5187 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service via the UnixMemoryAlloc function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2002 | CWE-532: Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log Files vulnerability exists that could cause the disclosure
of FTP server credentials wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2002</link><description>CWE-532: Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log Files vulnerability exists that could cause the disclosure
of FTP server credentials when the FTP server is deployed, and the device is placed in debug mode by an
administrative user and the debug files are exported from the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:36:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25711 | An issue in dtp.ae tNexus Airport View v.2.8 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the ProfileID value to the [/tnexus/rest/ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25711</link><description>An issue in dtp.ae tNexus Airport View v.2.8 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the ProfileID value to the [/tnexus/rest/admin/updateUser] API endpoint</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26260 | Plenti &lt;= 0.7.16 is vulnerable to code execution. Users uploading '.svelte' files with the /postLocal endpoint can define the file name as j...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26260</link><description>Plenti &lt;= 0.7.16 is vulnerable to code execution. Users uploading '.svelte' files with the /postLocal endpoint can define the file name as javascript codes. The server executes the uploaded file name in host, and cause code execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27763 | XPixelGroup BasicSR through 1.4.2 might locally allow code execution in contrived situations where "scontrol show hostname" is executed in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27763</link><description>XPixelGroup BasicSR through 1.4.2 might locally allow code execution in contrived situations where "scontrol show hostname" is executed in the presence of a crafted SLURM_NODELIST environment variable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:20:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22954 | Koha &lt;= 21.11 is contains a SQL Injection vulnerability in /serials/lateissues-export.pl via the supplierid parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22954</link><description>Koha &lt;= 21.11 is contains a SQL Injection vulnerability in /serials/lateissues-export.pl via the supplierid parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2240 | Smallrye-fault-tolerance: smallrye fault tolerance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2240</link><description>A flaw was found in Smallrye, where smallrye-fault-tolerance is vulnerable to an out-of-memory (OOM) issue. This vulnerability is externally triggered when calling the metrics URI. Every call creates a new object within meterMap and may lead to a denial of service (DoS) issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29891 | Apache Camel: Camel Message Header Injection through request parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29891</link><description>Bypass/Injection vulnerability in Apache Camel.

This issue affects Apache Camel: from 4.10.0 before 4.10.2, from 4.8.0 before 4.8.5, from 3.10.0 before 3.22.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 4.10.2 for 4.10.x LTS, 4.8.5 for 4.8.x LTS and 3.22.4 for 3.x releases.

This vulnerability is present in Camel's default incoming header filter, that allows an attacker to include Camel specific headers that for some Camel components can alter the behaviours such as the camel-bean component, or the camel-exec component.

If you have Camel applications that are directly connected to the internet via HTTP, then an attacker could include parameters in the HTTP requests that are sent to the Camel application that incorrectly get translated into headers. 

The headers could be both provided as request parameters for an HTTP methods invocation or as part of the payload of the HTTP methods invocation.

All the known Camel HTTP component such as camel-servlet, camel-jetty, camel-undertow, camel-platform-http, and camel-netty-http would be vulnerable out of the box.

This CVE is related to the CVE-2025-27636: while they have the same root cause and are fixed with the same fix, CVE-2025-27636 was assumed to only be exploitable if an attacker could add malicious HTTP headers, while we have now determined that it is also exploitable via HTTP parameters. Like in CVE-2025-27636, exploitation is only possible if the Camel route uses particular vulnerable components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:52:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27915 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27915</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Classic Web Client due to insufficient sanitization of HTML content in ICS files. When a user views an e-mail message containing a malicious ICS entry, its embedded JavaScript executes via an ontoggle event inside a &lt;details&gt; tag. This allows an attacker to run arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's session, potentially leading to unauthorized actions such as setting e-mail filters to redirect messages to an attacker-controlled address. As a result, an attacker can perform unauthorized actions on the victim's account, including e-mail redirection and data exfiltration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27914 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27914</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) 9.0 and 10.0 and 10.1. A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the /h/rest endpoint, allowing authenticated attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript in a victim's session. Exploitation requires a valid auth token and involves a crafted URL with manipulated query parameters that triggers XSS when accessed by a victim.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52362 | IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52362</link><description>IBM App Connect Enterprise Certified Container 7.2, 8.0, 8.1, 8.2, 9.0, 9.1, 9.2, 10.0, 10.1, 11.0, 11.1, 11.2, 11.3, 11.4, 11.5, 11.6, 12.0, 12.1, 12.2, 12.3, 12.4, 12.5, 12.6, 12.7, and 12.8 could allow an authenticated user to cause a denial of service in the App Connect flow due to improper validation of server-side input.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21590 | Junos OS: An local attacker with shell access can execute arbitrary code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21590</link><description>An Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability in the kernel of Juniper Networks Junos OS allows a local attacker with high privileges to compromise the integrity of the device.

A local attacker with access to the shell is able to inject arbitrary code which can compromise an affected device.
This issue is not exploitable from the Junos CLI.
This issue affects Junos OS: 



  *  All versions before 21.2R3-S9,
  *  21.4 versions before 21.4R3-S10, 
  *  22.2 versions before 22.2R3-S6, 
  *  22.4 versions before 22.4R3-S6, 
  *  23.2 versions before 23.2R2-S3, 
  *  23.4 versions before 23.4R2-S4,
  *  24.2 versions before 24.2R1-S2, 24.2R2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25709 | An issue in dtp.ae tNexus Airport View v.2.8 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the addUser and updateUser endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25709</link><description>An issue in dtp.ae tNexus Airport View v.2.8 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the addUser and updateUser endpoints</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27794 | Flarum Vulnerable to Session Hijacking via Authoritative Subdomain Cookie Overwrite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27794</link><description>Flarum is open-source forum software. A session hijacking vulnerability exists in versions prior to 1.8.10 when an attacker-controlled authoritative subdomain under a parent domain (e.g., `subdomain.host.com`) sets cookies scoped to the parent domain (`.host.com`). This allows session token replacement for applications hosted on sibling subdomains (e.g., `community.host.com`) if session tokens aren't rotated post-authentication. Key Constraints are that the attacker must control any subdomain under the parent domain (e.g., `evil.host.com` or `x.y.host.com`), and the parent domain must not be on the Public Suffix List. Due to non-existent session token rotation after authenticating we can theoretically reproduce the vulnerability by using browser dev tools, but due to the browser's security measures this does not seem to be exploitable as described. Version 1.8.10 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27788 | Ruby JSON Parser has Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27788</link><description>JSON is a JSON implementation for Ruby. Starting in version 2.10.0 and prior to version 2.10.2, a specially crafted document could cause an out of bound read, most likely resulting in a crash. Versions prior to 2.10.0 are not vulnerable. Version 2.10.2 fixes the problem. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 13:57:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10838 | Integer Underflow in DDS_Security_Deserialize_ methods may lead to OOB read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10838</link><description>An integer underflow during deserialization may allow any unauthenticated user to read out of bounds heap memory. This may result into secret data or pointers revealing the layout of the address space to be included into a deserialized data structure, which may potentially lead to thread crashes or cause denial of service conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 13:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29903 | In JetBrains Runtime before 21.0.6b872.80 arbitrary dynamic library execution due to insecure macOS flags was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29903</link><description>In JetBrains Runtime before 21.0.6b872.80 arbitrary dynamic library execution due to insecure macOS flags was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 13:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29904 | In JetBrains Ktor before 3.1.1 an HTTP Request Smuggling was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29904</link><description>In JetBrains Ktor before 3.1.1 an HTTP Request Smuggling was possible</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 13:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13870 | Unauthenticated Firmware Downgrade in Bitdefender Box v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13870</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability exists in Bitdefender Box 1 (firmware version 1.3.52.928 and below) that allows an unauthenticated attacker to downgrade the device's firmware to an older, potentially vulnerable version of a Bitdefender-signed firmware. The attack requires Bitdefender BOX to be booted in Recovery Mode and that the attacker be present within the WiFi range of the BOX unit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13871 | Unauthenticated Command Injection in Bitdefender BOX v1</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13871</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in the /check_image_and_trigger_recovery API endpoint of Bitdefender Box 1 (firmware version 1.3.11.490). This flaw allows an unauthenticated, network-adjacent attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device, potentially leading to full remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13872 | Bitdefender Box Insecure Update Mechanism Vulnerability in libboxhermes.so</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13872</link><description>Bitdefender Box, versions 1.3.11.490 through 1.3.11.505, uses the insecure HTTP protocol to download assets over the Internet to update and restart daemons and detection rules on the devices. Updates can be remotely triggered through the /set_temp_token API method. Then, an unauthenticated and network-adjacent attacker can use man-in-the-middle (MITM) techniques to return malicious responses. Restarted daemons that use malicious assets can then be exploited for remote code execution on the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1527 | ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp;amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via Flash Sale Countdown Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1527</link><description>The ShopLentor – WooCommerce Builder for Elementor &amp; Gutenberg +20 Modules – All in One Solution (formerly WooLentor) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to a Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Flash Sale Countdown module in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:28:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2239 | Absolute Path Disclosure Vulnerability in Hillstone Next Generation FireWall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2239</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in Hillstone Networks Hillstone Next Generation FireWall.This issue affects Hillstone Next Generation FireWall: from 5.5R8P1 before 5.5R8P23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:58:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58088 | bpf: Fix deadlock when freeing cgroup storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58088</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix deadlock when freeing cgroup storage

The following commit
bc235cdb423a ("bpf: Prevent deadlock from recursive bpf_task_storage_[get|delete]")
first introduced deadlock prevention for fentry/fexit programs attaching
on bpf_task_storage helpers. That commit also employed the logic in map
free path in its v6 version.

Later bpf_cgrp_storage was first introduced in
c4bcfb38a95e ("bpf: Implement cgroup storage available to non-cgroup-attached bpf progs")
which faces the same issue as bpf_task_storage, instead of its busy
counter, NULL was passed to bpf_local_storage_map_free() which opened
a window to cause deadlock:

	
		(acquiring local_storage-&gt;lock)
	_raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x3d/0x50
	bpf_local_storage_update+0xd1/0x460
	bpf_cgrp_storage_get+0x109/0x130
	bpf_prog_a4d4a370ba857314_cgrp_ptr+0x139/0x170
	? __bpf_prog_enter_recur+0x16/0x80
	bpf_trampoline_6442485186+0x43/0xa4
	cgroup_storage_ptr+0x9/0x20
		(holding local_storage-&gt;lock)
	bpf_selem_unlink_storage_nolock.constprop.0+0x135/0x160
	bpf_selem_unlink_storage+0x6f/0x110
	bpf_local_storage_map_free+0xa2/0x110
	bpf_map_free_deferred+0x5b/0x90
	process_one_work+0x17c/0x390
	worker_thread+0x251/0x360
	kthread+0xd2/0x100
	ret_from_fork+0x34/0x50
	ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
	

Progs:
 - A: SEC("fentry/cgroup_storage_ptr")
   - cgid (BPF_MAP_TYPE_HASH)
	Record the id of the cgroup the current task belonging
	to in this hash map, using the address of the cgroup
	as the map key.
   - cgrpa (BPF_MAP_TYPE_CGRP_STORAGE)
	If current task is a kworker, lookup the above hash
	map using function parameter @owner as the key to get
	its corresponding cgroup id which is then used to get
	a trusted pointer to the cgroup through
	bpf_cgroup_from_id(). This trusted pointer can then
	be passed to bpf_cgrp_storage_get() to finally trigger
	the deadlock issue.
 - B: SEC("tp_btf/sys_enter")
   - cgrpb (BPF_MAP_TYPE_CGRP_STORAGE)
	The only purpose of this prog is to fill Prog A's
	hash map by calling bpf_cgrp_storage_get() for as
	many userspace tasks as possible.

Steps to reproduce:
 - Run A;
 - while (true) { Run B; Destroy B; }

Fix this issue by passing its busy counter to the free procedure so
it can be properly incremented before storage/smap locking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58089 | btrfs: fix double accounting race when btrfs_run_delalloc_range() failed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58089</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

btrfs: fix double accounting race when btrfs_run_delalloc_range() failed

[BUG]
When running btrfs with block size (4K) smaller than page size (64K,
aarch64), there is a very high chance to crash the kernel at
generic/750, with the following messages:
(before the call traces, there are 3 extra debug messages added)

  BTRFS warning (device dm-3): read-write for sector size 4096 with page size 65536 is experimental
  BTRFS info (device dm-3): checking UUID tree
  hrtimer: interrupt took 5451385 ns
  BTRFS error (device dm-3): cow_file_range failed, root=4957 inode=257 start=1605632 len=69632: -28
  BTRFS error (device dm-3): run_delalloc_nocow failed, root=4957 inode=257 start=1605632 len=69632: -28
  BTRFS error (device dm-3): failed to run delalloc range, root=4957 ino=257 folio=1572864 submit_bitmap=8-15 start=1605632 len=69632: -28
  ------------[ cut here ]------------
  WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 3020984 at ordered-data.c:360 can_finish_ordered_extent+0x370/0x3b8 [btrfs]
  CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 3020984 Comm: kworker/u24:1 Tainted: G           OE      6.13.0-rc1-custom+ #89
  Tainted: [O]=OOT_MODULE, [E]=UNSIGNED_MODULE
  Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS unknown 2/2/2022
  Workqueue: events_unbound btrfs_async_reclaim_data_space [btrfs]
  pc : can_finish_ordered_extent+0x370/0x3b8 [btrfs]
  lr : can_finish_ordered_extent+0x1ec/0x3b8 [btrfs]
  Call trace:
   can_finish_ordered_extent+0x370/0x3b8 [btrfs] (P)
   can_finish_ordered_extent+0x1ec/0x3b8 [btrfs] (L)
   btrfs_mark_ordered_io_finished+0x130/0x2b8 [btrfs]
   extent_writepage+0x10c/0x3b8 [btrfs]
   extent_write_cache_pages+0x21c/0x4e8 [btrfs]
   btrfs_writepages+0x94/0x160 [btrfs]
   do_writepages+0x74/0x190
   filemap_fdatawrite_wbc+0x74/0xa0
   start_delalloc_inodes+0x17c/0x3b0 [btrfs]
   btrfs_start_delalloc_roots+0x17c/0x288 [btrfs]
   shrink_delalloc+0x11c/0x280 [btrfs]
   flush_space+0x288/0x328 [btrfs]
   btrfs_async_reclaim_data_space+0x180/0x228 [btrfs]
   process_one_work+0x228/0x680
   worker_thread+0x1bc/0x360
   kthread+0x100/0x118
   ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
  ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
  BTRFS critical (device dm-3): bad ordered extent accounting, root=4957 ino=257 OE offset=1605632 OE len=16384 to_dec=16384 left=0
  BTRFS critical (device dm-3): bad ordered extent accounting, root=4957 ino=257 OE offset=1622016 OE len=12288 to_dec=12288 left=0
  Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 0000000000000008
  BTRFS critical (device dm-3): bad ordered extent accounting, root=4957 ino=257 OE offset=1634304 OE len=8192 to_dec=4096 left=0
  CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 3286940 Comm: kworker/u24:3 Tainted: G        W  OE      6.13.0-rc1-custom+ #89
  Hardware name: QEMU KVM Virtual Machine, BIOS unknown 2/2/2022
  Workqueue:  btrfs_work_helper [btrfs] (btrfs-endio-write)
  pstate: 404000c5 (nZcv daIF +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
  pc : process_one_work+0x110/0x680
  lr : worker_thread+0x1bc/0x360
  Call trace:
   process_one_work+0x110/0x680 (P)
   worker_thread+0x1bc/0x360 (L)
   worker_thread+0x1bc/0x360
   kthread+0x100/0x118
   ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
  Code: f84086a1 f9000fe1 53041c21 b9003361 (f9400661)
  ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
  Kernel panic - not syncing: Oops: Fatal exception
  SMP: stopping secondary CPUs
  SMP: failed to stop secondary CPUs 2-3
  Dumping ftrace buffer:
     (ftrace buffer empty)
  Kernel Offset: 0x275bb9540000 from 0xffff800080000000
  PHYS_OFFSET: 0xffff8fbba0000000
  CPU features: 0x100,00000070,00801250,8201720b

[CAUSE]
The above warning is triggered immediately after the delalloc range
failure, this happens in the following sequence:

- Range [1568K, 1636K) is dirty

   1536K  1568K     1600K    1636K  1664K
   |      |/////////|////////|      |

  Where 1536K, 1600K and 1664K are page boundaries (64K page size)

- Enter extent_writepage() for page 1536K

- Enter run_delalloc_nocow() with locke
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21844 | smb: client: Add check for next_buffer in receive_encrypted_standard()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21844</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: Add check for next_buffer in receive_encrypted_standard()

Add check for the return value of cifs_buf_get() and cifs_small_buf_get()
in receive_encrypted_standard() to prevent null pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21845 | mtd: spi-nor: sst: Fix SST write failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21845</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mtd: spi-nor: sst: Fix SST write failure

'commit 18bcb4aa54ea ("mtd: spi-nor: sst: Factor out common write operation
to `sst_nor_write_data()`")' introduced a bug where only one byte of data
is written, regardless of the number of bytes passed to
sst_nor_write_data(), causing a kernel crash during the write operation.
Ensure the correct number of bytes are written as passed to
sst_nor_write_data().

Call trace:
[   57.400180] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   57.404842] While writing 2 byte written 1 bytes
[   57.409493] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 737 at drivers/mtd/spi-nor/sst.c:187 sst_nor_write_data+0x6c/0x74
[   57.418464] Modules linked in:
[   57.421517] CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 737 Comm: mtd_debug Not tainted 6.12.0-g5ad04afd91f9 #30
[   57.429517] Hardware name: Xilinx Versal A2197 Processor board revA - x-prc-02 revA (DT)
[   57.437600] pstate: 60000005 (nZCv daif -PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
[   57.444557] pc : sst_nor_write_data+0x6c/0x74
[   57.448911] lr : sst_nor_write_data+0x6c/0x74
[   57.453264] sp : ffff80008232bb40
[   57.456570] x29: ffff80008232bb40 x28: 0000000000010000 x27: 0000000000000001
[   57.463708] x26: 000000000000ffff x25: 0000000000000000 x24: 0000000000000000
[   57.470843] x23: 0000000000010000 x22: ffff80008232bbf0 x21: ffff000816230000
[   57.477978] x20: ffff0008056c0080 x19: 0000000000000002 x18: 0000000000000006
[   57.485112] x17: 0000000000000000 x16: 0000000000000000 x15: ffff80008232b580
[   57.492246] x14: 0000000000000000 x13: ffff8000816d1530 x12: 00000000000004a4
[   57.499380] x11: 000000000000018c x10: ffff8000816fd530 x9 : ffff8000816d1530
[   57.506515] x8 : 00000000fffff7ff x7 : ffff8000816fd530 x6 : 0000000000000001
[   57.513649] x5 : 0000000000000000 x4 : 0000000000000000 x3 : 0000000000000000
[   57.520782] x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000000 x0 : ffff0008049b0000
[   57.527916] Call trace:
[   57.530354]  sst_nor_write_data+0x6c/0x74
[   57.534361]  sst_nor_write+0xb4/0x18c
[   57.538019]  mtd_write_oob_std+0x7c/0x88
[   57.541941]  mtd_write_oob+0x70/0xbc
[   57.545511]  mtd_write+0x68/0xa8
[   57.548733]  mtdchar_write+0x10c/0x290
[   57.552477]  vfs_write+0xb4/0x3a8
[   57.555791]  ksys_write+0x74/0x10c
[   57.559189]  __arm64_sys_write+0x1c/0x28
[   57.563109]  invoke_syscall+0x54/0x11c
[   57.566856]  el0_svc_common.constprop.0+0xc0/0xe0
[   57.571557]  do_el0_svc+0x1c/0x28
[   57.574868]  el0_svc+0x30/0xcc
[   57.577921]  el0t_64_sync_handler+0x120/0x12c
[   57.582276]  el0t_64_sync+0x190/0x194
[   57.585933] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---

[pratyush@kernel.org: add Cc stable tag]</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21846 | acct: perform last write from workqueue</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21846</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

acct: perform last write from workqueue

In [1] it was reported that the acct(2) system call can be used to
trigger NULL deref in cases where it is set to write to a file that
triggers an internal lookup. This can e.g., happen when pointing acc(2)
to /sys/power/resume. At the point the where the write to this file
happens the calling task has already exited and called exit_fs(). A
lookup will thus trigger a NULL-deref when accessing current-&gt;fs.

Reorganize the code so that the the final write happens from the
workqueue but with the caller's credentials. This preserves the
(strange) permission model and has almost no regression risk.

This api should stop to exist though.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21847 | ASoC: SOF: stream-ipc: Check for cstream nullity in sof_ipc_msg_data()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21847</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: SOF: stream-ipc: Check for cstream nullity in sof_ipc_msg_data()

The nullity of sps-&gt;cstream should be checked similarly as it is done in
sof_set_stream_data_offset() function.
Assuming that it is not NULL if sps-&gt;stream is NULL is incorrect and can
lead to NULL pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21848 | nfp: bpf: Add check for nfp_app_ctrl_msg_alloc()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21848</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nfp: bpf: Add check for nfp_app_ctrl_msg_alloc()

Add check for the return value of nfp_app_ctrl_msg_alloc() in
nfp_bpf_cmsg_alloc() to prevent null pointer dereference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21849 | drm/i915/gt: Use spin_lock_irqsave() in interruptible context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21849</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/i915/gt: Use spin_lock_irqsave() in interruptible context

spin_lock/unlock() functions used in interrupt contexts could
result in a deadlock, as seen in GitLab issue #13399,
which occurs when interrupt comes in while holding a lock.

Try to remedy the problem by saving irq state before spin lock
acquisition.

v2: add irqs' state save/restore calls to all locks/unlocks in
 signal_irq_work() execution (Maciej)

v3: use with spin_lock_irqsave() in guc_lrc_desc_unpin() instead
 of other lock/unlock calls and add Fixes and Cc tags (Tvrtko);
 change title and commit message

(cherry picked from commit c088387ddd6482b40f21ccf23db1125e8fa4af7e)</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21850 | nvmet: Fix crash when a namespace is disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21850</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

nvmet: Fix crash when a namespace is disabled

The namespace percpu counter protects pending I/O, and we can
only safely diable the namespace once the counter drop to zero.
Otherwise we end up with a crash when running blktests/nvme/058
(eg for loop transport):

[ 2352.930426] [  T53909] Oops: general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000005: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN PTI
[ 2352.930431] [  T53909] KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000028-0x000000000000002f]
[ 2352.930434] [  T53909] CPU: 3 UID: 0 PID: 53909 Comm: kworker/u16:5 Tainted: G        W          6.13.0-rc6 #232
[ 2352.930438] [  T53909] Tainted: [W]=WARN
[ 2352.930440] [  T53909] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-3.fc41 04/01/2014
[ 2352.930443] [  T53909] Workqueue: nvmet-wq nvme_loop_execute_work [nvme_loop]
[ 2352.930449] [  T53909] RIP: 0010:blkcg_set_ioprio+0x44/0x180

as the queue is already torn down when calling submit_bio();

So we need to init the percpu counter in nvmet_ns_enable(), and
wait for it to drop to zero in nvmet_ns_disable() to avoid having
I/O pending after the namespace has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21851 | bpf: Fix softlockup in arena_map_free on 64k page kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21851</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: Fix softlockup in arena_map_free on 64k page kernel

On an aarch64 kernel with CONFIG_PAGE_SIZE_64KB=y,
arena_htab tests cause a segmentation fault and soft lockup.
The same failure is not observed with 4k pages on aarch64.

It turns out arena_map_free() is calling
apply_to_existing_page_range() with the address returned by
bpf_arena_get_kern_vm_start().  If this address is not page-aligned
the code ends up calling apply_to_pte_range() with that unaligned
address causing soft lockup.

Fix it by round up GUARD_SZ to PAGE_SIZE &lt;&lt; 1 so that the
division by 2 in bpf_arena_get_kern_vm_start() returns
a page-aligned value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21852 | net: Add rx_skb of kfree_skb to raw_tp_null_args[].</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21852</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: Add rx_skb of kfree_skb to raw_tp_null_args[].

Yan Zhai reported a BPF prog could trigger a null-ptr-deref [0]
in trace_kfree_skb if the prog does not check if rx_sk is NULL.

Commit c53795d48ee8 ("net: add rx_sk to trace_kfree_skb") added
rx_sk to trace_kfree_skb, but rx_sk is optional and could be NULL.

Let's add kfree_skb to raw_tp_null_args[] to let the BPF verifier
validate such a prog and prevent the issue.

Now we fail to load such a prog:

  libbpf: prog 'drop': -- BEGIN PROG LOAD LOG --
  0: R1=ctx() R10=fp0
  ; int BPF_PROG(drop, struct sk_buff *skb, void *location, @ kfree_skb_sk_null.bpf.c:21
  0: (79) r3 = *(u64 *)(r1 +24)
  func 'kfree_skb' arg3 has btf_id 5253 type STRUCT 'sock'
  1: R1=ctx() R3_w=trusted_ptr_or_null_sock(id=1)
  ; bpf_printk("sk: %d, %d\n", sk, sk-&gt;__sk_common.skc_family); @ kfree_skb_sk_null.bpf.c:24
  1: (69) r4 = *(u16 *)(r3 +16)
  R3 invalid mem access 'trusted_ptr_or_null_'
  processed 2 insns (limit 1000000) max_states_per_insn 0 total_states 0 peak_states 0 mark_read 0
  -- END PROG LOAD LOG --

Note this fix requires commit 838a10bd2ebf ("bpf: Augment raw_tp
arguments with PTR_MAYBE_NULL").

[0]:
BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000010
 PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
 PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
PGD 0 P4D 0
PREEMPT SMP
RIP: 0010:bpf_prog_5e21a6db8fcff1aa_drop+0x10/0x2d
Call Trace:
 
 ? __die+0x1f/0x60
 ? page_fault_oops+0x148/0x420
 ? search_bpf_extables+0x5b/0x70
 ? fixup_exception+0x27/0x2c0
 ? exc_page_fault+0x75/0x170
 ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x22/0x30
 ? bpf_prog_5e21a6db8fcff1aa_drop+0x10/0x2d
 bpf_trace_run4+0x68/0xd0
 ? unix_stream_connect+0x1f4/0x6f0
 sk_skb_reason_drop+0x90/0x120
 unix_stream_connect+0x1f4/0x6f0
 __sys_connect+0x7f/0xb0
 __x64_sys_connect+0x14/0x20
 do_syscall_64+0x47/0xc30
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x4b/0x53</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21853 | bpf: avoid holding freeze_mutex during mmap operation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21853</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

bpf: avoid holding freeze_mutex during mmap operation

We use map-&gt;freeze_mutex to prevent races between map_freeze() and
memory mapping BPF map contents with writable permissions. The way we
naively do this means we'll hold freeze_mutex for entire duration of all
the mm and VMA manipulations, which is completely unnecessary. This can
potentially also lead to deadlocks, as reported by syzbot in [0].

So, instead, hold freeze_mutex only during writeability checks, bump
(proactively) "write active" count for the map, unlock the mutex and
proceed with mmap logic. And only if something went wrong during mmap
logic, then undo that "write active" counter increment.

  [0] https://lore.kernel.org/bpf/678dcbc9.050a0220.303755.0066.GAE@google.com/</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21854 | sockmap, vsock: For connectible sockets allow only connected</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21854</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

sockmap, vsock: For connectible sockets allow only connected

sockmap expects all vsocks to have a transport assigned, which is expressed
in vsock_proto::psock_update_sk_prot(). However, there is an edge case
where an unconnected (connectible) socket may lose its previously assigned
transport. This is handled with a NULL check in the vsock/BPF recv path.

Another design detail is that listening vsocks are not supposed to have any
transport assigned at all. Which implies they are not supported by the
sockmap. But this is complicated by the fact that a socket, before
switching to TCP_LISTEN, may have had some transport assigned during a
failed connect() attempt. Hence, we may end up with a listening vsock in a
sockmap, which blows up quickly:

KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000120-0x0000000000000127]
CPU: 7 UID: 0 PID: 56 Comm: kworker/7:0 Not tainted 6.14.0-rc1+
Workqueue: vsock-loopback vsock_loopback_work
RIP: 0010:vsock_read_skb+0x4b/0x90
Call Trace:
 sk_psock_verdict_data_ready+0xa4/0x2e0
 virtio_transport_recv_pkt+0x1ca8/0x2acc
 vsock_loopback_work+0x27d/0x3f0
 process_one_work+0x846/0x1420
 worker_thread+0x5b3/0xf80
 kthread+0x35a/0x700
 ret_from_fork+0x2d/0x70
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30

For connectible sockets, instead of relying solely on the state of
vsk-&gt;transport, tell sockmap to only allow those representing established
connections. This aligns with the behaviour for AF_INET and AF_UNIX.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21855 | ibmvnic: Don&amp;#x27;t reference skb after sending to VIOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21855</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ibmvnic: Don't reference skb after sending to VIOS

Previously, after successfully flushing the xmit buffer to VIOS,
the tx_bytes stat was incremented by the length of the skb.

It is invalid to access the skb memory after sending the buffer to
the VIOS because, at any point after sending, the VIOS can trigger
an interrupt to free this memory. A race between reading skb-&gt;len
and freeing the skb is possible (especially during LPM) and will
result in use-after-free:
 ==================================================================
 BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in ibmvnic_xmit+0x75c/0x1808 [ibmvnic]
 Read of size 4 at addr c00000024eb48a70 by task hxecom/14495
 &lt;...&gt;
 Call Trace:
 [c000000118f66cf0] [c0000000018cba6c] dump_stack_lvl+0x84/0xe8 (unreliable)
 [c000000118f66d20] [c0000000006f0080] print_report+0x1a8/0x7f0
 [c000000118f66df0] [c0000000006f08f0] kasan_report+0x128/0x1f8
 [c000000118f66f00] [c0000000006f2868] __asan_load4+0xac/0xe0
 [c000000118f66f20] [c0080000046eac84] ibmvnic_xmit+0x75c/0x1808 [ibmvnic]
 [c000000118f67340] [c0000000014be168] dev_hard_start_xmit+0x150/0x358
 &lt;...&gt;
 Freed by task 0:
 kasan_save_stack+0x34/0x68
 kasan_save_track+0x2c/0x50
 kasan_save_free_info+0x64/0x108
 __kasan_mempool_poison_object+0x148/0x2d4
 napi_skb_cache_put+0x5c/0x194
 net_tx_action+0x154/0x5b8
 handle_softirqs+0x20c/0x60c
 do_softirq_own_stack+0x6c/0x88
 &lt;...&gt;
 The buggy address belongs to the object at c00000024eb48a00 which
  belongs to the cache skbuff_head_cache of size 224
==================================================================</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21856 | s390/ism: add release function for struct device</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21856</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/ism: add release function for struct device

According to device_release() in /drivers/base/core.c,
a device without a release function is a broken device
and must be fixed.

The current code directly frees the device after calling device_add()
without waiting for other kernel parts to release their references.
Thus, a reference could still be held to a struct device,
e.g., by sysfs, leading to potential use-after-free
issues if a proper release function is not set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21857 | net/sched: cls_api: fix error handling causing NULL dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21857</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: cls_api: fix error handling causing NULL dereference

tcf_exts_miss_cookie_base_alloc() calls xa_alloc_cyclic() which can
return 1 if the allocation succeeded after wrapping. This was treated as
an error, with value 1 returned to caller tcf_exts_init_ex() which sets
exts-&gt;actions to NULL and returns 1 to caller fl_change().

fl_change() treats err == 1 as success, calling tcf_exts_validate_ex()
which calls tcf_action_init() with exts-&gt;actions as argument, where it
is dereferenced.

Example trace:

BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
CPU: 114 PID: 16151 Comm: handler114 Kdump: loaded Not tainted 5.14.0-503.16.1.el9_5.x86_64 #1
RIP: 0010:tcf_action_init+0x1f8/0x2c0
Call Trace:
 tcf_action_init+0x1f8/0x2c0
 tcf_exts_validate_ex+0x175/0x190
 fl_change+0x537/0x1120 [cls_flower]</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21858 | geneve: Fix use-after-free in geneve_find_dev().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21858</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

geneve: Fix use-after-free in geneve_find_dev().

syzkaller reported a use-after-free in geneve_find_dev() [0]
without repro.

geneve_configure() links struct geneve_dev.next to
net_generic(net, geneve_net_id)-&gt;geneve_list.

The net here could differ from dev_net(dev) if IFLA_NET_NS_PID,
IFLA_NET_NS_FD, or IFLA_TARGET_NETNSID is set.

When dev_net(dev) is dismantled, geneve_exit_batch_rtnl() finally
calls unregister_netdevice_queue() for each dev in the netns,
and later the dev is freed.

However, its geneve_dev.next is still linked to the backend UDP
socket netns.

Then, use-after-free will occur when another geneve dev is created
in the netns.

Let's call geneve_dellink() instead in geneve_destroy_tunnels().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in geneve_find_dev drivers/net/geneve.c:1295 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in geneve_configure+0x234/0x858 drivers/net/geneve.c:1343
Read of size 2 at addr ffff000054d6ee24 by task syz.1.4029/13441

CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 13441 Comm: syz.1.4029 Not tainted 6.13.0-g0ad9617c78ac #24 dc35ca22c79fb82e8e7bc5c9c9adafea898b1e3d
Hardware name: linux,dummy-virt (DT)
Call trace:
 show_stack+0x38/0x50 arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:466 (C)
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:94 [inline]
 dump_stack_lvl+0xbc/0x108 lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_address_description mm/kasan/report.c:378 [inline]
 print_report+0x16c/0x6f0 mm/kasan/report.c:489
 kasan_report+0xc0/0x120 mm/kasan/report.c:602
 __asan_report_load2_noabort+0x20/0x30 mm/kasan/report_generic.c:379
 geneve_find_dev drivers/net/geneve.c:1295 [inline]
 geneve_configure+0x234/0x858 drivers/net/geneve.c:1343
 geneve_newlink+0xb8/0x128 drivers/net/geneve.c:1634
 rtnl_newlink_create+0x23c/0x868 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3795
 __rtnl_newlink net/core/rtnetlink.c:3906 [inline]
 rtnl_newlink+0x1054/0x1630 net/core/rtnetlink.c:4021
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x61c/0x918 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6911
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x1dc/0x398 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2543
 rtnetlink_rcv+0x34/0x50 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6938
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1322 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x618/0x838 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1348
 netlink_sendmsg+0x5fc/0x8b0 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1892
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:713 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg net/socket.c:728 [inline]
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x410/0x6f8 net/socket.c:2568
 ___sys_sendmsg+0x178/0x1d8 net/socket.c:2622
 __sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2654 [inline]
 __do_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2659 [inline]
 __se_sys_sendmsg net/socket.c:2657 [inline]
 __arm64_sys_sendmsg+0x12c/0x1c8 net/socket.c:2657
 __invoke_syscall arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:35 [inline]
 invoke_syscall+0x90/0x278 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:49
 el0_svc_common+0x13c/0x250 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:132
 do_el0_svc+0x54/0x70 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:151
 el0_svc+0x4c/0xa8 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:744
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x78/0x108 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:762
 el0t_64_sync+0x198/0x1a0 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:600

Allocated by task 13247:
 kasan_save_stack mm/kasan/common.c:47 [inline]
 kasan_save_track+0x30/0x68 mm/kasan/common.c:68
 kasan_save_alloc_info+0x44/0x58 mm/kasan/generic.c:568
 poison_kmalloc_redzone mm/kasan/common.c:377 [inline]
 __kasan_kmalloc+0x84/0xa0 mm/kasan/common.c:394
 kasan_kmalloc include/linux/kasan.h:260 [inline]
 __do_kmalloc_node mm/slub.c:4298 [inline]
 __kmalloc_node_noprof+0x2a0/0x560 mm/slub.c:4304
 __kvmalloc_node_noprof+0x9c/0x230 mm/util.c:645
 alloc_netdev_mqs+0xb8/0x11a0 net/core/dev.c:11470
 rtnl_create_link+0x2b8/0xb50 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3604
 rtnl_newlink_create+0x19c/0x868 net/core/rtnetlink.c:3780
 __rtnl_newlink net/core/rtnetlink.c:3906 [inline]
 rtnl_newlink+0x1054/0x1630 net/core/rtnetlink.c:4021
 rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x61c/0x918 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6911
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x1dc/0x398 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2543
 rtnetlink_rcv+0x34/0x50 net/core/rtnetlink.c:6938
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_n
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21859 | USB: gadget: f_midi: f_midi_complete to call queue_work</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21859</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

USB: gadget: f_midi: f_midi_complete to call queue_work

When using USB MIDI, a lock is attempted to be acquired twice through a
re-entrant call to f_midi_transmit, causing a deadlock.

Fix it by using queue_work() to schedule the inner f_midi_transmit() via
a high priority work queue from the completion handler.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21860 | mm/zswap: fix inconsistency when zswap_store_page() fails</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21860</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/zswap: fix inconsistency when zswap_store_page() fails

Commit b7c0ccdfbafd ("mm: zswap: support large folios in zswap_store()")
skips charging any zswap entries when it failed to zswap the entire folio.

However, when some base pages are zswapped but it failed to zswap the
entire folio, the zswap operation is rolled back.  When freeing zswap
entries for those pages, zswap_entry_free() uncharges the zswap entries
that were not previously charged, causing zswap charging to become
inconsistent.

This inconsistency triggers two warnings with following steps:
  # On a machine with 64GiB of RAM and 36GiB of zswap
  $ stress-ng --bigheap 2 # wait until the OOM-killer kills stress-ng
  $ sudo reboot

  The two warnings are:
    in mm/memcontrol.c:163, function obj_cgroup_release():
      WARN_ON_ONCE(nr_bytes &amp; (PAGE_SIZE - 1));

    in mm/page_counter.c:60, function page_counter_cancel():
      if (WARN_ONCE(new &lt; 0, "page_counter underflow: %ld nr_pages=%lu\n",
	  new, nr_pages))

zswap_stored_pages also becomes inconsistent in the same way.

As suggested by Kanchana, increment zswap_stored_pages and charge zswap
entries within zswap_store_page() when it succeeds.  This way,
zswap_entry_free() will decrement the counter and uncharge the entries
when it failed to zswap the entire folio.

While this could potentially be optimized by batching objcg charging and
incrementing the counter, let's focus on fixing the bug this time and
leave the optimization for later after some evaluation.

After resolving the inconsistency, the warnings disappear.

[42.hyeyoo@gmail.com: refactor zswap_store_page()]
  Link: https://lkml.kernel.org/r/20250131082037.2426-1-42.hyeyoo@gmail.com</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21861 | mm/migrate_device: don&amp;#x27;t add folio to be freed to LRU in migrate_device_finalize()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21861</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/migrate_device: don't add folio to be freed to LRU in migrate_device_finalize()

If migration succeeded, we called
folio_migrate_flags()-&gt;mem_cgroup_migrate() to migrate the memcg from the
old to the new folio.  This will set memcg_data of the old folio to 0.

Similarly, if migration failed, memcg_data of the dst folio is left unset.

If we call folio_putback_lru() on such folios (memcg_data == 0), we will
add the folio to be freed to the LRU, making memcg code unhappy.  Running
the hmm selftests:

  # ./hmm-tests
  ...
  #  RUN           hmm.hmm_device_private.migrate ...
  [  102.078007][T14893] page: refcount:1 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000000000000 index:0x7ff27d200 pfn:0x13cc00
  [  102.079974][T14893] anon flags: 0x17ff00000020018(uptodate|dirty|swapbacked|node=0|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x7ff)
  [  102.082037][T14893] raw: 017ff00000020018 dead000000000100 dead000000000122 ffff8881353896c9
  [  102.083687][T14893] raw: 00000007ff27d200 0000000000000000 00000001ffffffff 0000000000000000
  [  102.085331][T14893] page dumped because: VM_WARN_ON_ONCE_FOLIO(!memcg &amp;&amp; !mem_cgroup_disabled())
  [  102.087230][T14893] ------------[ cut here ]------------
  [  102.088279][T14893] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 14893 at ./include/linux/memcontrol.h:726 folio_lruvec_lock_irqsave+0x10e/0x170
  [  102.090478][T14893] Modules linked in:
  [  102.091244][T14893] CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 14893 Comm: hmm-tests Not tainted 6.13.0-09623-g6c216bc522fd #151
  [  102.093089][T14893] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.16.3-2.fc40 04/01/2014
  [  102.094848][T14893] RIP: 0010:folio_lruvec_lock_irqsave+0x10e/0x170
  [  102.096104][T14893] Code: ...
  [  102.099908][T14893] RSP: 0018:ffffc900236c37b0 EFLAGS: 00010293
  [  102.101152][T14893] RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffea0004f30000 RCX: ffffffff8183f426
  [  102.102684][T14893] RDX: ffff8881063cb880 RSI: ffffffff81b8117f RDI: ffff8881063cb880
  [  102.104227][T14893] RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000005 R09: 0000000000000000
  [  102.105757][T14893] R10: 0000000000000001 R11: 0000000000000002 R12: ffffc900236c37d8
  [  102.107296][T14893] R13: ffff888277a2bcb0 R14: 000000000000001f R15: 0000000000000000
  [  102.108830][T14893] FS:  00007ff27dbdd740(0000) GS:ffff888277a00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  [  102.110643][T14893] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  [  102.111924][T14893] CR2: 00007ff27d400000 CR3: 000000010866e000 CR4: 0000000000750ef0
  [  102.113478][T14893] PKRU: 55555554
  [  102.114172][T14893] Call Trace:
  [  102.114805][T14893]  
  [  102.115397][T14893]  ? folio_lruvec_lock_irqsave+0x10e/0x170
  [  102.116547][T14893]  ? __warn.cold+0x110/0x210
  [  102.117461][T14893]  ? folio_lruvec_lock_irqsave+0x10e/0x170
  [  102.118667][T14893]  ? report_bug+0x1b9/0x320
  [  102.119571][T14893]  ? handle_bug+0x54/0x90
  [  102.120494][T14893]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x17/0x50
  [  102.121433][T14893]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
  [  102.122435][T14893]  ? __wake_up_klogd.part.0+0x76/0xd0
  [  102.123506][T14893]  ? dump_page+0x4f/0x60
  [  102.124352][T14893]  ? folio_lruvec_lock_irqsave+0x10e/0x170
  [  102.125500][T14893]  folio_batch_move_lru+0xd4/0x200
  [  102.126577][T14893]  ? __pfx_lru_add+0x10/0x10
  [  102.127505][T14893]  __folio_batch_add_and_move+0x391/0x720
  [  102.128633][T14893]  ? __pfx_lru_add+0x10/0x10
  [  102.129550][T14893]  folio_putback_lru+0x16/0x80
  [  102.130564][T14893]  migrate_device_finalize+0x9b/0x530
  [  102.131640][T14893]  dmirror_migrate_to_device.constprop.0+0x7c5/0xad0
  [  102.133047][T14893]  dmirror_fops_unlocked_ioctl+0x89b/0xc80

Likely, nothing else goes wrong: putting the last folio reference will
remove the folio from the LRU again.  So besides memcg complaining, adding
the folio to be freed to the LRU is just an unnecessary step.

The new flow resembles what we have in migrate_folio_move(): add the dst
to the lru, rem
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21862 | drop_monitor: fix incorrect initialization order</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21862</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drop_monitor: fix incorrect initialization order

Syzkaller reports the following bug:

BUG: spinlock bad magic on CPU#1, syz-executor.0/7995
 lock: 0xffff88805303f3e0, .magic: 00000000, .owner: /-1, .owner_cpu: 0
CPU: 1 PID: 7995 Comm: syz-executor.0 Tainted: G            E     5.10.209+ #1
Hardware name: VMware, Inc. VMware Virtual Platform/440BX Desktop Reference Platform, BIOS 6.00 11/12/2020
Call Trace:
 __dump_stack lib/dump_stack.c:77 [inline]
 dump_stack+0x119/0x179 lib/dump_stack.c:118
 debug_spin_lock_before kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:83 [inline]
 do_raw_spin_lock+0x1f6/0x270 kernel/locking/spinlock_debug.c:112
 __raw_spin_lock_irqsave include/linux/spinlock_api_smp.h:117 [inline]
 _raw_spin_lock_irqsave+0x50/0x70 kernel/locking/spinlock.c:159
 reset_per_cpu_data+0xe6/0x240 [drop_monitor]
 net_dm_cmd_trace+0x43d/0x17a0 [drop_monitor]
 genl_family_rcv_msg_doit+0x22f/0x330 net/netlink/genetlink.c:739
 genl_family_rcv_msg net/netlink/genetlink.c:783 [inline]
 genl_rcv_msg+0x341/0x5a0 net/netlink/genetlink.c:800
 netlink_rcv_skb+0x14d/0x440 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:2497
 genl_rcv+0x29/0x40 net/netlink/genetlink.c:811
 netlink_unicast_kernel net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1322 [inline]
 netlink_unicast+0x54b/0x800 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1348
 netlink_sendmsg+0x914/0xe00 net/netlink/af_netlink.c:1916
 sock_sendmsg_nosec net/socket.c:651 [inline]
 __sock_sendmsg+0x157/0x190 net/socket.c:663
 ____sys_sendmsg+0x712/0x870 net/socket.c:2378
 ___sys_sendmsg+0xf8/0x170 net/socket.c:2432
 __sys_sendmsg+0xea/0x1b0 net/socket.c:2461
 do_syscall_64+0x30/0x40 arch/x86/entry/common.c:46
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x62/0xc7
RIP: 0033:0x7f3f9815aee9
Code: ff ff c3 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00 00 0f 1f 40 00 48 89 f8 48 89 f7 48 89 d6 48 89 ca 4d 89 c2 4d 89 c8 4c 8b 4c 24 08 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 3d 01 f0 ff ff 73 01 c3 48 c7 c1 b0 ff ff ff f7 d8 64 89 01 48
RSP: 002b:00007f3f972bf0c8 EFLAGS: 00000246 ORIG_RAX: 000000000000002e
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 00007f3f9826d050 RCX: 00007f3f9815aee9
RDX: 0000000020000000 RSI: 0000000020001300 RDI: 0000000000000007
RBP: 00007f3f981b63bd R08: 0000000000000000 R09: 0000000000000000
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000246 R12: 0000000000000000
R13: 000000000000006e R14: 00007f3f9826d050 R15: 00007ffe01ee6768

If drop_monitor is built as a kernel module, syzkaller may have time
to send a netlink NET_DM_CMD_START message during the module loading.
This will call the net_dm_monitor_start() function that uses
a spinlock that has not yet been initialized.

To fix this, let's place resource initialization above the registration
of a generic netlink family.

Found by InfoTeCS on behalf of Linux Verification Center
(linuxtesting.org) with Syzkaller.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21863 | io_uring: prevent opcode speculation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21863</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

io_uring: prevent opcode speculation

sqe-&gt;opcode is used for different tables, make sure we santitise it
against speculations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21864 | tcp: drop secpath at the same time as we currently drop dst</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21864</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tcp: drop secpath at the same time as we currently drop dst

Xiumei reported hitting the WARN in xfrm6_tunnel_net_exit while
running tests that boil down to:
 - create a pair of netns
 - run a basic TCP test over ipcomp6
 - delete the pair of netns

The xfrm_state found on spi_byaddr was not deleted at the time we
delete the netns, because we still have a reference on it. This
lingering reference comes from a secpath (which holds a ref on the
xfrm_state), which is still attached to an skb. This skb is not
leaked, it ends up on sk_receive_queue and then gets defer-free'd by
skb_attempt_defer_free.

The problem happens when we defer freeing an skb (push it on one CPU's
defer_list), and don't flush that list before the netns is deleted. In
that case, we still have a reference on the xfrm_state that we don't
expect at this point.

We already drop the skb's dst in the TCP receive path when it's no
longer needed, so let's also drop the secpath. At this point,
tcp_filter has already called into the LSM hooks that may require the
secpath, so it should not be needed anymore. However, in some of those
places, the MPTCP extension has just been attached to the skb, so we
cannot simply drop all extensions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21865 | gtp: Suppress list corruption splat in gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21865</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

gtp: Suppress list corruption splat in gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl().

Brad Spengler reported the list_del() corruption splat in
gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl(). [0]

Commit eb28fd76c0a0 ("gtp: Destroy device along with udp socket's netns
dismantle.") added the for_each_netdev() loop in gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl()
to destroy devices in each netns as done in geneve and ip tunnels.

However, this could trigger -&gt;dellink() twice for the same device during
-&gt;exit_batch_rtnl().

Say we have two netns A &amp; B and gtp device B that resides in netns B but
whose UDP socket is in netns A.

  1. cleanup_net() processes netns A and then B.

  2. gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl() finds the device B while iterating
     netns A's gn-&gt;gtp_dev_list and calls -&gt;dellink().

  [ device B is not yet unlinked from netns B
    as unregister_netdevice_many() has not been called. ]

  3. gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl() finds the device B while iterating
     netns B's for_each_netdev() and calls -&gt;dellink().

gtp_dellink() cleans up the device's hash table, unlinks the dev from
gn-&gt;gtp_dev_list, and calls unregister_netdevice_queue().

Basically, calling gtp_dellink() multiple times is fine unless
CONFIG_DEBUG_LIST is enabled.

Let's remove for_each_netdev() in gtp_net_exit_batch_rtnl() and
delegate the destruction to default_device_exit_batch() as done
in bareudp.

[0]:
list_del corruption, ffff8880aaa62c00-&gt;next (autoslab_size_M_dev_P_net_core_dev_11127_8_1328_8_S_4096_A_64_n_139+0xc00/0x1000 [slab object]) is LIST_POISON1 (ffffffffffffff02) (prev is 0xffffffffffffff04)
kernel BUG at lib/list_debug.c:58!
Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN
CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 1804 Comm: kworker/u8:7 Tainted: G                T   6.12.13-grsec-full-20250211091339 #1
Tainted: [T]=RANDSTRUCT
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
Workqueue: netns cleanup_net
RIP: 0010:[] __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x141/0x200 lib/list_debug.c:58
Code: c2 76 91 31 c0 e8 9f b1 f7 fc 0f 0b 4d 89 f0 48 c7 c1 02 ff ff ff 48 89 ea 48 89 ee 48 c7 c7 e0 c2 76 91 31 c0 e8 7f b1 f7 fc &lt;0f&gt; 0b 4d 89 e8 48 c7 c1 04 ff ff ff 48 89 ea 48 89 ee 48 c7 c7 60
RSP: 0018:fffffe8040b4fbd0 EFLAGS: 00010283
RAX: 00000000000000cc RBX: dffffc0000000000 RCX: ffffffff818c4054
RDX: ffffffff84947381 RSI: ffffffff818d1512 RDI: 0000000000000000
RBP: ffff8880aaa62c00 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: fffffbd008169f32
R10: fffffe8040b4f997 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: a1988d84f24943e4
R13: ffffffffffffff02 R14: ffffffffffffff04 R15: ffff8880aaa62c08
RBX: kasan shadow of 0x0
RCX: __wake_up_klogd.part.0+0x74/0xe0 kernel/printk/printk.c:4554
RDX: __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x141/0x200 lib/list_debug.c:58
RSI: vprintk+0x72/0x100 kernel/printk/printk_safe.c:71
RBP: autoslab_size_M_dev_P_net_core_dev_11127_8_1328_8_S_4096_A_64_n_139+0xc00/0x1000 [slab object]
RSP: process kstack fffffe8040b4fbd0+0x7bd0/0x8000 [kworker/u8:7+netns 1804 ]
R09: kasan shadow of process kstack fffffe8040b4f990+0x7990/0x8000 [kworker/u8:7+netns 1804 ]
R10: process kstack fffffe8040b4f997+0x7997/0x8000 [kworker/u8:7+netns 1804 ]
R15: autoslab_size_M_dev_P_net_core_dev_11127_8_1328_8_S_4096_A_64_n_139+0xc08/0x1000 [slab object]
FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff888116000000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 0000748f5372c000 CR3: 0000000015408000 CR4: 00000000003406f0 shadow CR4: 00000000003406f0
Stack:
 0000000000000000 ffffffff8a0c35e7 ffffffff8a0c3603 ffff8880aaa62c00
 ffff8880aaa62c00 0000000000000004 ffff88811145311c 0000000000000005
 0000000000000001 ffff8880aaa62000 fffffe8040b4fd40 ffffffff8a0c360d
Call Trace:
 
 [] __list_del_entry_valid include/linux/list.h:131 [inline] fffffe8040b4fc28
 [] __list_del_entry include/linux/list.h:248 [inline] fffffe8040b4fc28
 [] list_del include/linux/list.h:262 [inl
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21866 | powerpc/code-patching: Fix KASAN hit by not flagging text patching area as VM_ALLOC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21866</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

powerpc/code-patching: Fix KASAN hit by not flagging text patching area as VM_ALLOC

Erhard reported the following KASAN hit while booting his PowerMac G4
with a KASAN-enabled kernel 6.13-rc6:

  BUG: KASAN: vmalloc-out-of-bounds in copy_to_kernel_nofault+0xd8/0x1c8
  Write of size 8 at addr f1000000 by task chronyd/1293

  CPU: 0 UID: 123 PID: 1293 Comm: chronyd Tainted: G        W          6.13.0-rc6-PMacG4 #2
  Tainted: [W]=WARN
  Hardware name: PowerMac3,6 7455 0x80010303 PowerMac
  Call Trace:
  [c2437590] [c1631a84] dump_stack_lvl+0x70/0x8c (unreliable)
  [c24375b0] [c0504998] print_report+0xdc/0x504
  [c2437610] [c050475c] kasan_report+0xf8/0x108
  [c2437690] [c0505a3c] kasan_check_range+0x24/0x18c
  [c24376a0] [c03fb5e4] copy_to_kernel_nofault+0xd8/0x1c8
  [c24376c0] [c004c014] patch_instructions+0x15c/0x16c
  [c2437710] [c00731a8] bpf_arch_text_copy+0x60/0x7c
  [c2437730] [c0281168] bpf_jit_binary_pack_finalize+0x50/0xac
  [c2437750] [c0073cf4] bpf_int_jit_compile+0xb30/0xdec
  [c2437880] [c0280394] bpf_prog_select_runtime+0x15c/0x478
  [c24378d0] [c1263428] bpf_prepare_filter+0xbf8/0xc14
  [c2437990] [c12677ec] bpf_prog_create_from_user+0x258/0x2b4
  [c24379d0] [c027111c] do_seccomp+0x3dc/0x1890
  [c2437ac0] [c001d8e0] system_call_exception+0x2dc/0x420
  [c2437f30] [c00281ac] ret_from_syscall+0x0/0x2c
  --- interrupt: c00 at 0x5a1274
  NIP:  005a1274 LR: 006a3b3c CTR: 005296c8
  REGS: c2437f40 TRAP: 0c00   Tainted: G        W           (6.13.0-rc6-PMacG4)
  MSR:  0200f932   CR: 24004422  XER: 00000000

  GPR00: 00000166 af8f3fa0 a7ee3540 00000001 00000000 013b6500 005a5858 0200f932
  GPR08: 00000000 00001fe9 013d5fc8 005296c8 2822244c 00b2fcd8 00000000 af8f4b57
  GPR16: 00000000 00000001 00000000 00000000 00000000 00000001 00000000 00000002
  GPR24: 00afdbb0 00000000 00000000 00000000 006e0004 013ce060 006e7c1c 00000001
  NIP [005a1274] 0x5a1274
  LR [006a3b3c] 0x6a3b3c
  --- interrupt: c00

  The buggy address belongs to the virtual mapping at
   [f1000000, f1002000) created by:
   text_area_cpu_up+0x20/0x190

  The buggy address belongs to the physical page:
  page: refcount:1 mapcount:0 mapping:00000000 index:0x0 pfn:0x76e30
  flags: 0x80000000(zone=2)
  raw: 80000000 00000000 00000122 00000000 00000000 00000000 ffffffff 00000001
  raw: 00000000
  page dumped because: kasan: bad access detected

  Memory state around the buggy address:
   f0ffff00: 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00
   f0ffff80: 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00
  &gt;f1000000: f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8
             ^
   f1000080: f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8
   f1000100: f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8 f8
  ==================================================================

f8 corresponds to KASAN_VMALLOC_INVALID which means the area is not
initialised hence not supposed to be used yet.

Powerpc text patching infrastructure allocates a virtual memory area
using get_vm_area() and flags it as VM_ALLOC. But that flag is meant
to be used for vmalloc() and vmalloc() allocated memory is not
supposed to be used before a call to __vmalloc_node_range() which is
never called for that area.

That went undetected until commit e4137f08816b ("mm, kasan, kmsan:
instrument copy_from/to_kernel_nofault")

The area allocated by text_area_cpu_up() is not vmalloc memory, it is
mapped directly on demand when needed by map_kernel_page(). There is
no VM flag corresponding to such usage, so just pass no flag. That way
the area will be unpoisonned and usable immediately.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:51:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13446 | Workreap &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13446</link><description>The Workreap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.5. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to (1) performing a social auto-login or (2) updating their profile details (e.g. password). This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to (1) login as an arbitrary user if their email address is known or (2) change an arbitrary user's password, including administrators, and leverage that to gain access to their account. NOTE: This vulnerability was partially fixed in version 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 09:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13430 | Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder &amp;lt;= 1.9.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Private Post Disclosure in pagelayer_builder_posts_shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13430</link><description>The Page Builder: Pagelayer – Drag and Drop website builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.8 via the 'pagelayer_builder_posts_shortcode' function due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 08:30:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58087 | ksmbd: fix racy issue from session lookup and expire</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58087</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ksmbd: fix racy issue from session lookup and expire

Increment the session reference count within the lock for lookup to avoid
racy issue with session expire.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12589 | Finale Lite – Sales Countdown Timer &amp;amp; Discount for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.19.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via Countdown Timer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12589</link><description>The Finale Lite – Sales Countdown Timer &amp; Discount for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via the countdown timer in all versions up to, and including, 2.19.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13838 | Uncanny Automator – Easy Automation, Integration, Webhooks &amp;amp; Workflow Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery via Webhook</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13838</link><description>The Uncanny Automator – Easy Automation, Integration, Webhooks &amp; Workflow Builder Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.2 via the 'call_webhook' method of the Automator_Send_Webhook class This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 07:21:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13498 | NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more &amp;lt;= 8.8.1 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13498</link><description>The NEX-Forms – Ultimate Form Builder – Contact forms and much more plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 8.8.1 via file uploads due to insufficient directory listing prevention and lack of randomization of file names. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data including files uploaded via a form.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 05:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24912 | hostapd fails to process crafted RADIUS packets properly. When hostapd authenticates wi-fi devices with RADIUS authentication, an attacker i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24912</link><description>hostapd fails to process crafted RADIUS packets properly. When hostapd authenticates wi-fi devices with RADIUS authentication, an attacker in the position between the hostapd and the RADIUS server may inject crafted RADIUS packets and force RADIUS authentications to fail.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 04:51:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1508 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt;= 2.1.13 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Post Content Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1508</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the download_data action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.13. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to download all of a site's post content when WooCommerce is installed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2076 | binlayerpress &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2076</link><description>The binlayerpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2077 | Simple Amazon Affiliate &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2077</link><description>The Simple Amazon Affiliate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'msg' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2078 | BlogBuzzTime-for-wp &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2078</link><description>The BlogBuzzTime for WP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2205 | GDPR Cookie Compliance &amp;lt;= 4.15.6 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2205</link><description>The GDPR Cookie Compliance – Cookie Banner, Cookie Consent, Cookie Notice – CCPA, DSGVO, RGPD plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 4.15.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 03:32:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2220 | Odyssey CMS reCAPTCHA odyssey_contact_form.php key management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2220</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Odyssey CMS up to 10.34. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /modules/odyssey_contact_form/odyssey_contact_form.php of the component reCAPTCHA Handler. The manipulation of the argument g-recaptcha-response leads to key management error. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 02:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2218 | LoveCards LoveCardsV2 Setting other access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2218</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in LoveCards LoveCardsV2 up to 2.3.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/system/other of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2219 | LoveCards LoveCardsV2 image unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LoveCards LoveCardsV2 up to 2.3.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /api/upload/image. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2216 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System SaveCrash.ashx UploadCrash unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2216</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 1.3. Affected by this issue is the function UploadCrash of the file /crash/log/SaveCrash.ashx. The manipulation of the argument file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2217 | zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System getAdyData.ashx ProcessRequest sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2217</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in zzskzy Warehouse Refinement Management System 1.3. This affects the function ProcessRequest of the file /getAdyData.ashx. The manipulation of the argument showid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>