<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 19:09:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-1591 | Privilege Management for Windows &amp;lt; 24.1 Information Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1591</link><description>Prior to version 24.1, a local authenticated attacker can view Sysvol when Privilege Management for Windows is configured to use a GPO policy. This allows them to view the policy and potentially find configuration issues.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 19:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21165 | In DevmemIntUnmapPMR of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible arbitrary
    code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21165</link><description>In DevmemIntUnmapPMR of devicemem_server.c, there is a possible arbitrary
    code execution due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation
    of privilege in the kernel with no additional execution privileges needed.
    User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40085 | In convertSubgraphFromHAL of ShimConverter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40085</link><description>In convertSubgraphFromHAL of ShimConverter.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0015 | In convertToComponentName of DreamService.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary protected activities due to intent redirection. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0015</link><description>In convertToComponentName of DreamService.java, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary protected activities due to intent redirection. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21915 | Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform Elevated Privileges Vulnerability Through Web Service Functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21915</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in Rockwell Automation FactoryTalk® Service Platform (FTSP). If exploited, a malicious user with basic user group privileges could potentially sign into the software and receive FTSP Administrator Group privileges. A threat actor could potentially read and modify sensitive data, delete data and render the FTSP system unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23591 | ThinkSystem SR670V2 servers manufactured from approximately June 2021 to July 2023 were left in Manufacturing Mode which could allow 

an at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23591</link><description>ThinkSystem SR670V2 servers manufactured from approximately June 2021 to July 2023 were left in Manufacturing Mode which could allow 

an attacker with privileged logical access to the host or physical access to server internals to modify or disable Intel Boot Guard firmware integrity, SPS security, and other SPS configuration setting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1342 | Openshift: existing cross-site request forgery protection insufficient for websocket creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1342</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenShift. The existing Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) protections in place do not properly protect GET requests, allowing for the creation of WebSockets via CSRF.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25320 | Tongda OA v2017 and up to v11.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the $AFF_ID parameter at /affair/delete.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25320</link><description>Tongda OA v2017 and up to v11.9 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the $AFF_ID parameter at /affair/delete.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 14:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21775 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21775</link><description>Zoho ManageEngine Exchange Reporter Plus versions 5714 and below are vulnerable to the Authenticated SQL injection in report exporting feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 14:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22426 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 5.3.x contains an OS Command injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote
attacker could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22426</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 5.3.x contains an OS Command injection vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote
attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to execute arbitrary operating system commands, which will get executed in the context of the root user, resulting in a complete system compromise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22425 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 5.3.x contains a brute force/dictionary attack vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22425</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 5.3.x contains a brute force/dictionary attack vulnerability. An unauthenticated remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to launch a brute force attack or a dictionary attack against the RecoverPoint login form. This allows attackers to brute-force the password of valid users in an automated manner.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 11:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45860 | In Hazelcast Platform through 5.3.4, a security issue exists within the SQL mapping for the CSV File Source connector. This issue arises fro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45860</link><description>In Hazelcast Platform through 5.3.4, a security issue exists within the SQL mapping for the CSV File Source connector. This issue arises from inadequate permission checking, which could enable unauthorized clients to access data from files stored on a member's filesystem.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 09:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25466 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in React Native Document Picker before v.9.1.1 and fixed in v.9.1.1 allows a local attacker to execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25466</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in React Native Document Picker before v.9.1.1 and fixed in v.9.1.1 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the Android library component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 08:55:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51931 | An issue in alanclarke URLite v.3.1.0 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via a crafted payload to the parsing function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51931</link><description>An issue in alanclarke URLite v.3.1.0 allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) via a crafted payload to the parsing function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 08:41:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22854 | DOM-based HTML injection vulnerability in the main page of Darktrace Threat Visualizer version 6.1.27 (bundle version 61050) and before has ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22854</link><description>DOM-based HTML injection vulnerability in the main page of Darktrace Threat Visualizer version 6.1.27 (bundle version 61050) and before has been identified. A URL, crafted by a remote attacker and visited by an authenticated user, allows open redirect and potential credential stealing using an injected HTML form.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 08:41:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24377 | An issue in idocv v.14.1.3_20231228 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24377</link><description>An issue in idocv v.14.1.3_20231228 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 08:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49508 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in YetiForceCompany YetiForceCRM versions 6.4.0 and before allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49508</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in YetiForceCompany YetiForceCRM versions 6.4.0 and before allows a remote authenticated attacker to obtain sensitive information via the license parameter in the LibraryLicense.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 08:14:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6451 | Publicly Known Cryptographic Machine Key In Procura Portal Application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6451</link><description>Publicly known cryptographic machine key in AlayaCare's Procura Portal before 9.0.1.2 allows attackers to forge their own authentication cookies and bypass the application's authentication mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 04:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25413 | A XSLT Server Side injection vulnerability in the Import Jobs function of FireBear Improved Import And Export v3.8.6 allows attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25413</link><description>A XSLT Server Side injection vulnerability in the Import Jobs function of FireBear Improved Import And Export v3.8.6 allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands via a crafted XSLT file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25414 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /admin/upgrade of CSZ CMS v1.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25414</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in /admin/upgrade of CSZ CMS v1.3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted Zip file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25415 | A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in /admin/define_language.php of CE Phoenix v1.0.8.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary PHP ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25415</link><description>A remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability in /admin/define_language.php of CE Phoenix v1.0.8.20 allows attackers to execute arbitrary PHP code via injecting a crafted payload into the file english.php.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40093 | In multiple files, there is a possible way that trimmed content could be included in PDF output due to a logic error in the code. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40093</link><description>In multiple files, there is a possible way that trimmed content could be included in PDF output due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40122 | In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view other user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40122</link><description>In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view other user's images due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0014 | In startInstall of UpdateFetcher.java, there is a possible way to trigger a malicious config update due to a logic error. This could lead to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0014</link><description>In startInstall of UpdateFetcher.java, there is a possible way to trigger a malicious config update due to a logic error. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0029 | In multiple files, there is a possible way to capture the device screen when disallowed by device policy due to a logic error in the code. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0029</link><description>In multiple files, there is a possible way to capture the device screen when disallowed by device policy due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0030 | In btif_to_bta_response of btif_gatt_util.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0030</link><description>In btif_to_bta_response of btif_gatt_util.cc, there is a possible out of bounds read due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0031 | In attp_build_read_by_type_value_cmd of att_protocol.cc , there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0031</link><description>In attp_build_read_by_type_value_cmd of att_protocol.cc , there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0032 | In queryChildDocuments of FileSystemProvider.java, there is a possible way to request access to directories that should be hidden due to imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0032</link><description>In queryChildDocuments of FileSystemProvider.java, there is a possible way to request access to directories that should be hidden due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0033 | In multiple functions of ashmem-dev.cpp, there is a possible missing seal due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0033</link><description>In multiple functions of ashmem-dev.cpp, there is a possible missing seal due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0034 | In BackgroundLaunchProcessController, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activity from the background due to BAL Bypass. This could...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0034</link><description>In BackgroundLaunchProcessController, there is a possible way to launch arbitrary activity from the background due to BAL Bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0035 | In onNullBinding of TileLifecycleManager.java, there is a possible way to launch an activity from the background due to a missing null check...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0035</link><description>In onNullBinding of TileLifecycleManager.java, there is a possible way to launch an activity from the background due to a missing null check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0036 | In startNextMatchingActivity of ActivityTaskManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass the restrictions on starting activities f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0036</link><description>In startNextMatchingActivity of ActivityTaskManagerService.java, there is a possible way to bypass the restrictions on starting activities from the background due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0037 | In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view images belonging to a different user due to a missing permission c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0037</link><description>In applyCustomDescription of SaveUi.java, there is a possible way to view images belonging to a different user due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with User execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0038 | In injectInputEventToInputFilter of AccessibilityManagerService.java, there is a possible arbitrary input event injection due to a missing p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0038</link><description>In injectInputEventToInputFilter of AccessibilityManagerService.java, there is a possible arbitrary input event injection due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0040 | In setParameter of MtpPacket.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0040</link><description>In setParameter of MtpPacket.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0041 | In removePersistentDot of SystemStatusAnimationSchedulerImpl.kt, there is a possible race condition due to a logic error in the code. This c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0041</link><description>In removePersistentDot of SystemStatusAnimationSchedulerImpl.kt, there is a possible race condition due to a logic error in the code. This could lead to local escalation of privilege that fails to remove the persistent dot with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:54:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23674 | The Online-Ausweis-Funktion eID scheme in the German National Identity card through 2024-02-15 allows authentication bypass by spoofing. A m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23674</link><description>The Online-Ausweis-Funktion eID scheme in the German National Identity card through 2024-02-15 allows authentication bypass by spoofing. A man-in-the-middle attacker can assume a victim's identify for access to government, medical, and financial resources, and can also extract personal data from the card, aka the "sPACE (Spoofing Password Authenticated Connection Establishment)" issue. This occurs because of a combination of factors, such as insecure PIN entry (for basic readers) and eid:// deeplinking. The victim must be using a modified eID kernel, which may occur if the victim is tricked into installing a fake version of an official app. NOTE: the BSI position is "ensuring a secure operational environment at the client side is an obligation of the ID card owner."</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40100 | In discovery_thread of Dns64Configuration.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40100</link><description>In discovery_thread of Dns64Configuration.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40104 | In ca-certificates, there is a possible way to read encrypted TLS data due to untrusted cryptographic certificates. This could lead to remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40104</link><description>In ca-certificates, there is a possible way to read encrypted TLS data due to untrusted cryptographic certificates. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40105 | In backupAgentCreated of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible way to leak sensitive data due to a missing permission check. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40105</link><description>In backupAgentCreated of ActivityManagerService.java, there is a possible way to leak sensitive data due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40106 | In sanitizeSbn of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to launch an activity from the background due to BAL Bypass. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40106</link><description>In sanitizeSbn of NotificationManagerService.java, there is a possible way to launch an activity from the background due to BAL Bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40107 | In ARTPWriter of ARTPWriter.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40107</link><description>In ARTPWriter of ARTPWriter.cpp, there is a possible use after free due to uninitialized data. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40109 | In createFromParcel of UsbConfiguration.java, there is a possible background activity launch (BAL) due to a permissions bypass. This could l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40109</link><description>In createFromParcel of UsbConfiguration.java, there is a possible background activity launch (BAL) due to a permissions bypass. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40110 | In multiple functions of MtpPacket.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40110</link><description>In multiple functions of MtpPacket.cpp, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a heap buffer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40111 | In setMediaButtonReceiver of MediaSessionRecord.java, there is a possible way to send a pending intent on behalf of system_server due to a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40111</link><description>In setMediaButtonReceiver of MediaSessionRecord.java, there is a possible way to send a pending intent on behalf of system_server due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40112 | In ippSetValueTag of ipp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information discl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40112</link><description>In ippSetValueTag of ipp.c, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure of past print jobs or other print-related information, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40113 | In multiple locations, there is a possible way for apps to access cross-user message data due to a missing permission check. This could lead...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40113</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible way for apps to access cross-user message data due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40114 | In multiple functions of MtpFfsHandle.cpp , there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40114</link><description>In multiple functions of MtpFfsHandle.cpp , there is a possible out of bounds write due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40115 | In readLogs of StatsService.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40115</link><description>In readLogs of StatsService.cpp, there is a possible memory corruption due to a use after free. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40124 | In multiple locations, there is a possible cross-user read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure of phot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40124</link><description>In multiple locations, there is a possible cross-user read due to a confused deputy. This could lead to local information disclosure of photos or other images with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:37:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25123 | Path Manipulation in file mslib/index.py in MSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25123</link><description>MSS (Mission Support System) is an open source package designed for planning atmospheric research flights. In file: `index.py`, there is a method that is vulnerable to path manipulation attack. By modifying file paths, an attacker can acquire sensitive information from different resources. The `filename` variable is joined with other variables to form a file path in `_file`. However, `filename` is a route parameter that can capture path type values i.e. values including slashes (\). So it is possible for an attacker to manipulate the file being read by assigning a value containing ../ to `filename` and so the attacker may be able to gain access to other files on the host filesystem. This issue has been addressed in MSS version 8.3.3. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6123 | Improper Neutralization vulnerability affects OpenText ALM Octane. </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6123</link><description>Improper Neutralization vulnerability affects OpenText ALM Octane version 16.2.100 and above. The vulnerability could result in a remote code execution attack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0622 | Local privilege escalation vulnerability could affect OpenText Operations Agent on Non-Windows platforms. </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0622</link><description>Local privilege escalation vulnerability affects OpenText Operations Agent product versions 12.15 and 12.20-12.25 when installed on no-Windows platforms. The vulnerability could allow local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 21:10:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40057 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40057</link><description>The SolarWinds Access Rights Manager was found to be susceptible to a Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows an authenticated user to abuse a SolarWinds service resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23476 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23476</link><description>The SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to achieve the Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23477 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23477</link><description>The SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to achieve a Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23478 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Deserialization of Untrusted Data Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23478</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows an authenticated user to abuse a SolarWinds service, resulting in remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:43:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23479 | SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23479</link><description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) was found to be susceptible to a Directory Traversal Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. If exploited, this vulnerability allows an unauthenticated user to achieve a Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0240 | Silicon Labs EFR32 Bluetooth stack denial of service when sending notifications to multiple clients</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0240</link><description>A memory leak in the Silicon Labs' Bluetooth stack for EFR32 products may cause memory to be exhausted when sending notifications to multiple clients, this results in all Bluetooth operations, such as advertising and scanning, to stop.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21728 | Extension - smartcalc.es - Open redirect vulnerability in osTicky component for Joomla &amp;lt;= 2.2.8</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21728</link><description>An Open Redirect vulnerability was found in osTicky2 below 2.2.8. osTicky (osTicket Bridge) by SmartCalc is a Joomla 3.x extension that provides Joomla fronted integration with osTicket, a popular Support ticket system. The Open Redirect vulnerability allows attackers to control the return parameter in the URL to a base64 malicious URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25502 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in flusity CMS v.2.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25502</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in flusity CMS v.2.4 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via the download_backup.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 19:31:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25373 | Tenda AC10V4.0 V16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the sub_49B384 function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25373</link><description>Tenda AC10V4.0 V16.03.10.20 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the page parameter in the sub_49B384 function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6937 | Improper (D)TLS key boundary enforcement</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6937</link><description>wolfSSL prior to 5.6.6 did not check that messages in one (D)TLS record do not span key boundaries. As a result, it was possible to combine (D)TLS messages using different keys into one (D)TLS record. The most extreme edge case is that, in (D)TLS 1.3, it was possible that an unencrypted (D)TLS 1.3 record from the server containing first a ServerHello message and then the rest of the first server flight would be accepted by a wolfSSL client. In (D)TLS 1.3 the handshake is encrypted after the ServerHello but a wolfSSL client would accept an unencrypted flight from the server. This does not compromise key negotiation and authentication so it is assigned a low severity rating.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6255 | Hardcoded Credentals in SoliClub Mobile App</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6255</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Utarit Information Technologies SoliPay Mobile App allows Read Sensitive Strings Within an Executable.This issue affects SoliPay Mobile App: before 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5155 | SQLi in Utarit&amp;#x27;s Smart Deposit System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5155</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Utarit Information Technologies SoliPay Mobile App allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SoliPay Mobile App: before 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4993 | Sensetive Data Exposure in Utarit&amp;#x27;s Soliclub </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4993</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Utarit Information Technologies SoliPay Mobile App allows Collect Data as Provided by Users.This issue affects SoliPay Mobile App: before 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:47:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7081 | SQLi in PosTahsil&amp;#x27;s Online Payment System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7081</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in POSTAHSİL Online Payment System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Online Payment System: before 14.02.2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 15:40:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26206 | An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiNAC 9.4.0 - 9.4.2, 9.2.0 - 9.2.8, 9...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26206</link><description>An improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('cross-site scripting') in Fortinet FortiNAC 9.4.0 - 9.4.2, 9.2.0 - 9.2.8, 9.1.0 - 9.1.10 and 7.2.0 allows an attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via the name fields observed in the policy audit logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44253 | An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in Fortinet FortiManager version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44253</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in Fortinet FortiManager version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and before 7.2.5, FortiAnalyzer version 7.4.0 through 7.4.1 and before 7.2.5 and FortiAnalyzer-BigData before 7.2.5 allows an adom administrator to enumerate other adoms and device names via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45581 | An improper privilege management vulnerability [CWE-269] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7.0.10 allows an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45581</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability [CWE-269] in Fortinet FortiClientEMS version 7.2.0 through 7.2.2 and before 7.0.10 allows an Site administrator with Super Admin privileges to perform global administrative operations affecting other sites via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47537 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.0.0 - 7.0.13, 7.2.0 - 7.2.6 and 7.4.0 - 7.4.1 allows a remote and una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47537</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.0.0 - 7.0.13, 7.2.0 - 7.2.6 and 7.4.0 - 7.4.1 allows a remote and unauthenticated attacker to perform a Man-in-the-Middle attack on the FortiLink communication channel between the FortiOS device and FortiSwitch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23113 | A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, Fo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23113</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string in Fortinet FortiOS versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.6, 7.0.0 through 7.0.13, FortiProxy versions 7.4.0 through 7.4.2, 7.2.0 through 7.2.8, 7.0.0 through 7.0.14, FortiPAM versions 1.2.0, 1.1.0 through 1.1.2, 1.0.0 through 1.0.3, FortiSwitchManager versions 7.2.0 through 7.2.3, 7.0.0 through 7.0.3 allows attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specially crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20716 | Force high-usage of resources by generating unlimited coupons: Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20716</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.6-p3, 2.4.5-p5, 2.4.4-p6 and earlier are affected by an Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service. A high-privileged attacker could leverage this vulnerability to exhaust system resources, causing the application to slow down or crash. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20717 | Stored admin XSS via PayPal authentication certificate </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20717</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.6-p3, 2.4.5-p5, 2.4.4-p6 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low-privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20718 | [Spain] CSRF to delete Requisition Lists at Adobe Commerce</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20718</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.6-p3, 2.4.5-p5, 2.4.4-p6 and earlier are affected by a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to trick a victim into performing actions they did not intend to do, which could be used to bypass security measures and gain unauthorized access. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction, typically in the form of the victim clicking a link or visiting a malicious website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20719 | [Adobe Commerce] Stored XSS from low privileged admin user on every admin page, bypassing CVE-2023-29297</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20719</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.6-p3, 2.4.5-p5, 2.4.4-p6 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by an admin attacker to inject malicious scripts into every admin page. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field, that could be leveraged to gain admin access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20720 | Command injection in data collector backup due to insufficient patching of CVE-2023-38208</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20720</link><description>Adobe Commerce versions 2.4.6-p3, 2.4.5-p5, 2.4.4-p6 and earlier are affected by an Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability that could lead in arbitrary code execution by an attacker. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39245 | DELL ESI (Enterprise Storage Integrator) for SAP LAMA, version 10.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability in EHAC component. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39245</link><description>DELL ESI (Enterprise Storage Integrator) for SAP LAMA, version 10.0, contains an information disclosure vulnerability in EHAC component. An remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by eavesdropping the network traffic to gain admin level credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 13:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39244 | DELL ESI (Enterprise Storage Integrator) for SAP LAMA, version 10.0, contains an improper access control vulnerability in EHAC component. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39244</link><description>DELL ESI (Enterprise Storage Integrator) for SAP LAMA, version 10.0, contains an improper access control vulnerability in EHAC component. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability to gain unrestricted access to the SOAP APIs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32484 | Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC versions 4.1.0, 4.0.5, 3.5.4 and below contains an improper input validation vulnerability...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32484</link><description>Dell Networking Switches running Enterprise SONiC versions 4.1.0, 4.0.5, 3.5.4 and below contains an improper input validation vulnerability. A remote unauthenticated malicious user may exploit this vulnerability and escalate privileges up to the highest administrative level. This is a Critical vulnerability affecting certain protocols, Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1530 | ECshop view_sendlist.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1530</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in ECshop 4.1.8. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/view_sendlist.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-250562 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32462 | Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain an OS command injection vulnerability when using remote user authentication...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32462</link><description>Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain an OS command injection vulnerability when using remote user authentication. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the execution of arbitrary OS commands and possible system takeover. This is a critical vulnerability as it allows an attacker to cause severe damage. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:52:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28078 | Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain a vulnerability with zeroMQ when VLT is configured. A remote unauthenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28078</link><description>Dell OS10 Networking Switches running 10.5.2.x and above contain a vulnerability with zeroMQ when VLT is configured. A remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to information disclosure and a possible Denial of Service when a huge number of requests are sent to the switch. This is a high severity vulnerability as it allows an attacker to view sensitive data. Dell recommends customers to upgrade at the earliest opportunity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20739 | ZDI-CAN-22647: Adobe Audition AVI File Parsing Heap-based Buffer Overflow Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20739</link><description>Audition versions 24.0.3, 23.6.2 and earlier are affected by a Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20750 | Adobe Substance 3D Designer PICT Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20750</link><description>Substance3D - Designer versions 13.1.0 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20726 | [TianfuCup] JP2K Image Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20726</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20727 | [TianfuCup] out-of-bounds access vulnerability when parsing jpeg2000</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20727</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20728 | ZDI-CAN-22727: Adobe Acrobat Pro DC Annotation Out-Of-Bounds Write Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20728</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20729 | TALOS-2023-1890 -  Adobe Acrobat Reader Annot3D object zoom event use-after-free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20729</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20730 | TALOS-2023-1906  - Adobe Acrobat Reader Font CPAL integer overflow vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20730</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an Integer Overflow or Wraparound vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20731 | TALOS-2023-1901 - Adobe Acrobat Reader FileAttachment PDAnnot destroy use-after-free vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20731</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20733 | [ZS-VR-23-360] Adobe Acrobat Reader Parsing OTF font Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20733</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an Improper Input Validation vulnerability that could lead to an application denial-of-service. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to cause the application to crash, resulting in a denial of service. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20734 | ZDI-CAN-22516: Adobe Acrobat Pro DC AcroForm Use-After-Free Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20734</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by a Use After Free vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20735 | TALOS-2023-1905 - Adobe Acrobat Reader Font CPAL numColorRecords out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20735</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20736 | ZDI-CAN-22822: Adobe Acrobat Pro DC AcroForm Out-Of-Bounds Read Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20736</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20738 | Adobe FrameMaker Publishing Server Authentication Bypass Vulnerability | CVE-2023-44324 bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20738</link><description>Adobe Framemaker versions 2022.1 and earlier are affected by an Improper Authentication vulnerability that could result in a Security feature bypass. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass authentication mechanisms and gain unauthorized access. Exploitation of this issue does not require user interaction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20747 | TALOS-2023-1908 - Adobe Acrobat Reader Font CharStrings INDEX out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20747</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20748 | TALOS-2023-1909 - Adobe Acrobat Reader Font avar SegmentMaps out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20748</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20749 | TALOS-2023-1910 - Adobe Acrobat Reader Font CharStrings CharStringsOffset out-of-bounds read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20749</link><description>Acrobat Reader versions 20.005.30539, 23.008.20470 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 12:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20722 | Adobe Substance 3D Painter v9.0.1Build2822 OOBR Vulnerability III</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20722</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20723 | Adobe Substance 3D Painter v9.0.1Build2822 Buffer Overflow Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20723</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Buffer Overflow vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20724 | Adobe Substance 3D Painter v9.0.1Build2822 OOBR Vulnerability II</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20724</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20725 | Adobe Substance 3D Painter v9.0.1Build2822 OOBR Vulnerability I</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20725</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability that could lead to disclosure of sensitive memory. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to bypass mitigations such as ASLR. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20740 | Adobe Substance 3D Paint PSD Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20740</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20741 | Adobe Substance 3D Paint ICO Parsing Access Violation Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20741</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by a Write-what-where Condition vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20742 | Adobe Substance 3D Paint RAS File Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20742</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds read vulnerability when parsing a crafted file, which could result in a read past the end of an allocated memory structure. An attacker could leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20743 | Adobe Substance 3D Paint PSD Parsing Out-Of-Bounds Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20743</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20744 | Adobe Substance 3D Paint PICT Parsing Access Violation Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20744</link><description>Substance3D - Painter versions 9.1.1 and earlier are affected by an out-of-bounds write vulnerability that could result in arbitrary code execution in the context of the current user. Exploitation of this issue requires user interaction in that a victim must open a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0390 | Hard-coded credentials in iZZi connect application</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0390</link><description>INPRAX "iZZi connect" application on Android contains hard-coded MQTT queue credentials. The same MQTT queue is used by corresponding physical recuperation devices. Exploiting this vulnerability could potentially allow unauthorized access to manage and read parameters of the recuperation unit "reQnet iZZi".This issue affects "iZZi connect" application versions before 2024010401.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:26:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4538 | Shared Key in Comarch ERP XL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4538</link><description>The database access credentials configured during installation are stored in a special table, and are encrypted with a shared key, same among all Comarch ERP XL client installations. This could allow an attacker with access to that table to retrieve plain text passwords.

This issue affects ERP XL: from 2020.2.2 through 2023.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 08:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4539 | Hardcoded password in Comarch ERP XL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4539</link><description>Use of a hard-coded password for a special database account created during Comarch ERP XL installation allows an attacker to retrieve embedded sensitive data stored in the database. The password is same among all Comarch ERP XL installations. 

This issue affects ERP XL: from 2020.2.2 through 2023.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 08:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4537 | Protocol Downgrade in Comarch ERP XL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4537</link><description>Comarch ERP XL client is vulnerable to MS SQL protocol downgrade request from a server side, what could lead to an unencrypted communication vulnerable to data interception and modification.

This issue affects ERP XL: from 2020.2.2 through 2023.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 08:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24386 | An issue in VitalPBX v.3.2.4-5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the /var/lib/vitalpbx/scripts folder.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24386</link><description>An issue in VitalPBX v.3.2.4-5 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the /var/lib/vitalpbx/scripts folder.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 08:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0353 | Local privilege escalation in Windows products</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0353</link><description>Local privilege escalation vulnerability potentially allowed an attacker to misuse ESET’s file operations to delete files without having proper permission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24256 | SQL Injection vulnerability in Yonyou space-time enterprise information integration platform v.9.0 and before allows an attacker to obtain s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24256</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in Yonyou space-time enterprise information integration platform v.9.0 and before allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the gwbhAIM parameter in the saveMove.jsp in the hr_position directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21727 | Extension - digtal-peak.com - XSS vulnerability in DP Calendar component for Joomla 8.0.0-8.0.14</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21727</link><description>XSS vulnerability in DP Calendar component for Joomla.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:08:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0708 | The Landing Page Cat – Coming Soon Page, Maintenance Page &amp; Squeeze Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0708</link><description>The Landing Page Cat – Coming Soon Page, Maintenance Page &amp; Squeeze Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to access landing pages that may not be public.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:56:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46596 | Improper input validation in FireFlow’s VisualFlow workflow editor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46596</link><description>Improper input validation in Algosec FireFlow VisualFlow workflow editor via Name, Description and Configuration File field in version A32.20, A32.50, A32.60 permits an attacker to initiate an XSS attack by injecting malicious executable scripts into the application's code. Fixed in version A32.20 (b600 and above), A32.50 (b430 and above), A32.60 (b250 and above)</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51787 | An issue was discovered in Wind River VxWorks 7 22.09 and 23.03. If a VxWorks task or POSIX thread that uses OpenSSL exits, limited per-task...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51787</link><description>An issue was discovered in Wind River VxWorks 7 22.09 and 23.03. If a VxWorks task or POSIX thread that uses OpenSSL exits, limited per-task memory is not freed, resulting in a memory leak.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23093 | Stack overflow in ping(8)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23093</link><description>ping reads raw IP packets from the network to process responses in the pr_pack() function.  As part of processing a response ping has to reconstruct the IP header, the ICMP header and if present a "quoted packet," which represents the packet that generated an ICMP error.  The quoted packet again has an IP header and an ICMP header.

The pr_pack() copies received IP and ICMP headers into stack buffers for further processing.  In so doing, it fails to take into account the possible presence of IP option headers following the IP header in either the response or the quoted packet.  When IP options are present, pr_pack() overflows the destination buffer by up to 40 bytes.

The memory safety bugs described above can be triggered by a remote host, causing the ping program to crash.

The ping process runs in a capability mode sandbox on all affected versions of FreeBSD and is thus very constrained in how it can interact with the rest of the system at the point where the bug can occur.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23090 | AIO credential reference count leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23090</link><description>The aio_aqueue function, used by the lio_listio system call, fails to release a reference to a credential in an error case.

An attacker may cause the reference count to overflow, leading to a use after free (UAF).</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23091 | Memory disclosure by stale virtual memory mapping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23091</link><description>A particular case of memory sharing is mishandled in the virtual memory system.  This is very similar to SA-21:08.vm, but with a different root cause.

An unprivileged local user process can maintain a mapping of a page after it is freed, allowing that process to read private data belonging to other processes or the kernel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23092 | Missing bounds check in 9p message handling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23092</link><description>The implementation of lib9p's handling of RWALK messages was missing a bounds check needed when unpacking the message contents.  The missing check means that the receipt of a specially crafted message will cause lib9p to overwrite unrelated memory.

The bug can be triggered by a malicious bhyve guest kernel to overwrite memory in the bhyve(8) process.  This could potentially lead to user-mode code execution on the host, subject to bhyve's Capsicum sandbox.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:26:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23088 | 802.11 heap buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23088</link><description>The 802.11 beacon handling routine failed to validate the length of an IEEE 802.11s Mesh ID before copying it to a heap-allocated buffer.

While a FreeBSD Wi-Fi client is in scanning mode (i.e., not associated with a SSID) a malicious beacon frame may overwrite kernel memory, leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23089 | Out of bound read in elf_note_prpsinfo()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23089</link><description>When dumping core and saving process information, proc_getargv() might return an sbuf which have a sbuf_len() of 0 or -1, which is not properly handled.

An out-of-bound read can happen when user constructs a specially crafted ps_string, which in turn can cause the kernel to crash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1488 | Unbound: unrestricted reconfiguration enabled to anyone that may lead to local privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1488</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Unbound due to incorrect default permissions, allowing any process outside the unbound group to modify the unbound runtime configuration. If a process can connect over localhost to port 8953, it can alter the configuration of unbound.service. This flaw allows an unprivileged attacker to manipulate a running instance, potentially altering forwarders, allowing them to track all queries forwarded by the local resolver, and, in some cases, disrupting resolving altogether.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23086 | mpr/mps/mpt driver ioctl heap out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23086</link><description>Handlers for *_CFG_PAGE read / write ioctls in the mpr, mps, and mpt drivers allocated a buffer of a caller-specified size, but copied to it a fixed size header.  Other heap content would be overwritten if the specified size was too small.

Users with access to the mpr, mps or mpt device node may overwrite heap data, potentially resulting in privilege escalation.  Note that the device node is only accessible to root and members of the operator group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23087 | Bhyve e82545 device emulation out-of-bounds write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23087</link><description>The e1000 network adapters permit a variety of modifications to an Ethernet packet when it is being transmitted.  These include the insertion of IP and TCP checksums, insertion of an Ethernet VLAN header, and TCP segmentation offload ("TSO").  The e1000 device model uses an on-stack buffer to generate the modified packet header when simulating these modifications on transmitted packets.

When checksum offload is requested for a transmitted packet, the e1000 device model used a guest-provided value to specify the checksum offset in the on-stack buffer.  The offset was not validated for certain packet types.

A misbehaving bhyve guest could overwrite memory in the bhyve process on the host, possibly leading to code execution in the host context.

The bhyve process runs in a Capsicum sandbox, which (depending on the FreeBSD version and bhyve configuration) limits the impact of exploiting this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 05:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23084 | Potential jail escape vulnerabilities in netmap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23084</link><description>The total size of the user-provided nmreq to nmreq_copyin() was first computed and then trusted during the copyin.  This time-of-check to time-of-use bug could lead to kernel memory corruption.

On systems configured to include netmap in their devfs_ruleset, a privileged process running in a jail can affect the host environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23085 | Potential jail escape vulnerabilities in netmap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23085</link><description>A user-provided integer option was passed to nmreq_copyin() without checking if it would overflow.  This insufficient bounds checking could lead to kernel memory corruption.

On systems configured to include netmap in their devfs_ruleset, a privileged process running in a jail can affect the host environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25559 | URL spoofing vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.0 to Ver.3.1.8. If an attacker sends a specially crafted request, the administrator ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25559</link><description>URL spoofing vulnerability exists in a-blog cms Ver.3.1.0 to Ver.3.1.8. If an attacker sends a specially crafted request, the administrator of the product may be forced to access an arbitrary website when clicking a link in the audit log.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25941 | jail(2) information leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25941</link><description>The jail(2) system call has not limited a visiblity of allocated TTYs (the kern.ttys sysctl).  This gives rise to an information leak about processes outside the current jail.

Attacker can get information about TTYs allocated on the host or in other jails.  Effectively, the information printed by "pstat -t" may be leaked.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25940 | bhyveload(8) host file access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25940</link><description>`bhyveload -h &lt;host-path&gt;` may be used to grant loader access to the &lt;host-path&gt; directory tree on the host.  Affected versions of bhyveload(8) do not make any attempt to restrict loader's access to &lt;host-path&gt;, allowing the loader to read any file the host user has access to. In the bhyveload(8) model, the host supplies a userboot.so to boot with, but the loader scripts generally come from the guest image.  A maliciously crafted script could be used to exfiltrate sensitive data from the host accessible to the user running bhyhveload(8), which is often the system root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 04:29:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26264 | EBM Technologies RISWEB - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26264</link><description>EBM Technologies RISWEB's specific query function parameter does not properly restrict user input, and this feature page is accessible without login. This allows remote attackers to inject SQL commands without authentication, enabling them to read, modify, and delete database records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26263 | EBM Technologies RISWEB - Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26263</link><description>EBM Technologies RISWEB's specific URL path is not properly controlled by permission, allowing attackers to browse specific pages and query sensitive data without login.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 03:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26262 | EBM Technologies Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26262</link><description>EBM Technologies Uniweb/SoliPACS WebServer's query functionality lacks proper restrictions of user input, allowing remote attackers authenticated as regular user to inject SQL commands for reading, modifying, and deleting database records, as well as executing system commands. Attackers may even leverage the dbo privilege in the database for privilege escalation, elevating their privileges to administrator .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26261 | Hgiga OAKlouds - Arbitrary File Read And Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26261</link><description>The functionality for file download in HGiga OAKlouds' certain modules contains an Arbitrary File Read and Delete vulnerability. Attackers can put file path in specific request parameters, allowing them to download the file without login. Furthermore, the file will be deleted after being downloaded.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26260 | Hgiga OAKlouds - Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26260</link><description>The functionality for synchronization in HGiga OAKlouds' certain moudules has an OS Command Injection vulnerability, allowing remote attackers to inject system commands within specific request parameters. This enables the execution of arbitrary code on the remote server without permission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1523 | EC-WEB  FS-EZViewer(Web) - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1523</link><description>EC-WEB FS-EZViewer(Web)'s query functionality lacks proper restrictions of user input, allowing remote attackers authenticated as regular user to inject SQL commands for reading, modifying, and deleting database records, as well as executing system commands. Attackers may even leverage the dbo privilege in the database for privilege escalation, elevating their privileges to administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:14:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25620 | Dependency management path traversal in helm</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25620</link><description>Helm is a tool for managing Charts. Charts are packages of pre-configured Kubernetes resources. When either the Helm client or SDK is used to save a chart whose name within the `Chart.yaml` file includes a relative path change, the chart would be saved outside its expected directory based on the changes in the relative path. The validation and linting did not detect the path changes in the name. This issue has been resolved in Helm v3.14.1. Users unable to upgrade should check all charts used by Helm for path changes in their name as found in the `Chart.yaml` file. This includes dependencies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 23:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24300 | 4ipnet EAP-767 v3.42.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device uses the same set of credentials, regardless of how many times...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24300</link><description>4ipnet EAP-767 v3.42.00 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. The device uses the same set of credentials, regardless of how many times a user logs in, the content of the cookie remains unchanged.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:38:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48219 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48219</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusion detection bypass via a physical attack. HP is releasing firmware and guidance to mitigate these potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48220 | Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48220</link><description>Potential vulnerabilities have been identified in certain HP Desktop PC products using the HP TamperLock feature, which might allow intrusion detection bypass via a physical attack. HP is releasing firmware and guidance to mitigate these potential vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24301 | Command Injection vulnerability discovered in 4ipnet EAP-767 device v3.42.00 within the web interface of the device allows attackers with va...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24301</link><description>Command Injection vulnerability discovered in 4ipnet EAP-767 device v3.42.00 within the web interface of the device allows attackers with valid credentials to inject arbitrary shell commands to be executed by the device with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:31:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6138 | A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP Workstation PCs, which might allow escalation of pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6138</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the system BIOS for certain HP Workstation PCs, which might allow escalation of privilege, arbitrary code execution, or denial of service. HP is releasing mitigation for the potential vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49721 | An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in LXD. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49721</link><description>An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in LXD. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48733 | An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in Ubuntu's EDK2. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48733</link><description>An insecure default to allow UEFI Shell in EDK2 was left enabled in Ubuntu's EDK2. This allows an OS-resident attacker to bypass Secure Boot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:08:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1471 | HTML Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1471</link><description>An HTML injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Security Center application could modify Repository parameters, which could lead to HTML redirection attacks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1367 | Command Injection Vulnerability in Tenable Security Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1367</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists where an authenticated, remote attacker with administrator privileges on the Security Center application could modify Logging parameters, which could lead to the execution of arbitrary code on the Security Center host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25617 | Denial of Service in HTTP Header parser in squid proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25617</link><description>Squid is an open source caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to a Collapse of Data into Unsafe Value bug ,Squid may be vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against HTTP header parsing. This problem allows a remote client or a remote server to perform Denial of Service when sending oversized headers in HTTP messages. In versions of Squid prior to 6.5 this can be achieved if the request_header_max_size or reply_header_max_size settings are unchanged from the default. In Squid version 6.5 and later, the default setting of these parameters is safe. Squid will emit a critical warning in cache.log if the administrator is setting these parameters to unsafe values. Squid will not at this time prevent these settings from being changed to unsafe values. Users are advised to upgrade to version 6.5. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability. This issue is also tracked as SQUID-2024:2</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 21:12:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25619 | Destroying OAuth Applications doesn&amp;#x27;t notify Streaming of Access Tokens being destroyed in mastodon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25619</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. When an OAuth Application is destroyed, the streaming server wasn't being informed that the Access Tokens had also been destroyed, this could have posed security risks to users by allowing an application to continue listening to streaming after the application had been destroyed. Essentially this comes down to the fact that when Doorkeeper sets up the relationship between Applications and Access Tokens, it uses a `dependent: delete_all` configuration, which means the `after_commit` callback setup on `AccessTokenExtension` didn't actually fire, since `delete_all` doesn't trigger ActiveRecord callbacks. To mitigate, we need to add a `before_destroy` callback to `ApplicationExtension` which announces to streaming that all the Application's Access Tokens are being "killed". Impact should be negligible given the affected application had to be owned by the user. None the less this issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workaround for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25618 | External OpenID Connect Account Takeover by E-Mail Change in mastodon</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25618</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Mastodon allows new identities from configured authentication providers (CAS, SAML, OIDC) to attach to existing local users with the same e-mail address. This results in a possible account takeover if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address or multiple authentication providers are configured. When a user logs in through an external authentication provider for the first time, Mastodon checks the e-mail address passed by the provider to find an existing account. However, using the e-mail address alone means that if the authentication provider allows changing the e-mail address of an account, the Mastodon account can immediately be hijacked. All users logging in through external authentication providers are affected. The severity is medium, as it also requires the external authentication provider to misbehave. However, some well-known OIDC providers (like Microsoft Azure) make it very easy to accidentally allow unverified e-mail changes. Moreover, OpenID Connect also allows dynamic client registration. This issue has been addressed in versions 4.2.6, 4.1.14, 4.0.14, and 3.5.18. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1482 | Improper Authorization in GitHub Enterprise Server allowed unauthorized workflow execution </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1482</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability was identified in GitHub Enterprise Server that allowed an attacker to create new branches in public repositories and run arbitrary GitHub Actions workflows with permissions from the GITHUB_TOKEN. To exploit this vulnerability, an attacker would need access to the Enterprise Server. This vulnerability affected all versions of GitHub Enterprise Server after 3.8 and prior to 3.12, and was fixed in versions 3.9.10, 3.10.7, 3.11.5. This vulnerability was reported via the GitHub Bug Bounty program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 20:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25165 | A global-buffer-overflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function LineText at lib/swf5compiler.flex.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25165</link><description>A global-buffer-overflow vulnerability was found in SWFTools v0.9.2, in the function LineText at lib/swf5compiler.flex.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50926 | Unvalidated DIO prefix info length in RPL-Lite in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50926</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds read can be caused by an incoming DIO message when using the RPL-Lite implementation in the Contiki-NG operating system. More specifically, the prefix information of the DIO message contains a field that specifies the length of an IPv6 address prefix. The value of this field is not validated, which means that an attacker can set a value that is longer than the maximum prefix length. Subsequently, a memcmp function call that compares different prefixes can be called with a length argument that surpasses the boundary of the array allocated for the prefix, causing an out-of-bounds read. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG, and is expected to be included in the next release. Users are advised to update as soon as they are able to or to manually apply the changes in Contiki-NG pull request #2721.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50927 | Insufficient boundary checks for DIO and DAO messages in RPL-Lite in Contiki-NG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50927</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An attacker can trigger out-of-bounds reads in the RPL-Lite implementation of the RPL protocol in the Contiki-NG operating system. This vulnerability is caused by insufficient control of the lengths for DIO and DAO messages, in particular when they contain RPL sub-option headers. The problem has been patched in Contiki-NG 4.9. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should manually apply the code changes in PR #2484.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 19:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25300 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Redaxo v5.15.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25300</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Redaxo v5.15.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Name parameter in the Template section.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25301 | Redaxo v5.15.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /pages/templates.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25301</link><description>Redaxo v5.15.1 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the component /pages/templates.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48229 | Out-of-bounds write in the radio driver for Contiki-NG nRF platforms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48229</link><description>Contiki-NG is an open-source, cross-platform operating system for Next-Generation IoT devices. An out-of-bounds write exists in the driver for IEEE 802.15.4 radios on nRF platforms in the Contiki-NG operating system. The problem is triggered when parsing radio frames in the `read_frame` function in the `arch/cpu/nrf/net/nrf-ieee-driver-arch.c` module. More specifically, the `read_frame` function performs an incomplete validation of the payload length of the packet, which is a value that can be set by an external party that sends radio packets to a Contiki-NG system. Although the value is validated to be in the range of the MTU length, it is not validated to fit into the given buffer into which the packet will be copied. The problem has been patched in the "develop" branch of Contiki-NG and is expected to be included in subsequent releases. Users are advised to update their develop branch or to update to a subsequent release when available. Users unable to upgrade should consider manually applying the changes in PR #2741.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:39:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0008 | PAN-OS: Insufficient Session Expiration Vulnerability in the Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0008</link><description>Web sessions in the management interface in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software do not expire in certain situations, making it susceptible to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0009 | PAN-OS: Improper IP Address Verification in GlobalProtect Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0009</link><description>An improper verification vulnerability in the GlobalProtect gateway feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious user with stolen credentials to establish a VPN connection from an unauthorized IP address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0010 | PAN-OS: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in GlobalProtect Portal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0010</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the GlobalProtect portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of a user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0011 | PAN-OS: Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in Captive Portal Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0011</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Captive Portal feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables execution of malicious JavaScript (in the context of an authenticated Captive Portal user’s browser) if a user clicks on a malicious link, allowing phishing attacks that could lead to credential theft.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:39:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0007 | PAN-OS: Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability in the Panorama Web Interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0007</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software enables a malicious authenticated read-write administrator to store a JavaScript payload using the web interface on Panorama appliances. This enables the impersonation of another authenticated administrator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:32:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0568 | CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized tampering
of device configuration over NFC communication...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0568</link><description>CWE-287: Improper Authentication vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized tampering
of device configuration over NFC communication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27975 | CWE-522: Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to the project file in EcoStruxure C...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27975</link><description>CWE-522: Insufficiently Protected Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to the project file in EcoStruxure Control Expert when a local user tampers with the
memory of the engineering workstation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6408 | CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a
Communication Channel vulnerability exists that could cause a de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6408</link><description>CWE-924: Improper Enforcement of Message Integrity During Transmission in a
Communication Channel vulnerability exists that could cause a denial of service and loss of
confidentiality, integrity of controllers when conducting a Man in the Middle attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6409 | CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to a project file protected with applicatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6409</link><description>CWE-798: Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability exists that could cause unauthorized
access to a project file protected with application password when opening the file with
EcoStruxure Control Expert.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:53:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23982 | BIG-IP PEM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23982</link><description>When a BIG-IP PEM classification profile is configured on a UDP virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. This issue affects classification engines using signatures released between 09-08-2022 and 02-16-2023. See the table in the F5 Security Advisory for a complete list of affected classification signature files.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21763 | BIG-IP AFM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21763</link><description>When BIG-IP AFM Device DoS or DoS profile is configured with NXDOMAIN attack vector and bad actor detection, undisclosed queries can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21771 | F5 AFM Signature Matching Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21771</link><description>For unspecified traffic patterns, BIG-IP AFM IPS engine may spend an excessive amount of time matching the traffic against signatures, resulting in Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) restarting and traffic disruption.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21782 | BIG-IP and BIG-IQ secure copy vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21782</link><description>BIG-IP or BIG-IQ Resource Administrators and Certificate Managers who have access to the secure copy (scp) utility but do not have access to Advanced shell (bash) can execute arbitrary commands with a specially crafted command string. This vulnerability is due to an incomplete fix for CVE-2020-5873. 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21789 | BIG-IP ASM and Advanced WAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21789</link><description>When a BIG-IP ASM/Advanced WAF security policy is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in memory resource utilization.
 Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21849 | BIG-IP Websockets vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21849</link><description>When an Advanced WAF/ASM security policy and a Websockets profile are configured on a virtual server, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) process to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22093 | Appliance mode iControl REST vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22093</link><description>When running in appliance mode, an authenticated remote command injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed iControl REST endpoint on multi-bladed systems. A successful exploit can allow the attacker to cross a security boundary.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22389 | BIG-IP iControl REST API Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22389</link><description>When BIG-IP is deployed in high availability (HA) and an iControl REST API token is updated, the change does not sync to the peer device.  


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23306 | BIG-IP Next CNF &amp;amp; SPK vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23306</link><description>A vulnerability exists in BIG-IP Next CNF and SPK systems that may allow access to undisclosed sensitive files.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23308 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23308</link><description>When a BIG-IP Advanced WAF or BIG-IP ASM policy with a Request Body Handling option is attached to a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause the BD process to terminate. The condition results from setting the Request Body Handling option in the Header-Based Content Profile for an Allowed URL with "Apply value and content signatures and detect threat campaigns."  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23314 | BIG-IP HTTP/2 vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23314</link><description>When HTTP/2 is configured on BIG-IP or BIG-IP Next SPK systems, undisclosed responses can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23603 | BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM Configuration utility vulnerability </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23603</link><description>An SQL injection vulnerability exists in an undisclosed page of the BIG-IP Configuration utility.

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23607 | F5OS QKView utility vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23607</link><description>A directory traversal vulnerability exists in the F5OS QKView utility that allows an authenticated attacker to read files outside the QKView directory.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23805 | F5 Application Visibility and Reporting module and BIG-IP Advanced WAF/ASM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23805</link><description>Undisclosed requests can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate. For the Application Visibility and Reporting module, this may occur when the HTTP Analytics profile with URLs enabled under Collected Entities is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled. For BIG-IP Advanced WAF and ASM, this may occur when either a DoS or Bot Defense profile is configured on a virtual server and the DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI or avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are enabled.

Note: The DB variables avr.IncludeServerInURI and avr.CollectOnlyHostnameFromURI are not enabled by default. For more information about the HTTP Analytics profile and the Collect URLs setting, refer to  K30875743: Create a new Analytics profile and attach it to your virtual servers https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K30875743 .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23976 | BIG-IP Appliance mode iAppsLX vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23976</link><description>When running in Appliance mode, an authenticated attacker assigned the Administrator role may be able to bypass Appliance
mode restrictions utilizing iAppsLX templates on a BIG-IP system.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23979 | BIG-IP SSL Client Certificate LDAP and CRLDP Authentication profiles vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23979</link><description>When SSL Client Certificate LDAP or Certificate Revocation List Distribution Point (CRLDP) authentication profile is configured on a virtual server, undisclosed requests can cause an increase in CPU resource utilization. 

 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24775 | BIG-IP TMM vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24775</link><description>When a virtual server is enabled with VLAN group and SNAT listener is configured, undisclosed traffic can cause the Traffic Management Microkernel (TMM) to terminate.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24966 | F5OS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24966</link><description>When LDAP remote authentication is configured on F5OS, a remote user without an assigned role will be incorrectly authorized.  Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24989 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24989</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



NOTE: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24990 | NGINX HTTP/3 QUIC vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24990</link><description>When NGINX Plus or NGINX OSS are configured to use the HTTP/3 QUIC module, undisclosed requests can cause NGINX worker processes to terminate.

Note: The HTTP/3 QUIC module is not enabled by default and is considered experimental. For more information, refer to  Support for QUIC and HTTP/3 https://nginx.org/en/docs/quic.html .



 


Note: Software versions which have reached End of Technical Support (EoTS) are not evaluated</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:39:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50868 | The Closest Encloser Proof aspect of the DNS protocol (in RFC 5155 when RFC 9276 guidance is skipped) allows remote attackers to cause a den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50868</link><description>The Closest Encloser Proof aspect of the DNS protocol (in RFC 5155 when RFC 9276 guidance is skipped) allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption for SHA-1 computations) via DNSSEC responses in a random subdomain attack, aka the "NSEC3" issue. The RFC 5155 specification implies that an algorithm must perform thousands of iterations of a hash function in certain situations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50387 | Certain DNSSEC aspects of the DNS protocol (in RFC 4033, 4034, 4035, 6840, and related RFCs) allow remote attackers to cause a denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50387</link><description>Certain DNSSEC aspects of the DNS protocol (in RFC 4033, 4034, 4035, 6840, and related RFCs) allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (CPU consumption) via one or more DNSSEC responses, aka the "KeyTrap" issue. One of the concerns is that, when there is a zone with many DNSKEY and RRSIG records, the protocol specification implies that an algorithm must evaluate all combinations of DNSKEY and RRSIG records.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5122 | SSRF in CSV Datasource Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5122</link><description>Grafana is an open-source platform for monitoring and observability. The CSV datasource plugin is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing CSV data from a remote endpoint configured by an administrator. If this plugin was configured to send requests to a bare host with no path (e.g.  https://www.example.com/ https://www.example.com/` ), requests to an endpoint other than the one configured by the administrator could be triggered by a specially crafted request from any user, resulting in an SSRF vector. AV:N/AC:L/PR:L/UI:N/S:C/C:L/I:N/A:N https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln-metrics/cvss/v3-calculator</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5123 | Improper Path Sanitization in JSON Datasource Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5123</link><description>The JSON datasource plugin ( https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/marcusolsson-json-datasource/ ) is a Grafana Labs maintained plugin for Grafana that allows for retrieving and processing JSON data from a remote endpoint (including a specific sub-path) configured by an administrator. Due to inadequate sanitization of the dashboard-supplied path parameter, it was possible to include path traversal characters (../) in the path parameter and send requests to paths on the configured endpoint outside the configured sub-path. 





    
    
            






    
    
            This means that if the datasource was configured by an administrator to point at some sub-path of a domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ https://example.com/api/some_safe_api/ ), it was possible for an editor to create a dashboard referencing the datasource which issues queries containing path traversal characters, which would in turn cause the datasource to instead query arbitrary subpaths on the configured domain (e.g.  https://example.com/api/admin_api/) https://example.com/api/admin_api/) .

In the rare case that this plugin is configured by an administrator to point back at the Grafana instance itself, this vulnerability becomes considerably more severe, as an administrator browsing a maliciously configured panel could be compelled to make requests to Grafana administrative API endpoints with their credentials, resulting in the potential for privilege escalation, hence the high score for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25207 | Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25207</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function at /barangay-population-monitoring-system/masterlist.php. This vulnerabiity allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Contact Number parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25208 | Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25208</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System v1.0 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Add Resident function at /barangay-population-monitoring-system/masterlist.php. This vulnerabiity allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Full Name parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25209 | Barangay Population Monitoring System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the resident parameter at /endpoint/de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25209</link><description>Barangay Population Monitoring System 1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the resident parameter at /endpoint/delete-resident.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25210 | Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the expense parameter at /endpoint/delete_expense.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25210</link><description>Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the expense parameter at /endpoint/delete_expense.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25211 | Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the category parameter at /endpoint/delete_category....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25211</link><description>Simple Expense Tracker v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the category parameter at /endpoint/delete_category.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25212 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /delete.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25212</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /delete.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25213 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /edit.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25213</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /edit.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25214 | An issue in Employee Managment System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via injecting a crafted payload into the E-mail and Pas...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25214</link><description>An issue in Employee Managment System v1.0 allows attackers to bypass authentication via injecting a crafted payload into the E-mail and Password parameters at /alogin.html.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25215 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pwd parameter at /aprocess.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25215</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the pwd parameter at /aprocess.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25216 | Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the mailud parameter at /aprocess.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25216</link><description>Employee Managment System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the mailud parameter at /aprocess.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25217 | Online Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /omos/?p=products/view_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25217</link><description>Online Medicine Ordering System v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the id parameter at /omos/?p=products/view_product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25218 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25218</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Project Name parameter /TaskManager/Projects.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25219 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25219</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Task Name parameter /TaskManager/Task.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25220 | Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the taskID parameter at /TaskManager/EditTask.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25220</link><description>Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the taskID parameter at /TaskManager/EditTask.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25221 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25221</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Task Manager App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Note Section parameter at /TaskManager/Tasks.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25222 | Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectID parameter at /TaskManager/EditProject.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25222</link><description>Task Manager App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the projectID parameter at /TaskManager/EditProject.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25223 | Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderID parameter at /adminView/viewEachOrder.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25223</link><description>Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the orderID parameter at /adminView/viewEachOrder.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25224 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25224</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Size Number parameter under the Add Size function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25225 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25225</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Category Name parameter under the Add Category function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25226 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25226</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Simple Admin Panel App v1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the Category Name parameter under the Add Category function.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:17:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46186 | IBM Jazz for Service Management information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46186</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3.20 could allow an unauthorized user to obtain sensitive file information using forced browsing due to improper access controls.  IBM X-Force ID:  269929.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22293 | Improper access control in the Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22293</link><description>Improper access control in the Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22311 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem 100 Series Management Software before version 01.00.00.3547 may allow an authentica...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22311</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem 100 Series Management Software before version 01.00.00.3547 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22342 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22342</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22390 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22390</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22848 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22848</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24463 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to po...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24463</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24481 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24481</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24542 | Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24542</link><description>Unquoted search path or element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24589 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24589</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24591 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Binary Configuration Tool software before version 3.4.4 may allow an authenticated user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24591</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Binary Configuration Tool software before version 3.4.4 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25073 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25073</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25174 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25174</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25769 | Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25769</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25777 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25777</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25779 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25779</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25945 | Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25945</link><description>Protection mechanism failure in some Intel(R) OFU software before version 14.1.31 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25951 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow a privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25951</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26585 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26585</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26586 | Uncaught exception for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26586</link><description>Uncaught exception for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26591 | Unchecked return value in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26591</link><description>Unchecked return value in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via physical access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26592 | Deserialization of untrusted data in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26592</link><description>Deserialization of untrusted data in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable a denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26596 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26596</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27300 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27300</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27301 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27301</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27303 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27303</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27307 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27307</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27308 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27308</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) Thunderbolt(TM) DCH drivers for Windows before version 88 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27517 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem software before versions 01.00.00.3547, 02.00.00.3915, 03.00.00.0483 may allow an a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27517</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem software before versions 01.00.00.3547, 02.00.00.3915, 03.00.00.0483 may allow an athenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28374 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28374</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28396 | Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Thunderbol(TM) Controllers versions before 41 may allow a privileged user to enable de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28396</link><description>Improper access control in firmware for some Intel(R) Thunderbol(TM) Controllers versions before 41 may allow a privileged user to enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28407 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28407</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28715 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28715</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28720 | Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28720</link><description>Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access..</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28739 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to pot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28739</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) Chipset Driver Software before version 10.1.19444.8378 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28745 | Uncontrolled search path in Intel(R) QSFP+ Configuration Utility software, all versions, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28745</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in Intel(R) QSFP+ Configuration Utility software, all versions, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29153 | Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware before version SPS_E5_06.01.04.002.0 may allow a privileged user to potenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29153</link><description>Uncontrolled resource consumption for some Intel(R) SPS firmware before version SPS_E5_06.01.04.002.0 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29162 | Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) C++ Compiler Classic before version 2021.8 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29162</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in some Intel(R) C++ Compiler Classic before version 2021.8 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30767 | Improper buffer restrictions in Intel(R) Optimization for TensorFlow before version 2.13.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30767</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in Intel(R) Optimization for TensorFlow before version 2.13.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31189 | Improper authentication in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before version egs-1.09 may allow an authenticated user to enable e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31189</link><description>Improper authentication in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before version egs-1.09 may allow an authenticated user to enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31271 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31271</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32280 | Insufficiently protected credentials in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before versions egs-1.05 may allow an unauthenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32280</link><description>Insufficiently protected credentials in some Intel(R) Server Product OpenBMC firmware before versions egs-1.05 may allow an unauthenticated user to enable information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32618 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32618</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) oneAPI Toolkit and component software installers before version 4.3.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32642 | Insufficient adherence to expected conventions for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.24...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32642</link><description>Insufficient adherence to expected conventions for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32644 | Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an una...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32644</link><description>Protection mechanism failure for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32646 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially ena...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32646</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32647 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32647</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32651 | Improper validation of specified type of input for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.24...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32651</link><description>Improper validation of specified type of input for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33870 | Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33870</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33875 | Improper access control for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33875</link><description>Improper access control for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access..</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34315 | Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34315</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34351 | Buffer underflow in some Intel(R) PCM software before version 202307 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34351</link><description>Buffer underflow in some Intel(R) PCM software before version 202307 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34983 | Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34983</link><description>Improper input validation for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35003 | Path transversal in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35003</link><description>Path transversal in some Intel(R) VROC software before version 8.0.8.1001 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35060 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.3.1 may allow an authenticated user to pote...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35060</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool software before version 2.3.1 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35061 | Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthen...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35061</link><description>Improper initialization for some Intel(R) PROSet/Wireless and Intel(R) Killer(TM) Wi-Fi software before version 22.240 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable information disclosure via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35062 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35062</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35121 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2023.2.1 may allow authenticated user to potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35121</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) oneAPI DPC++/C++ Compiler software before version 2023.2.1 may allow authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35769 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10577 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escala...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35769</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) CIP software before version 2.4.10577 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36490 | Improper initialization in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36490</link><description>Improper initialization in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36493 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) SDK for OpenCL(TM) Applications software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable esc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36493</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) SDK for OpenCL(TM) Applications software may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38135 | Improper authorization in some Intel(R) PM software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38135</link><description>Improper authorization in some Intel(R) PM software may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38561 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38561</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) XTU software before version 7.12.0.29 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38566 | Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) ISPC software before version 1.21.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38566</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some Intel(R) ISPC software before version 1.21.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39425 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39425</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) DSA software before version 23.4.33 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39432 | Improper access control element in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software, before versions 28.2, may allow an authenticate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39432</link><description>Improper access control element in some Intel(R) Ethernet tools and driver install software, before versions 28.2, may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39932 | Uncontrolled search path in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow a privillaged user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39932</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow a privillaged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39941 | Improper access control in some Intel(R) SUR software before version 2.4.10587 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39941</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel(R) SUR software before version 2.4.10587 may allow an unauthenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via adjacent access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40154 | Incorrect default permissions in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow privillaged user to potentially en...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40154</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in the Intel(R) SUR for Gameplay Software before version 2.0.1901 may allow privillaged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40156 | Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) SSU software before version 3.0.0.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40156</link><description>Uncontrolled search path element in some Intel(R) SSU software before version 3.0.0.2 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40161 | Improper access control in some Intel Unite(R) Client software before version 4.2.35041 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enabl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40161</link><description>Improper access control in some Intel Unite(R) Client software before version 4.2.35041 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41090 | Race condition in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41090</link><description>Race condition in some Intel(R) MAS software before version 2.3 may allow a privileged user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41091 | Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library Software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41091</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some Intel(R) MPI Library Software before version 2021.11 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41231 | Incorrect default permissions in some ACAT software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potential...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41231</link><description>Incorrect default permissions in some ACAT software maintained by Intel(R) before version 2.0.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable escalation of privilege via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41252 | Out-of-bounds read in some Intel(R) QAT software drivers for Windows before version QAT1.7-W-1.11.0 may allow an authenticated user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41252</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in some Intel(R) QAT software drivers for Windows before version QAT1.7-W-1.11.0 may allow an authenticated user to potentially enable denial of service via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42776 | Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SGX DCAP software for Windows before version 1.19.100.3 may allow an authenticateed user to poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42776</link><description>Improper input validation in some Intel(R) SGX DCAP software for Windows before version 1.19.100.3 may allow an authenticateed user to potentially enable information disclosure via local access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6441 | SQLi in UNI-PA&amp;#x27;s University Information System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6441</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in UNI-PA University Marketing &amp; Computer Internet Trade Inc. University Information System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects University Information System: before 12.12.2023.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23952 | Apache Superset: Allows for uncontrolled resource consumption via a ZIP bomb (version range fix for CVE-2023-46104)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23952</link><description>This is a duplicate for CVE-2023-46104. With correct CVE version ranges for affected Apache Superset.
 
Uncontrolled resource consumption can be triggered by authenticated attacker that uploads a malicious ZIP to import database, dashboards or datasets.  
This vulnerability exists in Apache Superset versions up to and including 2.1.2 and versions 3.0.0, 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 11:19:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23789 | Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23789</link><description>Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary OS command on the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:42:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23784 | Improper access control vulnerability exists in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23784</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability exists in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier, which may allow a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain a username and its hashed password displayed on the management page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23785 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23785</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to change the product settings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23786 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a ne...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23786</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to execute an arbitrary script on the web browser of the user who is accessing the management page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23787 | Path traversal vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23787</link><description>Path traversal vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to obtain an arbitrary file in the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23788 | Server-side request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23788</link><description>Server-side request forgery vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to send an arbitrary HTTP request (GET) from the affected product.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:27:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-23783 | Improper authentication vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-23783</link><description>Improper authentication vulnerability in Energy Management Controller with Cloud Services JH-RVB1 /JH-RV11 Ver.B0.1.9.1 and earlier allows a network-adjacent unauthenticated attacker to access the affected product without authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 10:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48985 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48985</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the login.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48986 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48986</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the users.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48987 | Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48987</link><description>Blind SQL Injection vulnerability in CU Solutions Group (CUSG) Content Management System (CMS) before v.7.75 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code, escalate privileges, and obtain sensitive information via a crafted script to the pages.php component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:41:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44294 | In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44294</link><description>In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern has been identified, where a malicious user with a valid User session may inject malicious content in filters of Collection Rest API. 
This issue may potentially lead to unintentional information disclosure from the product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44293 | In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern ha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44293</link><description>In Dell Secure Connect Gateway Application and Secure Connect Gateway Appliance (between v5.10.00.00 and v5.18.00.00), a security concern has been identified, where a malicious user with a valid User session may inject malicious content in filters of IP Range Rest API. This issue may potentially lead to unintentional information disclosure from the product database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44283 | In Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs (between v3.0 and v3.14.1) and SupportAssist for Business PCs (between v3.0 and v3.4.1), a security conce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44283</link><description>In Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs (between v3.0 and v3.14.1) and SupportAssist for Business PCs (between v3.0 and v3.4.1), a security concern has been identified, impacting locally authenticated users on their respective PCs. This issue may potentially enable privilege escalation and the execution of arbitrary code, in the Windows system context, and confined to that specific local PC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:56:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39249 | Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs version 3.4.0 contains a local Authentication Bypass vulnerability that allows locally authenticated non...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39249</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Business PCs version 3.4.0 contains a local Authentication Bypass vulnerability that allows locally authenticated non-admin users to gain temporary privilege within the SupportAssist User Interface on their respective PC. The Run as Admin temporary privilege feature enables IT/System Administrators to perform driver scans and Dell-recommended driver installations without requiring them to log out of the local non-admin user session. However, the granted privilege is limited solely to the SupportAssist User Interface and automatically expires after 15 minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:42:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25535 | Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs Installer Executable file version prior to 3.13.2.19 used for initial installation has a high vulnerability ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25535</link><description>Dell SupportAssist for Home PCs Installer Executable file version prior to 3.13.2.19 used for initial installation has a high vulnerability that can result in local privilege escalation (LPE). This vulnerability only affects first-time installations done prior to 8th March 2023</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22455 | Dell E-Lab Navigator, [3.1.9, 3.2.0], contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability in Feedback submission. An attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22455</link><description>Dell E-Lab Navigator, [3.1.9, 3.2.0], contains an Insecure Direct Object Reference Vulnerability in Feedback submission. An attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, to manipulate the email's appearance, potentially deceiving recipients and causing reputational and security risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:10:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25125 | Absolute path traversal vulnerability in digdag server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25125</link><description>Digdag is an open source tool that to build, run, schedule, and monitor complex pipelines of tasks across various platforms. Treasure Data's digdag workload automation system is susceptible to a path traversal vulnerability if it's configured to store log files locally. This issue may lead to information disclosure and has been addressed in release version 0.10.5.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 01:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24690 | Zoom Clients  - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24690</link><description>Improper input validation in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct a denial of service via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24691 | Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows  - Improper Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24691</link><description>Improper input validation in Zoom Desktop Client for Windows, Zoom VDI Client for Windows, and Zoom Meeting SDK for Windows may allow an unauthenticated user to conduct an escalation of privilege via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24699 | Zoom Clients  - Business Logic Error</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24699</link><description>Business logic error in some Zoom clients may allow an authenticated user to conduct information disclosure via network access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>