<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:51:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-10640 | Missing Server-Side Authentication Checks in EfficientLab WorkExaminer Professional</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10640</link><description>An unauthenticated attacker with access to TCP port 12306 of the WorkExaminer server can exploit missing server-side authentication checks to bypass the login prompt in the WorkExaminer Professional console to gain administrative access to the WorkExaminer server and therefore all sensitive monitoring data. This includes monitored screenshots and keystrokes of all users.

The WorkExaminer Professional console is used for administrative access to the server. Before access to the console is granted administrators must login. Internally, a custom protocol is used to call a respective stored procedure on the MSSQL database. The return value of the call is not validated on the server-side. Instead it is only validated client-side which allows to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9428 | SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9428</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Analytics Plus versions 6171 and prior are vulnerable to authenticated SQL Injection via the key update api.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10639 | Usage of Hardcoded FTP Credentials EfficientLab WorkExaminer Professional</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10639</link><description>The WorkExaminer Professional server installation comes with an FTP server that is used to receive the client logs on TCP port 12304. An attacker with network access to this port can use weak hardcoded credentials to login to the FTP server and modify or read data, log files and gain remote code execution as NT Authority\SYSTEM on the server by exchanging accessible service binaries in the WorkExaminer installation directory (e.g. "C:\Program File (x86)\Work Examiner Professional Server").</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:42:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7473 | XML Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7473</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine EndPoint Central versions 11.4.2516.1 and prior are vulnerable to XML Injection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:22:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5496 | Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5496</link><description>ZohoCorp ManageEngine Endpoint Central versions earlier than 11.4.2508.14, 11.4.2516.06, and 11.4.2518.01 are affected by an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in the agent setup component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 10:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10612 | XSS in GiSoft&amp;#x27;s City Guide</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10612</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in giSoft Information Technologies City Guide allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects City Guide: before 1.4.45.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 08:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26392 | SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26392</link><description>SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted is susceptible to SQL injection vulnerability that may display sensitive data using a low-level account. This vulnerability requires authentication from a low-privilege account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11949 | Digiwin｜EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11949</link><description>EasyFlow .NET and EasyFlow AiNet, developed by Digiwin, has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to obtain database administrator credentials via a specific functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 06:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12004 | The compare API module breaks Extension:Lockdown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12004</link><description>Incorrect Permission Assignment for Critical Resource vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Lockdown Extension allows Privilege Abuse. Fixed in Mediawiki Core Action APIThis issue affects Mediawiki - Lockdown Extension: from master before 1.42.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 06:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10916 | FormGent &amp;lt; 1.0.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10916</link><description>The FormGent  WordPress plugin before 1.0.4 is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 06:17:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62701 | Stored XSS through system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62701</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - Wikistories allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - Wikistories: from master before 1.44.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:55:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62702 | Stored XSS through system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62702</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - PageTriage Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - PageTriage Extension: from master before 1.44.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62694 | Stored XSS through a system message</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - WikiLove Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - WikiLove Extension: 1.39.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:46:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62695 | Stored XSS through system messages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - WikiLambda Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - WikiLambda Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62696 | Multiple critical security issues in Springboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in a Command ('Command Injection') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki Foundation - Springboard Extension allows Command Injection.This issue affects Mediawiki Foundation - Springboard Extension: master.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62699 | Special:Translate tool do not use the correct IP and User-Agent in the CheckUser tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62699</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - CheckUser Extension allows Footprinting.This issue affects Mediawiki - CheckUser Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 04:02:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8078 | A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.40, USG FLEX series firmwa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8078</link><description>A post-authentication command injection vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.40, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.40, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.40, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.40 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to execute operating system (OS) commands on the affected device by passing a crafted string as an argument to a CLI command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 02:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9133 | A missing authorization vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.40, USG FLEX series firmware versions from...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9133</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability in Zyxel ATP series firmware versions from V4.32 through V5.40, USG FLEX series firmware versions from V4.50 through V5.40, USG FLEX 50(W) series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.40, and USG20(W)-VPN series firmware versions from V4.16 through V5.40 could allow a semi-authenticated attacker—who has completed only the first stage of the two-factor authentication (2FA) process—to view and download the system configuration from an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 02:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6541 | OS command injection using information obtained from the web management interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6541</link><description>An arbitrary OS command may be executed on the product by the user who can log in to the web management interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6542 | OS command injection in multiple parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6542</link><description>An arbitrary OS command may be executed on the product by the user who can log in to the web management interface.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:24:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7850 | Authenticated OS command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7850</link><description>A command injection vulnerability may be exploited after the admin's authentication on the web portal on Omada gateways.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7851 | Unauthorized root access via debug functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7851</link><description>An attacker may obtain the root shell on the underlying OS system with the restricted conditions on Omada gateways.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:24:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12001 | Incorrect Content-Type Header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12001</link><description>Lack of application manifest sanitation could lead to potential stored XSS.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11536 | Element Pack Addons for Elementor &amp;lt;= 8.2.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11536</link><description>The Element Pack Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.5 via the wp_ajax_import_elementor_template action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25118 | GeoVision Command Injection RCE via /PictureCatch.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25118</link><description>GeoVision embedded IP devices, confirmed on GV-BX1500 and GV-MFD1501, contain a remote command injection vulnerability via /PictureCatch.cgi that enables an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the device. VulnCheck has observed this vulnerability being exploited in the wild as of 2025-10-19 08:55:13.141502 UTC.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54764 | Mbed TLS before 3.6.5 allows a local timing attack against certain RSA operations, and direct calls to mbedtls_mpi_mod_inv or mbedtls_mpi_gc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54764</link><description>Mbed TLS before 3.6.5 allows a local timing attack against certain RSA operations, and direct calls to mbedtls_mpi_mod_inv or mbedtls_mpi_gcd.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61301 | Denial-of-analysis in reporting/mongodb.py and reporting/jsondump.py in CAPEv2 (commit 52e4b43, on 2025-05-17) allows attackers who can subm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61301</link><description>Denial-of-analysis in reporting/mongodb.py and reporting/jsondump.py in CAPEv2 (commit 52e4b43, on 2025-05-17) allows attackers who can submit samples to cause incomplete or missing behavioral analysis reports by generating deeply nested or oversized behavior data that trigger MongoDB BSON limits or orjson recursion errors when the sample executes in the sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61303 | Hatching Triage Sandbox Windows 10 build 2004 (2025-08-14) and Windows 10 LTSC 2021(2025-08-14) contains a vulnerability in its Windows beha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61303</link><description>Hatching Triage Sandbox Windows 10 build 2004 (2025-08-14) and Windows 10 LTSC 2021(2025-08-14) contains a vulnerability in its Windows behavioral analysis engine that allows a submitted malware sample to evade detection and cause denial-of-analysis. The vulnerability is triggered when a sample recursively spawns a large number of child processes, generating high log volume and exhausting system resources. As a result, key malicious behavior, including PowerShell execution and reverse shell activity, may not be recorded or reported, misleading analysts and compromising the integrity and availability of sandboxed analysis results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60781 | PHP Education Manager v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the worksheet.php file via the participant_name parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60781</link><description>PHP Education Manager v1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in the worksheet.php file via the participant_name parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:41:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60783 | There is a SQL injection vulnerability in Restaurant Management System DBMS Project v1.0 via login.php. The vulnerability allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60783</link><description>There is a SQL injection vulnerability in Restaurant Management System DBMS Project v1.0 via login.php. The vulnerability allows attackers to manipulate the application's database through specially crafted SQL query strings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62656 | GlobalBlocking Special:GlobalBlockList vulnerable to message key stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62656</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki GlobalBlocking extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki GlobalBlocking extension: 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62657 | Stored XSS through system messages in PageForms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki PageForms extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects MediaWiki PageForms extension: 1.44.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62658 | SQL injection in WatchAnalytics through Special:ClearPendingReviews</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62658</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation MediaWiki WatchAnalytics extension allows SQL Injection.This issue affects MediaWiki WatchAnalytics extension: 1.43, 1.44.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62522 | vite allows server.fs.deny bypass via backslash on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62522</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for JavaScript. In versions from 2.9.18 to before 3.0.0, 3.2.9 to before 4.0.0, 4.5.3 to before 5.0.0, 5.2.6 to before 5.4.21, 6.0.0 to before 6.4.1, 7.0.0 to before 7.0.8, and 7.1.0 to before 7.1.11, files denied by server.fs.deny were sent if the URL ended with \ when the dev server is running on Windows. Only apps explicitly exposing the Vite dev server to the network and running the dev server on Windows were affected. This issue has been patched in versions 5.4.21, 6.4.1, 7.0.8, and 7.1.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62527 | Taguette vulnerable to password reset link poisoning</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62527</link><description>Taguette is an open source qualitative research tool. An issue has been discovered in Taguette versions prior to 1.5.0. It was possible for an attacker to request password reset email containing a malicious link, allowing the attacker to set the email if clicked by the victim. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62528 | Taguette cross-site scripting vulnerability via tag name, tag description, document name and document description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62528</link><description>Taguette is an open source qualitative research tool. An issue has been discovered in Taguette versions prior to 1.5.0. It was possible for a project member to put JavaScript in name or description fields which would run on project load. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8052 | HQL Injection vulnerability has been discovered in Opentext Flipper.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8052</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in opentext Flipper allows SQL Injection. 

The vulnerability could allow a low privilege user to interact with the database in unintended ways and extract data by interacting with the HQL processor.

This issue affects Flipper: 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8048 | External Control of File path vulnerability has been discovered on Openext Flipper.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8048</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in opentext Flipper allows Path Traversal. The vulnerability could allow a user to submit a stored local file
path and then download the specified file from the system by requesting the
stored document ID.







This issue affects Flipper: 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8049 | Insufficient Access Control vulnerability has been discovered in OpenText Flipper.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8049</link><description>Insufficient Granularity of Access Control vulnerability in opentext Flipper allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. The vulnerability could allow a low-privilege user to elevate privileges within the application.

This issue affects Flipper: 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8051 | Path traversal validation vulnerability has been discovered in opentext Flipper.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8051</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in opentext Flipper allows Absolute Path Traversal. 

The vulnerability could allow a user to access files hosted on the server.

This issue affects Flipper: 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8053 | Insufficient access control vulnerability has been discovered in Opentext Flipper.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8053</link><description>Insufficient Granularity of Access Control vulnerability in opentext Flipper allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. The vulnerability could allow a low privilege user to interact with the backend API without sufficient privileges.

This issue affects Flipper: 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62697 | Improperly sanitized style parameter in LanguageSelector</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements in Output Used by a Downstream Component ('Injection') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - LanguageSelector Extension allows Code Injection.This issue affects Mediawiki - LanguageSelector Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5517 | Heap Memory Corruption Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5517</link><description>Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability in ABB Terra AC wallbox (UL40/80A), ABB Terra AC wallbox (UL32A), ABB Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC MID, ABB Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC Juno CE, ABB Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC PTB, ABB Terra AC wallbox (JP).This issue affects Terra AC wallbox (UL40/80A): through 1.8.32; Terra AC wallbox (UL32A): through 1.8.2; Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC MID: through 1.8.32; Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC Juno CE: through 1.8.32; Terra AC wallbox (MID/ CE) -Terra AC PTB: through 1.8.21; Terra AC wallbox (JP): through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61488 | An issue in Senayan Library Management System (SLiMS) 9 Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the scrap_imag...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61488</link><description>An issue in Senayan Library Management System (SLiMS) 9 Bulian v.9.6.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the scrap_image.php component and the imageURL parameter</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62698 | Stored XSS through system messages in ExternalGuidance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62698</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - ExternalGuidance allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - ExternalGuidance: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62700 | Stored XSS through a system message in MultiBoilerplate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - MultiBoilerplate Extensionmaste allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - MultiBoilerplate Extensionmaste: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11979 | Use-after-free in the MongoDB server query planner may lead to crash or undefined behavior</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11979</link><description>An authorized user may crash the MongoDB server by causing buffer over-read. This can be done by issuing a DDL operation while queries are being issued, under some conditions. This issue affects MongoDB Server v7.0 versions prior to 7.0.25, MongoDB Server v8.0 versions prior to 8.0.15, and MongoDB Server version 8.2.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3465 | Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3465</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in ABB CoreSense™ HM, ABB CoreSense™ M10.This issue affects CoreSense™ HM: through 2.3.1; CoreSense™ M10: through 1.4.1.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47901 | RCE on restore configuration password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Microchip Time Provider 4100 allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Time Provider 4100: before 2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47902 | SQL Injection in web resource</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47902</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Microchip Time Provider 4100 allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Time Provider 4100: before 2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55086 | In NetXDuo version before 6.4.4, a networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, in the DHCPV6 client there was an unchecked ind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55086</link><description>In NetXDuo version before 6.4.4, a networking support module for Eclipse Foundation ThreadX, in the DHCPV6 client there was an unchecked index extracting the server DUID from the server reply. With a crafted packet, an attacker could cause an out of memory read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62693 | Stored XSS through system messages in LastModified</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in The Wikimedia Foundation Mediawiki - LastModified Extension allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Mediawiki - LastModified Extension: from master before 1.39.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:14:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47900 | RCE on backup configuration password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47900</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Microchip Time Provider 4100 allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Time Provider 4100: before 2.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62509 | FileRise improper ownership/permission validation allowed cross-tenant file operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62509</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web-based file manager with multi-file upload, editing, and batch operations. Prior to version 1.4.0, a business logic flaw in FileRise’s file/folder handling allows low-privilege users to perform unauthorized operations (view/delete/modify) on files created by other users. The root cause was inferring ownership/visibility from folder names (e.g., a folder named after a username) and missing server-side authorization/ownership checks across file operation endpoints. This amounted to an IDOR pattern: an attacker could operate on resources identified only by predictable names. This issue has been patched in version 1.4.0 and further hardened in version 1.5.0. A workaround for this issue involves restricting non-admin users to read-only or disable delete/rename APIs server-side, avoid creating top-level folders named after other usernames, and adding server-side checks that verify ownership before delete/rename/move.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:43:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62510 | FileRise insecure folder visibility via name-based mapping and incomplete ACL checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62510</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web-based file manager with multi-file upload, editing, and batch operations. In version 1.4.0, a regression allowed folder visibility/ownership to be inferred from folder names. Low-privilege users could see or interact with folders matching their username and, in some cases, other users’ content. This issue has been patched in version 1.5.0, where it introduces explicit per-folder ACLs (owners/read/write/share/read_own) and strict server-side checks across list, read, write, share, rename, copy/move, zip, and WebDAV paths.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:43:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-9574 | Missing Authentication Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-9574</link><description>Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in ABB ALS-mini-s4 IP, ABB ALS-mini-s8 IP.This issue affects . 

All firmware versions with the Serial Number from 2000 to 5166</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:12:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62429 | ClipBucket v5 executes arbitrary PHP code</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62429</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Prior to version 5.5.2 #147, ClipBucket v5 is vulnerable to arbitrary PHP code execution. In /upload/admin_area/actions/update_launch.php, the "type" parameter from a POST request is embedded into PHP tags and executed. Proper sanitization is not performed, and by injecting malicious code an attacker can execute arbitrary PHP code. This allows an attacker to achieve RCE. This issue has been resolved in version 5.5.2 #147.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:42:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6515 | Reuse of session IDs in oatpp-mcp leads to session hijacking and prompt hijacking by remote attackers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6515</link><description>The MCP SSE endpoint in oatpp-mcp returns an instance pointer as the session ID, which is not unique nor cryptographically secure. This allows network attackers with access to the oatpp-mcp server to guess future session IDs and hijack legitimate client MCP sessions, returning malicious responses from the oatpp-mcp server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:42:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60856 | Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W allows root shell access through an unsecured UART/serial console. An attacker with physical acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60856</link><description>Reolink Video Doorbell WiFi DB_566128M5MP_W allows root shell access through an unsecured UART/serial console. An attacker with physical access can connect to the exposed interface and execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10678 | Admin with default credentials in NetBird VPN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10678</link><description>NetBird VPN when installed using vendor's provided script failed to remove or change default password of an admin account created by ZITADEL.
This issue affects instances installed using vendor's provided script. This issue may affect instances created with Docker if the default password was not changed nor the user was removed.

This issue has been fixed in version 0.57.0</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55568 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55568</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 9110, W920, W930, W1000, Modem 5123, Modem 5300, Modem 5400. The absence of a NULL check leads to a Denial of Service when an attacker sends malformed MM packets to the target.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40017 | media: iris: Fix memory leak by freeing untracked persist buffer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40017</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: iris: Fix memory leak by freeing untracked persist buffer

One internal buffer which is allocated only once per session was not
being freed during session close because it was not being tracked as
part of internal buffer list which resulted in a memory leak.

Add the necessary logic to explicitly free the untracked internal buffer
during session close to ensure all allocated memory is released
properly.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26781 | An issue was discovered in L2 in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26781</link><description>An issue was discovered in L2 in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 9110, W920, W930, Modem 5123, and Modem 5300. Incorrect handling of RLC AM PDUs leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26782 | An issue was discovered in L2 in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26782</link><description>An issue was discovered in L2 in Samsung Mobile Processor, Wearable Processor, and Modem Exynos 9820, 9825, 980, 990, 850, 1080, 2100, 1280, 2200, 1330, 1380, 1480, 9110, W920, W930, Modem 5123, and Modem 5300. Incorrect handling of RLC AM PDUs leads to a Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40005 | spi: cadence-quadspi: Implement refcount to handle unbind during busy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40005</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

spi: cadence-quadspi: Implement refcount to handle unbind during busy

driver support indirect read and indirect write operation with
assumption no force device removal(unbind) operation. However
force device removal(removal) is still available to root superuser.

Unbinding driver during operation causes kernel crash. This changes
ensure driver able to handle such operation for indirect read and
indirect write by implementing refcount to track attached devices
to the controller and gracefully wait and until attached devices
remove operation completed before proceed with removal operation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40006 | mm/hugetlb: fix folio is still mapped when deleted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40006</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/hugetlb: fix folio is still mapped when deleted

Migration may be raced with fallocating hole.  remove_inode_single_folio
will unmap the folio if the folio is still mapped.  However, it's called
without folio lock.  If the folio is migrated and the mapped pte has been
converted to migration entry, folio_mapped() returns false, and won't
unmap it.  Due to extra refcount held by remove_inode_single_folio,
migration fails, restores migration entry to normal pte, and the folio is
mapped again.  As a result, we triggered BUG in filemap_unaccount_folio.

The log is as follows:
 BUG: Bad page cache in process hugetlb  pfn:156c00
 page: refcount:515 mapcount:0 mapping:0000000099fef6e1 index:0x0 pfn:0x156c00
 head: order:9 mapcount:1 entire_mapcount:1 nr_pages_mapped:0 pincount:0
 aops:hugetlbfs_aops ino:dcc dentry name(?):"my_hugepage_file"
 flags: 0x17ffffc00000c1(locked|waiters|head|node=0|zone=2|lastcpupid=0x1fffff)
 page_type: f4(hugetlb)
 page dumped because: still mapped when deleted
 CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 395 Comm: hugetlb Not tainted 6.17.0-rc5-00044-g7aac71907bde-dirty #484 NONE
 Hardware name: QEMU Ubuntu 24.04 PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 0.0.0 02/06/2015
 Call Trace:
  
  dump_stack_lvl+0x4f/0x70
  filemap_unaccount_folio+0xc4/0x1c0
  __filemap_remove_folio+0x38/0x1c0
  filemap_remove_folio+0x41/0xd0
  remove_inode_hugepages+0x142/0x250
  hugetlbfs_fallocate+0x471/0x5a0
  vfs_fallocate+0x149/0x380

Hold folio lock before checking if the folio is mapped to avold race with
migration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40007 | netfs: fix reference leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40007</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: fix reference leak

Commit 20d72b00ca81 ("netfs: Fix the request's work item to not
require a ref") modified netfs_alloc_request() to initialize the
reference counter to 2 instead of 1.  The rationale was that the
requet's "work" would release the second reference after completion
(via netfs_{read,write}_collection_worker()).  That works most of the
time if all goes well.

However, it leaks this additional reference if the request is released
before the I/O operation has been submitted: the error code path only
decrements the reference counter once and the work item will never be
queued because there will never be a completion.

This has caused outages of our whole server cluster today because
tasks were blocked in netfs_wait_for_outstanding_io(), leading to
deadlocks in Ceph (another bug that I will address soon in another
patch).  This was caused by a netfs_pgpriv2_begin_copy_to_cache() call
which failed in fscache_begin_write_operation().  The leaked
netfs_io_request was never completed, leaving `netfs_inode.io_count`
with a positive value forever.

All of this is super-fragile code.  Finding out which code paths will
lead to an eventual completion and which do not is hard to see:

- Some functions like netfs_create_write_req() allocate a request, but
  will never submit any I/O.

- netfs_unbuffered_read_iter_locked() calls netfs_unbuffered_read()
  and then netfs_put_request(); however, netfs_unbuffered_read() can
  also fail early before submitting the I/O request, therefore another
  netfs_put_request() call must be added there.

A rule of thumb is that functions that return a `netfs_io_request` do
not submit I/O, and all of their callers must be checked.

For my taste, the whole netfs code needs an overhaul to make reference
counting easier to understand and less fragile &amp; obscure.  But to fix
this bug here and now and produce a patch that is adequate for a
stable backport, I tried a minimal approach that quickly frees the
request object upon early failure.

I decided against adding a second netfs_put_request() each time
because that would cause code duplication which obscures the code
further.  Instead, I added the function netfs_put_failed_request()
which frees such a failed request synchronously under the assumption
that the reference count is exactly 2 (as initially set by
netfs_alloc_request() and never touched), verified by a
WARN_ON_ONCE().  It then deinitializes the request object (without
going through the "cleanup_work" indirection) and frees the allocation
(with RCU protection to protect against concurrent access by
netfs_requests_seq_start()).

All code paths that fail early have been changed to call
netfs_put_failed_request() instead of netfs_put_request().
Additionally, I have added a netfs_put_request() call to
netfs_unbuffered_read() as explained above because the
netfs_put_failed_request() approach does not work there.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40008 | kmsan: fix out-of-bounds access to shadow memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40008</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

kmsan: fix out-of-bounds access to shadow memory

Running sha224_kunit on a KMSAN-enabled kernel results in a crash in
kmsan_internal_set_shadow_origin():

    BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: ffffbc3840291000
    #PF: supervisor read access in kernel mode
    #PF: error_code(0x0000) - not-present page
    PGD 1810067 P4D 1810067 PUD 192d067 PMD 3c17067 PTE 0
    Oops: 0000 [#1] SMP NOPTI
    CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 81 Comm: kunit_try_catch Tainted: G                 N  6.17.0-rc3 #10 PREEMPT(voluntary)
    Tainted: [N]=TEST
    Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.17.0-0-gb52ca86e094d-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
    RIP: 0010:kmsan_internal_set_shadow_origin+0x91/0x100
    [...]
    Call Trace:
    
    __msan_memset+0xee/0x1a0
    sha224_final+0x9e/0x350
    test_hash_buffer_overruns+0x46f/0x5f0
    ? kmsan_get_shadow_origin_ptr+0x46/0xa0
    ? __pfx_test_hash_buffer_overruns+0x10/0x10
    kunit_try_run_case+0x198/0xa00

This occurs when memset() is called on a buffer that is not 4-byte aligned
and extends to the end of a guard page, i.e.  the next page is unmapped.

The bug is that the loop at the end of kmsan_internal_set_shadow_origin()
accesses the wrong shadow memory bytes when the address is not 4-byte
aligned.  Since each 4 bytes are associated with an origin, it rounds the
address and size so that it can access all the origins that contain the
buffer.  However, when it checks the corresponding shadow bytes for a
particular origin, it incorrectly uses the original unrounded shadow
address.  This results in reads from shadow memory beyond the end of the
buffer's shadow memory, which crashes when that memory is not mapped.

To fix this, correctly align the shadow address before accessing the 4
shadow bytes corresponding to each origin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40009 | fs/proc/task_mmu: check p-&amp;gt;vec_buf for NULL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40009</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

fs/proc/task_mmu: check p-&gt;vec_buf for NULL

When the PAGEMAP_SCAN ioctl is invoked with vec_len = 0 reaches
pagemap_scan_backout_range(), kernel panics with null-ptr-deref:

[   44.936808] Oops: general protection fault, probably for non-canonical address 0xdffffc0000000000: 0000 [#1] SMP DEBUG_PAGEALLOC KASAN NOPTI
[   44.937797] KASAN: null-ptr-deref in range [0x0000000000000000-0x0000000000000007]
[   44.938391] CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 2480 Comm: reproducer Not tainted 6.17.0-rc6 #22 PREEMPT(none)
[   44.939062] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.3-0-ga6ed6b701f0a-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
[   44.939935] RIP: 0010:pagemap_scan_thp_entry.isra.0+0x741/0xa80



[   44.946828] Call Trace:
[   44.947030]  
[   44.949219]  pagemap_scan_pmd_entry+0xec/0xfa0
[   44.952593]  walk_pmd_range.isra.0+0x302/0x910
[   44.954069]  walk_pud_range.isra.0+0x419/0x790
[   44.954427]  walk_p4d_range+0x41e/0x620
[   44.954743]  walk_pgd_range+0x31e/0x630
[   44.955057]  __walk_page_range+0x160/0x670
[   44.956883]  walk_page_range_mm+0x408/0x980
[   44.958677]  walk_page_range+0x66/0x90
[   44.958984]  do_pagemap_scan+0x28d/0x9c0
[   44.961833]  do_pagemap_cmd+0x59/0x80
[   44.962484]  __x64_sys_ioctl+0x18d/0x210
[   44.962804]  do_syscall_64+0x5b/0x290
[   44.963111]  entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

vec_len = 0 in pagemap_scan_init_bounce_buffer() means no buffers are
allocated and p-&gt;vec_buf remains set to NULL.

This breaks an assumption made later in pagemap_scan_backout_range(), that
page_region is always allocated for p-&gt;vec_buf_index.

Fix it by explicitly checking p-&gt;vec_buf for NULL before dereferencing.

Other sites that might run into same deref-issue are already (directly or
transitively) protected by checking p-&gt;vec_buf.

Note:
From PAGEMAP_SCAN man page, it seems vec_len = 0 is valid when no output
is requested and it's only the side effects caller is interested in,
hence it passes check in pagemap_scan_get_args().

This issue was found by syzkaller.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40010 | afs: Fix potential null pointer dereference in afs_put_server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40010</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

afs: Fix potential null pointer dereference in afs_put_server

afs_put_server() accessed server-&gt;debug_id before the NULL check, which
could lead to a null pointer dereference. Move the debug_id assignment,
ensuring we never dereference a NULL server pointer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40011 | drm/gma500: Fix null dereference in hdmi teardown</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40011</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/gma500: Fix null dereference in hdmi teardown

pci_set_drvdata sets the value of pdev-&gt;driver_data to NULL,
after which the driver_data obtained from the same dev is
dereferenced in oaktrail_hdmi_i2c_exit, and the i2c_dev is
extracted from it. To prevent this, swap these calls.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with Svacer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40012 | net/smc: fix warning in smc_rx_splice() when calling get_page()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40012</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/smc: fix warning in smc_rx_splice() when calling get_page()

smc_lo_register_dmb() allocates DMB buffers with kzalloc(), which are
later passed to get_page() in smc_rx_splice(). Since kmalloc memory is
not page-backed, this triggers WARN_ON_ONCE() in get_page() and prevents
holding a refcount on the buffer. This can lead to use-after-free if
the memory is released before splice_to_pipe() completes.

Use folio_alloc() instead, ensuring DMBs are page-backed and safe for
get_page().

WARNING: CPU: 18 PID: 12152 at ./include/linux/mm.h:1330 smc_rx_splice+0xaf8/0xe20 [smc]
CPU: 18 UID: 0 PID: 12152 Comm: smcapp Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.17.0-rc3-11705-g9cf4672ecfee #10 NONE
Hardware name: IBM 3931 A01 704 (z/VM 7.4.0)
Krnl PSW : 0704e00180000000 000793161032696c (smc_rx_splice+0xafc/0xe20 [smc])
           R:0 T:1 IO:1 EX:1 Key:0 M:1 W:0 P:0 AS:3 CC:2 PM:0 RI:0 EA:3
Krnl GPRS: 0000000000000000 001cee80007d3001 00077400000000f8 0000000000000005
           0000000000000001 001cee80007d3006 0007740000001000 001c000000000000
           000000009b0c99e0 0000000000001000 001c0000000000f8 001c000000000000
           000003ffcc6f7c88 0007740003e98000 0007931600000005 000792969b2ff7b8
Krnl Code: 0007931610326960: af000000		mc	0,0
           0007931610326964: a7f4ff43		brc	15,00079316103267ea
          #0007931610326968: af000000		mc	0,0
          &gt;000793161032696c: a7f4ff3f		brc	15,00079316103267ea
           0007931610326970: e320f1000004	lg	%r2,256(%r15)
           0007931610326976: c0e53fd1b5f5	brasl	%r14,000793168fd5d560
           000793161032697c: a7f4fbb5		brc	15,00079316103260e6
           0007931610326980: b904002b		lgr	%r2,%r11
Call Trace:
 smc_rx_splice+0xafc/0xe20 [smc]
 smc_rx_splice+0x756/0xe20 [smc])
 smc_rx_recvmsg+0xa74/0xe00 [smc]
 smc_splice_read+0x1ce/0x3b0 [smc]
 sock_splice_read+0xa2/0xf0
 do_splice_read+0x198/0x240
 splice_file_to_pipe+0x7e/0x110
 do_splice+0x59e/0xde0
 __do_splice+0x11a/0x2d0
 __s390x_sys_splice+0x140/0x1f0
 __do_syscall+0x122/0x280
 system_call+0x6e/0x90
Last Breaking-Event-Address:
smc_rx_splice+0x960/0xe20 [smc]
---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40013 | ASoC: qcom: audioreach: fix potential null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40013</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ASoC: qcom: audioreach: fix potential null pointer dereference

It is possible that the topology parsing function
audioreach_widget_load_module_common() could return NULL or an error
pointer. Add missing NULL check so that we do not dereference it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40015 | media: stm32-csi: Fix dereference before NULL check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40015</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: stm32-csi: Fix dereference before NULL check

In 'stm32_csi_start', 'csidev-&gt;s_subdev' is dereferenced directly while
assigning a value to the 'src_pad'. However the same value is being
checked against NULL at a later point of time indicating that there
are chances that the value can be NULL.

Move the dereference after the NULL check.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40016 | media: uvcvideo: Mark invalid entities with id UVC_INVALID_ENTITY_ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40016</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: uvcvideo: Mark invalid entities with id UVC_INVALID_ENTITY_ID

Per UVC 1.1+ specification 3.7.2, units and terminals must have a non-zero
unique ID.

```
Each Unit and Terminal within the video function is assigned a unique
identification number, the Unit ID (UID) or Terminal ID (TID), contained in
the bUnitID or bTerminalID field of the descriptor. The value 0x00 is
reserved for undefined ID,
```

If we add a new entity with id 0 or a duplicated ID, it will be marked
as UVC_INVALID_ENTITY_ID.

In a previous attempt commit 3dd075fe8ebb ("media: uvcvideo: Require
entities to have a non-zero unique ID"), we ignored all the invalid units,
this broke a lot of non-compatible cameras. Hopefully we are more lucky
this time.

This also prevents some syzkaller reproducers from triggering warnings due
to a chain of entities referring to themselves. In one particular case, an
Output Unit is connected to an Input Unit, both with the same ID of 1. But
when looking up for the source ID of the Output Unit, that same entity is
found instead of the input entity, which leads to such warnings.

In another case, a backward chain was considered finished as the source ID
was 0. Later on, that entity was found, but its pads were not valid.

Here is a sample stack trace for one of those cases.

[   20.650953] usb 1-1: new high-speed USB device number 2 using dummy_hcd
[   20.830206] usb 1-1: Using ep0 maxpacket: 8
[   20.833501] usb 1-1: config 0 descriptor??
[   21.038518] usb 1-1: string descriptor 0 read error: -71
[   21.038893] usb 1-1: Found UVC 0.00 device  (2833:0201)
[   21.039299] uvcvideo 1-1:0.0: Entity type for entity Output 1 was not initialized!
[   21.041583] uvcvideo 1-1:0.0: Entity type for entity Input 1 was not initialized!
[   21.042218] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[   21.042536] WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 9 at drivers/media/mc/mc-entity.c:1147 media_create_pad_link+0x2c4/0x2e0
[   21.043195] Modules linked in:
[   21.043535] CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 9 Comm: kworker/0:1 Not tainted 6.11.0-rc7-00030-g3480e43aeccf #444
[   21.044101] Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (Q35 + ICH9, 2009), BIOS 1.15.0-1 04/01/2014
[   21.044639] Workqueue: usb_hub_wq hub_event
[   21.045100] RIP: 0010:media_create_pad_link+0x2c4/0x2e0
[   21.045508] Code: fe e8 20 01 00 00 b8 f4 ff ff ff 48 83 c4 30 5b 41 5c 41 5d 41 5e 41 5f 5d c3 cc cc cc cc 0f 0b eb e9 0f 0b eb 0a 0f 0b eb 06 &lt;0f&gt; 0b eb 02 0f 0b b8 ea ff ff ff eb d4 66 2e 0f 1f 84 00 00 00 00
[   21.046801] RSP: 0018:ffffc9000004b318 EFLAGS: 00010246
[   21.047227] RAX: ffff888004e5d458 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: ffffffff818fccf1
[   21.047719] RDX: 000000000000007b RSI: 0000000000000000 RDI: ffff888004313290
[   21.048241] RBP: ffff888004313290 R08: 0001ffffffffffff R09: 0000000000000000
[   21.048701] R10: 0000000000000013 R11: 0001888004313290 R12: 0000000000000003
[   21.049138] R13: ffff888004313080 R14: ffff888004313080 R15: 0000000000000000
[   21.049648] FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff88803ec00000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
[   21.050271] CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
[   21.050688] CR2: 0000592cc27635b0 CR3: 000000000431c000 CR4: 0000000000750ef0
[   21.051136] PKRU: 55555554
[   21.051331] Call Trace:
[   21.051480]  
[   21.051611]  ? __warn+0xc4/0x210
[   21.051861]  ? media_create_pad_link+0x2c4/0x2e0
[   21.052252]  ? report_bug+0x11b/0x1a0
[   21.052540]  ? trace_hardirqs_on+0x31/0x40
[   21.052901]  ? handle_bug+0x3d/0x70
[   21.053197]  ? exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x50
[   21.053511]  ? asm_exc_invalid_op+0x1a/0x20
[   21.053924]  ? media_create_pad_link+0x91/0x2e0
[   21.054364]  ? media_create_pad_link+0x2c4/0x2e0
[   21.054834]  ? media_create_pad_link+0x91/0x2e0
[   21.055131]  ? _raw_spin_unlock+0x1e/0x40
[   21.055441]  ? __v4l2_device_register_subdev+0x202/0x210
[   21.055837]  uvc_mc_register_entities+0x358/0x400
[   21.056144]  uvc_register_chains+0x1
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48025 | In Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 1280, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, W920, W930, and W1000, there is an improp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48025</link><description>In Samsung Mobile Processor and Wearable Processor Exynos 980, 1280, 1330, 1380, 1480, 2400, 1580, W920, W930, and W1000, there is an improper access control vulnerability related to a log file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61417 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in TastyIgniter 3.7.7, affecting the /admin/media_manager component. Attackers can upload a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61417</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in TastyIgniter 3.7.7, affecting the /admin/media_manager component. Attackers can upload a malicious SVG file containing JavaScript code. When an administrator previews the file, the code executes in their browser context, allowing the attacker to perform unauthorized actions such as modifying the admin account credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54957 | An issue was discovered in Dolby UDC 4.5 through 4.13. A crash of the DD+ decoder process can occur when a malformed DD+ bitstream is proces...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54957</link><description>An issue was discovered in Dolby UDC 4.5 through 4.13. A crash of the DD+ decoder process can occur when a malformed DD+ bitstream is processed. When Evolution data is processed by evo_priv.c from the DD+ bitstream, the decoder writes that data into a buffer. The length calculation for a write can overflow due to an integer wraparound. This can lead to the allocated buffer being too small, and the out-of-bounds check of the subsequent write to be ineffective, leading to an out-of-bounds write.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57738 | Apache Syncope: Remote Code Execution by delegated administrators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57738</link><description>Apache Syncope offers the ability to extend / customize the base behavior on every deployment by allowing to provide custom implementations of a few Java interfaces; such implementations can be provided either as Java or Groovy classes, with the latter being particularly attractive as the machinery is set for runtime reload.
Such a feature has been available for a while, but recently it was discovered that a malicious administrator can inject Groovy code that can be executed remotely by a running Apache Syncope Core instance.
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.0.14 / 4.0.2, which fix this issue by forcing the Groovy code to run in a sandbox.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:48:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61456 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the index endpoint. Unsanitized input...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61456</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the index endpoint. Unsanitized input in the /index parameter is directly reflected back into the response HTML, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of a user who visits a malicious link or submits a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8884 | IDOR in VHS Electronic Software&amp;#x27;s ACE Center</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8884</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in VHS Electronic Software Ltd. Co. ACE Center allows Privilege Abuse, Exploitation of Trusted Identifiers.This issue affects ACE Center: before 3.10.161.2255.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41390 | An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in the git functionality of Truffle Security Co. TruffleHog 3.90.2. A specially crafted rep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41390</link><description>An arbitrary code execution vulnerability exists in the git functionality of Truffle Security Co. TruffleHog 3.90.2. A specially crafted repository can lead to a arbitrary code execution. An attacker can provide a malicious respository to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11680 | Out-of-bounds Write in libwebsockets PNG parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11680</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write in unfilter_scanline in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_UPNG flag is enabled during compilation and the HTML display stack is used, to write past a heap allocated buffer possibly causing a crash, when the user visits an attacker controlled website that contains a crafted PNG file with a big width value that causes an integer overflow which value is used for determining the size of a heap allocation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11679 | Out-of-bounds Read in libwebsockets PNG parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11679</link><description>Out-of-bounds Read in lws_upng_emit_next_line in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_UPNG flag is enabled during compilation and the HTML display stack is used, to read past a heap allocated buffer possibly causing a crash, when the user visits an attacker controlled website that contains a crafted PNG file with a big height dimension.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11678 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in libwebsockets DNS response parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11678</link><description>Stack-based Buffer Overflow in lws_adns_parse_label in warmcat libwebsockets allows, when the LWS_WITH_SYS_ASYNC_DNS flag is enabled during compilation, to overflow the label_stack, when the attacker is able to sniff a DNS request in order to craft a response with a matching id containing a label longer than the maximum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:53:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11677 | Use After Free in libwebsockets WebSocket server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11677</link><description>Use After Free in WebSocket server implementation in lws_handshake_server in warmcat libwebsockets may allow an attacker, in specific configurations where the user provides a callback function that handles LWS_CALLBACK_HTTP_CONFIRM_UPGRADE, to achieve denial of service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61455 | SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the signup.inc.php endpoint. The application directl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61455</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the signup.inc.php endpoint. The application directly incorporates unsanitized user inputs into SQL queries, allowing unauthenticated attackers to bypass authentication and gain full access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56223 | A lack of rate limiting in the component /Home/UploadStreamDocument of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56223</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the component /Home/UploadStreamDocument of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via uploading an excessive number of files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61454 | A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the search endpoint. Unsanitized inpu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61454</link><description>A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Bhabishya-123 E-commerce 1.0, specifically within the search endpoint. Unsanitized input in the /search parameter is directly reflected back into the response HTML, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the browser of a user who visits a malicious link or submits a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56219 | Incorrect access control in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to arbitrarily add user accounts without any rate limiting. This can lead to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56219</link><description>Incorrect access control in SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to arbitrarily add user accounts without any rate limiting. This can lead to a resource exhaustion and a Denial of Service (DoS) when an excessively large number of user accounts are created.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-56224 | A lack of rate limiting in the One-Time Password (OTP) verification endpoint of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass verification vi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-56224</link><description>A lack of rate limiting in the One-Time Password (OTP) verification endpoint of SigningHub v8.6.8 allows attackers to bypass verification via a bruteforce attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8349 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) stored in Tawk Live Chat</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8349</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) stored vulnerability in Tawk Live Chat. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by uploading a malicious PDF with JavaScript payload through the chatbot. The PDF is stored by the application and subsequently displayed without proper sanitisation when other users access it. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:12:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41028 | SQL injection in Epsilon RH</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41028</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability has been found in Epsilon RH by Grupo Castilla. This vulnerability allows an attacker to retrieve, create, update and delete database via sending a POST request using the parameter ‘sEstadoUsr’ in ‘/epsilonnetws/WSAvisos.asmx’.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57837 | Tileservice module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57837</link><description>Tileservice module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57838 | Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confide...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57838</link><description>Some Honor products are affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57839 | Photo module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57839</link><description>Photo module is affected by information leak vulnerability, successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:35:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31342 | Galaxy Software Services Vitals ESP Forum Module - Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31342</link><description>An unrestricted upload of file with dangerous type vulnerability in the upload file function of Galaxy Software Services Corporation Vitals ESP Forum Module through 1.3 version allows remote authenticated users to execute arbitrary system commands via a malicious file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61932 | Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) (Client program (MR) and Detection agent (DA)) improperly verifies the origin of incoming requests, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61932</link><description>Lanscope Endpoint Manager (On-Premises) (Client program (MR) and Detection agent (DA)) improperly verifies the origin of incoming requests, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code by sending specially crafted packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 07:43:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62577 | ETERNUS SF provided by Fsas Technologies Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A low-privileged user with access to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62577</link><description>ETERNUS SF provided by Fsas Technologies Inc. contains an incorrect default permissions vulnerability. A low-privileged user with access to the management server may obtain database credentials, potentially allowing execution of OS commands with administrator privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 05:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40004 | net/9p: Fix buffer overflow in USB transport layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40004</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/9p: Fix buffer overflow in USB transport layer

A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the USB 9pfs transport layer
where inconsistent size validation between packet header parsing and
actual data copying allows a malicious USB host to overflow heap buffers.

The issue occurs because:
- usb9pfs_rx_header() validates only the declared size in packet header
- usb9pfs_rx_complete() uses req-&gt;actual (actual received bytes) for
memcpy

This allows an attacker to craft packets with small declared size
(bypassing validation) but large actual payload (triggering overflow
in memcpy).

Add validation in usb9pfs_rx_complete() to ensure req-&gt;actual does not
exceed the buffer capacity before copying data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 05:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11948 | Excellent Infotek｜Document Management System - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11948</link><description>Document Management System developed by Excellent Infotek has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:55:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11947 | bftpd Configuration File options.c expand_groups heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11947</link><description>A weakness has been identified in bftpd up to 6.2. Impacted is the function expand_groups of the file options.c of the component Configuration File Handler. Executing manipulation can lead to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is considered difficult. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 22:09:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11946 | LogicalDOC Community Edition Add Contact frontend.jsp cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11946</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in LogicalDOC Community Edition up to 9.2.1. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /frontend.jsp of the component Add Contact Page. Performing manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name/Company/Address/Phone/Mobile results in cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11945 | toeverything AFFiNE Avatar Upload Image Endpoint cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11945</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in toeverything AFFiNE up to 0.24.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Avatar Upload Image Endpoint. Such manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11944 | givanz Vvveb Raw SQL import.php import sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11944</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in givanz Vvveb up to 1.0.7.3. This affects the function Import of the file admin/controller/tools/import.php of the component Raw SQL Handler. This manipulation causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. Patch name: 52204b4a106b2fb02d16eee06a88a1f2697f9b35. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11943 | 70mai X200 HTTP Web Server default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11943</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 70mai X200 up to 20251010. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HTTP Web Server. The manipulation leads to use of default credentials. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 19:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11942 | 70mai X200 Pairing missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11942</link><description>A flaw has been found in 70mai X200 up to 20251010. Affected is an unknown function of the component Pairing. Executing manipulation can lead to missing authentication. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11941 | e107 CMS Avatar image.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11941</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in e107 CMS up to 2.3.3. This impacts an unknown function of the file /e107_admin/image.php?mode=main&amp;amp;action=avatar of the component Avatar Handler. Performing manipulation of the argument multiaction[] results in path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11940 | LibreWolf Installer setup.nsi uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11940</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in LibreWolf up to 143.0.4-1 on Windows. This affects an unknown function of the file assets/setup.nsi of the component Installer. Such manipulation leads to uncontrolled search path. The attack must be carried out locally. Attacks of this nature are highly complex. The exploitability is reported as difficult. Upgrading to version 144.0-1 mitigates this issue. The name of the patch is dd10e31dd873e9cb309fad8aed921d45bf905a55. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:39:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11939 | ChurchCRM Backup Restore RestoreJob.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11939</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file src/ChurchCRM/Backup/RestoreJob.php of the component Backup Restore Handler. Executing manipulation of the argument restoreFile can lead to path traversal. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11938 | ChurchCRM setup.php deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11938</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ChurchCRM up to 5.18.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file setup/routes/setup.php. Performing manipulation of the argument DB_PASSWORD/ROOT_PATH/URL results in deserialization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The attack's complexity is rated as high. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 07:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62672 | rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62672</link><description>rplay through 3.3.2 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (SIGSEGV and daemon crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact. This occurs in memcpy in the RPLAY_DATA case in rplay_unpack in librplay/rplay.c, potentially reachable via packet data with no authentication.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>