<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2026-0651 | Path Traversal on TP-Link Tapo D235 and C260 via Local https</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0651</link><description>On TP-Link Tapo C260 v1, path traversal is possible due to improper handling of specific GET request paths via https, allowing local unauthenticated probing of filesystem paths. An attacker on the local network can determine whether certain files exists on the device, with no read, write or code execution possibilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0652 | Remote Code Execution on TP-Link Tapo C260 by Guest User</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0652</link><description>On TP-Link Tapo C260 v1, command injection vulnerability exists due to improper sanitization in certain POST parameters during configuration synchronization. An authenticated attacker can execute arbitrary system commands with high impact on confidentiality, integrity and availability. It may cause full device compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0653 | Insecure Access Control on TP-Link Tapo D235 and C260</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0653</link><description>On TP-Link Tapo C260 v1, a guest‑level authenticated user can bypass intended access restrictions by sending crafted requests to a synchronization endpoint. This allows modification of protected device settings despite limited privileges. An attacker may change sensitive configuration parameters without authorization, resulting in unauthorized device state manipulation but not full code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1996 | Certain HP OfficeJet Pro Printers – Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1996</link><description>Certain HP OfficeJet Pro printers may be vulnerable to potential denial of service when the IPP requests are mishandled, failing to establish a TCP connection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25805 | Zed does not show Parameter Values for MCP Tool Calls. Users cannot detect tool poisoning.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25805</link><description>Zed is a multiplayer code editor. Prior to 0.219.4, Zed does not show with which parameters a tool is being invoked, when asking for allowance. Further it does not show after the tool was being invoked, which parameters were used. Thus, maybe unwanted or even malicious values could be used without the user having a chance to notice it. Patched in Zed Editor 0.219.4 which includes expandable tool call details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25947 | Worklenz Boolean-Based Blind SQL Injection via Improper ORDER BY Clause Input Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25947</link><description>Worklenz is a project management tool. Prior to 2.1.7, there are multiple SQL injection vulnerabilities were discovered in backend SQL query construction affecting project and task management controllers, reporting and financial data endpoints, real-time socket.io handlers, and resource allocation and scheduling features. The vulnerability has been patched in version v2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25956 | Frappe Affected by XSS and Open Redirect in Sign Up</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25956</link><description>Frappe is a full-stack web application framework. Prior to 14.99.14 and 15.94.0, an attacker could craft a malicious signup URL for a frappe site which could lead to an open redirect (or reflected XSS, depending on the crafted payload) when a user signs up. This vulnerability is fixed in 14.99.14 and 15.94.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24045 | Docmost Affected by Stored XSS in Public Share Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24045</link><description>Docmost is open-source collaborative wiki and documentation software. From g and before 0.25.0, the public share page functionality in Docmost does not properly HTML-escape page titles before inserting them into meta tags and the title tag. This allows Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks, where an attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of any user who opens a shared page link. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.25.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25577 | Emmett has an Unhandled CookieError Exception Causing Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25577</link><description>Emmett is a framework designed to simplify your development process. Prior to 1.3.11, the cookies property in mmett_core.http.wrappers.Request does not handle CookieError exceptions when parsing malformed Cookie headers. This allows unauthenticated attackers to trigger HTTP 500 errors and cause denial of service. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.3.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25646 | LIBPNG has a heap buffer overflow in png_set_quantize</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25646</link><description>LIBPNG is a reference library for use in applications that read, create, and manipulate PNG (Portable Network Graphics) raster image files. Prior to 1.6.55, an out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the png_set_quantize() API function. When the function is called with no histogram and the number of colors in the palette is more than twice the maximum supported by the user's display, certain palettes will cause the function to enter into an infinite loop that reads past the end of an internal heap-allocated buffer. The images that trigger this vulnerability are valid per the PNG specification. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.6.55.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25728 | ClipBucket v5 Affected by Remote Code Execution via Avatar/Background File Upload Race Condition</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25728</link><description>ClipBucket v5 is an open source video sharing platform. Prior to 5.5.3 - #40, a Time-of-Check to Time-of-Use (TOCTOU) race condition vulnerability exists in ClipBucket's avatar and background image upload functionality. The application moves uploaded files to a web-accessible location before validating them, creating a window where an attacker can execute arbitrary PHP code before the file is deleted. The uploaded file was moved to a web-accessible path via move_uploaded_file(), then validated via ValidateImage(). If validation failed, the file was deleted via @unlink(). This vulnerability is fixed in 5.5.3 - #40.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24885 | Kanboard Affected by Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) via Content-Type Misconfiguration in Project Role Assignment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24885</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Prior to 1.2.50, a Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in the ProjectPermissionController within the Kanboard application. The application fails to strictly enforce the application/json Content-Type for the changeUserRole action. Although the request body is JSON, the server accepts text/plain, allowing an attacker to craft a malicious form using the text/plain attribute. Which allows unauthorized modification of project user roles if an authenticated admin visits a malicious site This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.50.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25530 | Kanboard is missing authorization check in getSwimlane API allows cross-project data access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25530</link><description>Kanboard is project management software focused on Kanban methodology. Prior to 1.2.50, the getSwimlane API method lacks project-level authorization, allowing authenticated users to access swimlane data from projects they cannot access. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.50.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20070 | Improper conditions check for the Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem management software before versions CR_MGMT_02.00.00.4052, CR_MGMT_03.00.00.0538 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20070</link><description>Improper conditions check for the Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem management software before versions CR_MGMT_02.00.00.4052, CR_MGMT_03.00.00.0538 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable [cvss_threat_loss_factor]. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20080 | Null pointer dereference in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20080</link><description>Null pointer dereference in the firmware for some Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service. Network adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20106 | Uncontrolled search path in some software installer for some VTune(TM) Profiler software and Intel(R) oneAPI Base Toolkits before version 20...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20106</link><description>Uncontrolled search path in some software installer for some VTune(TM) Profiler software and Intel(R) oneAPI Base Toolkits before version 2025.0. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22453 | Improper input validation for some Server Firmware Update Utility(SysFwUpdt) before version 16.0.12 within Ring 3: User Applications may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22453</link><description>Improper input validation for some Server Firmware Update Utility(SysFwUpdt) before version 16.0.12 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable local code execution. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22849 | Incorrect default permissions for the Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem management software before versions CR_MGMT_01.00.00.3584, CR_MGMT_02.00.00.4...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22849</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for the Intel(R) Optane(TM) PMem management software before versions CR_MGMT_01.00.00.3584, CR_MGMT_02.00.00.4052, CR_MGMT_03.00.00.0538 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22885 | Improper buffer restrictions in the firmware for the TDX Module may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22885</link><description>Improper buffer restrictions in the firmware for the TDX Module may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24851 | Uncaught exception in the firmware for some 100GbE Intel(R) Ethernet Controller E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.8.x within Ring 0: Bare Metal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24851</link><description>Uncaught exception in the firmware for some 100GbE Intel(R) Ethernet Controller E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.8.x within Ring 0: Bare Metal OS may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25058 | Improper initialization for some ESXi kernel mode driver for the Intel(R) Ethernet 800-Series before version 2.2.2.0 (esxi 8.0) &amp;amp; 2.2.3....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25058</link><description>Improper initialization for some ESXi kernel mode driver for the Intel(R) Ethernet 800-Series before version 2.2.2.0 (esxi 8.0) &amp;amp; 2.2.3.0 (esxi 9.0) within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow an information disclosure. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25210 | Improper input validation for some Server Firmware Update Utility(SysFwUpdt) before version 16.0.12 within Ring 3: User Applications may all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25210</link><description>Improper input validation for some Server Firmware Update Utility(SysFwUpdt) before version 16.0.12 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27243 | Out-of-bounds write in the firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Controller E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.8.x within Ring 0: Bare Metal OS ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27243</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Controller E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.8.x within Ring 0: Bare Metal OS may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27535 | Exposed ioctl with insufficient access control in the firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection E825-C. before version NVM ver. 3.84 wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27535</link><description>Exposed ioctl with insufficient access control in the firmware for some Intel(R) Ethernet Connection E825-C. before version NVM ver. 3.84 within Ring 0: Bare Metal OS may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27560 | Loop with unreachable exit condition ('infinite loop') for some Intel(R) Platform within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service. Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27560</link><description>Loop with unreachable exit condition ('infinite loop') for some Intel(R) Platform within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27572 | Exposure of sensitive information during transient execution for some TDX within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Aut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27572</link><description>Exposure of sensitive information during transient execution for some TDX within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Authorized adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27708 | Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some Intel(R) Converged Security and Management Engine (CSME) Firmware (FW) within Ring 0: Kernel may...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27708</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some Intel(R) Converged Security and Management Engine (CSME) Firmware (FW) within Ring 0: Kernel may allow an information disclosure. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27940 | Out-of-bounds read for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Software side ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27940</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Software side channel adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30508 | Improper authorization in the Intel(R) Quick Assist Technology for some Intel(R) Platforms within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of servi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30508</link><description>Improper authorization in the Intel(R) Quick Assist Technology for some Intel(R) Platforms within Ring 0: Kernel may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30513 | Race condition for some TDX Module within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileg...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30513</link><description>Race condition for some TDX Module within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31648 | Improper handling of values in the microcode flow for some Intel(R) Processor Family may allow an escalation of privilege. Startup code and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31648</link><description>Improper handling of values in the microcode flow for some Intel(R) Processor Family may allow an escalation of privilege. Startup code and smm adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (low), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (low), integrity (low) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31655 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of pri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31655</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Battery Life Diagnostic Tool within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31944 | Race condition for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow a denial of service. Authorized adversary with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31944</link><description>Race condition for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow a denial of service. Authorized adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32003 | Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some 100GbE Intel(R) Ethernet Network Adapter E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.6, cpk 1.3.7 within Ring...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32003</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in the firmware for some 100GbE Intel(R) Ethernet Network Adapter E810 before version cvl fw 1.7.6, cpk 1.3.7 within Ring 0: Bare Metal OS may allow a denial of service. Network adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32007 | Out-of-bounds read for some TDX before version tdx module 1.5.24 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Authorized a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32007</link><description>Out-of-bounds read for some TDX before version tdx module 1.5.24 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Authorized adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32008 | Out-of-bounds write in the firmware for the Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a de...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32008</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in the firmware for the Intel(R) AMT and Intel(R) Standard Manageability within Ring 3: User Applications may allow a denial of service. Network adversary with an unauthenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via network access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32092 | Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Software before version 25.30.1702.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32092</link><description>Insecure inherited permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Software before version 25.30.1702.0 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32452 | Uncontrolled search path for some AI Playground before version 2.6.1 beta within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32452</link><description>Uncontrolled search path for some AI Playground before version 2.6.1 beta within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32453 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software within Ring 2: Privileged Process may allow an escalation of privil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32453</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Graphics Driver software within Ring 2: Privileged Process may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32467 | Use of uninitialized variable for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Autho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32467</link><description>Use of uninitialized variable for some TDX Module before version tdx1.5 within Ring 0: Hypervisor may allow an information disclosure. Authorized adversary with a privileged user combined with a high complexity attack may enable data exposure. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (none) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32735 | Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unpriv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32735</link><description>Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32739 | Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers and Intel LTS kernels within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32739</link><description>Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) Graphics Drivers and Intel LTS kernels within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (low) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33030 | Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33030</link><description>Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a low complexity attack may enable data corruption. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (low) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35992 | Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unpriv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35992</link><description>Improper conditions check in some firmware for some Intel(R) NPU Drivers within Ring 1: Device Drivers may allow a denial of service. Unprivileged software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable denial of service. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are not present without special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35998 | Missing protection mechanism for alternate hardware interface in the Intel(R) Quick Assist Technology for some Intel(R) Platforms within Rin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35998</link><description>Missing protection mechanism for alternate hardware interface in the Intel(R) Quick Assist Technology for some Intel(R) Platforms within Ring 0: Kernel may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present with special internal knowledge and requires no user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (none) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35999 | Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource for some System Firmware Update Utility (SysFwUpdt) for Intel(R) Server Boards and Int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35999</link><description>Incorrect permission assignment for critical resource for some System Firmware Update Utility (SysFwUpdt) for Intel(R) Server Boards and Intel(R) Server Systems Based before version 16.0.12. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with a privileged user combined with a low complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires passive user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36511 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Memory and Storage Tool before version 2.5.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36511</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Memory and Storage Tool before version 2.5.2 within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36522 | Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Chipset Software before version 10.1.20266.8668 or later. within Ring 3: User Applications m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36522</link><description>Incorrect default permissions for some Intel(R) Chipset Software before version 10.1.20266.8668 or later. within Ring 3: User Applications may allow an escalation of privilege. System software adversary with an authenticated user combined with a high complexity attack may enable escalation of privilege. This result may potentially occur via local access when attack requirements are present without special internal knowledge and requires active user interaction. The potential vulnerability may impact the confidentiality (high), integrity (high) and availability (high) of the vulnerable system, resulting in subsequent system confidentiality (none), integrity (none) and availability (none) impacts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54192 | An issue inTcpreplay v4.5.1 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted file to the tcpedit_dlt_getplugin function at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54192</link><description>An issue inTcpreplay v4.5.1 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted file to the tcpedit_dlt_getplugin function at src/tcpedit/plugins/dlt_utils.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52436 | An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability [CWE-79] vulnerability in Fortinet For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52436</link><description>An Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability [CWE-79] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiSandbox 5.0.0 through 5.0.1, FortiSandbox 4.4.0 through 4.4.7, FortiSandbox 4.2 all versions, FortiSandbox 4.0 all versions may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute commands via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-55018 | An inconsistent interpretation of http requests ('http request smuggling') vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-55018</link><description>An inconsistent interpretation of http requests ('http request smuggling') vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions, FortiOS 6.4.3 through 6.4.16 may allow  an unauthenticated attacker to smuggle an unlogged http request through the firewall policies via a specially crafted header</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62439 | An Improper Verification of Source of a Communication Channel vulnerability [CWE-940] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62439</link><description>An Improper Verification of Source of a Communication Channel vulnerability [CWE-940] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions may allow an authenticated user with knowledge of FSSO policy configurations to gain unauthorized access to protected network resources via crafted requests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62676 | An Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability [CWE-59] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62676</link><description>An Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability [CWE-59] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiClientWindows 7.4.0 through 7.4.4, FortiClientWindows 7.2.0 through 7.2.12, FortiClientWindows 7.0 all versions may allow a local low-privilege attacker to perform an arbitrary file write with elevated permissions via crafted named pipe messages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64157 | A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiOS 7.2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64157</link><description>A use of externally-controlled format string vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.9, FortiOS 7.2.0 through 7.2.11, FortiOS 7.0 all versions allows an authenticated admin to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted configuration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-68686 | An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability [CWE-200] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.1,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-68686</link><description>An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability [CWE-200] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.1, FortiOS 7.4.0 through 7.4.6, FortiOS 7.2 all versions, FortiOS 7.0 all versions, FortiOS 6.4 all versions may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass the patch developed for the symbolic link persistency mechanism observed in some post-exploit cases, via crafted HTTP requests. An attacker would need first to have compromised the product via another vulnerability, at filesystem level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-70347 | An issue in mquickjs before commit 74b7e (2026-01-15) allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted file to the get_mbl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-70347</link><description>An issue in mquickjs before commit 74b7e (2026-01-15) allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via a crafted file to the get_mblock_size function at mquickjs.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1774 | CASL Ability, versions 2.4.0 through 6.7.4, contains a prototype pollution vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1774</link><description>CASL Ability, versions 2.4.0 through 6.7.4, contains a prototype pollution vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21743 | A missing authorization vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAuthenticator 6.6.0 through 6.6.6, FortiAuthenticator 6.5 all versions, FortiAuthenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21743</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability in Fortinet FortiAuthenticator 6.6.0 through 6.6.6, FortiAuthenticator 6.5 all versions, FortiAuthenticator 6.4 all versions, FortiAuthenticator 6.3 all versions may allow a read-only user to make modification to local users via a file upload to an unprotected endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22153 | An Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness vulnerability [CWE-305] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4 may allow an unau...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22153</link><description>An Authentication Bypass by Primary Weakness vulnerability [CWE-305] vulnerability in Fortinet FortiOS 7.6.0 through 7.6.4 may allow an unauthenticated attacker to bypass LDAP authentication of Agentless VPN or FSSO policy, when the remote LDAP server is configured in a specific way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:49:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11004 | Reflected XSS vulnerability in Simplicity Device Manager tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11004</link><description>The Simplicity Device Manager Tool has a Reflected XSS (Cross-site-scripting) vulnerability in several API endpoints. The attacker needs to be on the same network to execute this attack. These APIs can affect confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the system that has Simplicity Device Manager tool running in the background.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15572 | wasm3 NewCodePage memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15572</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in wasm3 up to 0.5.0. The affected element is the function NewCodePage. The manipulation leads to memory leak. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Unfortunately, the project has no active maintainer at the moment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1602 | SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU5 allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the data...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1602</link><description>SQL injection in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU5 allows a remote authenticated attacker to read arbitrary data from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:52:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1603 | An authentication bypass in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak specific stored...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1603</link><description>An authentication bypass in Ivanti Endpoint Manager before version 2024 SU5 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to leak specific stored credential data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 15:52:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15571 | ckolivas lrzip stream.c ucompthread null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15571</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ckolivas lrzip up to 0.651. This vulnerability affects the function ucompthread of the file stream.c. Such manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7347 | IDOR in Dinibh Puzzle&amp;#x27;s Dinibh Patrol Tracking System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7347</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Dinibh Puzzle Software Solutions Dinibh Patrol Tracking System allows Exploitation of Trusted Identifiers.This issue affects Dinibh Patrol Tracking System: through 10022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7636 | SQLi in Ergosis Security Systems&amp;#x27; ZEUS PDKS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ergosis Security Systems Computer Industry and Trade Inc. ZEUS PDKS allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ZEUS PDKS: from &lt;1.0.5.10 through 10022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6967 | Authentication Bypass in Sarman Soft&amp;#x27;s CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6967</link><description>Execution After Redirect (EAR) vulnerability in Sarman Soft Software and Technology Services Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. CMS allows JSON Hijacking (aka JavaScript Hijacking), Authentication Bypass.This issue affects CMS: through 10022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15570 | ckolivas lrzip stream.c lzma_decompress_buf use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ckolivas lrzip up to 0.651. This impacts the function lzma_decompress_buf of the file stream.c. Performing a manipulation results in use after free. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11537 | Keycloak-server: sensitive headers shown in the http access logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11537</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. When the logging format is configured to a verbose, user-supplied pattern (such as the pre-defined 'long' pattern), sensitive headers including Authorization and Cookie are disclosed to the logs in cleartext. An attacker with read access to the log files can extract these credentials (e.g., bearer tokens, session cookies) and use them to impersonate users, leading to a full account compromise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 11:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15569 | Artifex MuPDF win_main.c get_system_dpi uncontrolled search path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15569</link><description>A flaw has been found in Artifex MuPDF up to 1.26.1 on Windows. The impacted element is the function get_system_dpi of the file platform/x11/win_main.c. This manipulation causes uncontrolled search path. The attack requires local access. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is regarded as difficult. Upgrading to version 1.26.2 is sufficient to resolve this issue. Patch name: ebb125334eb007d64e579204af3c264aadf2e244. Upgrading the affected component is recommended.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52334 | A vulnerability has been identified in syngo.plaza VB30E (All versions &lt; VB30E_HF07). The affected application does not encrypt the password...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52334</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in syngo.plaza VB30E (All versions &lt; VB30E_HF07). The affected application does not encrypt the passwords properly.
This could allow an attacker to recover the original passwords and might gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40587 | A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.5), Polarion V2410 (All versions &lt; V2410.2). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40587</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Polarion V2404 (All versions &lt; V2404.5), Polarion V2410 (All versions &lt; V2410.2). The affected application allows arbitrary JavaScript code be included in document titles. This could allow an authenticated remote attacker to conduct a stored cross-site scripting attack by creating specially crafted document titles that are later viewed by other users of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22923 | A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected application contains a data validation vulnerability that cou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22923</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in NX (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected application contains a data validation vulnerability that could allow an attacker with local access to interfere with internal data during the PDF export process that could potentially lead to arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23715 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23715</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an out of bounds write vulnerability while parsing specially crafted XDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23716 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23716</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted XDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23717 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23717</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted XDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23718 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23718</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted NDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23719 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23719</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected application is vulnerable to heap-based buffer overflow while parsing specially crafted NDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23720 | A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23720</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Simcenter Femap (All versions &lt; V2512), Simcenter Nastran (All versions &lt; V2512). The affected applications contains an out of bounds read vulnerability while parsing specially crafted NDB files. This could allow an attacker to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25655 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V4.0 SP2). The affected application permits improper modification of a conf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25655</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions &lt; V4.0 SP2). The affected application permits improper modification of a configuration file by a low-privileged user.
This could allow an attacker to load malicious DLLs, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution with administrative privilege.(ZDI-CAN-28107)</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25656 | A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.2.1). The affected ap...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25656</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in SINEC NMS (All versions), User Management Component (UMC) (All versions &lt; V2.15.2.1). The affected application permits improper modification of a configuration file by a low-privileged user.
This could allow an attacker to load malicious DLLs, potentially leading to arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM privileges.(ZDI-CAN-28108)</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14895 | PopupKit &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Disclosure and Data Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14895</link><description>The PopupKit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to authorization bypass in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.0. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to access the /popup/logs REST API endpoint. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read and delete analytics data including device types, browser information, countries, referrer URLs, and campaign metrics.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1866 | Name Directory &amp;lt;= 1.32.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Double HTML-Entity Encoding in Submission Form</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1866</link><description>The Name Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via double HTML-entity encoding in all versions up to, and including, 1.32.0. This is due to the plugin's sanitization function calling `html_entity_decode()` before `wp_kses()`, and then calling `html_entity_decode()` again on output. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page via the 'name_directory_name' and 'name_directory_description' parameters in the public submission form granted they can trick the site administrator into approving their submission or auto-publish is enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1922 | The Events Calendar Shortcode &amp;amp; Block &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode Attributes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1922</link><description>The The Events Calendar Shortcode &amp; Block plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's `ecs-list-events` shortcode `message` attribute in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23901 | Apache Shiro: Brute force attack possible to determine valid user names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23901</link><description>Observable Timing Discrepancy vulnerability in Apache Shiro.

This issue affects Apache Shiro: from 1.*, 2.* before 2.0.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.7 or later, which fixes the issue.

Prior to Shiro 2.0.7, code paths for non-existent vs. existing users are different enough,
that a brute-force attack may be able to tell, by timing the requests only, determine if
the request failed because of a non-existent user vs. wrong password.

The most likely attack vector is a local attack only.
Shiro security model  https://shiro.apache.org/security-model.html#username_enumeration  discusses this as well.

Typically, brute force attack can be mitigated at the infrastructure level.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23906 | Apache Druid: Authentication Bypass via LDAP Anonymous Bind</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23906</link><description>Affected Products and Versions
  *  Apache Druid
  *  Affected Versions: 0.17.0 through 35.x (all versions prior to 36.0.0)
  *  Prerequisites:  *  druid-basic-security extension enabled
  *  LDAP authenticator configured
  *  Underlying LDAP server permits anonymous bind                                                                                                                                                   






Vulnerability Description

An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in Apache Druid when using the druid-basic-security extension with LDAP authentication. If the underlying LDAP server is configured to allow anonymous
binds, an attacker can bypass authentication by providing an existing username with an empty password. This allows unauthorized access to otherwise restricted Druid resources without valid credentials.

The vulnerability stems from improper validation of LDAP authentication responses when anonymous binds are permitted, effectively treating anonymous bind success as valid user authentication. 

Impact

A remote, unauthenticated attacker can:
  *  Gain unauthorized access to the Apache Druid cluster
  *  Access sensitive data stored in Druid datasources
  *  Execute queries and potentially manipulate data
  *  Access administrative interfaces if the bypassed account has elevated privileges
  *  Completely compromise the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the Druid deployment                                                                                                                                                                                    


Mitigation
 
Immediate Mitigation (No Druid Upgrade Required):                                                                                                                                                    
  *  Disable anonymous bind on your LDAP server. This prevents the vulnerability from being exploitable and is the recommended immediate action.



Resolution
  *  Upgrade Apache Druid to version 36.0.0 or later, which includes fixes to properly reject anonymous LDAP bind attempts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24343 | Apache HertzBeat: Uncontrolled Resource Consumption via Crafted XPath Expressions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24343</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Data within XPath Expressions ('XPath Injection') vulnerability in Apache HertzBeat.

This issue affects Apache HertzBeat: from 1.7.1 before 1.8.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.8.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2268 | Ninja Forms &amp;lt;= 3.14.0 - Unauthenticated Information Disclosure in nf_ajax_submit AJAX Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2268</link><description>The Ninja Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.14.0. This is due to the unsafe application of the `ninja_forms_merge_tags` filter to user-supplied input within repeater fields, which allows the resolution of `{post_meta:KEY}` merge tags without authorization checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract arbitrary post metadata from any post on the site, including sensitive data such as WooCommerce billing emails, API keys, private tokens, and customer personal information via the `nf_ajax_submit` AJAX action.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11242 | SSRF in Teknolist Computer&amp;#x27;s Okulistik</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11242</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Teknolist Computer Systems Software Publishing Industry and Trade Inc. Okulistik allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Okulistik: through 21102025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:36:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1722 | WCFM Marketplace &amp;lt;= 3.7.0 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Refund Request Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1722</link><description>The WCFM Marketplace – Multivendor Marketplace for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0. This is due to the plugin not implementing authorization checks in the `wcfm-refund-requests-form` AJAX controller. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary refund requests for any order ID and item ID, potentially leading to financial loss if automatic refund approval is enabled in the plugin settings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2093 | Flowring｜Docpedia - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2093</link><description>Docpedia developed by Flowring has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2094 | Flowring｜Docpedia - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2094</link><description>Docpedia developed by Flowring has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read, modify, and delete database contents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2095 | Flowring｜Agentflow - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2095</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Authentication Bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to exploit a specific functionality to obtain arbitrary user authentication token and log into the system as any user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2096 | Flowring｜Agentflow - Missing Authenticaton</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2096</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read, modify, and delete database contents by using a specific functionality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2097 | Flowring｜Agentflow - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2097</link><description>Agentflow developed by Flowring has an Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2098 | Flowring｜AgentFlow - Reflected Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2098</link><description>AgentFlow developed by Flowring has a Reflected Cross-site Scripting vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript codes in user's browser through phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2099 | Flowring｜AgentFlow - Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2099</link><description>AgentFlow developed by Flowring has a Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject persistent JavaScript codes that are executed in users' browsers upon page load.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 07:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12063 | An insecure direct object reference allowed a non-admin user to modify or remove certain data objects without having the appropriate permiss...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12063</link><description>An insecure direct object reference allowed a non-admin user to modify or remove certain data objects without having the appropriate permissions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11142 | The VAPIX API mediaclip.cgi that did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code execution. This flaw can onl...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11142</link><description>The VAPIX API mediaclip.cgi that did not have a sufficient input validation allowing for a possible remote code execution. This flaw can only be exploited after authenticating with an operator- or administrator- privileged service account.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11547 | AXIS Camera Station Pro contained a flaw to perform a privilege escalation attack on the server as a non-admin user.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11547</link><description>AXIS Camera Station Pro contained a flaw to perform a privilege escalation attack on the server as a non-admin user.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12757 | An AXIS Camera Station Pro feature can be exploited in a way that allows a non-admin user to view information they are not permitted to.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12757</link><description>An AXIS Camera Station Pro feature can be exploited in a way that allows a non-admin user to view information they are not permitted to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-13064 | A server-side injection was possible for a malicious admin to manipulate the application to include a malicious script which is executed by ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-13064</link><description>A server-side injection was possible for a malicious admin to manipulate the application to include a malicious script which is executed by the server. This attack is only possible if the admin uses a client that have been tampered with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0996 | Fluent Forms &amp;lt;= 6.1.14 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via AI Form Builder Module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0996</link><description>The Fluent Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the AI Form Builder module in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.14 due to a combination of missing authorization checks, a leaked nonce, and insufficient input sanitization. The vulnerability allows Subscriber-level users to trigger AI form generation via a protected endpoint. When prompted, AI services will typically return bare JavaScript code (without</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:48:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0484 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and SAP S/4HANA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0484</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and SAP S/4HANA, an authenticated attacker could access a specific transaction code and modify the text data in the system. This vulnerability has a high impact on integrity of the application with no effect on the confidentiality and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0485 | Denial of service (DOS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects BI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0485</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects BI Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to send specially crafted requests that could cause the Content Management Server (CMS) to crash and automatically restart. By repeatedly submitting these requests, the attacker could induce a persistent service disruption, rendering the CMS completely unavailable. Successful exploitation results in a high impact on availability, while confidentiality and integrity remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0486 | Missing Authorization Check in ABAP based SAP systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0486</link><description>In ABAP based SAP systems a remote enabled function module does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user resulting in disclosure of system information.This has low impact on confidentiality. Integrity and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0488 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP CRM and SAP S/4HANA (Scripting Editor)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0488</link><description>An authenticated attacker in SAP CRM and SAP S/4HANA (Scripting Editor) could exploit a flaw in a generic function module call and execute unauthorized critical functionalities, which includes the ability to execute an arbitrary SQL statement. This leads to a full database compromise with high impact on confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0490 | Denial of service (DOS) in SAP BusinessObjects BI Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0490</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects BI Platform allows an unauthenticated attacker to craft a specific network request to the trusted endpoint that breaks the authentication, which prevents the legitimate users from accessing the platform. As a result, it has a high impact on the availability but no impact on the confidentiality and integrity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0505 | Multiple vulnerabilities in BSP Applications of SAP Document Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0505</link><description>The BSP applications allow an unauthenticated user to manipulate user-controlled URL parameters that are not sufficiently validated. This could result in unvalidated redirection to attacker-controlled websites, leading to a low impact on confidentiality and integrity, and no impact on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0508 | Open Redirect vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0508</link><description>The SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform allows an authenticated attacker with high privileges to insert malicious URL within the application. Upon successful exploitation, the victim may click on this malicious URL, resulting in an unvalidated redirect to the attacker-controlled domain and subsequently download the malicious content. This vulnerability has a high impact on the confidentiality and integrity of the application, with no effect on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0509 | Missing Authorization check in SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0509</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an authenticated, low-privileged user to perform background Remote Function Calls without the required S_RFC authorization in certain cases. This can result in a high impact on integrity and availability, and no impact on the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23681 | Missing Authorization check in a function module in SAP Support Tools Plug-In</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23681</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in a function module in SAP Support Tools Plug-In, an authenticated attacker could invoke specific function modules to retrieve information about the system and its configuration. This disclosure of the system information could assist the attacker to plan subsequent attacks. This vulnerability has a low impact on the confidentiality of the application, with no effect on its integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23684 | Race condition vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23684</link><description>A race condition vulnerability exists in the SAP Commerce cloud. Because of this when an attacker adds products to a cart, it may result in a cart entry being created with erroneous product value which could be checked out. This leads to high impact on data integrity, with no impact on data confidentiality or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23685 | Insecure Deserialization vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver (JMS service)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23685</link><description>Due to a Deserialization vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver (JMS service), an attacker authenticated as an administrator with local access could submit specially crafted content to the server. If processed by the application, this content could trigger unintended behavior during internal logic execution, potentially causing a denial of service. Successful exploitation results in a high impact on availability, while confidentiality and integrity remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23686 | CRLF Injection vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23686</link><description>Due to a CRLF Injection vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver Application Server Java, an authenticated attacker with administrative access could submit specially crafted content to the application. If processed by the application, this content enables injection of untrusted entries into generated configuration, allowing manipulation of application-controlled settings. Successful exploitation leads to a low impact on integrity, while confidentiality and availability remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23687 | XML Signature Wrapping in SAP NetWeaver AS ABAP and ABAP Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23687</link><description>SAP NetWeaver Application Server ABAP and ABAP Platform allows an authenticated attacker with normal privileges to obtain a valid signed message and send modified signed XML documents to the verifier. This may result in acceptance of tampered identity information, unauthorized access to sensitive user data and potential disruption of normal system usage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23688 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Fiori App (Manage Service Entry Sheets - Lean Services)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23688</link><description>SAP Fiori App Manage Service Entry Sheets does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. This has low impact on integrity, confidentiality and availability are not impacted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23689 | Denial of service (DOS) in SAP Supply Chain Management</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23689</link><description>Due to an uncontrolled resource consumption (Denial of Service) vulnerability, an authenticated attacker with regular user privileges and network access can repeatedly invoke a remote-enabled function module with an excessively large loop-control parameter. This triggers prolonged loop execution that consumes excessive system resources, potentially rendering the system unavailable. Successful exploitation results in a denial-of-service condition that impacts availability, while confidentiality and integrity remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24312 | Missing authorization check in SAP Business Workflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24312</link><description>An erroneous authorization check in SAP Business Workflow leads to privilege escalation. An authenticated administrative user can bypass role restrictions by leveraging permissions from a less sensitive function to execute unauthorized, high-privilege actions. This has a high impact on data integrity, with low impact on confidentiality and no impact on availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24319 | Information Disclosure Vulnerability in SAP Business One (B1 Client Memory Dump Files)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24319</link><description>In SAP Business One, sensitive information is written to the application�s memory dump files without obfuscation. Gaining access to this information could potentially lead to unauthorized operations within the B1 environment, including modification of company data. This issue results in a high impact on confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24320 | Memory Corruption vulnerability in SAP NetWeaver and ABAP Platform (Application Server ABAP)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24320</link><description>Due to improper memory management in SAP NetWeaver and ABAP Platform (Application Server ABAP), an authenticated attacker could exploit logical errors in memory management by supplying specially crafted input containing unique characters, which are improperly converted. This may result in memory corruption and the potential leakage of memory content. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability would have a low impact on the confidentiality of the application, with no effect on its integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24321 | Information Disclosure vulnerability in SAP Commerce Cloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24321</link><description>SAP Commerce Cloud exposes multiple API endpoints to unauthenticated users, allowing them to submit requests to these open endpoints to retrieve sensitive information that is not intended to be publicly accessible via the front-end. This vulnerability has a low impact on confidentiality and does not affect integrity and availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24322 | Missing Authorization check in SAP Solution Tools Plug-In (ST-PI)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24322</link><description>SAP Solution Tools Plug-In (ST-PI) contains a function module that does not perform the necessary authorization checks for authenticated users, allowing sensitive information to be disclosed. This vulnerability has a high impact on confidentiality and does not affect integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24323 | Multiple vulnerabilities in BSP Applications of SAP Document Management System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24323</link><description>The BSP applications allow an unauthenticated user to inject malicious script content via user-controlled URL parameters that are not sufficiently sanitized. When a victim accesses a crafted URL, the injected script is executed in the victim�s browser, leading to a low impact on confidentiality and integrity, and no impact on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24324 | Denial of service (DOS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (AdminTools)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24324</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Business Intelligence Platform (AdminTools) allows an authenticated attacker with user privileges to execute a specific query in AdminTools that could cause the Content Management Server (CMS) to crash, rendering the CMS partially or completely unavailable and resulting in the denial of service of the Content Management Server (CMS). Successful exploitation impacts system availability, while confidentiality and integrity remain unaffected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24325 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in SAP BusinessObjects Enterprise (Central Management Console)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24325</link><description>SAP BusinessObjects Enterprise does not sufficiently encode user-controlled inputs, leading to Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability. This enables an admin user to inject malicious JavaScript into a website and the injected script gets executed when the user visits the compromised page.This vulnerability has low impact on confidentiality and integrity of the data. There is no impact on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24326 | Missing authorization check in SAP S/4HANA Defense &amp;amp; Security (Disconnected Operations)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24326</link><description>Due to a missing authorization check in the Disconnected Operations of the SAP S/4HANA Defense &amp; Security, an attacker with user privileges could call remote-enabled function modules to do direct update on standard SAP database table . This results in low impact on integrity, with no impact on confidentiality or availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24327 | Missing Authorization Check in SAP Strategic Enterprise Management (Balanced Scorecard in BSP Application)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24327</link><description>Due to missing authorization check in SAP Strategic Enterprise Management (Balanced Scorecard in Business Server Pages), an authenticated attacker could access information that they are otherwise unauthorized to view. This leads to low impact on confidentiality and no effect on integrity or availability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24328 | Open Redirection vulnerability in Business Server Pages Application (TAF_APPLAUNCHER)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24328</link><description>SAP TAF_APPLAUNCHER within Business Server Pages allows unauthenticated attacker to craft malicious links that, when clicked by a victim, redirect them to attacker?controlled sites, potentially exposing or altering sensitive information in the victim�s browser. This results in a low impact on confidentiality and integrity, with no impact on the availability of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2259 | aardappel lobster Parsing parser.h ParseStatements memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2259</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in aardappel lobster up to 2025.4. Affected by this issue is the function lobster::Parser::ParseStatements in the library dev/src/lobster/parser.h of the component Parsing. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is 2f45fe860d00990e79e13250251c1dde633f1f89. Applying a patch is the recommended action to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2260 | D-Link DCS-931L setSysAdmin os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2260</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-931L up to 1.13.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /goform/setSysAdmin. The manipulation of the argument AdminID results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:05:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2258 | aardappel lobster wfc.h WaveFunctionCollapse memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2258</link><description>A flaw has been found in aardappel lobster up to 2025.4. Affected by this vulnerability is the function WaveFunctionCollapse in the library dev/src/lobster/wfc.h. Executing a manipulation can lead to memory corruption. The attack can only be executed locally. The exploit has been published and may be used. This patch is called c2047a33e1ac2c42ab7e8704b33f7ea518a11ffd. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 01:06:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15147 | WCFM Membership – WooCommerce Memberships for Multivendor Marketplace &amp;lt;= 2.11.8 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Update Membership Payment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15147</link><description>The WCFM Membership – WooCommerce Memberships for Multivendor Marketplace plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 2.11.8 via the 'WCFMvm_Memberships_Payment_Controller::processing' due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to modify other users' membership payments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0845 | WCFM - WooCommerce Frontend Manager &amp;lt;= 6.7.24 - Authenticated (Shop Manager+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0845</link><description>The WCFM – Frontend Manager for WooCommerce along with Bookings Subscription Listings Compatible plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the 'WCFM_Settings_Controller::processing' function in all versions up to, and including, 6.7.24. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Shop Manager-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:49:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15310 | Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Patch Endpoint Tools.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15310</link><description>Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Patch Endpoint Tools.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15313 | Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in Tanium EUSS.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15313</link><description>Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in Tanium EUSS.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15314 | Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in end-user-cx.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15314</link><description>Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in end-user-cx.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:49:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15318 | Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in End User Notifications and Endpoint Configuration Toolset Solution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15318</link><description>Tanium addressed an arbitrary file deletion vulnerability in Endpoint Configuration Toolset Solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15319 | Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Endpoint Configuration Toolset Solution.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15319</link><description>Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Endpoint Configuration Toolset Solution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25957 | Cube Denial of Service (DoS) - An authenticated attacker can crash the server by sending a specially crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25957</link><description>Cube is a semantic layer for building data applications. From 1.1.17 to before 1.5.13 and 1.4.2, it is possible to make the entire Cube API unavailable by submitting a specially crafted request to a Cube API endpoint. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.13 and 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25958 | Cube privilege escalation via a specially crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25958</link><description>Cube is a semantic layer for building data applications. From 0.27.19 to before 1.5.13, 1.4.2, and 1.0.14, it is possible to make a specially crafted request with a valid API token that leads to privilege escalation. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.5.13, 1.4.2, and 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25893 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Admin JWT Minting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25893</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. Prior to 1.2.10, an authentication bypass vulnerability in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain administrative access via the heartbeat refresh API and execute arbitrary code on the server. This issue has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25894 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Hardcoded JWT Secret in Default Configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25894</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. An insecure default configuration in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to gain administrative access and execute arbitrary code on the server. This affects FUXA through version 1.2.9 when authentication is enabled, but the administrator JWT secret is not configured. This issue has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25895 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via Arbitrary File Write in Upload API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25895</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. A path traversal vulnerability in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to write arbitrary files to arbitrary locations on the server filesystem. This affects FUXA through version 1.2.9. This issue has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.10.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25951 | FUXA has a Path Traversal Sanitization Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25951</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. Prior to 1.2.11, there is a flaw in the path sanitization logic allows an authenticated attacker with administrative privileges to bypass directory traversal protections. By using nested traversal sequences (e.g., ....//), an attacker can write arbitrary files to the server filesystem, including sensitive directories like runtime/scripts. This leads to Remote Code Execution (RCE) when the server reloads the malicious scripts. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25931 | vscode-spell-checker has a workspace-trust bypass Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25931</link><description>vscode-spell-checker is a basic spell checker that works well with code and documents. Prior to v4.5.4, DocumentSettings._determineIsTrusted treats the configuration value cSpell.trustedWorkspace as the authoritative trust flag. The value defaults to true (package.json) and is read from workspace configuration each time settings are fetched. The code coerces any truthy value to true and forwards it to ConfigLoader.setIsTrusted , which in turn allows JavaScript/TypeScript configuration files ( .cspell.config.js/.mjs/.ts , etc.) to be located and executed. Because no VS Code workspace-trust state is consulted, an untrusted workspace can keep the flag true and place a malicious .cspell.config.js ; opening the workspace causes the extension host to execute attacker-controlled Node.js code with the user’s privileges. This vulnerability is fixed in v4.5.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25934 | go-git improperly verifies data integrity values for .idx and .pack files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25934</link><description>go-git is a highly extensible git implementation library written in pure Go. Prior to 5.16.5, a vulnerability was discovered in go-git whereby data integrity values for .pack and .idx files were not properly verified. This resulted in go-git potentially consuming corrupted files, which would likely result in unexpected errors such as object not found. For context, clients fetch packfiles from upstream Git servers. Those files contain a checksum of their contents, so that clients can perform integrity checks before consuming it. The pack indexes (.idx) are generated locally by go-git, or the git cli, when new .pack files are received and processed. The integrity checks for both files were not being verified correctly. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.16.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25938 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in Node-RED Integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25938</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. From 1.2.8 through 1.2.10, an authentication bypass vulnerability in FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on the server when the Node-RED plugin is enabled. This has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25939 | FUXA Unauthenticated Remote Arbitrary Scheduler Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25939</link><description>FUXA is a web-based Process Visualization (SCADA/HMI/Dashboard) software. From 1.2.8 through version 1.2.10, 
an authorization bypass vulnerability in the FUXA allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to create and modify arbitrary schedulers, exposing connected ICS/SCADA environments to follow-on actions. This has been patched in FUXA version 1.2.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25923 | Phar Deserialization leading to Arbitrary File Deletion in my little forum</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25923</link><description>my little forum is a PHP and MySQL based internet forum that displays the messages in classical threaded view. Prior to 20260208.1, the application fails to filter the phar:// protocol in URL validation, allowing attackers to upload a malicious Phar Polyglot file (disguised as JPEG) via the image upload feature, trigger Phar deserialization through BBCode [img] tag processing, and exploit Smarty 4.1.0 POP chain to achieve arbitrary file deletion. This vulnerability is fixed in 20260208.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25925 | PowerDocu Affected by Remote Code Execution via Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25925</link><description>PowerDocu contains a Windows GUI executable to perform technical documentations. Prior to 2.4.0, PowerDocu contains a critical security vulnerability in how it parses JSON files within Flow or App packages. The application blindly trusts the $type property in JSON files, allowing an attacker to instantiate arbitrary .NET objects and execute code. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15315 | Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Tanium Module Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15315</link><description>Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Tanium Module Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15316 | Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Tanium Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15316</link><description>Tanium addressed a local privilege escalation vulnerability in Tanium Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15317 | Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Tanium Server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15317</link><description>Tanium addressed an uncontrolled resource consumption vulnerability in Tanium Server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25807 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution via P2P Sharing in ZAI-Shell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25807</link><description>ZAI Shell is an autonomous SysOps agent designed to navigate, repair, and secure complex environments. Prior to 9.0.3, the P2P terminal sharing feature (share start) opens a TCP socket on port 5757 without any authentication mechanism. Any remote attacker can connect to this port using a simple socket script. An attacker who connects to a ZAI-Shell P2P session running in --no-ai mode can send arbitrary system commands. If the host user approves the command without reviewing its contents, the command executes directly with the user's privileges, bypassing all Sentinel safety checks. This vulnerability is fixed in 9.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25808 | Hollo DMs get leaked and can be seen on Webfinger Browser</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25808</link><description>Hollo is a federated single-user microblogging software designed to be federated through ActivityPub. Prior to 0.6.20 and 0.7.2, there is a security vulnerability where DMs and followers-only posts were exposed through the ActivityPub outbox endpoint without authorization. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.6.20 and 0.7.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 22:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25890 | File Browser has a Path-Based Access Control Bypass via Multiple Leading Slashes in URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25890</link><description>File Browser provides a file managing interface within a specified directory and it can be used to upload, delete, preview, rename and edit files. Prior to 2.57.1, an authenticated user can bypass the application's "Disallow" file path rules by modifying the request URL. By adding multiple slashes (e.g., //private/) to the path, the authorization check fails to match the rule, while the underlying filesystem resolves the path correctly, granting unauthorized access to restricted files. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.57.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25892 | Adminer has an Unauthenticated Persistent DoS via Array Injection in ?script=version Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25892</link><description>Adminer is open-source database management software. Adminer v5.4.1 and earlier has a version check mechanism where adminer.org sends signed version info via JavaScript postMessage, which the browser then POSTs to ?script=version. This endpoint lacks origin validation and accepts POST data from any source. An attacker can POST version[] parameter which PHP converts to an array. On next page load, openssl_verify() receives this array instead of string and throws TypeError, returning HTTP 500 to all users. Upgrade to Adminer 5.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25918 | unity-cli Exposes Plaintext Credentials in Debug Logs (sign-package command)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25918</link><description>unity-cli is a command line utility for the Unity Game Engine. Prior to 1.8.2 , the sign-package command in @rage-against-the-pixel/unity-cli logs sensitive credentials in plaintext when the --verbose flag is used. Command-line arguments including --email and --password are output via JSON.stringify without sanitization, exposing secrets to shell history, CI/CD logs, and log aggregation systems. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25920 | SumatraPDF has a heap out-of-bounds read in MOBI HuffDic decompressor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25920</link><description>SumatraPDF is a multi-format reader for Windows. In 3.5.2 and earlier, tA heap out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in SumatraPDF's MOBI HuffDic decompressor. The bounds check in AddCdicData() only validates half the range that DecodeOne() actually accesses. Opening a crafted .mobi file can read nearly (1 &lt;&lt; codeLength) bytes beyond the CDIC dictionary buffer, leading to a crash.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25961 | SumatraPDF Update MITM -&amp;gt; Arbitrary Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25961</link><description>SumatraPDF is a multi-format reader for Windows. In 3.5.0 through 3.5.2, SumatraPDF's update mechanism disables TLS hostname verification (INTERNET_FLAG_IGNORE_CERT_CN_INVALID) and executes installers without signature checks. A network attacker with any valid TLS certificate (e.g., Let's Encrypt) can intercept the update check request, inject a malicious installer URL, and achieve arbitrary code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25811 | PlaciPy Email Domain Trust Enables Cross-Tenant Data Access (Multi-Tenant Isolation Failure)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25811</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the application derives the tenant identifier directly from the email domain provided by the user, without validating domain ownership or registration. This allows cross-tenant data access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25812 | PlaciPy is Missing CSRF Protection on State-Changing Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25812</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the application enables credentialed CORS requests but does not implement any CSRF protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25813 | PlaciPy Exposes Sensitive Data via Application Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25813</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, The application logs highly sensitive data directly to console output without masking or redaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25814 | NoSQL Injection Risk via Unsanitized Query Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25814</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, User-controlled query parameters are passed directly into DynamoDB query/filter construction without validation or sanitization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25875 | PlaciPy Admin Privilege Escalation via Trusted JWT Claims</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25875</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, The admin authorization middleware trusts client-controlled JWT claims (role and scope) without enforcing server-side role verification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25880 | Untrusted Search Path in SumatraPDF Reader (explorer.exe on Windows)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25880</link><description>SumatraPDF is a multi-format reader for Windows. In 3.5.2 and earlier, the PDF reader allows execution of a malicious binary (explorer.exe) located in the same directory as the opened PDF when the user clicks File → “Show in folder”. This behavior leads to arbitrary code execution on the victim’s system with the privileges of the current user, without any warning or user interaction beyond the menu click.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25881 | @nyariv/sandboxjs has host prototype pollution from sandbox via array intermediary (sandbox escape)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25881</link><description>SandboxJS is a JavaScript sandboxing library. Prior to 0.8.31, a sandbox escape vulnerability allows sandboxed code to mutate host built-in prototypes by laundering the isGlobal protection flag through array literal intermediaries. When a global prototype reference (e.g., Map.prototype, Set.prototype) is placed into an array and retrieved, the isGlobal taint is stripped, permitting direct prototype mutation from within the sandbox. This results in persistent host-side prototype pollution and may enable RCE in applications that use polluted properties in sensitive sinks (example gadget: execSync(obj.cmd)). This vulnerability is fixed in 0.8.31.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25885 | PolarLearn allows Unauthenticated WebSocket access allows subscribing to and posting in arbitrary group chats</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25885</link><description>PolarLearn is a free and open-source learning program. In 0-PRERELEASE-16 and earlier, the group chat WebSocket at wss://polarlearn.nl/api/v1/ws can be used without logging in. An unauthenticated client can subscribe to any group chat by providing a group UUID, and can also send messages to any group. The server accepts the message and stores it in the group’s chatContent, so this is not just a visual spam issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25889 | File Browser has an Authentication Bypass in User Password Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25889</link><description>File Browser provides a file managing interface within a specified directory and it can be used to upload, delete, preview, rename and edit files. Prior to 2.57.1, a case-sensitivity flaw in the password validation logic allows any authenticated user to change their password (or an admin to change any user's password) without providing the current password. By using Title Case field name "Password" instead of lowercase "password" in the API request, the current_password verification is completely bypassed. This enables account takeover if an attacker obtains a valid JWT token through XSS, session hijacking, or other means. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.57.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25806 | PlaciPy has Missing Authorization Checks on Student Management Endpoints (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25806</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the GET /api/students/:email
PUT /api/students/:email/status, and DELETE /api/students/:email routes in backend/src/routes/student.routes.ts only enforce authentication using authenticateToken but do not enforce authorization. The application does not verify whether the authenticated user owns the student record being accessed, has an administrative / staff role, or is permitted to modify or delete the target student.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25809 | PlaciPy Code Execution Allowed Without Assessment Active State Validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25809</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the code evaluation endpoint does not validate the assessment lifecycle state before allowing execution. There is no check to ensure that the assessment has started, is not expired, or the submission window is currently open.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25810 | PlaciPy is Missing Object-Level Authorization in student.submission.routes.ts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25810</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the backend/src/routes/student.submission.routes.ts verify authentication but fails to enforce object-level authorization (ownership checks).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25876 | PlaciPy is Missing Authorization on Assessment Results Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25876</link><description>PlaciPy is a placement management system designed for educational institutions. In version 1.0.0, the backend/src/routes/results.routes.ts verify authentication but fails to enforce object-level authorization (ownership checks). For example, this can be used to return all results for an assessment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25878 | FroshAdminer Adminer UI is accessible without admin session</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25878</link><description>FroshAdminer is the Adminer plugin for Shopware Platform. Prior to 2.2.1, the Adminer route (/admin/adminer) was accessible without Shopware admin authentication. The route was configured with auth_required=false and performed no session validation, exposing the Adminer UI to unauthenticated users. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25761 | Command injection via crafted filenames in Super-linter Action</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25761</link><description>Super-linter is a combination of multiple linters to run as a GitHub Action or standalone. From 6.0.0 to 8.3.0, the Super-linter GitHub Action is vulnerable to command injection via crafted filenames. When this action is used in downstream GitHub Actions workflows, an attacker can submit a pull request that introduces a file whose name contains shell command substitution syntax, such as $(...). In affected Super-linter versions, runtime scripts may execute the embedded command during file discovery processing, enabling arbitrary command execution in the workflow runner context. This can be used to disclose the job’s GITHUB_TOKEN depending on how the workflow configures permissions. This vulnerability is fixed in 8.3.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25765 | Faraday affected by SSRF via protocol-relative URL host override in build_exclusive_url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25765</link><description>Faraday is an HTTP client library abstraction layer that provides a common interface over many adapters. Prior to 2.14.1, Faraday's build_exclusive_url method (in lib/faraday/connection.rb) uses Ruby's URI#merge to combine the connection's base URL with a user-supplied path. Per RFC 3986, protocol-relative URLs (e.g. //evil.com/path) are treated as network-path references that override the base URL's host/authority component. This means that if any application passes user-controlled input to Faraday's get(), post(), build_url(), or other request methods, an attacker can supply a protocol-relative URL like //attacker.com/endpoint to redirect the request to an arbitrary host, enabling Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25791 | Sliver has a DNS C2 OTP Bypass Allows Unauthenticated Session Flooding and Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25791</link><description>Sliver is a command and control framework that uses a custom Wireguard netstack. Prior to 1.7.0, the DNS C2 listener accepts unauthenticated TOTP bootstrap messages and allocates server-side DNS sessions without validating OTP values, even when EnforceOTP is enabled. Because sessions are stored without a cleanup/expiry path in this flow, an unauthenticated remote actor can repeatedly create sessions and drive memory exhaustion. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25528 | LangSmith Client SDK Affected by Server-Side Request Forgery via Tracing Header Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25528</link><description>LangSmith Client SDKs provide SDK's for interacting with the LangSmith platform. The LangSmith SDK's distributed tracing feature is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery via malicious HTTP headers. An attacker can inject arbitrary api_url values through the baggage header, causing the SDK to exfiltrate sensitive trace data to attacker-controlled endpoints. When using distributed tracing, the SDK parses incoming HTTP headers via RunTree.from_headers() in Python or RunTree.fromHeaders() in Typescript. The baggage header can contain replica configurations including api_url and api_key fields. Prior to the fix, these attacker-controlled values were accepted without validation. When a traced operation completes, the SDK's post() and patch() methods send run data to all configured replica URLs, including any injected by an attacker. This vulnerability is fixed in version 0.6.3 of the Python SDK and  0.4.6 of the JavaScript SDK.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25639 | Axios affected by Denial of Service via __proto__ Key in mergeConfig</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25639</link><description>Axios is a promise based HTTP client for the browser and Node.js. Prior to 1.13.5, the mergeConfig function in axios crashes with a TypeError when processing configuration objects containing __proto__ as an own property. An attacker can trigger this by providing a malicious configuration object created via JSON.parse(), causing complete denial of service. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.13.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25740 | Privilege escalation to the `CAP_NET_RAW` capability via the `programs.captive-browser` NixOS module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25740</link><description>captive browser, a dedicated Chrome instance to log into captive portals without messing with DNS settings. In 25.05 and earlier, when programs.captive-browser is enabled, any user of the system can run arbitrary commands with the CAP_NET_RAW capability (binding to privileged ports, spoofing localhost traffic from privileged services...). This vulnerability is fixed in 25.11 and 26.05.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25498 | Craft has a potential authenticated Remote Code Execution via malicious attached Behavior</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25498</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, a Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability exists in Craft CMS where the assembleLayoutFromPost() function in src/services/Fields.php fails to sanitize user-supplied configuration data before passing it to Craft::createObject(). This allows authenticated administrators to inject malicious Yii2 behavior configurations that execute arbitrary system commands on the server. This vulnerability represents an unpatched variant of the behavior injection vulnerability addressed in CVE-2025-68455, affecting different endpoints through a separate code path. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25492 | Craft has a save_images_Asset graphql mutation can be abused to exfiltrate AWS credentials of underlying host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25492</link><description>Craft CMS is a content management system. In Craft versions 3.5.0 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the save_images_Asset GraphQL mutation can be abused to fetch internal URLs by providing a domain name that resolves to an internal IP address, bypassing hostname validation. When a non-image file extension such as .txt is allowed, downstream image validation is bypassed, which can allow an authenticated attacker with permission to use save_images_Asset to retrieve sensitive data such as AWS instance metadata credentials from the underlying host. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25493 | Craft has a SSRF in GraphQL Asset Mutation via HTTP Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25493</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the saveAsset GraphQL mutation validates the initial URL hostname and resolved IP against a blocklist, but Guzzle follows HTTP redirects by default. An attacker can bypass all SSRF protections by hosting a redirect that points to cloud metadata endpoints or any internal IP addresses. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25494 | Craft has a SSRF in GraphQL Asset Mutation via Alternative IP Notation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25494</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences.  In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the saveAsset GraphQL mutation uses filter_var(..., FILTER_VALIDATE_IP) to block a specific list of IP addresses. However, alternative IP notations (hexadecimal, mixed) are not recognized by this function, allowing attackers to bypass the blocklist and access cloud metadata services. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25495 | Craft has a SQL Injection in Element Indexes via criteria[orderBy]</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25495</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, the element-indexes/get-elements endpoint is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the criteria[orderBy] parameter (JSON body). The application fails to sanitize this input before using it in the database query. An attacker with Control Panel access can inject arbitrary SQL into the ORDER BY clause by omitting viewState[order] (or setting both to the same payload). This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25496 | Craft has a stored XSS in Number Prefix &amp;amp; Suffix Fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25496</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions 4.0.0-RC1 through 4.16.17 and 5.0.0-RC1 through 5.8.21, a stored XSS vulnerability exists in the Number field type settings. The Prefix and Suffix fields are rendered using the |md|raw Twig filter without proper escaping, allowing script execution when the Number field is displayed on users' profiles. This issue is patched in versions 4.16.18 and 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25497 | Craft has a GraphQL Asset Mutation Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25497</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. In Craft versions from 4.0.0-RC1 to before 4.17.0-beta.1 and 5.9.0-beta.1, there is a Privilege Escalation vulnerability in Craft CMS’s GraphQL API that allows an authenticated user with write access to one asset volume to escalate their privileges and modify/transfer assets belonging to any other volume, including restricted or private volumes to which they should not have access. The saveAsset GraphQL mutation validates authorization against the schema-resolved volume but fetches the target asset by ID without verifying that the asset belongs to the authorized volume. This allows unauthorized cross-volume asset modification and transfer. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.17.0-beta.1 and 5.9.0-beta.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2246 | AprilRobotics apriltag apriltag.c apriltag_detector_detect memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2246</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in AprilRobotics apriltag up to 3.4.5. Affected by this vulnerability is the function apriltag_detector_detect of the file apriltag.c. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. The identifier of the patch is cfac2f5ce1ffe2de25967eb1ab80bc5d99fc1a61. It is suggested to install a patch to address this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14778 | Keycloak: incorrect ownership checks in /uma-policy/</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14778</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A significant Broken Access Control vulnerability exists in the UserManagedPermissionService (UMA Protection API). When updating or deleting a UMA policy associated with multiple resources, the authorization check only verifies the caller's ownership against the first resource in the policy's list. This allows a user (Owner A) who owns one resource (RA) to update a shared policy and modify authorization rules for other resources (e.g., RB) in that same policy, even if those other resources are owned by a different user (Owner B). This constitutes a horizontal privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1486 | Org.keycloak.protocol.oidc.grants: disabled identity providers are still accepted for jwt authorization grant</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1486</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. A vulnerability exists in the jwt-authorization-grant flow where the server fails to verify if an Identity Provider (IdP) is enabled before issuing tokens. The issuer lookup mechanism (lookupIdentityProviderFromIssuer) retrieves the IdP configuration but does not filter for isEnabled=false. If an administrator disables an IdP (e.g., due to a compromise or offboarding), an entity possessing that IdP's signing key can still generate valid JWT assertions that Keycloak accepts, resulting in the issuance of valid access tokens.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1529 | Org.keycloak.services.resources.organizations: keycloak: unauthorized organization registration via improper invitation token validation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1529</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by modifying the organization ID and target email within a legitimate invitation token's JSON Web Token (JWT) payload. This lack of cryptographic signature verification allows the attacker to successfully self-register into an unauthorized organization, leading to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24900 | MarkUs has a submission-view IDOR exposes all student submissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24900</link><description>MarkUs is a web application for the submission and grading of student assignments. Prior to 2.9.1, the courses/&lt;:course_id&gt;/assignments/&lt;:assignment_id&gt;/submissions/html_content accepted a select_file_id parameter to serve SubmissionFile objects containing a record of files submitted by students. This parameter was not correctly scoped to the requesting user, allowing users access arbitrary submission file contents by id. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25057 | Zip Slip in MarkUs config upload allowing RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25057</link><description>MarkUs is a web application for the submission and grading of student assignments. Prior to 2.9.1, instructors are able to upload a zip file to create an assignment from an exported configuration (courses/&lt;:course_id&gt;/assignments/upload_config_files). The uploaded zip file entry names are used to create paths to write files to disk without checking these paths. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.9.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25230 | FileRise affected by HTML Injection using color property in file tags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25230</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web file manager / WebDAV server. Prior to 3.3.0, an HTML Injection vulnerability allows an authenticated user to modify the DOM and add e.g. form elements that call certain endpoints or link elements that redirect the user on active interaction. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25231 | FileRise affected by an Unauthenticated File Read Due to Insufficient Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25231</link><description>FileRise is a self-hosted web file manager / WebDAV server. Versions prior to 3.3.0, the application contains an unauthenticated file read vulnerability due to the lack of access control on the /uploads directory. Files uploaded to this directory can be accessed directly by any user who knows or can guess the file path, without requiring authentication. As a result, sensitive data could be exposed, and privacy may be breached. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25478 | Litestar has a CORS origin allowlist bypass due to unescaped regex metacharacters in allowed origins</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25478</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, CORSConfig.allowed_origins_regex is constructed using a regex built from configured allowlist values and used with fullmatch() for validation. Because metacharacters are not escaped, a malicious origin can match unexpectedly. The check relies on allowed_origins_regex.fullmatch(origin). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25479 | Litestar has an AllowedHosts validation bypass due to unescaped regex metacharacters in configured host patterns</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25479</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, in litestar.middleware.allowed_hosts, allowlist entries are compiled into regex patterns in a way that allows regex metacharacters to retain special meaning (e.g., . matches any character). This enables a bypass where an attacker supplies a host that matches the regex but is not the intended literal hostname. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25480 | FileStore key canonicalization collisions allow response cache mixup/poisoning (ASCII ord + Unicode NFKD)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25480</link><description>Litestar is an Asynchronous Server Gateway Interface (ASGI) framework. Prior to 2.20.0, FileStore maps cache keys to filenames using Unicode NFKD normalization and ord() substitution without separators, creating key collisions. When FileStore is used as response-cache backend, an unauthenticated remote attacker can trigger cache key collisions via crafted paths, causing one URL to serve cached responses of another (cache poisoning/mixup). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25491 | Craft has a Stored XSS in Entry Types Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25491</link><description>Craft is a platform for creating digital experiences. From 5.0.0-RC1 to 5.8.21, Craft has a stored XSS via Entry Type names. The name is not sanitized when displayed in the Entry Types list. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.8.22.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25598 | Bypassing Logging of Outbound Connections Using sendto, sendmsg, and sendmmsg in Harden-Runner (Community Tier)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25598</link><description>Harden-Runner is a CI/CD security agent that works like an EDR for GitHub Actions runners. Prior to 2.14.2, a security vulnerability has been identified in the Harden-Runner GitHub Action (Community Tier) that allows outbound network connections to evade audit logging. Specifically, outbound traffic using the sendto, sendmsg, and sendmmsg socket system calls can bypass detection and logging when using egress-policy: audit. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.14.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2245 | CCExtractor MPEG-TS File ts_tables.c parse_PMT out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2245</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in CCExtractor up to 183. This affects the function parse_PAT/parse_PMT in the library src/lib_ccx/ts_tables.c of the component MPEG-TS File Parser. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack can only be performed from a local environment. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The name of the patch is fd7271bae238ccb3ae8a71304ea64f0886324925. It is best practice to apply a patch to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23948 | FreeRDP has a NULL Pointer Dereference in rdp_write_logon_info_v2()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23948</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, a NULL pointer dereference vulnerability in rdp_write_logon_info_v2() allows a malicious RDP server to crash FreeRDP proxy by sending a specially crafted LogonInfoV2 PDU with cbDomain=0 or cbUserName=0. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24491 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in video_timer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24491</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, video_timer can send client notifications after the control channel is closed, dereferencing a freed callback and triggering a use after free. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24675 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in urb_select_interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24675</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, urb_select_interface can free the device's MS config on error but later code still dereferences it, leading to a use after free in libusb_udev_select_interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24676 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in audio_format_compatible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24676</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, AUDIN format renegotiation frees the active format list while the capture thread continues using audin-&gt;format, leading to a use after free in audio_format_compatible. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24677 | FreeRDP has a heap-buffer-overflow in ecam_encoder_compress_h264</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24677</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, ecam_encoder_compress_h264 trusts server-controlled dimensions and does not validate the source buffer size, leading to an out-of-bounds read in sws_scale. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24678 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in cam_v4l_stream_capture_thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24678</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, A capture thread sends sample responses using a freed channel callback after a device channel close, leading to a use after free in ecam_channel_write. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24679 | FreeRDP has a heap-buffer-overflow in urb_select_interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24679</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, The URBDRC client uses server-supplied interface numbers as array indices without bounds checks, causing an out-of-bounds read in libusb_udev_select_interface. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24680 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in update_pointer_new(SDL)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24680</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, sdl_Pointer_New frees data on failure, then pointer_free calls sdl_Pointer_Free and frees it again, triggering ASan UAF. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24681 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in urb_bulk_transfer_cb</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24681</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, aAsynchronous bulk transfer completions can use a freed channel callback after URBDRC channel close, leading to a use after free in urb_write_completion. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24682 | FreeRDP has a Heap-buffer-overflow in audio_formats_free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24682</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, audin_server_recv_formats frees an incorrect number of audio formats on parse failure (i + i), leading to out-of-bounds access in audio_formats_free. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24683 | FreeRDP has a heap-use-after-free in ainput_send_input_event</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24683</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. ainput_send_input_event caches channel_callback in a local variable and later uses it without synchronization; a concurrent channel close can free or reinitialize the callback, leading to a use after free. Prior to 3.22.0, This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24684 | FreeRDP has a Heap-use-after-free in play_thread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24684</link><description>FreeRDP is a free implementation of the Remote Desktop Protocol. Prior to 3.22.0, the RDPSND async playback thread can process queued PDUs after the channel is closed and internal state is freed, leading to a use after free in rdpsnd_treat_wave. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.22.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24777 | OpenProject has Improper Access Control on User Management allows user managers to lock admin accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24777</link><description>OpenProject is an open-source, web-based project management software. Prior to 17.0.2, users with the Manage Users permission can lock and unlock users. This functionality should only be possible for users of the application, but they were not supposed to be able to lock application administrators. Due to a missing permission check this logic was not enforced. The problem was fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2The problem was fixed in OpenProject 17.0.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66630 | Fiber insecurely fallsback in utils.UUIDv4() / utils.UUID() — predictable / zero‑UUID on crypto/rand failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66630</link><description>Fiber is an Express inspired web framework written in Go. Before 2.52.11, on Go versions prior to 1.24, the underlying crypto/rand implementation can return an error if secure randomness cannot be obtained. Because no error is returned by the Fiber v2 UUID functions, application code may unknowingly rely on predictable, repeated, or low-entropy identifiers in security-critical pathways. This is especially impactful because many Fiber v2 middleware components (session middleware, CSRF, rate limiting, request-ID generation, etc.) default to using utils.UUIDv4(). This vulnerability is fixed in 2.52.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:21:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-21419 | Dell Display and Peripheral Manager (Windows) versions prior to 2.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-21419</link><description>Dell Display and Peripheral Manager (Windows) versions prior to 2.2 contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') vulnerability in the Installer and Service. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of Privileges</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2242 | janet-lang janet specials.c janetc_if out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2242</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. This impacts the function janetc_if of the file src/core/specials.c. Executing a manipulation can lead to out-of-bounds read. The attack needs to be launched locally. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This patch is called c43e06672cd9dacf2122c99f362120a17c34b391. It is advisable to implement a patch to correct this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7432 | DPA countermeasures not reseeded under certain conditions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7432</link><description>DPA countermeasures in Silicon Labs' Series 2 devices are not reseeded under certain conditions. 

This may allow an attacker to eventually extract secret keys through a DPA attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2241 | janet-lang janet os.c os_strftime out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2241</link><description>A vulnerability was found in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. This affects the function os_strftime of the file src/core/os.c. Performing a manipulation results in out-of-bounds read. The attack must be initiated from a local position. The exploit has been made public and could be used. The patch is named 0f285855f0e34f9183956be5f16e045f54626bff. To fix this issue, it is recommended to deploy a patch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2240 | janet-lang janet compile.c janetc_pop_funcdef out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2240</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in janet-lang janet up to 1.40.1. The impacted element is the function janetc_pop_funcdef of the file src/core/compile.c. Such manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. The attack must be carried out locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is 4dd08a4cdef5b1c42d9a2c19fc24412e97ef51d5. A patch should be applied to remediate this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24095 | Missing Permission Check on Analyze Configuration Page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24095</link><description>Improper permission enforcement in Checkmk versions 2.4.0 before 2.4.0p21, 2.3.0 before 2.3.0p43, and 2.2.0 (EOL) allows users with the "Use WATO" permission to access the "Analyze configuration" page by directly navigating to its URL, bypassing the intended "Access analyze configuration" permission check. If these users also have the "Make changes, perform actions" permission, they can perform unauthorized actions such as disabling checks or acknowledging results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:15:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-14831 | Gnutls: gnutls: denial of service via excessive resource consumption during certificate verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-14831</link><description>A flaw was found in GnuTLS. This vulnerability allows a denial of service (DoS) by excessive CPU (Central Processing Unit) and memory consumption via specially crafted malicious certificates containing a large number of name constraints and subject alternative names (SANs).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59023 | Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59023</link><description>Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59024 | Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59024</link><description>Crafted delegations or IP fragments can poison cached delegations in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63354 | Hitron HI3120 v7.2.4.5.2b1 allows stored XSS via the Parental Control option when creating a new filter. The device fails to properly handle...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63354</link><description>Hitron HI3120 v7.2.4.5.2b1 allows stored XSS via the Parental Control option when creating a new filter. The device fails to properly handle inputs, allowing an attacker to inject and execute JavaScript.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24027 | Crafted zones can lead to increased incoming network traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24027</link><description>Crafted zones can lead to increased incoming network traffic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0398 | Crafted zones can lead to increased resource usage and crafted CNAME chains can lead to cache poisoning in Recursor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0398</link><description>Crafted zones can lead to increased resource usage and crafted CNAME chains can lead to cache poisoning in Recursor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:15:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10465 | Unrestricted File Upload in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10465</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Sensaway allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Sensaway: through 09022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10464 | Cleartext password storage in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10464</link><description>Insecure Storage of Sensitive Information vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Senseway allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Senseway: through 09022026.

NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10463 | Improper Authentication in Birtech Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Sensaway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10463</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Birtech Information Technologies Industry and Trade Ltd. Co. Senseway allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects Senseway: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:05:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7708 | Sensitive Data Exposure in Atlas Software&amp;#x27;s k12net</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7708</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Atlas Educational Software Industry Ltd. Co. K12net allows Communication Channel Manipulation.This issue affects k12net: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1959 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1959</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes, via the 

'descripción'

parameter in the '/loggrodemo/jbrain/MaestraCuentasBancarias' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1960 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1960</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Loggro Pymes, via the 'Facebook' parameter in '/loggrodemo/jbrain/ConsultaTerceros' endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6830 | SQLi in Xpoda Türkiye Information Technology&amp;#x27;s Xpoda Studio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6830</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Xpoda Türkiye Information Technology Inc. Xpoda Studio allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Xpoda Studio: through 09022026. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0632 | Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack &amp;lt;= 6.1.12 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery via &amp;#x27;saveDataSource&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0632</link><description>The Fluent Forms Pro Add On Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.12 via the 'saveDataSource' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22922 | Apache Airflow: Airflow externalLogUrl Permission Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22922</link><description>Apache Airflow versions 3.1.0 through 3.1.6 contain an authorization flaw that can allow an authenticated user with custom permissions limited to task access to view task logs without having task log access. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to Apache Airflow 3.1.7 or later, which resolves this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24098 | Apache Airflow: Assigning single DAG permission leaked all DAGs Import Errors</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24098</link><description>Apache Airflow versions before 3.1.7, has vulnerability that allows authenticated UI users with permission to one or more specific Dags to view import errors generated by other Dags they did not have access to. 

Users are advised to upgrade to 3.1.7 or later, which resolves this issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25846 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.119033 access tokens could be exposed in Mailbox logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25846</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.3.119033 access tokens could be exposed in Mailbox logs</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25847 | In JetBrains PyCharm before 2025.3.2 a DOM-based XSS on Jupyter viewer page was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25847</link><description>In JetBrains PyCharm before 2025.3.2 a DOM-based XSS on Jupyter viewer page was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25848 | In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.119807 authentication bypass allowing administrative actions was possible</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25848</link><description>In JetBrains Hub before 2025.3.119807 authentication bypass allowing administrative actions was possible</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2227 | D-Link DCS-931L setSystemAdmin doSystem command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-931L up to 1.13.0. Impacted is the function doSystem of the file /setSystemAdmin. Performing a manipulation of the argument AdminID results in command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-23903 | Apache Shiro: Auth bypass when accessing static files only on case-insensitive filesystems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-23903</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Alternate Name vulnerability in Apache Shiro.

This issue affects Apache Shiro: before 2.0.7.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.0.7, which fixes the issue.

The issue only effects static files. If static files are served from a case-insensitive filesystem,
such as default macOS setup, static files may be accessed by varying the case of the filename in the request.
If only lower-case (common default) filters are present in Shiro, they may be bypassed this way.

Shiro 2.0.7 and later has a new parameters to remediate this issue
shiro.ini: filterChainResolver.caseInsensitive = true
application.propertie: shiro.caseInsensitive=true

Shiro 3.0.0 and later (upcoming) makes this the default.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2226 | DouPHP ZIP File file.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2226</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in DouPHP up to 1.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/file.php of the component ZIP File Handler. Such manipulation of the argument sql_filename leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25905 | Lack of isolation in mcp-run-python leads to MCP server takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25905</link><description>The Python code being run by 'runPython' or 'runPythonAsync' is not isolated from the rest of the JS code, allowing any Python code to use the Pyodide APIs to modify the JS environment. This may result in an attacker hijacking the MCP server - for malicious purposes including MCP tool shadowing. Note - the "mcp-run-python" project is archived and unlikely to receive a fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2225 | itsourcecode News Portal Project Administrator Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2225</link><description>A flaw has been found in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php of the component Administrator Login. This manipulation of the argument email causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:15:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7799 | Reflected XSS in Zirve Information Technologies&amp;#x27; e-Taxpayer Accounting Website</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7799</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zirve Information Technologies Inc. E-Taxpayer Accounting Website allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects e-Taxpayer Accounting Website: through 07082025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-25916 | Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.13 and 1.6 before 1.6.13, when "Block remote images" is used, does not block SVG feImage.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-25916</link><description>Roundcube Webmail before 1.5.13 and 1.6 before 1.6.13, when "Block remote images" is used, does not block SVG feImage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2223 | code-projects Online Reviewer System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2223</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /system/system/students/assessments/pretest/take/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22903 | Stack Overflow via SESSIONID Cookie in lighttpd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22903</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can send a crafted HTTP request containing an overly long SESSIONID cookie. This can trigger a stack buffer overflow in the modified lighttpd server, causing it to crash and potentially enabling remote code execution due to missing stack protections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22904 | Stack Overflow via Oversized Cookie Fields in lighttpd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22904</link><description>Improper length handling when parsing multiple cookie fields (including TRACKID) allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to send oversized cookie values and trigger a stack buffer overflow, resulting in a denial‑of‑service condition and possible remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22905 | Authentication Bypass via URI Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22905</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can bypass authentication by exploiting insufficient URI validation and using path traversal sequences (e.g., /js/../cgi-bin/post.cgi), gaining unauthorized access to protected CGI endpoints and configuration downloads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22906 | Hardcoded Key Allows Credential Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22906</link><description>User credentials are stored using AES‑ECB encryption with a hardcoded key. An unauthenticated remote attacker obtaining the configuration file can decrypt and recover plaintext usernames and passwords, especially when combined with the authentication bypass.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 08:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2222 | code-projects Online Reviewer System btn_functions.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2222</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /system/system/admins/manage/users/btn_functions.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument firstname can lead to cross site scripting. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2234 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - Missing Authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2234</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga  has a Missing Authentication vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to read and modify any user's mail content.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2235 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2235</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing authenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2236 | HGiga｜C&amp;amp;Cm@il - SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2236</link><description>C&amp;amp;Cm@il developed by HGiga  has a SQL Injection vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to inject arbitrary SQL commands to read database contents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-24466 | Products provided by Oki Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and its OEM products (Ricoh Co., Ltd., Murata Machinery, Ltd.) register Windows service...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-24466</link><description>Products provided by Oki Electric Industry Co., Ltd. and its OEM products (Ricoh Co., Ltd., Murata Machinery, Ltd.) register Windows services with unquoted file paths. A user with the write permission on the root directory of the system drive may execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privilege.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2221 | code-projects Online Reviewer System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2221</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login/index.php of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-0870 | GIGABYTE｜MacroHub - Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-0870</link><description>MacroHub developed by GIGABYTE has a Local Privilege Escalation vulnerability. Due to the MacroHub application launching external applications with improper privileges, allowing authenticated local attackers to execute arbitrary code with SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1868 | Improper Neutralization of Special Elements Used in a Template Engine in GitLab AI Gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1868</link><description>GitLab has remediated a vulnerability in the Duo Workflow Service component of GitLab AI Gateway affecting all versions of the AI Gateway from 18.1.6, 18.2.6, 18.3.1 to 18.6.1, 18.7.0, and 18.8.0 in which AI Gateway was vulnerable to insecure template expansion of user supplied data via crafted Duo Agent Platform Flow definitions. This vulnerability could be used to cause Denial of Service or gain code execution on the Gateway. This has been fixed in versions 18.6.2, 18.7.1, and 18.8.1 of the GitLab AI Gateway.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2220 | code-projects Online Reviewer System btn_functions.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2220</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/btn_functions.php. Such manipulation of the argument difficulty_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 07:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-22613 | The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-22613</link><description>The server identity check mechanism for firmware upgrade performed via command shell is insecurely implemented potentially allowing an attacker to perform a Man-in-the-middle attack. This security issue has been fixed in the latest firmware version of Eaton 

Network M3

 which is available on the Eaton download center.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2218 | D-Link DCS-933L alphapd setSystemAdmin command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2218</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in D-Link DCS-933L up to 1.14.11. This affects an unknown function of the file /setSystemAdmin of the component alphapd. This manipulation of the argument AdminID causes command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2216 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss tools.py download_export_file path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2216</link><description>A flaw has been found in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.8. Impacted is the function download_export_file of the file apis/tools.py. Executing a manipulation of the argument filename can lead to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2217 | itsourcecode Event Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2217</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Event Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-1615 | All versions of the package jsonpath are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection via unsafe evaluation of user-supplied JSON Path expressions...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-1615</link><description>All versions of the package jsonpath are vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Injection via unsafe evaluation of user-supplied JSON Path expressions. The library relies on the static-eval module to process JSON Path input, which is not designed to handle untrusted data safely. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by supplying a malicious JSON Path expression that, when evaluated, executes arbitrary JavaScript code, leading to Remote Code Execution in Node.js environments or Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in browser contexts. This affects all methods that evaluate JSON Paths against objects, including .query, .nodes, .paths, .value, .parent, and .apply.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2215 | rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss JWT auth.py default key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2215</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in rachelos WeRSS we-mp-rss up to 1.4.8. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file core/auth.py of the component JWT Handler. Performing a manipulation of the argument SECRET_KEY results in use of default cryptographic key. The attack can be initiated remotely. The attack is considered to have high complexity. The exploitability is assessed as difficult. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66594 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.

Detailed messages are displayed on the error
page. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66594</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.

Detailed messages are displayed on the error
page. This information could be exploited by an attacker for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66595 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product is
vulnerable to Cross-Site Request ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66595</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product is
vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF). When a user accesses a link
crafted by an attacker, the user’s account could be compromised.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66596 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate request h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66596</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate request headers. When an attacker inserts an invalid host
header, users could be redirected to malicious sites.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66597 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
weak cryptographic algorith...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66597</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
weak cryptographic algorithms, potentially allowing an attacker to decrypt
communications with the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66598 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
old SSL/TLS versions, poten...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66598</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product supports
old SSL/TLS versions, potentially allowing an attacker to decrypt
communications with the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2213 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminAddAlbum.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2213</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddAlbum.php. The manipulation of the argument txtimage results in unrestricted upload. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2214 | code-projects for Plugin AdminAddAlbum.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2214</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects for Plugin 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminAddAlbum.php. This manipulation of the argument txtalbum causes cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66599 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Physical paths could
be displayed on web pages. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66599</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Physical paths could
be displayed on web pages. This information could be exploited by an attacker
for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66600 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product lacks
HSTS (HTTP Strict Transport Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66600</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product lacks
HSTS (HTTP Strict Transport Security) configuration. When an attacker performs
a Man in the middle (MITM) attack, communications with the web server could be
sniffed.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66601 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
specify MIME types. When an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66601</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
specify MIME types. When an attacker performs a content sniffing attack,
malicious scripts could be executed.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66602 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
access by IP address. When...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66602</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
access by IP address. When a worm that randomly searches for IP addresses
intrudes into the network, it could potentially be attacked by the worm.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66603 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
the OPTIONS method. An att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66603</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The web server accepts
the OPTIONS method. An attacker could potentially use this information to carry
out other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66604 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The library version
could be displayed on the web...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66604</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The library version
could be displayed on the web page. This information could be exploited by an
attacker for other attacks.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66605 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Since there are input
fields on this webpage with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66605</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



Since there are input
fields on this webpage with the autocomplete attribute enabled, the input
content could be saved in the browser the user is using.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66606 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly encode URLs. An at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66606</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly encode URLs. An attacker could tamper with web pages or execute
malicious scripts.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66607 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The response header
contains an insecure setting....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66607</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



The response header
contains an insecure setting. Users could be redirected to malicious sites by
an attacker.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-66608 | A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate URLs. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-66608</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FAST/TOOLS provided by Yokogawa Electric Corporation.



This product does not
properly validate URLs. An attacker could send specially crafted requests to
steal files from the web server.



The
affected products and versions are as follows: FAST/TOOLS (Packages: RVSVRN, UNSVRN, HMIWEB, FTEES, HMIMOB) R9.01 to
R10.04</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2211 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminDeleteCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2211</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminDeleteCategory.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2212 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminEditCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2212</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminEditCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:13:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2202 | Tenda AC8 httpd WifiGuestSet fromSetWifiGusetBasic buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2202</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected is the function fromSetWifiGusetBasic of the file /goform/WifiGuestSet of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument shareSpeed results in buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2203 | Tenda AC8 Embedded Httpd Service fast_setting_wifi_set buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2203</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda AC8 16.03.33.05. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set of the component Embedded Httpd Service. This manipulation of the argument timeZone causes buffer overflow. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2210 | D-Link DIR-823X set_filtering sub_4211C8 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2210</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4211C8 of the file /goform/set_filtering. Such manipulation leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2200 | heyewei JFinalCMS API Endpoint save cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2200</link><description>A weakness has been identified in heyewei JFinalCMS 5.0.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/admin/save of the component API Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2201 | ZeroWdd studentmanager LeaveController.java addLeave cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2201</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in ZeroWdd studentmanager up to 2151560fc0a50ec00426785ec1e01a3763b380d9. This impacts the function addLeave of the file src/main/java/com/wdd/studentmanager/controller/LeaveController.java. The manipulation of the argument Reason for Leave leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used. This product uses a rolling release model to deliver continuous updates. As a result, specific version information for affected or updated releases is not available. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2198 | code-projects Online Reviewer System loaddata.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2198</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/loaddata.php. Such manipulation of the argument difficulty_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2199 | code-projects Online Reviewer System user-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2199</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /reviewer/system/system/admins/manage/users/user-delete.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2196 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2196</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-update.php. The manipulation of the argument test_id results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2197 | code-projects Online Reviewer System exam-delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2197</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/exam-delete.php. This manipulation of the argument test_id causes sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2194 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 start_proxy_client_email command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2194</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. This affects the function start_proxy_client_email. Executing a manipulation can lead to command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2195 | code-projects Online Reviewer System questions-view.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2195</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /system/system/admins/assessments/pretest/questions-view.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2192 | Tenda AC9 formGetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2192</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formGetRebootTimer. Such manipulation of the argument sys.schedulereboot.start_time/sys.schedulereboot.end_time leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2193 | D-Link DI-7100G C1 set_jhttpd_info command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2193</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in D-Link DI-7100G C1 24.04.18D1. Affected by this issue is the function set_jhttpd_info. Performing a manipulation of the argument usb_username results in command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 23:17:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2190 | itsourcecode School Management System controller.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2190</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/user/controller.php. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2191 | Tenda AC9 formGetDdosDefenceList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2191</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC9 15.03.06.42_multi. Affected is the function formGetDdosDefenceList. This manipulation of the argument security.ddos.map causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2189 | itsourcecode School Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2189</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in itsourcecode School Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /ramonsys/report/index.php. The manipulation of the argument ay leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2188 | UTT 进取 521G formPdbUpConfig sub_446B18 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2188</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. The impacted element is the function sub_446B18 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Executing a manipulation of the argument policyNames can lead to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2186 | Tenda RX3 SetIpMacBind fromSetIpMacBind stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2186</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Impacted is the function fromSetIpMacBind of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. Such manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2187 | Tenda RX3 formSetQosBand set_qosMib_list stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. The affected element is the function set_qosMib_list of the file /goform/formSetQosBand. Performing a manipulation of the argument list results in stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:31:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2184 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2184</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation of the argument photo results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. This product implements a rolling release for ongoing delivery, which means version information for affected or updated releases is unavailable. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2185 | Tenda RX3 MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint setBlackRule set_device_name stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2185</link><description>A flaw has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. This issue affects the function set_device_name of the file /goform/setBlackRule of the component MAC Filtering Configuration Endpoint. This manipulation of the argument devName/mac causes stack-based buffer overflow. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2182 | UTT 进取 521G setSysAdm doSystem command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2182</link><description>A weakness has been identified in UTT 进取 521G 3.1.1-190816. Affected by this issue is the function doSystem of the file /goform/setSysAdm. Executing a manipulation of the argument passwd1 can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2183 | Great Developers Certificate Generation System csv.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2183</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Great Developers Certificate Generation System up to 97171bb0e5e22e52eacf4e4fa81773e5f3cffb73. This affects an unknown part of the file /restructured/csv.php. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. This product follows a rolling release approach for continuous delivery, so version details for affected or updated releases are not provided. The code repository of the project has not been active for many years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2179 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2179</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /admin/manage-users.php. This manipulation of the argument ID causes sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2180 | Tenda RX3 fast_setting_wifi_set stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2180</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. Such manipulation of the argument ssid_5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2181 | Tenda RX3 openSchedWifi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2181</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /goform/openSchedWifi. Performing a manipulation of the argument schedStartTime/schedEndTime results in stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:51:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2176 | code-projects Contact Management System index.py sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2176</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file index.py. Such manipulation of the argument selecteditem[0] leads to sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2177 | SourceCodester Prison Management System Login session fixiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2177</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Prison Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the component Login. The manipulation leads to session fixiation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2178 | r-huijts xcode-mcp-server run_lldb index.ts registerXcodeTools command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in r-huijts xcode-mcp-server up to f3419f00117aa9949e326f78cc940166c88f18cb. This affects the function registerXcodeTools of the file src/tools/xcode/index.ts of the component run_lldb. The manipulation of the argument args results in command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available. The patch is identified as 11f8d6bacadd153beee649f92a78a9dad761f56f. Applying a patch is advised to resolve this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2173 | code-projects Online Examination System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2173</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Online Examination System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2174 | code-projects Contact Management System CRUD Endpoint improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2174</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Contact Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component CRUD Endpoint. The manipulation of the argument ID results in improper authentication. The attack may be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2175 | D-Link DIR-823X set_upnp sub_420618 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2175</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420618 of the file /goform/set_upnp. This manipulation of the argument upnp_enable causes os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2171 | code-projects Online Student Management System Login accounts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2171</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file accounts.php of the component Login. Performing a manipulation of the argument username/password results in sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2172 | code-projects Online Application System for Admission Login Endpoint index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2172</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in code-projects Online Application System for Admission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file enrollment/index.php of the component Login Endpoint. Executing a manipulation can lead to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2168 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel sub_419920 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2168</link><description>A flaw has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This affects the function sub_419920 of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel. This manipulation of the argument fota_url causes command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2169 | D-Link DWR-M921 formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2169</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DWR-M921 1.1.50. This impacts an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeFibocom. Such manipulation of the argument fota_url leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:57:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2166 | code-projects Online Reviewer System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2166</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in code-projects Online Reviewer System 1.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /login/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2167 | Totolink WA300 cstecgi.cgi setAPNetwork os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2167</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in Totolink WA300 5.2cu.7112_B20190227. The impacted element is the function setAPNetwork of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument Ipaddr results in os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:36:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2163 | D-Link DIR-600 ssdp.cgi command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2163</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-600 up to 2.15WWb02. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file ssdp.cgi. Such manipulation of the argument HTTP_ST/REMOTE_ADDR/REMOTE_PORT/SERVER_ID leads to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2164 | detronetdip E-commerce addadhar.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2164</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /seller/assets/backend/profile/addadhar.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2165 | detronetdip E-commerce Account Creation Endpoint add_seller.php missing authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2165</link><description>A weakness has been identified in detronetdip E-commerce 1.0.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Admin/assets/backend/seller/add_seller.php of the component Account Creation Endpoint. Executing a manipulation of the argument email can lead to missing authentication. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2161 | itsourcecode Directory Management System forget-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Directory Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/forget-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email results in sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2162 | itsourcecode News Portal Project aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2162</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in itsourcecode News Portal Project 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/aboutus.php. This manipulation of the argument pagetitle causes sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2159 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Registration Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2159</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=register of the component Registration. Executing a manipulation of the argument firstname/lastname/username can lead to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2160 | SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Simple Responsive Tourism Website 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /tourism/classes/Master.php?f=save_package. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2157 | D-Link DIR-823X set_static_route_table sub_4175CC os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2157</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects the function sub_4175CC of the file /goform/set_static_route_table. Such manipulation of the argument interface/destip/netmask/gateway/metric leads to os command injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2158 | code-projects Student Web Portal check_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2158</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in code-projects Student Web Portal 1.0. This impacts an unknown function of the file /check_user.php. Performing a manipulation of the argument Username results in sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:13:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2156 | code-projects Online Student Management System Announcement Management index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2156</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Student Management System 1.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/announcement/index.php?view=add of the component Announcement Management Module. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2155 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration set_dmz sub_4208A0 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2155</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. The affected element is the function sub_4208A0 of the file /goform/set_dmz of the component Configuration Handler. The manipulation of the argument dmz_host/dmz_enable results in os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:17:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2154 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System Patient Registration registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2154</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /registration.php of the component Patient Registration Module. The manipulation of the argument First Name leads to cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2153 | mwielgoszewski doorman views.py is_safe_url redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2153</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in mwielgoszewski doorman up to 0.6. This issue affects the function is_safe_url of the file doorman/users/views.py. Executing a manipulation of the argument Next can lead to open redirect. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:52:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2152 | D-Link DIR-615 Web Configuration adv_routing.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2152</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file adv_routing.php of the component Web Configuration Interface. Performing a manipulation of the argument dest_ip/ submask/ gw results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2151 | D-Link DIR-615 DMZ Host Feature adv_firewall.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2151</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-615 4.10. This affects an unknown part of the file adv_firewall.php of the component DMZ Host Feature. Such manipulation of the argument dmz_ipaddr  leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 13:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2150 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System checkin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2150</link><description>A flaw has been found in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /checkin.php. This manipulation of the argument patient_id causes cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2149 | SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System appointments.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2149</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in SourceCodester/Patrick Mvuma Patients Waiting Area Queue Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appointments.php. The manipulation of the argument patient_id results in cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:31:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2148 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadFlash information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2148</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. Affected is an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadFlash of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2147 | Tenda AC21 Web Management DownloadLog information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2147</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC21 16.03.08.16. This impacts an unknown function of the file /cgi-bin/DownloadLog of the component Web Management Interface. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 10:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2146 | guchengwuyue yshopmall co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil updateAvatar unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2146</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in guchengwuyue yshopmall up to 1.9.1. This affects the function updateAvatar of the file /api/users/updateAvatar of the component co.yixiang.utils.FileUtil. Performing a manipulation of the argument File results in unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2145 | cym1102 nginxWebUI Web Management check cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2145</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in cym1102 nginxWebUI up to 4.3.7. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /adminPage/conf/check of the component Web Management Interface. Such manipulation of the argument nginxDir leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The project was informed of the problem early through an issue report but has not responded yet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2143 | D-Link DIR-823X DDNS Service set_ddns os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2143</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/set_ddns of the component DDNS Service. The manipulation of the argument ddnsType/ddnsDomainName/ddnsUserName/ddnsPwd leads to os command injection. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2142 | D-Link DIR-823X set_qos sub_420688 os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2142</link><description>A weakness has been identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This vulnerability affects the function sub_420688 of the file /goform/set_qos. Executing a manipulation can lead to os command injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2141 | WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM URL PermissionServiceImpl.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2141</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WuKongOpenSource WukongCRM up to 11.3.3. This affects an unknown part of the file gateway/src/main/java/com/kakarote/gateway/service/impl/PermissionServiceImpl.java of the component URL Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper authorization. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2140 | Tenda TX9 setMacFilterCfg sub_4223E0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2140</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this issue is the function sub_4223E0 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg. Such manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2139 | Tenda TX9 fast_setting_wifi_set sub_432580 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2139</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_432580 of the file /goform/fast_setting_wifi_set. This manipulation of the argument ssid causes buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2138 | Tenda TX9 SetStaticRouteCfg sub_42D03C buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2138</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda TX9 up to 22.03.02.10_multi. Affected is the function sub_42D03C of the file /goform/SetStaticRouteCfg. The manipulation of the argument list results in buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2137 | Tenda TX3 SetIpMacBind buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2137</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda TX3 up to 16.03.13.11_multi. This impacts an unknown function of the file /goform/SetIpMacBind. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2136 | projectworlds Online Food Ordering System view-ticket.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2136</link><description>A flaw has been found in projectworlds Online Food Ordering System 1.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /view-ticket.php. Executing a manipulation of the argument ID can lead to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been published and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2134 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System manage-doctors.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2134</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. The affected element is an unknown function of the file /hms/admin/manage-doctors.php. Such manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been disclosed publicly and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2135 | UTT HiPER 810 formPdbUpConfig sub_43F020 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2135</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_43F020 of the file /goform/formPdbUpConfig. Performing a manipulation of the argument policyNames results in command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit is now public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2132 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2132</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtcat results in sql injection. The attack can be executed remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2133 | code-projects Online Music Site AdminUpdateCategory.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2133</link><description>A weakness has been identified in code-projects Online Music Site 1.0. Impacted is an unknown function of the file /Administrator/PHP/AdminUpdateCategory.php. This manipulation of the argument txtimage causes unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be used for attacks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2130 | BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret search_username index.ts command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2130</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in BurtTheCoder mcp-maigret up to 1.0.12. This affects an unknown part of the file src/index.ts of the component search_username. Executing a manipulation of the argument Username can lead to command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.0.13 is able to mitigate this issue. This patch is called b1ae073c4b3e789ab8de36dc6ca8111ae9399e7a. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2131 | XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server input_text os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2131</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in XixianLiang HarmonyOS-mcp-server 0.1.0. This vulnerability affects the function input_text. The manipulation of the argument text leads to os command injection. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15027 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15027</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_login_register_ajax_create_final_user' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-15100 | JAY Login &amp;amp; Register &amp;lt;= 2.6.03 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via jay_panel_ajax_update_profile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-15100</link><description>The JAY Login &amp; Register plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.03. This is due to the plugin allowing a user to update arbitrary user meta through the 'jay_panel_ajax_update_profile' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to elevate their privileges to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2129 | D-Link DIR-823X set_ac_status os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2129</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /goform/set_ac_status. Performing a manipulation of the argument ac_ipaddr/ac_ipstatus/ap_randtime results in os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been made public and could be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2205 | WeKan Meteor Publication cards.js CardPubSubBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2205</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This affects an unknown part of the file server/publications/cards.js of the component Meteor Publication Handler. Such manipulation leads to information disclosure. The attack may be performed from remote. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to mitigate this issue. The name of the patch is 0f5a9c38778ca550cbab6c5093470e1e90cb837f. Upgrading the affected component is advised.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2206 | WeKan Administrative Repair fixDuplicateLists.js FixDuplicateBleed access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2206</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in WeKan up to 8.20. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file server/methods/fixDuplicateLists.js of the component Administrative Repair Handler. Performing a manipulation results in improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is able to resolve this issue. The patch is named 4ce181d17249778094f73d21515f7f863f554743. It is advisable to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2207 | WeKan Activity Publication activities.js LinkedBoardActivitiesBleed information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2207</link><description>A weakness has been identified in WeKan up to 8.20. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file server/publications/activities.js of the component Activity Publication Handler. Executing a manipulation can lead to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is capable of addressing this issue. This patch is called 91a936e07d2976d4246dfe834281c3aaa87f9503. You should upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2208 | WeKan Rules rules.js RulesBleed authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2208</link><description>A security vulnerability has been detected in WeKan up to 8.20. Impacted is an unknown function of the file server/publications/rules.js of the component Rules Handler. The manipulation leads to missing authorization. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.21 is recommended to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is a787bcddf33ca28afb13ff5ea9a4cb92dceac005. The affected component should be upgraded.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2209 | WeKan Custom Translation translationBody.js setCreateTranslation improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2209</link><description>A vulnerability was detected in WeKan up to 8.18. The affected element is the function setCreateTranslation of the file client/components/settings/translationBody.js of the component Custom Translation Handler. The manipulation results in improper authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 8.19 is sufficient to fix this issue. The patch is identified as f244a43771f6ebf40218b83b9f46dba6b940d7de. It is suggested to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2120 | D-Link DIR-823X Configuration Parameter set_server_settings os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2120</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in D-Link DIR-823X 250416. This affects an unknown function of the file /goform/set_server_settings of the component Configuration Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument terminal_addr/server_ip/server_port leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2122 | Xiaopi Panel WAF Firewall demo.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2122</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in Xiaopi Panel up to 20260126. This impacts an unknown function of the file /demo.php of the component WAF Firewall. The manipulation of the argument ID results in sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been released to the public and may be used for attacks. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2026-2118 | UTT HiPER 810 rehttpd formReleaseConnect sub_4407D4 command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2026-2118</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in UTT HiPER 810 1.7.4-141218. The impacted element is the function sub_4407D4 of the file /goform/formReleaseConnect of the component rehttpd. Executing a manipulation of the argument Isp_Name can lead to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>