<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:55:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-7260 | Keycloak-core: open redirect on account page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7260</link><description>An open redirect vulnerability was found in Keycloak. A specially crafted URL can be constructed where the referrer and referrer_uri parameters are made to trick a user to visit a malicious webpage. A trusted URL can trick users and automation into believing that the URL is safe, when, in fact, it redirects to a malicious server. This issue can result in a victim inadvertently trusting the destination of the redirect, potentially leading to a successful phishing attack or other types of attacks.&#13;
&#13;
Once a crafted URL is made, it can be sent to a Keycloak admin via email for example. This will trigger this vulnerability when the user visits the page and clicks the link. A malicious actor can use this to target users they know are Keycloak admins for further attacks. It may also be possible to bypass other domain-related security checks, such as supplying this as a OAuth redirect uri. The malicious actor can further obfuscate the redirect_uri using URL encoding, to hide the text of the actual malicious website domain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7318 | Keycloak-core: one time passcode (otp) is valid longer than expiration timeseverity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7318</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Keycloak. Expired OTP codes are still usable when using FreeOTP when the OTP token period is set to 30 seconds (default). Instead of expiring and deemed unusable around 30 seconds in, the tokens are valid for an additional 30 seconds totaling 1 minute.&#13;
A one time passcode that is valid longer than its expiration time increases the attack window for malicious actors to abuse the system and compromise accounts. Additionally, it increases the attack surface because at any given time, two OTPs are valid.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:55:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7341 | Wildfly-elytron: org.keycloak/keycloak-services: session fixation in elytron saml adapters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7341</link><description>A session fixation issue was discovered in the SAML adapters provided by Keycloak. The session ID and JSESSIONID cookie are not changed at login time, even when the turnOffChangeSessionIdOnLogin option is configured. This flaw allows an attacker who hijacks the current session before authentication to trigger session fixation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:55:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42759 | An issue in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /api/usuario/cadastrodesuplente endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42759</link><description>An issue in Ellevo v.6.2.0.38160 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /api/usuario/cadastrodesuplente endpoint.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:45:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45411 | Twig has a possible sandbox bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45411</link><description>Twig is a template language for PHP. Under some circumstances, the sandbox security checks are not run which allows user-contributed templates to bypass the sandbox restrictions. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.44.8, 2.16.1, and 3.14.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44334 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v24.04.18D1, and DI-7400...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44334</link><description>D-Link DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v24.04.18D1, and DI-7400G+V2 v24.04.18D1 are vulnerable to Remote Command Execution due to insufficient parameter filtering in the CGI handling function of upgrade_filter.asp.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44335 | D-Link DI-7003G v19.12.24A1, DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v2...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44335</link><description>D-Link DI-7003G v19.12.24A1, DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v24.04.18D1, and DI-7400G+V2 v24.04.18D1 are vulnerable to Remote Command Execution (RCE) via version_upgrade.asp.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44849 | Qualitor up to 8.24 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Arbitrary File Upload in checkAcesso.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44849</link><description>Qualitor up to 8.24 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Arbitrary File Upload in checkAcesso.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:31:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44333 | D-Link DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v24.04.18D1, and DI-7400...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44333</link><description>D-Link DI-7003GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100G+V2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7100GV2 v24.04.18D1, DI-7200GV2 v24.04.18E1, DI-7300G+V2 v24.04.18D1, and DI-7400G+V2 v24.04.18D1 are vulnerable to Remote Command Execution. An attacker can achieve arbitrary command execution by sending a carefully crafted malicious string to the CGI function responsible for handling usb_paswd.asp.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:13:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45406 | Craft CMS stored XSS in breadcrumb list and title fields</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45406</link><description>Craft is a content management system (CMS). Craft CMS 5 stored XSS can be triggered by the breadcrumb list and title fields with user input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:55:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8604 | SourceCodester Online Food Ordering System Create an Account Page index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8604</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Online Food Ordering System 2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file index.php of the component Create an Account Page. The manipulation of the argument First Name/Last Name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8605 | code-projects Inventory Management Registration Form registration.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8605</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Inventory Management 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view/registration.php of the component Registration Form. The manipulation with the input  leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:29:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44720 | SeaCMS v13.1 was discovered to an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the component admin_safe.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44720</link><description>SeaCMS v13.1 was discovered to an arbitrary file read vulnerability via the component admin_safe.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44721 | SeaCMS v13.1 was discovered to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the url parameter at /admin_reslib.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44721</link><description>SeaCMS v13.1 was discovered to a Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) via the url parameter at /admin_reslib.php.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:41:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8042 | Rapid7 Insight Platform Unauthorized Empty Group Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8042</link><description>Rapid7 Insight Platform versions between November 2019 and August 14, 2024 suffer from missing authorization issues whereby an attacker can intercept local requests to set the name and description of a new user group. This could potentially lead to an empty user group being added to the incorrect customer. This vulnerability is remediated as of August 14, 2024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45041 | External Secrets Operator vulnerable to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45041</link><description>External Secrets Operator is a Kubernetes operator that integrates external secret management systems. The external-secrets has a deployment called default-external-secrets-cert-controller, which is bound with a same-name ClusterRole. This ClusterRole has "get/list" verbs of secrets resources. It also has path/update verb of validatingwebhookconfigurations resources.  This can be used to abuse the SA token of the deployment to retrieve or get ALL secrets in the whole cluster, capture and log all data from requests attempting to update Secrets, or make a webhook deny all Pod create and update requests. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.10.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:12:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8372 | AngularJS improper sanitization in &amp;#x27;srcset&amp;#x27; attribute</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8372</link><description>Improper sanitization of the value of the [srcset] attribute in AngularJS allows attackers to bypass common image source restrictions, which can also lead to a form of  Content Spoofing https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/Content_Spoofing .

This issue affects AngularJS versions 1.3.0-rc.4 and greater.

Note:
The AngularJS project is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://docs.angularjs.org/misc/version-support-status .</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8373 | AngularJS improper sanitization in &amp;#x27;&amp;lt;source&amp;gt;&amp;#x27; element</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8373</link><description>Improper sanitization of the value of the [srcset] attribute in &lt;source /&gt; HTML elements in AngularJS allows attackers to bypass common image source restrictions, which can also lead to a form of  Content Spoofing https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/Content_Spoofing .

This issue affects all versions of AngularJS.

Note:
The AngularJS project is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://docs.angularjs.org/misc/version-support-status .</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:54:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40643 | Joplin has a parsing error leading to Cross-site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40643</link><description>Joplin is a free, open source note taking and to-do application. Joplin fails to take into account that "&lt;" followed by a non letter character will not be considered html. As such it is possible to do an XSS by putting an "illegal" tag within a tag.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7015 | Improper Authentication in Profelis Informatics and Consulting&amp;#x27;s PassBOX</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7015</link><description>Improper Authentication, Missing Authentication for Critical Function, Improper Authorization vulnerability in Profelis Informatics and Consulting PassBox allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects PassBox: before v1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-44375 | D-Link DI-8100 v16.07.26A1 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the dbsrv_asp function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-44375</link><description>D-Link DI-8100 v16.07.26A1 has a stack overflow vulnerability in the dbsrv_asp function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 13:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6572 | Improper host key checking in active check &amp;#x27;Check SFTP Service&amp;#x27; and special agent &amp;#x27;VNX quotas and filesystem&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6572</link><description>Improper host key checking in active check 'Check SFTP Service' and special agent 'VNX quotas and filesystem' in Checkmk before Checkmk 2.3.0p15, 2.2.0p33, 2.1.0p48 and 2.0.0 (EOL) allows man-in-the-middle attackers to intercept traffic</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 09:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8601 | Improper Access Control Vulnerability in TechExcel Back Office Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8601</link><description>This vulnerability exists in TechExcel Back Office Software versions prior to 1.0.0 due to improper access controls on certain API endpoints. An authenticated remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability by manipulating a parameter through API request URL which could lead to unauthorized access to sensitive information belonging to other users.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 09:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37288 | A deserialization issue in Kibana can lead to arbitrary code execution when Kibana attempts to parse a YAML document containing a crafted pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37288</link><description>A deserialization issue in Kibana can lead to arbitrary code execution when Kibana attempts to parse a YAML document containing a crafted payload. This issue only affects users that use  Elastic Security’s built-in AI tools https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/security/current/ai-for-security.html  and have configured an  Amazon Bedrock connector https://www.elastic.co/guide/en/security/current/assistant-connect-to-bedrock.html .</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45203 | Improper authorization in handler for custom URL scheme issue in "@cosme" App for Android versions prior 5.69.0 and "@cosme" App for iOS ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45203</link><description>Improper authorization in handler for custom URL scheme issue in "@cosme" App for Android versions prior 5.69.0 and "@cosme" App for iOS versions prior to 6.74.0 allows an attacker to lead a user to access an arbitrary website via the vulnerable App. As a result, the user may become a victim of a phishing attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5561 | Popup Maker &amp;lt; 1.19.1 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5561</link><description>The Popup Maker  WordPress plugin before 1.19.1 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6910 | EventON &amp;lt; 2.2.17 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6910</link><description>The EventON WordPress plugin before 2.2.17 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7687 | AZIndex &amp;lt;= 0.8.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7687</link><description>The AZIndex WordPress plugin through 0.8.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7688 | AZIndex &amp;lt;= 0.8.1 - Index Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7688</link><description>The AZIndex WordPress plugin through 0.8.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin delete arbitrary indexes via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7689 | Snapshot Backup &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7689</link><description>The Snapshot Backup WordPress plugin through 2.1.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7918 | Pocket Widget &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7918</link><description>The Pocket Widget WordPress plugin through 0.1.3 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 06:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45625 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Forminator versions prior to 1.34.1. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script ma...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45625</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in Forminator versions prior to 1.34.1. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary script may be executed on the web browser of the user who follows a crafted URL and accesses the webpage with the web form created by Forminator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 04:54:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8585 | LEARNING DIGITAL Orca HCM - Arbitrary File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8585</link><description>Orca HCM from LEARNING DIGITA does not properly restrict a specific parameter of the file download functionality, allowing a remote attacker with regular privileges to download arbitrary system files.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:27:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8586 | Uniong WebITR - Open Redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8586</link><description>WebITR from Uniong has an Open Redirect vulnerability, which allows unauthorized remote attackers to exploit this vulnerability to forge URLs. Users, believing they are accessing a trusted domain, can be redirected to another page, potentially leading to phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:27:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8584 | LEARNING DIGITAL Orca HCM - Improper Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8584</link><description>Orca HCM from LEARNING DIGITAL does not properly restrict access to a specific functionality, allowing unauthenticated remote attacker to exploit this functionality to create an account with administrator privilege and subsequently use it to log in.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8582 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 22:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8583 | SourceCodester Online Bank Management System Feedback mfeedback.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8583</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Bank Management System and Online Bank Management System - 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /mfeedback.php of the component Feedback Handler. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 22:23:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8580 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 shadow.sample hard-coded password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8580</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /etc/shadow.sample. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded password. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 20:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8579 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiRepeaterCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8579</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220. This affects the function setWiFiRepeaterCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument password leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 19:45:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8578 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiMeshName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8578</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setWiFiMeshName of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument device_name leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 19:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8577 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8/AC1200 T10 cstecgi.cgi setStaticDhcpRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8577</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 and AC1200 T10 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220/4.1.8cu.5207. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setStaticDhcpRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 18:46:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8576 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8/AC1200 T10 cstecgi.cgi setIpPortFilterRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8576</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 and AC1200 T10 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220/4.1.8cu.5207. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setIpPortFilterRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8575 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 cstecgi.cgi setWiFiScheduleCfg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8575</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function setWiFiScheduleCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 16:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42341 | Loway - CWE-601: URL Redirection to Untrusted Site (&amp;#x27;Open Redirect&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42341</link><description>Loway - CWE-601: URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect')</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42342 | Loway -  CWE-444: Inconsistent Interpretation of HTTP Requests (&amp;#x27;HTTP Request/Response Smuggling&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42342</link><description>Loway -  CWE-444: Inconsistent Interpretation of HTTP Requests ('HTTP Request/Response Smuggling')</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42343 | Loway - CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42343</link><description>Loway - CWE-204: Observable Response Discrepancy</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8574 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8574</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument slaveIpList leads to os command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 11:09:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8573 | TOTOLINK AC1200 T8/AC1200 T10 cstecgi.cgi setParentalRules buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8573</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK AC1200 T8 and AC1200 T10 4.1.5cu.861_B20230220/4.1.8cu.5207. This affects the function setParentalRules of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument desc leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 10:17:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8572 | Gouniverse GoLang CMS FrontendHandler.go PageRenderHtmlByAlias cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Gouniverse GoLang CMS 1.4.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function PageRenderHtmlByAlias of the file FrontendHandler.go. The manipulation of the argument alias leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.4.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 3e661cdfb4beeb9fe2ad507cdb8104c0b17d072c. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 08:15:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8571 | erjemin roll_cms views.py information exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in erjemin roll_cms up to 1484fe2c4e0805946a7bcf46218509fcb34883a9. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file roll_cms/roll_cms/views.py. The manipulation leads to information exposure through error message. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 07:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8570 | itsourcecode Tailoring Management System inccatadd.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8570</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Tailoring Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /inccatadd.php. The manipulation of the argument title leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6852 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6852</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6853 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Welcome Popup Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6853</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check when updating welcome popups, which could allow attackers to make logged admins perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6855 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Exit Popup Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6855</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check when updating exit popups, which could allow attackers to make logged admins perform such action via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6856 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - SMTP Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6856</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6859 | WP MultiTasking &amp;lt;= 0.1.12 - Reflected XSS via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6859</link><description>The WP MultiTasking  WordPress plugin through 0.1.12 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6924 | TrueBooker &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Multiple Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6924</link><description>The TrueBooker  WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6925 | TrueBooker &amp;lt; 1.0.3 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6925</link><description>The TrueBooker  WordPress plugin before 1.0.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6928 | Opti Marketing &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6928</link><description>The Opti Marketing WordPress plugin through 2.0.9 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 06:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8569 | code-projects Hospital Management System user-login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8569</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file user-login.php. The manipulation of the argument username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 05:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8568 | Mini-Tmall 1 rewardMapper.select sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8568</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Mini-Tmall up to 20240901. Affected is the function rewardMapper.select of the file tmall/admin/order/1/1. The manipulation of the argument orderBy leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8567 | itsourcecode Payroll Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8567</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Payroll Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ajax.php?action=delete_deductions. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8566 | code-projects Online Shop Store settings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8566</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in code-projects Online Shop Store 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /settings.php. The manipulation of the argument error leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 23:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8565 | SourceCodesters Clinics Patient Management System print_diseases.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8565</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodesters Clinics Patient Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /print_diseases.php. The manipulation of the argument disease/from/to leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 22:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8564 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD update.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8564</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /endpoint/update.php. The manipulation of the argument tbl_person_id/first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 20:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8563 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD update.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8563</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /endpoint/update.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 20:22:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8562 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD Add.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/Add.php. The manipulation of the argument first_name/middle_name/last_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:20:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8561 | SourceCodester PHP CRUD Delete Person delete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8561</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester PHP CRUD 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /endpoint/delete.php of the component Delete Person Handler. The manipulation of the argument person leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 18:42:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8560 | SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System save_invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8560</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in SourceCodester Simple Invoice Generator System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /save_invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument invoice_code/customer/cashier/total_amount/discount_percentage/discount_amount/tendered_amount leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 18:28:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8559 | SourceCodester Online Food Menu delete-menu.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8559</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Food Menu 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /endpoint/delete-menu.php. The manipulation of the argument menu leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38650 | An authentication bypass vulnerability can allow a low privileged attacker to access the NTLM hash of service account on the VSPC server.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38650</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability can allow a low privileged attacker to access the NTLM hash of service account on the VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38651 | A code injection vulnerability can allow a low-privileged user to overwrite files on that VSPC server, which can lead to remote code executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38651</link><description>A code injection vulnerability can allow a low-privileged user to overwrite files on that VSPC server, which can lead to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39714 | A code injection vulnerability that permits a low-privileged user to upload arbitrary files to the server, leading to remote code execution ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39714</link><description>A code injection vulnerability that permits a low-privileged user to upload arbitrary files to the server, leading to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39715 | A code injection vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user with REST API access granted to remotely upload arbitrary files to the VSPC...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39715</link><description>A code injection vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user with REST API access granted to remotely upload arbitrary files to the VSPC server using REST API, leading to remote code execution on VSPC server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39718 | An improper input validation vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user to remotely remove files on the system with permissions equival...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39718</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability that allows a low-privileged user to remotely remove files on the system with permissions equivalent to those of the service account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40709 | A missing authorization vulnerability allows a local low-privileged user on the machine to escalate their privileges to root level.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40709</link><description>A missing authorization vulnerability allows a local low-privileged user on the machine to escalate their privileges to root level.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40710 | A series of related high-severity vulnerabilities, the most notable enabling remote code execution (RCE) as the service account and extracti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40710</link><description>A series of related high-severity vulnerabilities, the most notable enabling remote code execution (RCE) as the service account and extraction of sensitive information (savedcredentials and passwords). Exploiting these vulnerabilities requires a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40711 | A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability with a malicious payload can allow an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE).</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40711</link><description>A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability with a malicious payload can allow an unauthenticated remote code execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40712 | A path traversal vulnerability allows an attacker with a low-privileged account and local access to the system to perform local privilege es...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40712</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability allows an attacker with a low-privileged account and local access to the system to perform local privilege escalation (LPE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40713 | A vulnerability that allows a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication to alter Multi-Factor Authe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40713</link><description>A vulnerability that allows a user who has been assigned a low-privileged role within Veeam Backup &amp; Replication to alter Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) settings and bypass MFA.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40714 | An improper certificate validation vulnerability in TLS certificate validation allows an attacker on the same network to intercept sensitive...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40714</link><description>An improper certificate validation vulnerability in TLS certificate validation allows an attacker on the same network to intercept sensitive credentials during restore operations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40718 | A server side request forgery vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to perform local privilege escalation through exploiting an SSRF vu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40718</link><description>A server side request forgery vulnerability allows a low-privileged user to perform local privilege escalation through exploiting an SSRF vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42019 | A vulnerability that allows an attacker to access the NTLM hash of the Veeam Reporter Service service account. This attack requires user int...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42019</link><description>A vulnerability that allows an attacker to access the NTLM hash of the Veeam Reporter Service service account. This attack requires user interaction and data collected from Veeam Backup &amp; Replication.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42020 | A Cross-site-scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Reporter Widgets that allows HTML injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42020</link><description>A Cross-site-scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the Reporter Widgets that allows HTML injection.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42021 | An improper access control vulnerability allows an attacker with valid access tokens to access saved credentials.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42021</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability allows an attacker with valid access tokens to access saved credentials.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42022 | An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability allows an attacker to modify product configuration files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42022</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability allows an attacker to modify product configuration files.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42023 | An improper access control vulnerability allows low-privileged users to execute code with Administrator privileges remotely.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42023</link><description>An improper access control vulnerability allows low-privileged users to execute code with Administrator privileges remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42024 | A vulnerability that allows an attacker in possession of the Veeam ONE Agent service account credentials to perform remote code execution on...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42024</link><description>A vulnerability that allows an attacker in possession of the Veeam ONE Agent service account credentials to perform remote code execution on the machine where the Veeam ONE Agent is installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30582 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js version 20, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read fla...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30582</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js version 20, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-read flag is used with a non-* argument. This flaw arises from an inadequate permission model that fails to restrict file watching through the fs.watchFile API. As a result, malicious actors can monitor files that they do not have explicit read access to.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30583 | fs.openAsBlob() can bypass the experimental permission model when using the file system read restriction with the `--allow-fs-read` flag in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30583</link><description>fs.openAsBlob() can bypass the experimental permission model when using the file system read restriction with the `--allow-fs-read` flag in Node.js 20. This flaw arises from a missing check in the `fs.openAsBlob()` API.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30584 | A vulnerability has been discovered in Node.js version 20, specifically within the experimental permission model. This flaw relates to impro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30584</link><description>A vulnerability has been discovered in Node.js version 20, specifically within the experimental permission model. This flaw relates to improper handling of path traversal bypass when verifying file permissions.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30587 | A vulnerability in Node.js version 20 allows for bypassing restrictions set by the --experimental-permission flag using the built-in inspect...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30587</link><description>A vulnerability in Node.js version 20 allows for bypassing restrictions set by the --experimental-permission flag using the built-in inspector module (node:inspector).

By exploiting the Worker class's ability to create an "internal worker" with the kIsInternal Symbol, attackers can modify the isInternal value when an inspector is attached within the Worker constructor before initializing a new WorkerImpl. This vulnerability exclusively affects Node.js users employing the permission model mechanism.

Please note that at the time this CVE was issued, the permission model is an experimental feature of Node.js.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39333 | Maliciously crafted export names in an imported WebAssembly module can inject JavaScript code. The injected code may be able to access data ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39333</link><description>Maliciously crafted export names in an imported WebAssembly module can inject JavaScript code. The injected code may be able to access data and functions that the WebAssembly module itself does not have access to, similar to as if the WebAssembly module was a JavaScript module.

This vulnerability affects users of any active release line of Node.js. The vulnerable feature is only available if Node.js is started with the `--experimental-wasm-modules` command line option.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46809 | Node.js versions which bundle an unpatched version of OpenSSL or run against a dynamically linked version of OpenSSL which are unpatched are...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46809</link><description>Node.js versions which bundle an unpatched version of OpenSSL or run against a dynamically linked version of OpenSSL which are unpatched are vulnerable to the Marvin Attack - https://people.redhat.com/~hkario/marvin/, if PCKS #1 v1.5 padding is allowed when performing RSA descryption using a private key.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36137 | A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-write flag is used....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36137</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in Node.js, affecting users of the experimental permission model when the --allow-fs-write flag is used.

Node.js Permission Model do not operate on file descriptors, however, operations such as fs.fchown or fs.fchmod can use a "read-only" file descriptor to change the owner and permissions of a file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-36138 | Bypass incomplete fix of CVE-2024-27980, that arises from improper handling of batch files with all possible extensions on Windows via child...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-36138</link><description>Bypass incomplete fix of CVE-2024-27980, that arises from improper handling of batch files with all possible extensions on Windows via child_process.spawn / child_process.spawnSync. A malicious command line argument can inject arbitrary commands and achieve code execution even if the shell option is not enabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 16:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8558 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System Price place-order.php improper validation of specified quantity in input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8558</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /foms/routers/place-order.php of the component Price Handler. The manipulation of the argument total leads to improper validation of specified quantity in input. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:37:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8557 | SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System cancel-order.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8557</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Food Ordering Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /foms/routers/cancel-order.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:09:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8555 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System congratulations.php redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8555</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 2.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file congratulations.php. The manipulation of the argument goto_page leads to open redirect. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:42:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40681 | IBM MQ Operator security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40681</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.26 and 3.2.4 could allow an authenticated user in a specifically defined role, to bypass security restrictions and execute actions against the queue manager.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40680 | IBM MQ Operator denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40680</link><description>IBM MQ Operator 2.0.26 and 3.2.4 could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper memory allocation causing a segmentation fault.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:20:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37068 | IBM Maximo Application Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37068</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite - Manage Component 8.10, 8.11, and 9.0 uses weaker than expected cryptographic algorithms that could allow an attacker to decrypt highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:50:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8554 | SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System users.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8554</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Clinics Patient Management System 2.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /users.php. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1596 | Ninja Forms File Uploads &amp;lt;= 3.3.16 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1596</link><description>The Ninja Forms - File Uploads plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via an uploaded file (e.g. RTX file) in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.16 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6010 | Cost Calculator Builder PRO &amp;lt;= 3.1.96 -  Unauthenticated Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6010</link><description>The Cost Calculator Builder PRO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to price manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.1.96. This is due to the plugin allowing the price field to be manipulated prior to processing via the 'create_cc_order' function, called from the Cost Calculator Builder plugin. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate the price of orders submitted via the calculator. Note: this vulnerability was partially patched with the release of Cost Calculator Builder version 3.2.17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7112 | Pinpoint Booking System &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.0- Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7112</link><description>The Pinpoint Booking System – #1 WordPress Booking Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the ‘schedule’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.9.5.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-7620 | Customizer Export/Import &amp;lt;= 0.9.7 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload via Customization Settings Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7620</link><description>The Customizer Export/Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the '_import' function in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. NOTE: This vulnerability is only exploitable when used in conjunction with a race condition as the uploaded file is deleted shortly after it is created.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 11:25:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8523 | lmxcms SQL Command Execution Module admin.php formatData code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8523</link><description>A vulnerability was found in lmxcms up to 1.4 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formatData of the file /admin.php?m=Acquisi&amp;amp;a=testcj&amp;amp;lid=1 of the component SQL Command Execution Module. The manipulation of the argument data leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6849 | Preloader Plus – WordPress Loading Screen Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6849</link><description>The Preloader Plus – WordPress Loading Screen Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:45:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8538 | Big File Uploads &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Full Path Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8538</link><description>The Big File Uploads – Increase Maximum File Upload Size plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2. This is due the plugin not sanitizing a file path in an error message. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-8521 | Wavelog Live QSO qso index cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-8521</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Wavelog up to 1.8.0. Affected is the function index of the file /qso of the component Live QSO. The manipulation of the argument manual leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.8.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as b31002cec6b71ab5f738881806bb546430ec692e. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45034 | Apache Airflow: Authenticated DAG authors could execute code on scheduler nodes</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45034</link><description>Apache Airflow versions before 2.10.1 have a vulnerability that allows DAG authors to add local settings to the DAG folder and get it executed by the scheduler, where the scheduler is not supposed to execute code submitted by the DAG author. 
Users are advised to upgrade to version 2.10.1 or later, which has fixed the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 07:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45498 | Apache Airflow: Command Injection in an example DAG</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45498</link><description>Example DAG: example_inlet_event_extra.py shipped with Apache Airflow version 2.10.0 has a vulnerability that allows an authenticated attacker with only DAG trigger permission to execute arbitrary commands. If you used that example as the base of your DAGs - please review if you have not copied the dangerous example; see  https://github.com/apache/airflow/pull/41873  for more information. We recommend against exposing the example DAGs in your deployment. If you must expose the example DAGs, upgrade Airflow to version 2.10.1 or later.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 07:57:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>