<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-7701 | Misuse of SHA256 to create an encryption key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-7701</link><description>Use of Password Hash With Insufficient Computational Effort vulnerability in percona percona-toolkit allows Encryption Brute Forcing.This issue affects percona-toolkit: 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 11:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56082 | ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56082</link><description>ChatBar.tsx in Lumos before 1.0.17 parses raw HTML in Markdown because the markdown-to-jsx package is used without disableParsingRawHTML set to true.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 04:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55969 | DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an exter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55969</link><description>DocIO in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 throws XMLException during the resaving of a DOCX document with an external reference XML, aka I640714.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56074 | gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56074</link><description>gitingest before 9996a06 mishandles symbolic links that point outside of the base directory.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55970 | File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55970</link><description>File Manager in Syncfusion Essential Studio for ASP.NET MVC before 27.1.55 has a traversal issue that is related to the request parameter, aka I644734.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56072 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of serv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56072</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. The sFlow v5 plugin allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (application crash) via a crafted packet that specifies many sFlow samples.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56073 | An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56073</link><description>An issue was discovered in FastNetMon Community Edition through 1.2.7. Zero-length templates for Netflow v9 allow remote attackers to cause a denial of service (divide-by-zero error and application crash).</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31891 | IBM Storage Scale privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31891</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 

contains a local privilege escalation vulnerability. A malicious actor with command line access to the 'scalemgmt' user can elevate privileges to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31892 | IBM Storage Scale SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31892</link><description>IBM Storage Scale GUI 5.1.9.0 through 5.1.9.6 and 5.2.0.0 through 5.2.1.1 could allow a user to perform unauthorized actions after intercepting and modifying a csv file due to improper neutralization of formula elements.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 13:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11720 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11720</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via submission forms in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the new Taxonomy form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This is only exploitable when lower-level users have been granted access to submit specific forms, which is disabled by default.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11721 | Frontend Admin by DynamiApps &amp;lt;= 3.24.5 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11721</link><description>The Frontend Admin by DynamiApps plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 3.24.5. This is due to insufficient controls on the user role select field when utilizing the 'Role' field in a form. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create new administrative user accounts, even when the administrative user role has not been provided as an option to the user, granted that unauthenticated users have been provided access to the form.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:35:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11710 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11710</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'fieldfor', 'visibleParent' and 'id' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11711 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11711</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'resumeid' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11712 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Arbitrary Resume Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11712</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the getResumeFileDownloadById() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download other users resumes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11713 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via wpjobportal_deactivate()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11713</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'page_id' parameter of the wpjobportal_deactivate() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11714 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection via getFieldsForVisibleCombobox()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11714</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'ff' parameter of the getFieldsForVisibleCombobox() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11715 | WP Job Portal &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Missing Authorization to Limited Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11715</link><description>The WP Job Portal – A Complete Recruitment System for Company or Job Board website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the assignUserRole() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to elevate their privileges to that of an employer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12446 | Post to Pdf &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12446</link><description>The Post to Pdf plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gmptp_single_post' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12628 | bodi0’s Easy Cache &amp;lt;= 0.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12628</link><description>The bodi0`s Easy cache plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'cache-folder' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:51:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10646 | Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp;amp; Drop WP Form Builder &amp;lt;= 5.2.6 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Form Subject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10646</link><description>The Contact Form Plugin by Fluent Forms for Quiz, Survey, and Drag &amp; Drop WP Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the form's subject parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10690 | Shortcodes for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Post Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10690</link><description>The Shortcodes for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 via the 'SHORTCODE_ELEMENTOR' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract data from private and draft posts created with Elementor that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11752 | Eveeno &amp;lt;= 1.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11752</link><description>The Eveeno plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'eveeno' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12422 | Import Eventbrite Events &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12422</link><description>The Import Eventbrite Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12459 | Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12459</link><description>The Ganohrs Toggle Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'toggle' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12474 | GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12474</link><description>The GeoDataSource Country Region DropDown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gds-country-dropdown' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12501 | Simple Locator &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12501</link><description>The Simple Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 05:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11095 | Visualmodo Elements &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11095</link><description>The Visualmodo Elements plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via REST API SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11462 | Filestack Official &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11462</link><description>The Filestack Official plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'fstab' and 'filestack_options' parameters in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11751 | TCBD Popover &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11751</link><description>The TCBD Popover plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tcbd-popover-image ' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11755 | IMS Countdown &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11755</link><description>The IMS Countdown plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown post settings in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11759 | Bukza &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11759</link><description>The Bukza plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bukza' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11763 | Plezi &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11763</link><description>The Plezi plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'plezi' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11770 | Post Carousel &amp;amp; Slider &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11770</link><description>The Post Carousel &amp; Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'post-cs' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11855 | Koalendar – Events &amp;amp; Appointments Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via height Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11855</link><description>The Koalendar – Events &amp; Appointments Booking Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘height’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11865 | Tabs Maker &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11865</link><description>The Tabs Maker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on tab descriptions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11867 | Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11867</link><description>The Companion Portfolio – Responsive Portfolio Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'companion-portfolio' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11869 | Buk for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11869</link><description>The Buk for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'buk' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11873 | glomex oEmbed &amp;lt;= 0.9.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11873</link><description>The glomex oEmbed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'glomex_integration' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.9.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11876 | Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11876</link><description>The Kredeum NFTs, the easiest way to sell your NFTs directly on your WordPress site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'kredeum_opensky' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11877 | Cricket Live Score &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11877</link><description>The Cricket Live Score plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cricket_score' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11879 | Stripe Donation &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11879</link><description>The Stripe Donation plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stripe_donation' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11883 | Connatix Video Embed &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11883</link><description>The Connatix Video Embed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cnx_script_code' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11884 | Wp photo text slider 50 &amp;lt;= 8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11884</link><description>The Wp photo text slider 50 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp-photo-slider' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11888 | IDer Login for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11888</link><description>The IDer Login for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'ider_login_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11889 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11889</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11894 | The Permalinker &amp;lt;= 1.8.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11894</link><description>The The Permalinker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'permalink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12411 | WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp;amp; More &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12411</link><description>The WP Ad Guru – Banner ad, Responsive popup, Popup maker, Ad rotator &amp; More plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'page' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12447 | Get Post Content Shortcode &amp;lt;= 0.4 - Insecure Direct Object Reference to Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via post_content Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12447</link><description>The Get Post Content Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 0.4 via the 'post-content' shortcode due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to read the content of password-protected, private, draft, and pending posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12448 | Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12448</link><description>The Posts and Products Views for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'papvfwc_views' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12458 | Smart PopUp Blaster &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12458</link><description>The Smart PopUp Blaster plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spb-button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12502 | My IDX Home Search &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12502</link><description>The My IDX Home Search plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'homeasap-idx-landing' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12517 | WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12517</link><description>The WooCommerce Cart Count Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cart_button' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12523 | States Map US &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12523</link><description>The States Map US plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'states_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12555 | SIP Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12555</link><description>The SIP Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0. This is due to missing nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12578 | Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.8 - Unauthenticated Customer Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12578</link><description>The Tickera – WordPress Event Ticketing plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.8 via the 'tickera_tickets_info' endpoint. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from bookings like full names, email addresses, check-in/out timestamps and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9698 | Crafthemes Demo Import &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Upload in process_uploaded_files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9698</link><description>The Crafthemes Demo Import plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'process_uploaded_files' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 04:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-29476 | In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. T...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-29476</link><description>In Menlo On-Premise Appliance before 2.88, web policy may not be consistently applied properly to intentionally malformed client requests. This is fixed in 2.88.2+, 2.89.1+, and 2.90.1+.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 02:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12552 | Wacom Center WTabletServicePro Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12552</link><description>Wacom Center WTabletServicePro Link Following Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows local attackers to escalate privileges on affected installations of Wacom Center. An attacker must first obtain the ability to execute low-privileged code on the target system in order to exploit this vulnerability. 

The specific flaw exists within WTabletServicePro.exe. By creating a symbolic link, an attacker can abuse the service to create an arbitrary file. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to escalate privileges and execute arbitrary code in the context of SYSTEM. Was ZDI-CAN-25359.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 22:44:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12553 | GeoVision GV-ASManager Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12553</link><description>GeoVision GV-ASManager Missing Authorization Information Disclosure Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information on affected installations of GeoVision GV-ASManager. Although authentication is required to exploit this vulnerability, default guest credentials may be used.

The specific flaw exists within the GV-ASWeb service. The issue results from the lack of authorization prior to allowing access to functionality. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose stored credentials, leading to further compromise. Was ZDI-CAN-25394.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 22:44:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55946 | Playloom Engine Data Storage Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55946</link><description>Playloom Engine is an open-source, high-performance game development engine. Engine Beta v0.0.1 has a security vulnerability related to data storage, specifically when using the collaboration features. When collaborating with another user, they may have access to personal information you have entered into the software. This poses a risk to user privacy. The maintainers of Playloom Engine have temporarily disabled the collaboration feature until a fix can be implemented. When Engine Beta v0.0.2 is released, it is expected to contain a patch addressing this issue. Users should refrain from using the collaboration feature in the meantime.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 21:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12632 | In Cleo Harmony up to and including 5.8.0.21, VLTrader up to and including 5.8.0.21, and LexiCom up to and including 5.8.0.21, there is an u...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12632</link><description>In Cleo Harmony up to and including 5.8.0.21, VLTrader up to and including 5.8.0.21, and LexiCom up to and including 5.8.0.21, there is an unrestricted file upload and download that could lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 20:50:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55956 | In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.24, VLTrader before 5.8.0.24, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.24, an unauthenticated user can import and execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55956</link><description>In Cleo Harmony before 5.8.0.24, VLTrader before 5.8.0.24, and LexiCom before 5.8.0.24, an unauthenticated user can import and execute arbitrary Bash or PowerShell commands on the host system by leveraging the default settings of the Autorun directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 20:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55890 | D-Tale allows Remote Code Execution through the Custom Filter Input</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55890</link><description>D-Tale is a visualizer for pandas data structures. Prior to version 3.16.1, users hosting D-Tale publicly can be vulnerable to remote code execution allowing attackers to run malicious code on the server. Users should upgrade to version 3.16.1 where the `update-settings` endpoint blocks the ability for users to update the `enable_custom_filters` flag. The only workaround for versions earlier than 3.16.1 is to only host D-Tale to trusted users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:20:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46971 | GPU DDK - UAF of memory in PMRUnlockSysPhysAddressesLocalMem for on-demand PMRs on PCI (LMA) systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46971</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct GPU system calls to read and write freed physical memory from the GPU.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47892 | GPU DDK - UAF of kernel memory in PMRUnlockPhysAddressesOSMem for on-demand non-4KB PMRs in system memory (UMA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47892</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct GPU system calls to read and write freed physical memory from the GPU.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 17:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55661 | Laravel Pulse Allows Remote Code Execution via Unprotected Query Method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55661</link><description>Laravel Pulse is a real-time application performance monitoring tool and dashboard for Laravel applications. A vulnerability has been discovered in Laravel Pulse prior to version 1.3.1 that could allow remote code execution through the public `remember()` method in the `Laravel\Pulse\Livewire\Concerns\RemembersQueries` trait. This method is accessible via Livewire components and can be exploited to call arbitrary callables within the application. An authenticated user with access to Laravel Pulse dashboard can execute arbitrary code by calling any function or static method in which the callable is a function or static method and the callable has no parameters or no strict parameter types. The vulnerable to component is `remember(callable $query, string $key = '')` method in `Laravel\Pulse\Livewire\Concerns\RemembersQueries`, and the vulnerability affects all Pulse card components that use this trait. Version 1.3.1 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55887 | Ucum-java has an XXE vulnerability in XML parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55887</link><description>Ucum-java is a FHIR Java library providing UCUM Services. In versions prior to 1.0.9, XML parsing performed by the UcumEssenceService is vulnerable to XML external entity injections. A processed XML file with a malicious DTD tag could produce XML containing data from the host system. This impacts use cases where ucum is being used to within a host where external clients can submit XML. Release 1.0.9 of Ucum-java fixes this vulnerability. As a workaround, ensure that the source xml for instantiating UcumEssenceService is trusted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:21:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54139 | Combodo iTop vulnerable to XSS leading to CSRF breach on _table_id parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54139</link><description>Combodo iTop is an open source and web-based IT service management platform. Prior to versions 2.7.11, 3.1.2, and 3.2.0., iTop has a cross-site scripting vulnerability that can lead to cross-site request forgery on the `_table_id` parameter. Versions 2.7.11, 3.1.2, and 3.2.0 contain a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:21:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9945 | Limited Information Disclosure in GoAnywhere MFT Prior to 7.7.0</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9945</link><description>An information-disclosure vulnerability exists in Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT application prior to version 7.7.0 that allows external access to the resources in certain admin root folders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 15:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-43472 | WordPress eRoom plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-43472</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes eRoom – Zoom Meetings &amp; Webinar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects eRoom – Zoom Meetings &amp; Webinar: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-44578 | WordPress Owl Carousel plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-44578</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pierre JEHAN Owl Carousel allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Owl Carousel: from n/a through 0.5.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45806 | WordPress Formidable Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45806</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Strategy11 Form Builder Team Formidable Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Formidable Forms: from n/a through 5.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45819 | WordPress Popup Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.17.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45819</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Popup Maker Popup Maker allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Popup Maker: from n/a through 1.17.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45826 | WordPress Sunshine Photo Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.13 - Auth. Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45826</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Sunshine Sunshine Photo Cart allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Sunshine Photo Cart: from n/a through 2.9.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45840 | WordPress Auto Affiliate Links plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.1.5 - Unauth. Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45840</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Lucian Apostol Auto Affiliate Links allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Auto Affiliate Links: from n/a through 6.2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45841 | WordPress Robo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.9 - Auth. Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45841</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RoboSoft Robo Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Robo Gallery: from n/a through 3.2.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46795 | WordPress Print Invoice &amp;amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7.2 - CSRF Plugin Settings Reset vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46795</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Print Invoice &amp; Delivery Notes for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46796 | WordPress CURCY plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.25 - Unauthenticated plugin settings change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46796</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VillaTheme CURCY allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CURCY: from n/a through 2.1.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46807 | WordPress Stock Sync for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46807</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Lauri Karisola / WP Trio Stock Sync for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Stock Sync for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46811 | WordPress ALD Dropshipping and Fulfillment for AliExpress and WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Broken Access Control + CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46811</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in VillaTheme(villatheme.com) ALD – Dropshipping and Fulfillment for AliExpress and WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ALD – Dropshipping and Fulfillment for AliExpress and WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.0.21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46838 | WordPress JS Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Unauthenticated Settings Change Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46838</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Help Desk JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46840 | WordPress JS Help Desk plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46840</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in JS Help Desk JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JS Help Desk – Best Help Desk &amp; Support Plugin: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46846 | WordPress Trending/Popular Post Slider and Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46846</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP OnlineSupport, Essential Plugin Trending/Popular Post Slider and Widget allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Trending/Popular Post Slider and Widget: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47168 | WordPress Printful Integration for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47168</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Printful Printful Integration for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Printful Integration for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47176 | WordPress Depicter Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47176</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Depicter Slider and Popup by Averta Depicter Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Depicter Slider: from n/a through 1.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47182 | WordPress APIExperts Square for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.4.1 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47182</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wpexpertsio APIExperts Square for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects APIExperts Square for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47429 | WordPress Coming Soon Landing Page and Maintenance Mode WordPress Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47429</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 8Degree Themes Coming Soon Landing Page and Maintenance Mode WordPress Plugin allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Coming Soon Landing Page and Maintenance Mode WordPress Plugin: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47594 | WordPress Essential Blocks for Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.5 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47594</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Blocks for Gutenberg allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Essential Blocks for Gutenberg: from n/a through 3.8.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22697 | WordPress Survey Maker plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22697</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Survey Maker team Survey Maker allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Survey Maker: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25988 | WordPress Video Gallery – YouTube Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25988</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Video Gallery by Total-Soft Video Gallery – YouTube Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Video Gallery – YouTube Gallery: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27456 | WordPress Total theme &amp;lt;= 2.1.19 - Authenticated Arbitrary Plugin Activation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27456</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HashThemes Total allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Total: from n/a through 2.1.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28990 | WordPress Viral Mag theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Authenticated Arbitrary Plugin Activation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28990</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in HashThemes Viral Mag allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Viral Mag: from n/a through 1.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30490 | WordPress Easing Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Plugin Settings Reset Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30490</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Matthew Ruddy Easing Slider  allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easing Slider : from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32506 | WordPress Link Whisper Free plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.3 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32506</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Link Whisper Link Whisper Free allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Link Whisper Free: from n/a through 0.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32507 | WordPress Woo Custom Emails plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32507</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wp3sixty Woo Custom Emails allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Woo Custom Emails: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32519 | WordPress WCP Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32519</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Webcodin WCP Contact Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WCP Contact Form: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32520 | WordPress WCP Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32520</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Webcodin WCP Contact Form allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WCP Contact Form: from n/a through 3.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32574 | WordPress Injection Guard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32574</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood Injection Guard allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Injection Guard: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32581 | WordPress WP-Chatbot for Messenger plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32581</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MobileMonkey WP-Chatbot for Messenger allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP-Chatbot for Messenger: from n/a through 4.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32585 | WordPress Portfolio Gallery – Responsive Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32585</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Total-Soft Portfolio Gallery – Responsive Image Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Portfolio Gallery – Responsive Image Gallery: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32586 | WordPress SoundCloud Is Gold plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32586</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Thomas Michalak Soundcloud Is Gold allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Soundcloud Is Gold: from n/a through 2.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32593 | WordPress GS Pins for Pinterest plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32593</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in GS Plugins GS Pins for Pinterest allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GS Pins for Pinterest: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32599 | WordPress reCAPTCHA for all plugin &amp;lt;= 1.22 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32599</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bill Minozzi reCAPTCHA for all allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects reCAPTCHA for all: from n/a through 1.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32601 | WordPress Booking Ultra Pro Appointments Booking Calendar Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32601</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Booking Ultra Pro Booking Ultra Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Booking Ultra Pro: from n/a through 1.1.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32798 | WordPress Simple Page Ordering plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32798</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 10up Simple Page Ordering allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple Page Ordering: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32963 | WordPress Predictive Search for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.8.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32963</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in a3rev Software WooCommerce Predictive Search allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Predictive Search: from n/a through 5.8.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33215 | WordPress Taggbox plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33215</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tagbox Taggbox allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Taggbox: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33324 | WordPress Easy Captcha plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33324</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wppal Easy Captcha allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Captcha: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33928 | WordPress WordPress Backup &amp;amp; Migration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33928</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee WordPress Backup &amp; Migration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WordPress Backup &amp; Migration: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33994 | WordPress Slimstat Analytics plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33994</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jason Crouse, VeronaLabs Slimstat Analytics allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Slimstat Analytics: from n/a through 5.0.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33995 | WordPress Photo Gallery by 10Web plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Photo Gallery Team Photo Gallery by 10Web allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Photo Gallery by 10Web: from n/a through 1.8.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33996 | WordPress Spam protection, AntiSpam, FireWall by CleanTalk plugin &amp;lt;= 6.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33996</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in СleanTalk - Anti-Spam Protection Spam protection, AntiSpam, FireWall by CleanTalk allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Spam protection, AntiSpam, FireWall by CleanTalk: from n/a through 6.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33998 | WordPress Easy Social Icons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33998</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in cybernetikz Easy Social Icons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Social Icons: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34009 | WordPress Social Media Share Buttons &amp;amp; Social Sharing Icons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.1 - Broken Access Control + CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34009</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Inisev Social Media &amp; Share Icons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Social Media &amp; Share Icons: from n/a through 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34014 | WordPress Grid Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34014</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in G5Theme Grid Plus allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Grid Plus: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34019 | WordPress Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.4.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34019</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Toolkit for LearnDash: from n/a through 3.6.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34376 | WordPress Change WooCommerce Add To Cart Button Text plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34376</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rextheme Change WooCommerce Add To Cart Button Text allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Change WooCommerce Add To Cart Button Text: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34381 | WordPress Zippy plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34381</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Gesundheit Bewegt GmbH Zippy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Zippy: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-34387 | WordPress Constant Contact Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-34387</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Constant Contact Constant Contact Forms allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Constant Contact Forms: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35037 | WordPress Surfer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2.357 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35037</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Surfer Surfer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Surfer: from n/a through 1.3.2.357.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35046 | WordPress Dynamic Visibility for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35046</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dynamic.ooo Dynamic Visibility for Elementor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Dynamic Visibility for Elementor: from n/a through 5.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35051 | WordPress Contact Forms by Cimatti plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35051</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cimatti Consulting Contact Forms by Cimatti allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Contact Forms by Cimatti: from n/a through 1.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35052 | WordPress Directorist plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.4 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35052</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpWax - WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory Directorist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Directorist: from n/a through 7.5.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35777 | WordPress The Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 6.1.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35777</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The Events Calendar The Events Calendar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects The Events Calendar: from n/a through 6.1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35875 | WordPress Gutenverse – Gutenberg Blocks – Page Builder for Site Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35875</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Jegstudio Gutenverse allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Gutenverse: from n/a through 1.8.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36506 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Waitlist plugin &amp;lt;= 2.13.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36506</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Waiting List allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Waiting List: from n/a through 2.13.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36509 | WordPress CHP Ads Block Detector plugin &amp;lt;= 3.9.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36509</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Suresh Chand CHP Ads Block Detector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CHP Ads Block Detector: from n/a through 3.9.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36510 | WordPress ReDi Restaurant Reservation plugin &amp;lt;= 23.0211 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36510</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Reservation Diary ReDi Restaurant Reservation allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ReDi Restaurant Reservation: from n/a through 23.0211.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36518 | WordPress Post Hit Counter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36518</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Hugh Lashbrooke Post Hit Counter allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post Hit Counter: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36519 | WordPress SW Product Bundles plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36519</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpthemego SW Product Bundles allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SW Product Bundles: from n/a through 2.0.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36526 | WordPress Duplicate Post Page Menu &amp;amp; Custom Post Type plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36526</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Inqsys Technology Duplicate Post Page Menu &amp; Custom Post Type allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Duplicate Post Page Menu &amp; Custom Post Type: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36528 | WordPress kk Star Ratings plugin &amp;lt;= 5.4.3 - Rate Manipulation due to IP Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36528</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in FeedbackWP kk Star Ratings allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects kk Star Ratings: from n/a through 5.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36531 | WordPress LiquidPoll plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.68 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36531</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in LiquidPoll LiquidPoll – Advanced Polls for Creators and Brands allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects LiquidPoll – Advanced Polls for Creators and Brands: from n/a through 3.3.68.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36680 | WordPress Image Regenerate &amp;amp; Select Crop plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36680</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Iulia Cazan Image Regenerate &amp; Select Crop allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Image Regenerate &amp; Select Crop: from n/a through 7.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36681 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp;amp; Coins List plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36681</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Cool Plugins Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Widgets – Price Ticker &amp; Coins List: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37887 | WordPress WPSchoolPress plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37887</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPSchoolPress Team WPSchoolPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WPSchoolPress: from n/a through 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37967 | WordPress DirectoryPress plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Unauthenticated Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37967</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Designinvento DirectoryPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects DirectoryPress: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37969 | WordPress Checkout with Zelle on Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37969</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in The African Boss Checkout with Zelle on Woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Checkout with Zelle on Woocommerce: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37971 | WordPress WooCommerce Product Stock Alert plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37971</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MultiVendorX WooCommerce Product Stock Alert allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WooCommerce Product Stock Alert: from n/a through 2.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37984 | WordPress Quiz And Survey Master  plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37984</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ExpressTech Quiz And Survey Master allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Quiz And Survey Master: from n/a through 8.1.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37987 | WordPress YourMembership Single Sign On plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37987</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in miniOrange YourMembership Single Sign On allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects YourMembership Single Sign On: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37989 | WordPress Easyship WooCommerce Shipping Rates plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37989</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Easyship Easyship WooCommerce Shipping Rates allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easyship WooCommerce Shipping Rates: from n/a through 0.9.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38383 | WordPress Language plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38383</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OnTheGoSystems Language allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Language: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38385 | WordPress Jupiter X Core plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.0 - Multiple Auth. Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38385</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Artbees JupiterX Core allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects JupiterX Core: from 3.0.0 through 3.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38475 | WordPress Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38475</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RedNao Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations: from n/a through 4.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38477 | WordPress QR code MeCard/vCard generator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38477</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stanislav Kuznetsov QR code MeCard/vCard generator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects QR code MeCard/vCard generator: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38479 | WordPress Simple Googlebot Visit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38479</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Codents Simple Googlebot Visit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple Googlebot Visit: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38480 | WordPress Booster Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38480</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Certain Dev Booster Elementor Addons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Booster Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38483 | WordPress Instant CSS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38483</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dylan Blokhuis Instant CSS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Instant CSS: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38514 | WordPress Social Share Icons &amp;amp; Social Share Buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38514</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in social share pro Social Share Icons &amp; Social Share Buttons allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Social Share Icons &amp; Social Share Buttons: from n/a through 3.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39305 | WordPress Yet Another Stars Rating plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39305</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in YetAnotherStarsRating.com Yet Another Stars Rating allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Yet Another Stars Rating: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39920 | WordPress Redirection for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39920</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeisle Redirection for Contact Form 7 allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Redirection for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39995 | WordPress Portfolio and Projects plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39995</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP OnlineSupport, Essential Plugin Portfolio and Projects allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Portfolio and Projects: from n/a through 1.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39996 | WordPress Accordion and Accordion Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39996</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP OnlineSupport, Essential Plugin Accordion and Accordion Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Accordion and Accordion Slider: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39997 | WordPress Popup by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.19 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39997</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in supsystic.com Popup by Supsystic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Popup by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.10.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40001 | WordPress iThemes Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.13 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40001</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SolidWP iThemes Sync allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects iThemes Sync: from n/a through 2.1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40003 | WordPress WP Project Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40003</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in weDevs WP Project Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Project Manager: from n/a through 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40005 | WordPress Easy Digital Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.5 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40005</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Easy Digital Downloads Easy Digital Downloads allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Digital Downloads: from n/a through 3.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40011 | WordPress Cost Calculator Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.42 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40011</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in StylemixThemes Cost Calculator Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Cost Calculator Builder: from n/a through 3.1.42.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40203 | WordPress MailChimp Forms by MailMunch plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.4 - Broken Access Control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40203</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MailMunch MailChimp Forms by MailMunch allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects MailChimp Forms by MailMunch: from n/a through 3.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40213 | WordPress Justified Gallery  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40213</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mateusz Czardybon Justified Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Justified Gallery: from n/a through 1.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40331 | WordPress Accordion Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40331</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bqworks Accordion Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Accordion Slider: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40334 | WordPress HUSKY – Products Filter for WooCommerce Professional plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40334</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in realmag777 HUSKY allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects HUSKY: from n/a through 1.3.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40670 | WordPress ReviewX plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.17 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40670</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ReviewX Team ReviewX allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects ReviewX: from n/a through 1.6.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40678 | WordPress Simple URLs plugin &amp;lt;= 117 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40678</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Lasso Simple URLs allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple URLs: from n/a through 117.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41130 | WordPress Premmerce User Roles plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41130</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Premmerce Premmerce User Roles allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Premmerce User Roles: from n/a through 1.0.12.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41132 | WordPress Category Slider for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41132</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ShapedPlugin LLC Category Slider for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Category Slider for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41133 | WordPress Secure Admin IP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - IP Spoofing vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41133</link><description>Authentication Bypass by Spoofing vulnerability in Michal Novák Secure Admin IP allows Functionality Bypass.This issue affects Secure Admin IP: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41649 | WordPress Ovic Product Bundle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2  - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41649</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ovic Team Ovic Product Bundle allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Ovic Product Bundle: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41664 | WordPress Easy Newsletter Signups plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41664</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in AlphaBPO Easy Newsletter Signups allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Easy Newsletter Signups: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41671 | WordPress Abandoned Cart Lite for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 5.16.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41671</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tyche Softwares Abandoned Cart Lite for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Abandoned Cart Lite for WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.16.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41683 | WordPress TelSender plugin &amp;lt;= 1.14.11 - Broken Access Control + CSRF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41683</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Pechenki TelSender allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects TelSender: from n/a through 1.14.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41686 | WordPress Woocommerce Support System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41686</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ilGhera Woocommerce Support System allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Woocommerce Support System: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41688 | WordPress Bulk NoIndex &amp;amp; NoFollow Toolkit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41688</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Mad Fish Digital Bulk NoIndex &amp; NoFollow Toolkit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Bulk NoIndex &amp; NoFollow Toolkit: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41689 | WordPress Post to Google My Business (Google Business Profile) plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41689</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Koen Reus Post to Google My Business (Google Business Profile) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Post to Google My Business (Google Business Profile): from n/a through 3.1.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41690 | WordPress WiserNotify Social Proof plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41690</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Wiser Notify WiserNotify Social Proof allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WiserNotify Social Proof: from n/a through 2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41695 | WordPress Analytify plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41695</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Analytify Analytify allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Analytify: from n/a through 5.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41802 | WordPress Super Socializer plugin &amp;lt;= 7.13.54 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41802</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Heateor Super Socializer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Super Socializer: from n/a through 7.13.54.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41803 | WordPress BitPay Checkout for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41803</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BitPay BitPay Checkout for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects BitPay Checkout for WooCommerce: from n/a through 4.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41848 | WordPress Carousel Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41848</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Majeed Raza Carousel Slider allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Carousel Slider: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41849 | WordPress Posts Like Dislike plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41849</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Happy Coders Posts Like Dislike allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Posts Like Dislike: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41857 | WordPress Click To Tweet plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41857</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ClickToTweet.com Click To Tweet allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Click To Tweet: from n/a through 2.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41862 | WordPress VS Contact Form plugin &amp;lt;= 14.0 - Sum Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41862</link><description>Weak Authentication vulnerability in Guido VS Contact Form allows Authentication Abuse.This issue affects VS Contact Form: from n/a through 14.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41865 | WordPress Slider Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41865</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in bqworks Slider Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Slider Pro: from n/a through 4.8.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41866 | WordPress Automatic YouTube Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41866</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team Plugins360 Automatic YouTube Gallery allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Automatic YouTube Gallery: from n/a through 2.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41869 | WordPress WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41869</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Alex Volkov WP Accessibility Helper (WAH) allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Accessibility Helper (WAH): from n/a through 0.6.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:33:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41870 | WordPress WP Crowdfunding plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41870</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Themeum WP Crowdfunding allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Crowdfunding: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41873 | WordPress SAML Single Sign On – SSO Login plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41873</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in miniOrange SAML SP Single Sign On allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SAML SP Single Sign On: from n/a through 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41875 | WordPress WP Directory Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41875</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in wpdirectorykit.com WP Directory Kit allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WP Directory Kit: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41951 | WordPress rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress plugin &amp;lt;= 4.6.14 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41951</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in rtCamp rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects rtMedia for WordPress, BuddyPress and bbPress: from n/a through 4.6.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41952 | WordPress Fluent Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41952</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Contact Form - WPManageNinja LLC FluentForm allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects FluentForm: from n/a through 5.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44142 | WordPress Inactive Logout plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44142</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Inactive Logout Inactive Logout allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Inactive Logout: from n/a through 3.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44147 | WordPress Comment Blacklist Updater plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44147</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Apasionados Comment Blacklist Updater allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Comment Blacklist Updater: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44149 | WordPress Brands for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8.2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44149</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BeRocket Brands for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Brands for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.8.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28980 | Dell RecoverPoint for VMs, version(s) 6.0.x contain(s) a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in the SSH. An unaut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28980</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for VMs, version(s) 6.0.x contain(s) a Use of a Broken or Risky Cryptographic Algorithm vulnerability in the SSH. An unauthenticated attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Remote execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54231 | WordPress Ni WooCommerce Order Export plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54231</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in anzia Ni WooCommerce Order Export allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ni WooCommerce Order Export: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54233 | WordPress Advanced Control Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.16.0 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Enea Overclokk Advanced Control Manager for WordPress by ItalyStrap allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Advanced Control Manager for WordPress by ItalyStrap: from n/a through 2.16.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54234 | WordPress Limit Login Attempts plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in wp-buy Limit Login Attempts allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Limit Login Attempts: from n/a through 5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54235 | WordPress Shiptimize for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.86 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54235</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Shiptimize Shiptimize for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Shiptimize for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.1.86.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54236 | WordPress Ni WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in anzia Ni WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ni WooCommerce Bulk Product Editor: from n/a through 1.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54237 | WordPress  Ni CRM Lead plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54237</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in anzia Ni CRM Lead allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Ni CRM Lead: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54238 | WordPress Board Document Manager from CHUHPL plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Colin Tomele Board Document Manager from CHUHPL allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Board Document Manager from CHUHPL: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54239 | WordPress Eyewear prescription form plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.18 - Arbitrary Option Update to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54239</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in dugudlabs Eyewear prescription form allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Eyewear prescription form: from n/a through 4.0.18.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54240 | WordPress Blaze Online eParcel for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blaze Online Blaze Online eParcel for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Blaze Online eParcel for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54241 | WordPress Elite Notification  plugin 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54241</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Appsbd Elite Notification – Sales Popup, Social Proof, FOMO &amp; WooCommerce Notification allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Elite Notification – Sales Popup, Social Proof, FOMO &amp; WooCommerce Notification: from 1.5 through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54242 | WordPress Simple Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54242</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Appsbd Simple Notification allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Simple Notification: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54243 | WordPress Echoza plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54243</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 Echoza allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Echoza: from n/a through 0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54244 | WordPress Easy Replace plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54244</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 Easy Replace allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Easy Replace: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54245 | WordPress Clients plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54245</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 Clients allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Clients: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54246 | WordPress FAQs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54246</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Think201 FAQs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects FAQs: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54248 | WordPress Eewee Admin Custom plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2.4 - CSRF to Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54248</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael DUMONTET eewee admin custom allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects eewee admin custom: from n/a through 1.8.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54250 | WordPress Prodigy Commerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54250</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prodigy Commerce Prodigy Commerce allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Prodigy Commerce: from n/a through 3.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54252 | WordPress Pinpoint Booking System Plugin  &amp;lt;= 2.9.9.5.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54252</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in PINPOINT.WORLD Pinpoint Booking System allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Pinpoint Booking System: from n/a through 2.9.9.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54256 | WordPress Easy Blocks pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.21 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54256</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Seerox Easy Blocks pro allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Easy Blocks pro: from n/a through 1.0.21.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54258 | WordPress Ni CRM Lead plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54258</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in anzia Ni CRM Lead allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Ni CRM Lead: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54259 | WordPress DELUCKS SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.5 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54259</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in DELUCKS GmbH DELUCKS SEO allows Path Traversal.This issue affects DELUCKS SEO: from n/a through 2.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54261 | WordPress TAX SERVICE Electronic HDM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54261</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in HK Digital Agency LLC TAX SERVICE Electronic HDM allows SQL Injection.This issue affects TAX SERVICE Electronic HDM: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54262 | WordPress Import Export For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54262</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Siddharth Nagar Import Export For WooCommerce allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects Import Export For WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54264 | WordPress Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54264</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in César Morillas Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Shortcodes Blocks Creator Ultimate: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54265 | WordPress Barcode Scanner and Inventory manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54265</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UkrSolution Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Barcode Scanner with Inventory &amp; Order Manager: from n/a through 1.6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54266 | WordPress ImageRecycle pdf &amp;amp; image compression plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54266</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ImageRecycle ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ImageRecycle pdf &amp; image compression: from n/a through 3.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54267 | WordPress CM Answers plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54267</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Answers allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects CM Answers: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54268 | WordPress SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.64.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54268</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in SiteOrigin SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects SiteOrigin Widgets Bundle: from n/a through 1.64.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54271 | WordPress WPCargo Track &amp;amp; Trace plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.6 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54271</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPTaskForce WPCargo Track &amp; Trace allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects WPCargo Track &amp; Trace: from n/a through 7.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54272 | WordPress Radius Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54272</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in RadiusTheme Radius Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Radius Blocks – WordPress Gutenberg Blocks: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54273 | WordPress Mail Picker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54273</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PickPlugins Mail Picker allows Object Injection.This issue affects Mail Picker: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54274 | WordPress Octrace Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54274</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Octrace Studio WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Ticket System Plugin – Octrace Support allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WordPress HelpDesk &amp; Support Ticket System Plugin – Octrace Support: from n/a through 1.2.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54275 | WordPress CSV to html plugin &amp;lt;= 3.04 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54275</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Wibergs Web CSV to html allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CSV to html: from n/a through 3.04.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54276 | WordPress Poll Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54276</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Felix Moira Poll Builder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Poll Builder: from n/a through 1.3.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54277 | WordPress Nias course plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54277</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alireza aliniya Nias course allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Nias course: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54278 | WordPress News Ticker for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54278</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Plugin Devs News Ticker for Elementor allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects News Ticker for Elementor: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54282 | WordPress WP Mega Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54282</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Themeum WP Mega Menu allows Object Injection.This issue affects WP Mega Menu: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54286 | WordPress Smaily for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54286</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sendsmaily LLC Smaily for WP allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Smaily for WP: from n/a through 3.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54287 | WordPress Advanced Blog Post Block plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54287</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Best Wp Developer Advanced Blog Post Block allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Blog Post Block: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54288 | WordPress LDD Directory Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54288</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LDD Web Design LDD Directory Lite allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LDD Directory Lite: from n/a through 3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54289 | WordPress Awesome Support plugin &amp;lt;= 6.3.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54289</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Awesome Support Team Awesome Support allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Awesome Support: from n/a through 6.3.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54290 | WordPress Role Includer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54290</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Justin Fletcher Role Includer allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Role Includer: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54292 | WordPress Appsplate plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54292</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Appsplate Appsplate allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Appsplate: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54293 | WordPress CE21 Suite plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54293</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in CE21 CE21 Suite allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects CE21 Suite: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54294 | WordPress Firebase OTP Authentication plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54294</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in appgenixinfotech Firebase OTP Authentication allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Firebase OTP Authentication: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54295 | WordPress ListApp Mobile Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.7 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54295</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in InspireUI ListApp Mobile Manager allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects ListApp Mobile Manager: from n/a through 1.7.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54296 | WordPress CoSchool LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54296</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Codexpert, Inc CoSchool LMS allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects CoSchool LMS: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54297 | WordPress vBSSO-lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54297</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in www.vbsso.com vBSSO-lite allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects vBSSO-lite: from n/a through 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54298 | WordPress Car Dealer plugin &amp;lt;= 4.46 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54298</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bill Minozzi Car Dealer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Car Dealer: from n/a through 4.46.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54299 | WordPress Revi.io plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54299</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Revi Revi.io allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Revi.io: from n/a through 5.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54300 | WordPress AutoWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54300</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Neuralabz LTD. AutoWP allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects AutoWP: from n/a through 2.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54301 | WordPress FormFacade plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54301</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FormFacade FormFacade allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FormFacade: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54302 | WordPress VForm plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54302</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vikas Ratudi VForm allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects VForm: from n/a through 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54303 | WordPress Simple Payment plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.7 -  Refleceted Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54303</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ido Kobelkowsky / yalla ya! Simple Payment allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Payment: from n/a through 2.3.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54304 | WordPress Hive Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54304</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Hive Support Hive Support – WordPress Help Desk allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Hive Support – WordPress Help Desk: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54305 | WordPress J&amp;amp;T Express Malaysia plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.13 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54305</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in woocs J&amp;amp;T Express Malaysia allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects J&amp;amp;T Express Malaysia: from n/a through 2.0.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54306 | WordPress AIKCT Engine Chatbot, ChatGPT, Gemini, GPT-4o Best AI Chatbot plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54306</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in KCT AIKCT Engine Chatbot, ChatGPT, Gemini, GPT-4o Best AI Chatbot allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects AIKCT Engine Chatbot, ChatGPT, Gemini, GPT-4o Best AI Chatbot: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54307 | WordPress AIcomments plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54307</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in AIpost AIcomments allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects AIcomments: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54308 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Price Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54308</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CurrencyRate.today Cryptocurrency Price Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Price Widget: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54309 | WordPress PostBox plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54309</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in wpdebuglog PostBox allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects PostBox: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54310 | WordPress Gou Manage My Account Menu plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54310</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aslam Khan Gouran Gou Manage My Account Menu allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Gou Manage My Account Menu: from n/a through 1.0.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54311 | WordPress Mark New Posts plugin &amp;lt;= 7.5.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54311</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in i.lychkov Mark New Posts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Mark New Posts: from n/a through 7.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54312 | WordPress افزونه پیامک ووکامرس Persian WooCommerce SMS plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54312</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ووکامرس فارسی Persian Woocommerce SMS allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Persian Woocommerce SMS: from n/a through 7.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54313 | WordPress FULL – Cliente plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.25 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54313</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in FULL. FULL Customer allows Path Traversal.This issue affects FULL Customer: from n/a through 3.1.25.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54314 | WordPress Primary Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54314</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Primary Addon for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Primary Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54315 | WordPress Events Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54315</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Events Addon for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Events Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54316 | WordPress Restaurant &amp;amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54316</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NicheAddons Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Restaurant &amp; Cafe Addon for Elementor: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54317 | WordPress Web Stories plugin &amp;lt;= 1.37.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54317</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Google Web Stories allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Web Stories: from n/a through 1.37.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54318 | WordPress NiceJob plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54318</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in nicejob NiceJob allows Stored XSS.This issue affects NiceJob: from n/a through 3.6.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54319 | WordPress Kundgenerator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54319</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MultiNet Interactive AB Kundgenerator allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Kundgenerator: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54320 | WordPress ICDSoft Reseller Store plugin&amp;lt;= 2.4.5 -Reflected  Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54320</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ICDSoft Hosting ICDSoft Reseller Store allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ICDSoft Reseller Store: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54321 | WordPress Hive Support plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54321</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hive Support Hive Support – WordPress Help Desk allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Hive Support – WordPress Help Desk: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54322 | WordPress Media Downloader plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.7.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54322</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ederson Peka Media Downloader allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Media Downloader: from n/a through 0.4.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54323 | WordPress New User Approve plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54323</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPExpertsio New User Approve allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects New User Approve: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54324 | WordPress SMSify plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54324</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Cloud Inn SMSify allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects SMSify: from n/a through 6.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54325 | WordPress CarDealerPress plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.2410.02 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54325</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in DealerTrend CarDealerPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CarDealerPress: from n/a through 6.6.2410.02.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54326 | WordPress GEO my WP plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54326</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eyal Fitoussi GEO my WordPress allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects GEO my WordPress: from n/a through 4.5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54327 | WordPress UNIVERSAM plugin &amp;lt; 8.59 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54327</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in universam UNIVERSAM allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects UNIVERSAM: from n/a through n/a.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54328 | WordPress Invoice Payment for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54328</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Link Nacional Invoice Payment for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Invoice Payment for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54329 | WordPress CleverNode Related Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54329</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Metup s.r.l. CleverNode Related Content allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects CleverNode Related Content: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54330 | WordPress Hurrakify plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54330</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Hep Hep Hurra (HHH) Hurrakify allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Hurrakify: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54333 | WordPress Check Pincode For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54333</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in silverplugins217 Check Pincode For Woocommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Check Pincode For Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54334 | WordPress Quran Phrases About Most People Shortcodes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54334</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Zeshan B Quran Phrases About Most People Shortcodes allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Quran Phrases About Most People Shortcodes: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54335 | WordPress ImmoToolBox Connect plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54335</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ZebraSoft Monaco ImmoToolBox Connect allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ImmoToolBox Connect: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54336 | WordPress Projectopia plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.7 - Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54336</link><description>Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Projectopia Projectopia allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects Projectopia: from n/a through 5.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54337 | WordPress DX Dark Site plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54337</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in DevriX DX Dark Site allows Stored XSS.This issue affects DX Dark Site: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54338 | WordPress Hello Event Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54338</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Christer Fernstrom Hello Event Widgets For Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Hello Event Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54339 | WordPress geoFlickr plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54339</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jbd7 geoFlickr allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects geoFlickr: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54340 | WordPress Simple Presenter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54340</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sylvia van Os Simple Presenter allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Simple Presenter: from n/a through 1.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54341 | WordPress LabelGrid Tools plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.58 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54341</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LabelGrid LabelGrid Tools allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects LabelGrid Tools: from n/a through 1.3.58.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54342 | WordPress Staggs plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54342</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in STAGGS Staggs Product Configurator for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Staggs Product Configurator for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54343 | WordPress Connect Contact Form 7 to Constant Contact plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54343</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Howard Ehrenberg Connect Contact Form 7 to Constant Contact allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Connect Contact Form 7 to Constant Contact: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54344 | WordPress WP Quick Shop plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54344</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fahad Mahmood WP Quick Shop allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects WP Quick Shop: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54345 | WordPress Bicycleshop theme &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54345</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes Bicycleshop allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Bicycleshop: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54346 | WordPress Barter theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54346</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SKT Themes Barter allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Barter: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54347 | WordPress FloristPress plugin &amp;lt;= 7.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54347</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in BAKKBONE Australia FloristPress allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects FloristPress: from n/a through 7.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54349 | WordPress Plain Post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54349</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in mashiurz.com Plain Post allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Plain Post: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-54351 | WordPress Fancy Roller Scroller plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-54351</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tom Landis Fancy Roller Scroller allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fancy Roller Scroller: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24902 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains an Improper access control vulnerability. A low privileged local attacker could potent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24902</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains an Improper access control vulnerability. A low privileged local attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to gaining access to unauthorized data for a limited time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47984 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains Denial of Service vulnerability. A User with Remote access could potentially exploit t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47984</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains Denial of Service vulnerability. A User with Remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to the disruption of most functionalities of the RPA persistent after reboot, resulting in need of technical support intervention in getting system back to stable state.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38488 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains a vulnerability. An improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication vulnerability whe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38488</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains a vulnerability. An improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication vulnerability where a Network attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to a brute force attack or a dictionary attack against the RecoverPoint login form and a complete system compromise.
This allows attackers to brute-force the password of valid users in an automated manner.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48007 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability. A Remote unauthenticated attacker could p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48007</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability. A Remote unauthenticated attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by gaining access to the source code, easily retrieving these secrets and reusing them to access the system leading to gaining access to unauthorized data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11986 | Stored XSS in CrushFTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11986</link><description>Improper input handling in the 'Host Header' allows an unauthenticated attacker to store a payload in web application logs. When an Administrator views the logs using the application's standard functionality, it enables the execution of the payload, resulting in Stored XSS or 'Cross-Site Scripting'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55889 | phpMyFAQ Vulnerable to Unintended File Download Triggered by Embedded Frames</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55889</link><description>phpMyFAQ is an open source FAQ web application. Prior to version 3.2.10, a vulnerability exists in the FAQ Record component where a privileged attacker can trigger a file download on a victim's machine upon page visit by embedding it in an  element without user interaction or explicit consent. Version 3.2.10 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:48:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48008 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains a OS Command Injection vulnerability. An Low privileged remote attacker could potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48008</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains a OS Command Injection vulnerability. An Low privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability leading to information disclosure ,allowing of unintended actions like reading files that may contain sensitive information</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22461 | Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains an OS Command injection vulnerability. A low privileged remote attacker could potentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22461</link><description>Dell RecoverPoint for Virtual Machines 6.0.x contains an OS Command injection vulnerability. A low privileged remote attacker could potentially exploit this vulnerability by running any command as root, leading to gaining of root-level access and compromise of complete system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 13:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11827 | Out of the Block: OpenStreetMap &amp;lt;= 2.8.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ootb_query Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11827</link><description>The Out of the Block: OpenStreetMap plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's ootb_query shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:32:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9608 | MyParcel &amp;lt;= 4.24.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9608</link><description>The MyParcel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link. Please note this is only exploitable when the WooCommerce store is set to Belgium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21576 | ComfyUI-Bmad-Nodes is vulnerable to Code Injection. The issue stems from a validation bypass in the BuildColorRangeHSVAdvanced, FilterContou...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21576</link><description>ComfyUI-Bmad-Nodes is vulnerable to Code Injection. The issue stems from a validation bypass in the BuildColorRangeHSVAdvanced, FilterContour and FindContour custom nodes. In the entrypoint function to each node, there’s a call to eval which can be triggered by generating a workflow that injects a crafted string into the node. This can result in executing arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21577 | ComfyUI-Ace-Nodes is vulnerable to Code Injection. The ACE_ExpressionEval node contains an eval() in its entrypoint function that accepts ar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21577</link><description>ComfyUI-Ace-Nodes is vulnerable to Code Injection. The ACE_ExpressionEval node contains an eval() in its entrypoint function that accepts arbitrary user-controlled data. A user can create a workflow that results in executing arbitrary code on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-32007 | Missing security header: Referrer-Policy URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-32007</link><description>This issue affects:
Secomea GateManager
Version 9.5 and all prior versions.
Protection Mechanism Failure vulnerability in web server of Secomea GateManager to potentially leak information to remote servers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52058 | Potential arbitrary command execution in System Designer while parsing malicious HTTP/REST requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52058</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (System Designer) allows OS Command Injection.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.2, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52059 | Potential heap buffer overflow in Security Plugins while creating a DomainParticipant that uses a malformed Identity Certificate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52059</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Security Plugins) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.2, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52060 | Potential stack overflow when using XML configuration file referencing environment variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52060</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Routing Service, Recording Service, Queuing Service, Observability Collector Service, Cloud Discovery Service) allows Buffer Overflow via Environment Variables.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.5, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.*, from 5.3.0 before 5.3.1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52061 | Potential stack buffer overflow when parsing an XML type</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52061</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Core Libraries, Queuing Service, Recording Service, Routing Service) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.4.0 before 7.5.0, from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.5, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.1.40, from 5.0.0 before 5.3.1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52062 | Potential stack buffer write overflow in Connext applications while parsing malicious XML types document</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52062</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Core Libraries) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.5, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.1.40, from 5.0.0 before 5.3.1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52063 | Potential stack buffer write overflow in Connext applications while parsing malicious XML types document</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52063</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Core Libraries, Routing Service) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.5, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.1.40, from 5.0.0 before 5.3.1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52064 | Potential stack buffer write overflow in Connext applications while parsing malicious license file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52064</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Core Libraries) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.2, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.1.40, from 5.0.0 before 5.3.1.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52065 | Potential stack buffer write overflow in Persistence Service while parsing malicious environment variable on non-Windows systems</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52065</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional on non-Windows (Persistence Service) allows Buffer Overflow via Environment Variables.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.2, from 6.1.1.2 before 6.1.2.21, from 5.3.1.40 before 5.3.1.41.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52066 | Potential stack corruption in Routing Service when using a malicious XML configuration document</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52066</link><description>Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input ('Classic Buffer Overflow') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Routing Service) allows Overflow Variables and Tags.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.4.0 before 7.5.0, from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0.5, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.21, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.1.40.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52057 | Potential arbitrary SQL query execution in Queuing Service while parsing malicious remote commands or configuration files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52057</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in RTI Connext Professional (Queuing Service) allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Connext Professional: from 7.0.0 before 7.3.0, from 6.1.0 before 6.1.2.17, from 6.0.0 before 6.0.*, from 5.2.0 before 5.3.*.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 10:17:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10783 | MainWP Child &amp;lt;= 5.2 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10783</link><description>The MainWP Child – Securely Connects to the MainWP Dashboard to Manage Multiple Sites plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing authorization checks on the register_site function in all versions up to, and including, 5.2 when a site is left in an unconfigured state. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as an administrator on instances where MainWP Child is not yet connected to the MainWP Dashboard. IMPORTANT: this only affects sites who have MainWP Child installed and have not yet connected to the MainWP Dashboard, and do not have the unique security ID feature enabled. Sites already connected to the MainWP Dashboard plugin and do not have the unique security ID feature enabled, are NOT affected and not required to upgrade. Please note 5.2.1 contains a partial patch, though we consider 5.3 to be the complete patch.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 09:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11012 | Notibar – Notification Bar for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via njt_nofi_text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11012</link><description>The The Notibar – Notification Bar for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via njt_nofi_text AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.4. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 09:35:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9290 | Super Backup &amp;amp; Clone - Migrate for WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.3.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9290</link><description>The Super Backup &amp; Clone - Migrate for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation and a missing capability check on the ibk_restore_migrate_check() function in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 09:35:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11275 | WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.27 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary User Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11275</link><description>The WP Timetics- AI-powered Appointment Booking Calendar and Online Scheduling Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the /wp-json/timetics/v1/customers/ REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.27. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Timetics Customer access and above, to delete arbitrary users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11754 | Booking System Trafft &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11754</link><description>The Booking System Trafft plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'trafftbooking' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11832 | Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.8.4.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11832</link><description>The Beaver Builder – WordPress Page Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom JavaScript row settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.4.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11910 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11910</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the wp-crowdfunding/search block in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.12 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11911 | WP Crowdfunding &amp;lt;= 2.1.12 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) WooCommerce Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11911</link><description>The WP Crowdfunding plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized plugin installation due to a missing capability check on the install_woocommerce_plugin() function action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.12. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install WooCommerce. This has a limited impact on most sites because WooCommerce is a requirement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12042 | MStore API – Create Native Android &amp;amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud &amp;lt;= 4.16.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) HTML File Upload (Stored Cross-Site Scripting)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12042</link><description>The MStore API – Create Native Android &amp; iOS Apps On The Cloud plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the profile picture upload functionality in all versions up to, and including, 4.16.4 due to insufficient file type validation. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to upload HTML files with arbitrary web scripts that will execute whenever a user accesses the file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12309 | Rate My Post – Star Rating Plugin by FeedbackWP &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Unauthenticated Voting On Scheduled Posts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12309</link><description>The Rate My Post – Star Rating Plugin by FeedbackWP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 via the get_post_status() due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to vote on unpublished scheduled posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12414 | Themify Store Locator &amp;lt;= 1.1.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12414</link><description>The Themify Store Locator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.9. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the setting_page() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify the plugin's settings via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12417 | Simple Link Directory &amp;lt;= 8.4.0 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12417</link><description>The The Simple Link Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.0. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12420 | WPMobile.App — Android and iOS Mobile Application &amp;lt;= 11.52 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12420</link><description>The The WPMobile.App — Android and iOS Mobile Application plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 11.52. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12421 | Coupon Affiliates – Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.16.7.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution and Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12421</link><description>The The Coupon Affiliates – Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 5.16.7.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes. This functionality is also vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting. The Cross-Site Scripting was patched in version 5.16.7.1, while the arbitrary shortcode execution was patched in 5.16.7.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12465 | Property Hive Stamp Duty Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.0.22 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12465</link><description>The Property Hive Stamp Duty Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'stamp_duty_calculator_scotland' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.22 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:41:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55918 | An issue was discovered in the Graphics::ColorNames package before 3.2.0 for Perl. There is an ambiguity between modules and filenames that ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55918</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Graphics::ColorNames package before 3.2.0 for Perl. There is an ambiguity between modules and filenames that can lead to HTML injection by an attacker who can create a file in the current working directory.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:45:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10678 | Ultimate Blocks &amp;lt; 3.2.4 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10678</link><description>The Ultimate Blocks  WordPress plugin before 3.2.4 does not validate and escape some of its block options before outputting them back in a page/post where the block is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10939 | Image Widget &amp;lt; 4.4.11 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10939</link><description>The Image Widget WordPress plugin before 4.4.11 does not sanitise and escape some of its Image Widget settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 06:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11833 | Arbitrary Directory Write via Runbooks Artifact Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11833</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in PlexTrac allows arbitrary file writes.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11834 | Arbitrary File Write via PTRAC Import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11834</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in PlexTrac allows arbitrary file writes.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11835 | Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11835</link><description>Uncontrolled Resource Consumption vulnerability in PlexTrac allows WebSocket DoS.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11836 | N1QL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11836</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in PlexTrac allowing requests to internal system resources.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11837 | N1QL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11837</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an N1QL Command ('N1QL Injection') vulnerability in PlexTrac  allows N1QL Injection.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11838 | Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11838</link><description>External Control of File Name or Path vulnerability in PlexTrac allows Local Code Inclusion through use of an undocumented API endpoint.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11839 | Insecure Deserialization via Runbooks Imports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11839</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PlexTrac (Runbooks modules) which allows Object Injection and arbitrary file writes.This issue affects PlexTrac: from 1.61.3 before 2.8.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12581 | Kadence Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.2.53 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12581</link><description>The Gutenberg Blocks with AI by Kadence WP – Page Builder Features plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.53 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:33:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21543 | Versions of the package djoser before 2.3.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass when the authenticate() function fails. This is because ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21543</link><description>Versions of the package djoser before 2.3.0 are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass when the authenticate() function fails. This is because the system falls back to querying the database directly, granting access to users with valid credentials, and eventually bypassing custom authentication checks such as two-factor authentication, LDAP validations, or requirements from configured AUTHENTICATION_BACKENDS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:13:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21544 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.1 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21544</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot before 5.0.1 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to improper URL validation through the setUrl method.&#13;An attacker can exploit this vulnerability by using leading whitespace (%20) before the file:// protocol, resulting in Local File Inclusion, which allows the attacker to read sensitive files on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 05:13:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11767 | NewsmanApp &amp;lt;= 2.7.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11767</link><description>The NewsmanApp plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'newsman_subscribe_widget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11809 | Primer MyData for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 4.2.1 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11809</link><description>The Primer MyData for Woocommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'img_src' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:39:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12574 | SVG Shortcode &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12574</link><description>The SVG Shortcode plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12579 | Minify HTML &amp;lt;= 2.1.10 - - Regular Expressions Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12579</link><description>The Minify HTML plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Regular Expression Denial of Service (ReDoS) in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.10. This is due to processing user-supplied input as a regular expression.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create comments that can cause catastrophic backtracking and break pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 04:39:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25221 | Responsive Filterable Portfolio &amp;lt;=1.0.8 - Authenticated (Admin+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25221</link><description>The Responsive Filterable Portfolio plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:49:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12300 | AR for WordPress &amp;lt;= 7.3 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Limited File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12300</link><description>The AR for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized double extension file upload due to a missing capability check on the set_ar_featured_image() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.3. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload php files leveraging a double extension attack. It's important to note the file is deleted immediately and double extension attacks only work on select servers making this unlikely to be successfully exploited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12572 | Hello in All Languages &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12572</link><description>The Hello In All Languages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on a function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:49:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12603 | A logic vulnerability in the the mobile application (com.transsion.applock) can lead to bypassing the application password.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12603</link><description>A logic vulnerability in the the mobile application (com.transsion.applock) can lead to bypassing the application password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12212 | Horner Automation Cscape Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12212</link><description>The vulnerability occurs in the parsing of CSP files. The issues result 
from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which could 
allow reading past the end of allocated data structures, resulting in 
execution of arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 01:06:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9508 | Horner Automation Cscape Out-of-bounds Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9508</link><description>Horner Automation Cscape contains a memory corruption vulnerability, which 
could allow an attacker to disclose information and execute arbitrary 
code.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 01:06:25 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>