<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:18:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-57835 | Amon2::Auth::Site::LINE versions through 0.04 for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57835</link><description>Amon2::Auth::Site::LINE uses the String::Random module to generate nonce values. 

String::Random defaults to Perl's built-in predictable random number generator, the rand() function, which is not cryptographically secure</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58036 | Net::Dropbox::API 1.9 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58036</link><description>Net::Dropbox::API 1.9 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Net::Dropbox::API uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57868 | Web::API 2.8 and earlier for Perl uses insecure rand() function for cryptographic functions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57868</link><description>Web::API 2.8 and earlier for Perl uses the rand() function as the default source of entropy, which is not cryptographically secure, for cryptographic functions.

Specifically Web::API uses the Data::Random library which specifically states that it is "Useful mostly for test programs". Data::Random uses the rand() function.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30401 | A spoofing issue in WhatsApp for Windows prior to version 2.2450.6 displayed attachments according to their MIME type but selected the file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30401</link><description>A spoofing issue in WhatsApp for Windows prior to version 2.2450.6 displayed attachments according to their MIME type but selected the file opening handler based on the attachment’s filename extension. A maliciously crafted mismatch could have caused the recipient to inadvertently execute arbitrary code rather than view the attachment when manually opening the attachment inside WhatsApp.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 11:51:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3299 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3299</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 11:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3298 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Registration Master.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3298</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /oews/classes/Master.php?f=save_product of the component Registration Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 10:42:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3297 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Master.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3297</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /classes/Master.php?f=save_product. The manipulation of the argument brand leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:39:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3296 | SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop Users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3296</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in SourceCodester Online Eyewear Shop 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /classes/Users.php?f=delete_customer. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2941 | Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Move</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2941</link><description>The Drag and Drop Multiple File Upload for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file moving due to insufficient file path validation via the wc-upload-file[] parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to move arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is moved (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 07:09:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13776 | ZoomSounds - WordPress Wave Audio Player with Playlist &amp;lt;= 6.91 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Limited Options Update and Settings Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13776</link><description>The ZoomSounds - WordPress Wave Audio Player with Playlist plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to a denial of service due to a missing capability check on the 'dzsap_delete_notice' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 6.91. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update option values to 'seen' on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update an option that would create an error on the site and deny service to legitimate users or be used to set some values to true such as registration. There are several other functions also vulnerable to missing authorization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0839 | ZoomSounds &amp;lt;= 6.91 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0839</link><description>The ZoomSounds plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via shortcodes in versions up to, and including, 6.91 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1233 | Lafka Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Option Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1233</link><description>The Lafka Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'lafka_options_upload' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 7.1.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to update the theme option that overrides the site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2789 | MultiVendorX – The Ultimate WooCommerce Multivendor Marketplace Solution &amp;lt;= 4.2.19 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Table Rates Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2789</link><description>The MultiVendorX – Empower Your WooCommerce Store with a Dynamic Multivendor Marketplace – Build the Next Amazon, eBay, Etsy plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the delete_table_rate_shipping_row function in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.19. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete Table Rates that can impact the shipping cost calculations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:41:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-47667 | An OS command injection vulnerability in lib/NSSDropoff.php in ZendTo 5.24-3 through 6.x before 6.10-7 allows unauthenticated remote attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-47667</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability in lib/NSSDropoff.php in ZendTo 5.24-3 through 6.x before 6.10-7 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell metacharacters in the tmp_name parameter when dropping off a file via a POST /dropoff request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32352 | A type confusion vulnerability in lib/NSSAuthenticator.php in ZendTo before v5.04-7 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication for use...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32352</link><description>A type confusion vulnerability in lib/NSSAuthenticator.php in ZendTo before v5.04-7 allows remote attackers to bypass authentication for users with passwords stored as MD5 hashes that can be interpreted as numbers. A solution requires moving from MD5 to bcrypt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 05:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13604 | KB Support – Customer Support Ticket &amp;amp; Helpdesk Plugin, Knowledge Base Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Unauthenticated Sensitive Information Exposure Through Unprotected Directory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13604</link><description>The KB Support – Customer Support Ticket &amp; Helpdesk Plugin, Knowledge Base Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.4 via the 'kbs' directory. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data stored insecurely in the /wp-content/uploads/kbs directory which can contain file attachments included in support tickets. The vulnerability was partially patched in version 1.7.3.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0810 | Read More &amp;amp; Accordion &amp;lt;= 3.4.5 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0810</link><description>The Read More &amp; Accordion plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.5. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the addNewButtons() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute arbitrary PHP files via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2544 | AI Content Pipelines &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2544</link><description>The AI Content Pipelines plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in all versions up to, and including, 1.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2933 | Email Notifications for Updates &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2933</link><description>The Email Notifications for Updates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the awun_import_settings() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1500 | IBM Maximo Application Suite file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1500</link><description>IBM Maximo Application Suite 9.0 could allow an authenticated user to upload a file with dangerous types that could be executed by another user if opened.</description><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 01:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2889 | Link Library &amp;lt;= 7.7.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Link Additional Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2889</link><description>The Link Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Link Additional Parameters in all versions up to, and including, 7.7.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 23:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3268 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3268</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument m_url_real leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3267 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3267</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument name/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3265 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System add-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-category.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3266 | qinguoyi TinyWebServer http_conn.cpp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3266</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in qinguoyi TinyWebServer up to 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /http/http_conn.cpp. The manipulation of the argument name/password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29476 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in compress_chunk_fuzzer with oss-fuzz on commit 16450518afddcb3139de627157208e49bfef6987 in c-blosc2 v.2.17.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29476</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in compress_chunk_fuzzer with oss-fuzz on commit 16450518afddcb3139de627157208e49bfef6987 in c-blosc2 v.2.17.0 and before.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29477 | An issue in fluent-bit v.3.7.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the function consume_event.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29477</link><description>An issue in fluent-bit v.3.7.2 allows a local attacker to cause a denial of service via the function consume_event.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11235 | Reference counting in php_request_shutdown causes Use-After-Free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11235</link><description>In PHP versions 8.3.* before 8.3.19 and 8.4.* before 8.4.5, a code sequence involving __set handler and exceptions can lead to a use-after-free vulnerability. If the third party can control the memory layout leading to this, it could lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3259 | Tenda RX3 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3259</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda RX3 16.03.13.11. This issue affects the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3258 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3258</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3256 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3256</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation of the argument email leads to improper access controls. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3257 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3257</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32112 | WordPress  Sidebar Manager Light plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32112</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OTWthemes Sidebar Manager Light allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sidebar Manager Light: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32113 | WordPress Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32113</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Renzo Tejada Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Libro de Reclamaciones y Quejas: from n/a through 0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32118 | WordPress CMP – Coming Soon &amp;amp; Maintenance plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.13 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32118</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NiteoThemes CMP – Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance allows Using Malicious Files. This issue affects CMP – Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance: from n/a through 4.1.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32120 | WordPress Easy Query – WP Query Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32120</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Erick Danzer Easy Query – WP Query Builder allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Easy Query – WP Query Builder: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32121 | WordPress Video &amp;amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32121</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in SuitePlugins Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Video &amp; Photo Gallery for Ultimate Member: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32122 | WordPress uListing plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32122</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Stylemix uListing allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects uListing: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32124 | WordPress Behance Portfolio Manager plugin &amp;lt;=1.7.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32124</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in eleopard Behance Portfolio Manager allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Behance Portfolio Manager: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32125 | WordPress Silvasoft boekhouden Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32125</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in silvasoft Silvasoft boekhouden allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Silvasoft boekhouden: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32126 | WordPress Pay with Contact Form 7 Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32126</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in cmsMinds Pay with Contact Form 7 allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Pay with Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32127 | WordPress onOffice for WP-Websites plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32127</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in onOffice GmbH onOffice for WP-Websites allows SQL Injection. This issue affects onOffice for WP-Websites: from n/a through 5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32129 | WordPress Welcome Bar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32129</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Data443 Risk Migitation, Inc. Welcome Bar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Welcome Bar: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32130 | WordPress Posts Footer Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32130</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Data443 Risk Migitation, Inc. Posts Footer Manager allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Posts Footer Manager: from n/a through 2.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32131 | WordPress Social Intents plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in socialintents Social Intents allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Social Intents: from n/a through 1.6.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32132 | WordPress FunnelCockpit Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FunnelCockpit FunnelCockpit allows Stored XSS. This issue affects FunnelCockpit: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32133 | WordPress Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ays Pro Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Secure Copy Content Protection and Content Locking: from n/a through 4.5.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32134 | WordPress URL Shortify Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in KaizenCoders URL Shortify allows Stored XSS. This issue affects URL Shortify: from n/a through 1.10.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32135 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32135</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rocketelements Split Test For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32136 | WordPress ActiveCampaign Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.16 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32136</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in activecampaign ActiveCampaign allows Stored XSS. This issue affects ActiveCampaign: from n/a through 8.1.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32137 | WordPress s2Member plugin &amp;lt;= 250214 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32137</link><description>Relative Path Traversal vulnerability in Cristián Lávaque s2Member allows Path Traversal. This issue affects s2Member: from n/a through 250214.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32138 | WordPress Easy Google Maps plugin &amp;lt;= 1.11.17 - XML External Entity vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32138</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in supsystic Easy Google Maps allows XML Injection. This issue affects Easy Google Maps: from n/a through 1.11.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32141 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.23 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32141</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Stylemix MasterStudy LMS allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.5.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32142 | WordPress Motors plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.65 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32142</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Stylemix Motors allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Motors: from n/a through 1.4.65.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32146 | WordPress JS Job Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32146</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in JoomSky JS Job Manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects JS Job Manager: from n/a through 2.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32147 | WordPress Easy WP Optimizer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32147</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in coothemes Easy WP Optimizer allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Easy WP Optimizer: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32148 | WordPress Daisycon prijsvergelijkers plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.4 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32148</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Daisycon Daisycon prijsvergelijkers allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Daisycon prijsvergelijkers: from n/a through 4.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32149 | WordPress teachPress plugin &amp;lt;= 9.0.11 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32149</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in winkm89 teachPress allows SQL Injection. This issue affects teachPress: from n/a through 9.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32150 | WordPress Real Estate Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 7.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32150</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Rameez Iqbal Real Estate Manager allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Real Estate Manager: from n/a through 7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32151 | WordPress BuddyForms Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.15 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32151</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Sven Lehnert BuddyForms allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects BuddyForms: from n/a through 2.8.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32152 | WordPress Slider a SlidersPack Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32152</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Essential Plugins by WP OnlineSupport Slider a SlidersPack allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Slider a SlidersPack: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32153 | WordPress VG WooCarousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32153</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in vinagecko VG WooCarousel allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects VG WooCarousel: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32154 | WordPress Catch Dark Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32154</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Catch Themes Catch Dark Mode allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Catch Dark Mode: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32155 | WordPress Beds24 Online Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.26 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32155</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in markkinchin Beds24 Online Booking allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Beds24 Online Booking: from n/a through 2.0.26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32156 | WordPress Just Post Preview Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32156</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Alex Prokopenko / JustCoded Just Post Preview Widget allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Just Post Preview Widget: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32157 | WordPress Sparkle Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32157</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Jakub Glos Sparkle Elementor Kit allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Sparkle Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32159 | WordPress Radius Blocks plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32159</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in RadiusTheme Radius Blocks allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Radius Blocks: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32161 | WordPress Arkhe Blocks &amp;lt;= 2.27.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32161</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ryo Arkhe Blocks allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Arkhe Blocks: from n/a through 2.27.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32162 | WordPress Chamber Dashboard Business Directory plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32162</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Morgan Kay Chamber Dashboard Business Directory allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Chamber Dashboard Business Directory: from n/a through 3.3.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32163 | WordPress Xpro Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32163</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Xpro Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32165 | WordPress Doppler Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32165</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fromdoppler Doppler Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Doppler Forms: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32166 | WordPress Emma for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32166</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in John Housholder Emma for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Emma for WordPress: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32167 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32167</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in devsoftbaltic SurveyJS allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SurveyJS: from n/a through 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32168 | WordPress Gutenify plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32168</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeYatri Gutenify allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gutenify: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32169 | WordPress Showeblogin Social plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32169</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Suresh Prasad Showeblogin Social allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Showeblogin Social: from n/a through 7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32170 | WordPress Motors plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.65 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32170</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Stylemix Motors allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Motors: from n/a through 1.4.65.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32171 | WordPress Table Block by Tableberg – Best WordPress Table Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32171</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Imtiaz Rayhan Table Block by Tableberg allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Table Block by Tableberg: from n/a through 0.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32172 | WordPress YaMaps for WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6.31 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32172</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yuri Baranov YaMaps for WordPress allows Stored XSS. This issue affects YaMaps for WordPress: from n/a through 0.6.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32173 | WordPress B Blocks - The ultimate block collection plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32173</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bPlugins B Blocks - The ultimate block collection allows Stored XSS. This issue affects B Blocks - The ultimate block collection: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32174 | WordPress Tockify Events Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.13 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32174</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tockify Tockify Events Calendar allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Tockify Events Calendar: from n/a through 2.2.13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32175 | WordPress VK Filter Search plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14.1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32175</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vektor,Inc. VK Filter Search allows Stored XSS. This issue affects VK Filter Search: from n/a through 2.14.1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32176 | WordPress Gallery Blocks with Lightbox plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32176</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in GalleryCreator Gallery Blocks with Lightbox allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Gallery Blocks with Lightbox: from n/a through 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32177 | WordPress Embed Chessboard plugin &amp;lt;= 3.07.00 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32177</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in pgn4web Embed Chessboard allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Embed Chessboard: from n/a through 3.07.00.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32178 | WordPress 6Storage Rentals Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.18.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32178</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in 6Storage 6Storage Rentals allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 6Storage Rentals: from n/a through 2.18.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32179 | WordPress Maps for WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32179</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in icopydoc Maps for WP allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Maps for WP: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32181 | WordPress Search, Filters &amp;amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.57 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32181</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Fast Simon Search, Filters &amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Search, Filters &amp; Merchandising for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.0.57.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32182 | WordPress Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32182</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Spider Themes Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Spider Elements – Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32183 | WordPress Video Playlist For YouTube plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32183</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Galaxy Weblinks Video Playlist For YouTube allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Video Playlist For YouTube: from n/a through 6.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32184 | WordPress Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32184</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in bdthemes Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Store Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32185 | WordPress Colibri Page Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.319 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32185</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Extend Themes Colibri Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Colibri Page Builder: from n/a through 1.0.319.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32186 | WordPress Turbo Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32186</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Turbo Addons Turbo Addons for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Turbo Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32187 | WordPress Administrator Z plugin &amp;lt;= 2025.03.04 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32187</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Quý Lê 91 Administrator Z allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Administrator Z: from n/a through 2025.03.04.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32188 | WordPress Advanced Woo Labels plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32188</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ILLID Advanced Woo Labels allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advanced Woo Labels: from n/a through 2.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32189 | WordPress BWD Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.20 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32189</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Best WP Developer BWD Elementor Addons allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects BWD Elementor Addons: from n/a through 4.3.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32190 | WordPress Musician&amp;#x27;s Pack for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32190</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in smartwpress Musician's Pack for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Musician's Pack for Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32191 | WordPress News Element Elementor Blog Magazine plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32191</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in webangon News Element Elementor Blog Magazine allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects News Element Elementor Blog Magazine: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32192 | WordPress Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32192</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in UltraPress Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ultra Addons Lite for Elementor: from n/a through 1.1.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32193 | WordPress Simple WP Events plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.17 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32193</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WPMinds Simple WP Events allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple WP Events: from n/a through 1.8.17.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32194 | WordPress LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32194</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LA-Studio LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects LA-Studio Element Kit for Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32195 | WordPress Ecwid Shopping Cart plugin &amp;lt;= 7.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32195</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ecwid by Lightspeed Ecommerce Shopping Cart Ecwid Shopping Cart allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ecwid Shopping Cart: from n/a through 7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32196 | WordPress News Kit Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32196</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in blazethemes News Kit Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS. This issue affects News Kit Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32197 | WordPress Piotnet Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.34 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32197</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in piotnetdotcom Piotnet Addons For Elementor allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Piotnet Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 2.4.34.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32200 | WordPress Advanced WordPress Backgrounds Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32200</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Nikita Advanced WordPress Backgrounds allows Code Injection. This issue affects Advanced WordPress Backgrounds: from n/a through 1.12.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32201 | WordPress Xpro Theme Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32201</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Xpro Xpro Theme Builder allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Xpro Theme Builder: from n/a through 1.2.8.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32203 | WordPress Falling things Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.08 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32203</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in manu225 Falling things allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Falling things: from n/a through 1.08.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32204 | WordPress Split Test For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.8.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32204</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in rocketelements Split Test For Elementor allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Split Test For Elementor: from n/a through 1.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32207 | WordPress Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Anzar Ahmed Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods: from n/a through 3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32217 | WordPress Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32217</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Messiah Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Ai Image Alt Text Generator for WP: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32218 | WordPress TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable  Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32218</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in RealMag777 TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TableOn – WordPress Posts Table Filterable: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32219 | WordPress eaSYNC plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32219</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Syntactics, Inc. eaSYNC allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects eaSYNC: from n/a through 1.3.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32220 | WordPress Salon Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 10.10.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32220</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dimitri Grassi Salon booking system allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Salon booking system: from n/a through 10.10.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32224 | WordPress Privyr CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32224</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in shivammani Privyr CRM allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Privyr CRM: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32225 | WordPress WP Event Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.47 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32225</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Event Manager WP Event Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Event Manager: from n/a through 3.1.47.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32226 | WordPress Display product variations dropdown on shop page plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32226</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Anzar Ahmed Display product variations dropdown on shop page allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Display product variations dropdown on shop page: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32229 | WordPress Variable Inspector plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32229</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bowo Variable Inspector allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Variable Inspector: from n/a through 2.6.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32231 | WordPress Bookingor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32231</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Bookingor Bookingor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Bookingor: from n/a through 1.0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32232 | WordPress StaffList plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32232</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ERA404 StaffList allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects StaffList: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32233 | WordPress Revive.so &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32233</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WP Chill Revive.so – Bulk Rewrite and Republish Blog Posts allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Revive.so – Bulk Rewrite and Republish Blog Posts: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32234 | WordPress AdMail plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32234</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in aleswebs AdMail – Multilingual Back in-Stock Notifier for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects AdMail – Multilingual Back in-Stock Notifier for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.7.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32235 | WordPress MP3 Audio Player – Music Player, Podcast Player &amp;amp; Radio by Sonaar plugin &amp;lt;= 5.9.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32235</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in sonaar MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MP3 Audio Player for Music, Radio &amp; Podcast by Sonaar: from n/a through 5.9.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32237 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.23 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32237</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Stylemix MasterStudy LMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through 3.5.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32238 | WordPress Online Booking &amp;amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32238</link><description>Generation of Error Message Containing Sensitive Information vulnerability in vcita Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Online Booking &amp; Scheduling Calendar for WordPress by vcita: from n/a through 4.5.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32239 | WordPress Social Share Buttons &amp;amp; Analytics Plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32239</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Joao Romao Social Share Buttons &amp; Analytics Plugin – GetSocial.io allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Social Share Buttons &amp; Analytics Plugin – GetSocial.io: from n/a through 4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32241 | WordPress Official CleverReach WooCommerce Integration Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - CSRF to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32241</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CleverReach® Official CleverReach Plugin for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Official CleverReach Plugin for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32246 | WordPress 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32246</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Tim Nguyen 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects 1-Click Backup &amp;amp; Restore Database: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32247 | WordPress AI Content Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32247</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ABCdatos AI Content Creator allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects AI Content Creator: from n/a through 1.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32248 | WordPress SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32248</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SwiftXR SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects SwiftXR (3D/AR/VR) Viewer: from n/a through 1.0.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32249 | WordPress DirectoryPress – Business Directory And Classified Ad Listing Plugin &amp;lt;=3.6.19 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32249</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in designinvento DirectoryPress allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects DirectoryPress: from n/a through 3.6.19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32250 | WordPress Rollbar plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32250</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in rollbar Rollbar allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Rollbar: from n/a through 2.7.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32251 | WordPress Jetpack Feedback Exporter &amp;lt;= 1.23 - Sensitive Data Exposure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32251</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in J. Tyler Wiest Jetpack Feedback Exporter allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects Jetpack Feedback Exporter: from n/a through 1.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32252 | WordPress WP Genealogy plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.9 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32252</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in blackandwhitedigital WP Genealogy – Your Family History Website allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Genealogy – Your Family History Website: from n/a through 0.1.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32253 | WordPress Course Booking System Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32253</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in ComMotion Course Booking System allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Course Booking System: from n/a through 6.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32254 | WordPress WPBookit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32254</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Iqonic Design WPBookit allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects WPBookit: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32255 | WordPress StaffList plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32255</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in ERA404 StaffList allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects StaffList: from n/a through 3.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32256 | WordPress SurveyJS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12.20 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32256</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in devsoftbaltic SurveyJS allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects SurveyJS: from n/a through 1.12.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32257 | WordPress 1 Click WordPress Migration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32257</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information Due to Uncleared Debug Information vulnerability in 1clickmigration 1 Click WordPress Migration allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects 1 Click WordPress Migration: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32258 | WordPress Simple Website Logo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32258</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in InfoGiants Simple Website Logo allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Simple Website Logo: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32261 | WordPress Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32261</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kuppuraj Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Advanced All in One Admin Search by WP Spotlight: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32262 | WordPress RDP Wiki Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.20 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32262</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Robert D Payne RDP Wiki Embed allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects RDP Wiki Embed: from n/a through 1.2.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32263 | WordPress Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32263</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BeRocket Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Sequential Order Numbers for WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32264 | WordPress UltraAddons – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32264</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Saiful Islam UltraAddons Elementor Lite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32265 | WordPress JobWP plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.9 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32265</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Hossni Mubarak JobWP allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects JobWP: from n/a through 2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32266 | WordPress 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images) plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32266</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wp-buy 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images) allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects 404 Image Redirection (Replace Broken Images): from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32267 | WordPress WP to Hootsuite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.8 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32267</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wpzinc Post to Social Media – WordPress to Hootsuite allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Post to Social Media – WordPress to Hootsuite: from n/a through 1.5.8.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32268 | WordPress QR Code Tag for WC plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.36 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32268</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in www.15.to QR Code Tag for WC allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects QR Code Tag for WC: from n/a through 1.9.36.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32269 | WordPress  WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32269</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CRM Perks WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Zendesk for Contact Form 7, WPForms, Elementor, Formidable and Ninja Forms: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32270 | WordPress Broadstreet Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.51.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) to Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32270</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Broadstreet Broadstreet allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Broadstreet: from n/a through 1.51.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32271 | WordPress Woocommerce Role Pricing Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32271</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ablancodev Woocommerce Role Pricing allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Woocommerce Role Pricing: from n/a through 3.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32272 | WordPress Wishlist Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.44 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32272</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PickPlugins Wishlist allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Wishlist: from n/a through 1.0.44.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32273 | WordPress Freetobook Responsive Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32273</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in freetobook Freetobook Responsive Widget allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Freetobook Responsive Widget: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32274 | WordPress w3all phpBB integration Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.9.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32274</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in axew3 WP w3all phpBB allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP w3all phpBB: from n/a through 2.9.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32276 | WordPress Administrator Z plugin &amp;lt;= 2025.03.04 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32276</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Quý Lê 91 Administrator Z allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Administrator Z: from n/a through 2025.03.04.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32277 | WordPress RepairBuddy plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8211 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32277</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Ateeq Rafeeq RepairBuddy allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects RepairBuddy: from n/a through 3.8211.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32278 | WordPress Table Block by RioVizual plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32278</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in wprio Table Block by RioVizual allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Table Block by RioVizual: from n/a through 2.1.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32280 | WordPress WP Project Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.22 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32280</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in weDevs WP Project Manager allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects WP Project Manager: from n/a through 2.6.22.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3254 | xujiangfei admintwo add server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3254</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /resource/add. The manipulation of the argument description leads to server-side request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3255 | xujiangfei admintwo home access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3255</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/home. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper access controls. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:12:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25178 | GPU DDK - PhysmemWrapExtMem uiSize=0 corrupts kernel memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25178</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to cause kernel system memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0468 | GPU DDK - ui64RobustnessAddress can overwrite Freelist / HWRT (and bypass PMMETA)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0468</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to subvert GPU HW to write to arbitrary physical memory pages.

Under certain circumstances this exploit could be used to corrupt data pages not allocated by the GPU driver but memory pages in use by the kernel and drivers running on the platform altering their behaviour.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3252 | xujiangfei admintwo add cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3252</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /resource/add. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3253 | xujiangfei admintwo insertTree cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3253</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /ztree/insertTree. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3250 | elunez eladmin Maintenance Management Module testConnect deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3250</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in elunez eladmin 2.7. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/database/testConnect of the component Maintenance Management Module. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3251 | xujiangfei admintwo updateSet cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3251</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in xujiangfei admintwo 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /user/updateSet. The manipulation of the argument motto leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:21:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31480 | aiven-extras allows PostgreSQL Privilege Escalation through format function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31480</link><description>aiven-extras is a PostgreSQL extension. This is a privilege escalation vulnerability, allowing elevation to superuser inside PostgreSQL databases that use the aiven-extras package. The vulnerability leverages the format function not being schema-prefixed. Affected users should install 1.1.16 and ensure they run the latest version issuing ALTER EXTENSION aiven_extras UPDATE TO '1.1.16' after installing it. This needs to happen in each database aiven_extras has been installed in.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31130 | gitoxide does not detect SHA-1 collision attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31130</link><description>gitoxide is an implementation of git written in Rust. Before 0.42.0, gitoxide uses SHA-1 hash implementations without any collision detection, leaving it vulnerable to hash collision attacks. gitoxide uses the sha1_smol or sha1 crate, both of which implement standard SHA-1 without any mitigations for collision attacks. This means that two distinct Git objects with colliding SHA-1 hashes would break the Git object model and integrity checks when used with gitoxide. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.42.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:46:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27520 | BentoML Allows Remote Code Execution (RCE) via Insecure Deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27520</link><description>BentoML is a Python library for building online serving systems optimized for AI apps and model inference. A Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability caused by insecure deserialization has been identified in the latest version (v1.4.2) of BentoML. It allows any unauthenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the server. It exists an unsafe code segment in serde.py. This vulnerability is fixed in 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:46:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3249 | TOTOLINK A6000R mtkwifi.lua apcli_cancel_wps command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3249</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK A6000R 1.0.1-B20201211.2000. Affected by this vulnerability is the function apcli_cancel_wps of the file /usr/lib/lua/luci/controller/mtkwifi.lua. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22285 | WordPress Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22285</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eniture Technology Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Pallet Packaging for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.1.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51800 | WordPress Homey theme &amp;lt;= 2.4.1 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51800</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Favethemes Homey allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Homey: from n/a through 2.4.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22281 | WordPress Simplish theme &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22281</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in joshix Simplish allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Simplish: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2798 | Woffice &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Authentication Bypass via Registration Role</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2798</link><description>The Woffice CRM theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This is due to a misconfiguration of excluded roles during registration. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register with an Administrator role if a custom login form is being used. This can be combined with CVE-2025-2797 to bypass the user approval process if an Administrator can be tricked into taking an action such as clicking a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31381 | WordPress Booking Calendar and Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - Broken Authentication vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31381</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in shiptrack Booking Calendar and Notification allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Booking Calendar and Notification: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31384 | WordPress Videos plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31384</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability in Aviplugins Videos allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Videos: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:52:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31389 | WordPress Sequel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31389</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sequel.Io Sequel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Sequel: from n/a through 1.0.11.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31403 | WordPress Booking Calendar and Notification plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31403</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in shiptrack Booking Calendar and Notification allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects Booking Calendar and Notification: from n/a through 4.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28146 | Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via fota_url i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28146</link><description>Edimax AC1200 Wave 2 Dual-Band Gigabit Router BR-6478AC V3 1.0.15 was discovered to contain a command injection vulnerability via fota_url in /boafrm/formLtefotaUpgradeQuectel</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31405 | WordPress Fami WooCommerce Compare plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31405</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in zankover Fami WooCommerce Compare allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Fami WooCommerce Compare: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31407 | WordPress Tiger theme &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31407</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in hutsixdigital Tiger allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Tiger: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31416 | WordPress Awesome Event Booking plugin &amp;lt;= 2.8.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31416</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AwesomeTOGI Awesome Event Booking allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Awesome Event Booking: from n/a through 2.8.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31418 | WordPress Gravel theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31418</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in noonnoo Gravel allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Gravel: from n/a through 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31420 | WordPress wpForo Forum plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Privilege Escalation vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31420</link><description>Incorrect Privilege Assignment vulnerability in Tomdever wpForo Forum allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects wpForo Forum: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31421 | WordPress Srbtranslatin plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.0 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31421</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Oblak Studio Srbtranslatin allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Srbtranslatin: from n/a through 3.2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3189 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in DoWISP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3189</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in DoWISP in versions prior to 1.16.2.50, which consists of an stored XSS through the upload of a profile picture in SVG format with malicious Javascript code in it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3245 | itsourcecode Library Management System Forgot.java search sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3245</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itsourcecode Library Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Search of the file library_management/src/Library_Management/Forgot.java. The manipulation of the argument txtuname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3243 | code-projects Patient Record Management System dental_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3243</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /dental_form.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3244 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System Create User Page add-admin.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3244</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add-admin.php of the component Create User Page. The manipulation of the argument Avatar leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3241 | zhangyanbo2007 youkefu XML Document CallCenterRouterController.java xml external entity reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3241</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in zhangyanbo2007 youkefu up to 4.2.0. This affects an unknown part of the file src/main/java/com/ukefu/webim/web/handler/admin/callcenter/CallCenterRouterController.java of the component XML Document Handler. The manipulation of the argument routercontent leads to xml external entity reference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3242 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System search-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3242</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /search-result.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22282 | WordPress ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin plugin &amp;lt;= 2.14.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22282</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EPC ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects ez Form Calculator - WordPress plugin: from n/a through 2.14.1.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3239 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System edit-guard-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3239</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-guard-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3240 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System search.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3240</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/search.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:46:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3237 | Tenda FH1202 wrlwpsset access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3237</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/wrlwpsset. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3238 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System search-request.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3238</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-request.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1865 | Local Privilege Escalation in Virtual CloneDrive Kernel Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1865</link><description>The kernel driver, accessible to low-privileged users, exposes a function that fails to properly validate the privileges of the calling process. This allows creating files at arbitrary locations with full user control, ultimately allowing for privilege escalation to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2243 | SSRF in GravityZone Console via DNS Truncation (VA-12634)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2243</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Bitdefender GravityZone Console allows an attacker to bypass input validation logic using leading characters in DNS requests. Paired with other potential vulnerabilities, this bypass could be used for execution of third party code. This issue affects GravityZone Console: before 6.41.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2244 | Insecure PHP deserialization issue in GravityZone Console (VA-12634)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2244</link><description>A vulnerability in the sendMailFromRemoteSource method in Emails.php  as used in Bitdefender GravityZone Console unsafely uses php unserialize() on user-supplied input without validation. By crafting a malicious serialized payload, an attacker can trigger PHP object injection, perform a file write, and gain arbitrary command execution on the host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2245 | Server Side Request Forgery in GravityZone Update Server Using Null Bytes (VA-12646)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2245</link><description>A server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability exists in the Bitdefender GravityZone Update Server when operating in Relay Mode. The HTTP proxy component on port 7074 uses a domain allowlist to restrict outbound requests, but fails to properly sanitize hostnames containing null-byte (%00) sequences. By crafting a request to a domain such as evil.com%00.bitdefender.com, an attacker can bypass the allowlist check, causing the proxy to forward requests to arbitrary external or internal systems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3235 | PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3235</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Old Age Home Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument adminname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3236 | Tenda FH1202 Web Management Interface VirSerDMZ access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3236</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda FH1202 1.2.0.14(408). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/VirSerDMZ of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3231 | PHPGurukul Zoo Management System aboutus.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3231</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Zoo Management System 2.1. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /aboutus.php. The manipulation of the argument pagetitle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 09:14:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3229 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System edit-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3229</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3220 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System dashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3220</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /dashboard.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3105 | Vehica Core &amp;lt;= 1.0.97 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3105</link><description>The Vehica Core plugin for WordPress, used by the Vehica - Car Dealer &amp; Listing WordPress Theme, is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.97. This is due to the plugin not properly validating user meta fields prior to updating them in the database. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change escalate their privileges to Administrator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3219 | CodeCanyon Perfex CRM Project Discussions Module 2 cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeCanyon Perfex CRM 3.2.1. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /perfex/clients/project/2 of the component Project Discussions Module. The manipulation of the argument description leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2780 | Woffice Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2780</link><description>The Woffice Core plugin for WordPress, used by the Woffice Theme, is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'saveFeaturedImage' function in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2797 | Woffice Core &amp;lt;= 5.4.21 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to User Registration Approval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2797</link><description>The Woffice Core plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 5.4.21. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'woffice_handle_user_approval_actions' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to approve registration for any user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3217 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3217</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /registration.php. The manipulation of the argument emailid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32111 | The Docker image from acme.sh before 40b6db6 is based on a .github/workflows/dockerhub.yml file that lacks "persist-credentials: false" for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32111</link><description>The Docker image from acme.sh before 40b6db6 is based on a .github/workflows/dockerhub.yml file that lacks "persist-credentials: false" for actions/checkout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3086 | User in anonymous role could create and delete views</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3086</link><description>Improper isolation of users in M-Files Server version before 25.3.14549 allows anonymous user to affect other anonymous users views and possibly cause a denial of service</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3087 | Stored XSS Vulnerability in M-Files Web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3087</link><description>Stored XSS in M-Files Web versions from 25.1.14445.5 to 25.2.14524.4 allows an authenticated user to run scripts</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:53:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3215 | PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System add-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3215</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Restaurant Table Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3216 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System password-recovery.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3216</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /password-recovery.php. The manipulation of the argument username/contactno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2159 | Stored XSS in M-Files Admin user interface</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2159</link><description>Stored XSS in Desktop UI in M-Files Server Admin tool before version 25.3.14681.7 on Windows allows authenticated local user to run scripts via UI</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2279 | Maps - Google Maps &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2279</link><description>The Maps  WordPress plugin through 1.0.6 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3214 | JFinal CMS readTemplate engine.getTemplate path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3214</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in JFinal CMS up to 5.2.4 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function engine.getTemplate of the file /readTemplate. The manipulation of the argument template leads to path traversal. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The vendor explains that this is not a bug but a feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 06:21:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13645 | TagDiv Composer &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary PHP Object Instantiation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13645</link><description>The tagDiv Composer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Instantiation in all versions up to, and including, 5.3 via module parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to Instantiate a PHP Object. No known POP chain is present in the vulnerable software, which means this vulnerability has no impact unless another plugin or theme containing a POP chain is installed on the site. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it may allow the attacker to perform actions like delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code depending on the POP chain present.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13708 | Booster for WooCommerce 4.0.1 - 7.2.4 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13708</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via SVG File uploads in versions 4.0.1 to 7.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses the SVG file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13898 | Simple Banner &amp;lt;= 3.0.4 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13898</link><description>The Simple Banner – Easily add multiple Banners/Bars/Notifications/Announcements to the top or bottom of your website plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42208 | HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42208</link><description>HCL Connections is vulnerable to an information disclosure vulnerability which could allow a user to obtain sensitive information they are not entitled to, caused by improper handling of request data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2270 | Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp;amp; Clock &amp;lt;= 2.8.9.1 - Unauthenticated Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2270</link><description>The Countdown, Coming Soon, Maintenance – Countdown &amp; Clock plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.9.1 via the createCdObj function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include and execute files with the specific filenames on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in some cases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2317 | Product Filter by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.7.9 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via filtersDataBackend Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2317</link><description>The Product Filter by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the filtersDataBackend parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2836 | RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login &amp;lt;= 6.0.4.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2836</link><description>The RegistrationMagic – Custom Registration Forms, User Registration, Payment, and User Login plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘payment_method’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.0.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3211 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3211</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /birthing_print.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3213 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System view-note.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3213</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view-note.php?noteid=11. The manipulation of the argument remark leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3191 | All versions of the package react-draft-wysiwyg are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Embedded button which will then result ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3191</link><description>All versions of the package react-draft-wysiwyg are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Embedded button which will then result in saving the payload in the  tag.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3192 | Versions of the package spatie/browsershot from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the setUrl() function due to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3192</link><description>Versions of the package spatie/browsershot from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) in the setUrl() function due to a missing restriction on user input, enabling attackers to access localhost and list all of its directories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3194 | Versions of the package bigint-buffer from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the toBigIntLE() function. Attackers can exploit this ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3194</link><description>Versions of the package bigint-buffer from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the toBigIntLE() function. Attackers can exploit this to crash the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3197 | Versions of the package expand-object from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the expand() function in index.js. This function e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3197</link><description>Versions of the package expand-object from 0.0.0 are vulnerable to Prototype Pollution in the expand() function in index.js. This function expands the given string into an object and allows a nested property to be set without checking the provided keys for sensitive properties like __proto__.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3209 | code-projects Patient Record Management System add_patient.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3209</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /add_patient.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3210 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_pending.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /birthing_pending.php. The manipulation of the argument birth_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:14:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3208 | code-projects Patient Record Management System xray_print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3208</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /xray_print.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13744 | Booster for WooCommerce 4.0.1 - 7.2.4 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13744</link><description>The Booster for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the validate_product_input_fields_on_add_to_cart function in versions 4.0.1 to 7.2.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2075 | Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.3.0.2 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2075</link><description>The Uncanny Automator – Easy Automation, Integration, Webhooks &amp; Workflow Builder Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.0.2. This is due to add_role() and user_role() functions missing proper capability checks performed through the validate_rest_call() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to set the role of arbitrary users to administrator granting full access to the site, though privilege escalation requires an active account on the site so this is considered an authenticated privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3207 | code-projects Patient Record Management System birthing_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /birthing_form.php. The manipulation of the argument birth_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 04:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3206 | code-projects Hospital Management System doctor-specilization.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3206</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/doctor-specilization.php. The manipulation of the argument doctorspecilization leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3204 | CodeAstro Car Rental System returncar.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3204</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeAstro Car Rental System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /returncar.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3205 | CodeAstro Student Grading System studentsubject.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3205</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Student Grading System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file studentsubject.php. The manipulation of the argument studentId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3202 | ageerle ruoyi-ai SysNoticeController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3202</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in ageerle ruoyi-ai up to 2.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file ruoyi-modules/ruoyi-system/src/main/java/org/ruoyi/system/controller/system/SysNoticeController.java. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.1 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 6382e177bf90cc56ff70521842409e35c50df32d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3203 | Tenda W18E setModules formSetAccountList stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3203</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda W18E 16.01.0.11. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetAccountList of the file /goform/setModules. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 03:08:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24310 | Improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24310</link><description>Improper restriction of rendered UI layers or frames issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to trick the product user to perform operations on the product's web pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24317 | Allocation of resources without limits or throttling issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24317</link><description>Allocation of resources without limits or throttling issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25061 | Unintended proxy or intermediary ('Confused Deputy') issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remot...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25061</link><description>Unintended proxy or intermediary ('Confused Deputy') issue exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series and HMI GC-A2 series, which may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to use the product as an intermediary for FTP bounce attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26401 | Weak encoding for password vulnerability exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series. If this vulnerability is exploited, authentication information...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26401</link><description>Weak encoding for password vulnerability exists in HMI ViewJet C-more series. If this vulnerability is exploited, authentication information may be obtained by a local authenticated attacker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3199 | ageerle ruoyi-ai API Interface SysModelController.java improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3199</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ageerle ruoyi-ai up to 2.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file ruoyi-modules/ruoyi-system/src/main/java/org/ruoyi/system/controller/system/SysModelController.java of the component API Interface. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 2.0.2 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is c0daf641fb25b244591b7a6c3affa35c69d321fe. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3195 | itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System bbms.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3195</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in itsourcecode Online Blood Bank Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /bbms.php. The manipulation of the argument Search leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3196 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp Malformed File MD2Loader.cpp InternReadFile stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3196</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. Affected is the function Assimp::MD2Importer::InternReadFile in the library code/AssetLib/MD2/MD2Loader.cpp of the component Malformed File Handler. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3198 | GNU Binutils objdump bucomm.c display_info memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3198</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.43/2.44 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function display_info of the file binutils/bucomm.c of the component objdump. The manipulation leads to memory leak. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named ba6ad3a18cb26b79e0e3b84c39f707535bbc344d. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25000 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25000</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25001 | Microsoft Edge for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25001</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29796 | Microsoft Edge for iOS Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29796</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29815 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29815</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3187 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument logindetail leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3188 | PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System add-notes.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-notes.php. The manipulation of the argument Category leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3186 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System invoice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /patient/invoice.php. The manipulation of the argument appid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:41:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3185 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System patientupdateprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /patient/patientupdateprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument patientFirstName leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 23:14:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3184 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /patient/profile.php?patientId=1. The manipulation of the argument patientFirstName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:43:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0278 | An internal path disclosure vulnerability affects HCL Traveler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0278</link><description>HCL Traveler is affected by an internal path disclosure in a Windows application when the application inadvertently reveals internal file paths, in error messages, debug logs, or responses to user requests.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30370 | jupyterlab-git has a command injection vulnerability in &amp;quot;Open Git Repository in Terminal&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30370</link><description>jupyterlab-git is a JupyterLab extension for version control using Git. On many platforms, a third party can create a Git repository under a name that includes a shell command substitution string in the syntax $(&lt;command /&gt;). These directory names are allowed in macOS and a majority of Linux distributions. If a user starts jupyter-lab in a parent directory of this inappropriately-named Git repository, opens it, and clicks "Git &gt; Open Git Repository in Terminal" from the menu bar, then the injected command &lt;command /&gt; is run in the user's shell without the user's permission. This issue is occurring because when that menu entry is clicked, jupyterlab-git opens the terminal and runs cd  through the shell to set the current directory. Doing so runs any command substitution strings present in the directory name, which leads to the command injection issue described here. A previous patch provided an incomplete fix. This vulnerability is fixed in 0.51.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3183 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System patientupdateprofile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3183</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /patient/patientupdateprofile.php. The manipulation of the argument patientFirstName leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:15:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0279 | HCL Traveler is affected by generation of error messages containing sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0279</link><description>HCL Traveler generates some error messages that provide detailed information about errors and failures, such as internal paths, file names, sensitive tokens, credentials, error codes, or stack traces.  Attackers could exploit this information to gain insights into the system's architecture and potentially launch targeted attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:51:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3181 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3181</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /patient/appointment.php?scheduleDate=1&amp;amp;appid=1. The manipulation of the argument scheduleDate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3182 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System getschedule.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3182</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /patient/getschedule.php. The manipulation of the argument q leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3179 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System deletepatient.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3179</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /doctor/deletepatient.php. The manipulation of the argument ic leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3180 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System deleteschedule.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3180</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /doctor/deleteschedule.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:15:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47214 | An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It is similar to CVE-2024-47212, but involves a different kind of malicious payload...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47214</link><description>An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It is similar to CVE-2024-47212, but involves a different kind of malicious payload. As above, it can render Iglu Server completely unresponsive. If the operation of Iglu Server is not restored, event processing in the pipeline would eventually halt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47215 | An issue was discovered in Snowbridge setups sending data to Google Tag Manager Server Side. It involves attaching an invalid GTM SS preview...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47215</link><description>An issue was discovered in Snowbridge setups sending data to Google Tag Manager Server Side. It involves attaching an invalid GTM SS preview header to events, causing them to be retried indefinitely. As a result, the performance of forwarding events to GTM SS overall can be affected (latency, throughput).</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47217 | An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It is similar to CVE-2024-47214, but involves an authenticated endpoint. It can ren...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47217</link><description>An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It is similar to CVE-2024-47214, but involves an authenticated endpoint. It can render Iglu Server completely unresponsive. If the operation of Iglu Server is not restored, event processing in the pipeline would eventually halt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56528 | This vulnerability affects Snowplow Collector 3.x before 3.3.0 (unless it’s set up behind a reverse proxy that establishes payload limits). ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56528</link><description>This vulnerability affects Snowplow Collector 3.x before 3.3.0 (unless it’s set up behind a reverse proxy that establishes payload limits). It involves sending very large payloads to the Collector and can render it unresponsive to the rest of the requests. As a result, data would not enter the pipeline and would be potentially lost.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3178 | projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System deleteappointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3178</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Doctor Appointment Booking System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /doctor/deleteappointment.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45199 | insightsoftware Hive JDBC through 2.6.13 has a remote code execution vulnerability. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45199</link><description>insightsoftware Hive JDBC through 2.6.13 has a remote code execution vulnerability. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC URL, triggering JNDI injection during the process when the JDBC Driver uses this URL to connect to the database. This can further lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47212 | An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It involves sending very large payloads to a particular API endpoint of Iglu Server...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47212</link><description>An issue was discovered in Iglu Server 0.13.0 and below. It involves sending very large payloads to a particular API endpoint of Iglu Server and can render it completely unresponsive. If the operation of Iglu Server is not restored, event processing in the pipeline would eventually halt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-47213 | An issue was discovered affecting Enrich 5.1.0 and below. It involves sending a maliciously crafted Snowplow event to the pipeline. Upon rec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-47213</link><description>An issue was discovered affecting Enrich 5.1.0 and below. It involves sending a maliciously crafted Snowplow event to the pipeline. Upon receiving this event and trying to validate it, Enrich crashes and attempts to restart indefinitely. As a result, event processing would be halted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45198 | insightsoftware Spark JDBC 2.6.21 has a remote code execution vulnerability. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC URL, tr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45198</link><description>insightsoftware Spark JDBC 2.6.21 has a remote code execution vulnerability. Attackers can inject malicious parameters into the JDBC URL, triggering JNDI injection during the process when the JDBC Driver uses this URL to connect to the database. This can further lead to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:18:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29504 | Insecure Permission vulnerability in student-manage 1 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Unsafe permission verification.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29504</link><description>Insecure Permission vulnerability in student-manage 1 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the Unsafe permission verification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29064 | An issue in TOTOLINK x18 v.9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the sub_410E54 function of the cste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29064</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK x18 v.9.1.0cu.2024_B20220329 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the sub_410E54 function of the cstecgi.cgi.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3177 | FastCMS JWT hard-coded key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3177</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FastCMS 0.1.5. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component JWT Handler. The manipulation leads to use of hard-coded cryptographic key&#13; . The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:18:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31485 | GraphQL grant on a property might be cached with different objects</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31485</link><description>API Platform Core is a system to create hypermedia-driven REST and GraphQL APIs. Prior to 4.0.22, a GraphQL grant on a property might be cached with different objects. The ApiPlatform\GraphQl\Serializer\ItemNormalizer::isCacheKeySafe() method is meant to prevent the caching but the parent::normalize method that is called afterwards still creates the cache key and causes the issue. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31489 | MinIO performs incomplete signature validation for unsigned-trailer uploads</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31489</link><description>MinIO is a High Performance Object Storage released under GNU Affero General Public License v3.0. The signature component of the authorization may be invalid, which would mean that as a client you can use any arbitrary secret to upload objects given the user already has prior WRITE permissions on the bucket. Prior knowledge of access-key, and bucket name this user might have access
to - and an access-key with a WRITE permissions is necessary. However with relevant information in place, uploading random objects to buckets is trivial and easy via curl. This issue is fixed in RELEASE.2025-04-03T14-56-28Z.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3176 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System single_lawyer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /single_lawyer.php. The manipulation of the argument u_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26817 | Netwrix Password Secure 9.2.0.32454 allows OS command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26817</link><description>Netwrix Password Secure 9.2.0.32454 allows OS command injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26818 | Netwrix Password Secure through 9.2 allows command injection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26818</link><description>Netwrix Password Secure through 9.2 allows command injection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30406 | Gladinet CentreStack through 16.1.10296.56315 (fixed in 16.4.10315.56368) has a deserialization vulnerability due to the CentreStack portal'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30406</link><description>Gladinet CentreStack through 16.1.10296.56315 (fixed in 16.4.10315.56368) has a deserialization vulnerability due to the CentreStack portal's hardcoded machineKey use, which enables threat actors (who know the machineKey) to serialize a payload for server-side deserialization to achieve remote code execution. NOTE: the CentreStack admin can manually delete the machineKey defined in portal\web.config.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29570 | An issue in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v3.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the function tftp_ima...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29570</link><description>An issue in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v3.2 allows a local attacker to escalate privileges via the function tftp_image_check of a binary named rc.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:28:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31161 | CrushFTP 10 before 10.8.4 and 11 before 11.3.1 allows authentication bypass and takeover of the crushadmin account (unless a DMZ proxy insta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31161</link><description>CrushFTP 10 before 10.8.4 and 11 before 11.3.1 allows authentication bypass and takeover of the crushadmin account (unless a DMZ proxy instance is used), as exploited in the wild in March and April 2025, aka "Unauthenticated HTTP(S) port access." A race condition exists in the AWS4-HMAC (compatible with S3) authorization method of the HTTP component of the FTP server. The server first verifies the existence of the user by performing a call to login_user_pass() with no password requirement. This will authenticate the session through the HMAC verification process and up until the server checks for user verification once more. The vulnerability can be further stabilized, eliminating the need for successfully triggering a race condition, by sending a mangled AWS4-HMAC header. By providing only the username and a following slash (/), the server will successfully find a username, which triggers the successful anypass authentication process, but the server will fail to find the expected SignedHeaders entry, resulting in an index-out-of-bounds error that stops the code from reaching the session cleanup. Together, these issues make it trivial to authenticate as any known or guessable user (e.g., crushadmin), and can lead to a full compromise of the system by obtaining an administrative account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31481 | GraphQL query operations security can be bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31481</link><description>API Platform Core is a system to create hypermedia-driven REST and GraphQL APIs. Using the Relay special node type you can bypass the configured security on an operation. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.0.22.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29462 | A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in Tenda Ac15 V15.13.07.13. The vulnerability occurs when the webCgiGetUploadFile functi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29462</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability has been discovered in Tenda Ac15 V15.13.07.13. The vulnerability occurs when the webCgiGetUploadFile function calls the socketRead function to process HTTP request messages, resulting in the overwriting of a buffer on the stack.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:21:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31119 | CWE-470 in generator-jhipster-entity-audit when having Javers selected as Entity Audit Framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31119</link><description>generator-jhipster-entity-audit is a JHipster module to enable entity audit and audit log page. Prior to 5.9.1, generator-jhipster-entity-audit allows unsafe reflection when having Javers selected as Entity Audit Framework. If an attacker manages to place some malicious classes into the classpath and also has access to these REST interface for calling the mentioned REST endpoints, using these lines of code can lead to unintended remote code execution. This vulnerability is fixed in 5.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29647 | SeaCMS v13.3 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the component admin_tempvideo.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29647</link><description>SeaCMS v13.3 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the component admin_tempvideo.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3174 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System searchLawyer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3174</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /searchLawyer.php. The manipulation of the argument experience leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3175 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System save_user_edit_profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /save_user_edit_profile.php. The manipulation of the argument first_Name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31487 | The XWiki JIRA extension allows data leak through an XXE attack by using a fake JIRA server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31487</link><description>The XWiki JIRA extension provides various integration points between XWiki and JIRA (macros, UI, CKEditor plugin). If the JIRA macro is installed, any logged in XWiki user could edit his/her user profile wiki page and use that JIRA macro, specifying a fake JIRA URL that returns an XML specifying a DOCTYPE pointing to a local file on the XWiki server host and displaying that file's content in one of the returned JIRA fields (such as the summary or description for example). The vulnerability has been patched in the JIRA Extension v8.6.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:54:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22611 | OpenEMR 7.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via \openemr\library\classes\Pharmacy.class.php, \controllers\C_Pharmacy.class.php and \openemr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22611</link><description>OpenEMR 7.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via \openemr\library\classes\Pharmacy.class.php, \controllers\C_Pharmacy.class.php and \openemr\controller.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31486 | Vite allows server.fs.deny to be bypassed with .svg or relative paths</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31486</link><description>Vite is a frontend tooling framework for javascript. The contents of arbitrary files can be returned to the browser. By adding ?.svg with ?.wasm?init or with sec-fetch-dest: script header, the server.fs.deny restriction was able to bypass. This bypass is only possible if the file is smaller than build.assetsInlineLimit (default: 4kB) and when using Vite 6.0+. Only apps explicitly exposing the Vite dev server to the network (using --host or server.host config option) are affected. This vulnerability is fixed in 4.5.12, 5.4.17, 6.0.14, 6.1.4, and 6.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3173 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System save_booking.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3173</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /save_booking.php. The manipulation of the argument lawyer_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:47:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31483 | Stored XSS in Miniflux Media Proxy due to improper Content-Security-Policy configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31483</link><description>Miniflux is a feed reader. Due to a weak Content Security Policy on the /proxy/* route, an attacker can bypass the CSP of the media proxy and execute cross-site scripting when opening external images in a new tab/window. To mitigate the vulnerability, the CSP for the media proxy has been changed from default-src 'self' to default-src 'none'; form-action 'none'; sandbox;. This vulnerability is fixed in 2.2.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3171 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System approve_lawyer.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3171</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /approve_lawyer.php. The manipulation of the argument unblock_id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3172 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System lawyer_booking.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3172</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /lawyer_booking.php. The manipulation of the argument unblock_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31126 | Element X iOS allows the entity in control of the well-known file to break the confidentiality of embedded Element Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31126</link><description>Element X iOS is a Matrix iOS Client provided by Element. In Element X iOS version between 1.6.13 and 25.03.7, the entity in control of the element.json well-known file is able, under certain conditions, to get access to the media encryption keys used for an Element Call call. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.03.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31127 | Element X Android allows the entity in control of the well-known file to break the confidentiality embedded Element Call</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31127</link><description>Element X Android is a Matrix Android Client provided by element.io. In Element X Android versions between 0.4.16 and 25.03.3, the entity in control of the element.json well-known file is able, under certain conditions, to get access to the media encryption keys used for an Element Call call. This vulnerability is fixed in 25.03.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3170 | Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System admin_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3170</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Project Worlds Online Lawyer Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin_user.php. The manipulation of the argument block_id/unblock_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31115 | XZ has a heap-use-after-free bug in threaded .xz decoder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31115</link><description>XZ Utils provide a general-purpose data-compression library plus command-line tools. In XZ Utils 5.3.3alpha to 5.8.0, the multithreaded .xz decoder in liblzma has a bug where invalid input can at least result in a crash. The effects include heap use after free and writing to an address based on the null pointer plus an offset. Applications and libraries that use the lzma_stream_decoder_mt function are affected. The bug has been fixed in XZ Utils 5.8.1, and the fix has been committed to the v5.4, v5.6, v5.8, and master branches in the xz Git repository. No new release packages will be made from the old stable branches, but a standalone patch is available that applies to all affected releases.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3168 | PHPGurukul Time Table Generator System edit-class.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3168</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Time Table Generator System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-class.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3169 | Projeqtor saveAttachment.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3169</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Projeqtor up to 12.0.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /tool/saveAttachment.php. The manipulation of the argument attachmentFiles leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 12.0.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor explains, that "this vulnerability can be exploited only on not securely installed instances, as it is adviced during product install: attachment directory should be out of web reach, so that even if executable file can be uploaded, it cannot be executed through the web."</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47639 | API Platform Core can leak exceptions message that may contain sensitive information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47639</link><description>API Platform Core is a system to create hypermedia-driven REST and GraphQL APIs. From 3.2.0 until 3.2.4, exception messages, that are not HTTP exceptions, are visible in the JSON error response. This vulnerability is fixed in 3.2.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32054 | In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2024.3, 2024.2.4 source code could be logged in the idea.log file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32054</link><description>In JetBrains IntelliJ IDEA before 2024.3, 2024.2.4 source code could be logged in the idea.log file</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:55:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3166 | code-projects Product Management System Search Product Menu search_item stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3166</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Product Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects the function search_item of the component Search Product Menu. The manipulation of the argument target leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3167 | Tenda AC23 API Interface VerAPIMant denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3167</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /goform/VerAPIMant of the component API Interface. The manipulation of the argument getuid leads to denial of service. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:43:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3165 | thu-pacman chitu backend.py torch.load deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3165</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in thu-pacman chitu 0.1.0. This affects the function torch.load of the file chitu/chitu/backend.py. The manipulation of the argument ckpt_path/quant_ckpt_dir leads to deserialization. An attack has to be approached locally.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3163 | InternLM LMDeploy conf.py open code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3163</link><description>A vulnerability was found in InternLM LMDeploy up to 0.7.1. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Open of the file lmdeploy/docs/en/conf.py. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3164 | Tencent Music Entertainment SuperSonic H2 Database Connection testConnect code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3164</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tencent Music Entertainment SuperSonic up to 0.9.8. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /api/semantic/database/testConnect of the component H2 Database Connection Handler. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4877 | OpenVPN version 2.4.0 through 2.6.10 on Windows allows an external, lesser privileged process to create a named pipe which the OpenVPN GUI c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4877</link><description>OpenVPN version 2.4.0 through 2.6.10 on Windows allows an external, lesser privileged process to create a named pipe which the OpenVPN GUI component would connect to allowing it to escalate its privileges</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:21:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22457 | A stack-based buffer overflow in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.6, Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.4, and Ivanti ZTA...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22457</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow in Ivanti Connect Secure before version 22.7R2.6, Ivanti Policy Secure before version 22.7R1.4, and Ivanti ZTA Gateways before version 22.8R2.2 allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29987 | Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) versions prior to 8.3.0.15 contain an Insufficient Granularity of Ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29987</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Domain with Data Domain Operating System (DD OS) versions prior to 8.3.0.15 contain an Insufficient Granularity of Access Control vulnerability. An authenticated user from a trusted remote client could exploit this vulnerability to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:21:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0272 | HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is susceptible to an HTML injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0272</link><description>HCL DevOps Deploy / HCL Launch is vulnerable to HTML injection. This vulnerability may allow a user to embed arbitrary HTML tags in the Web UI potentially leading to sensitive information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3162 | InternLM LMDeploy PT File utils.py load_weight_ckpt deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3162</link><description>A vulnerability was found in InternLM LMDeploy up to 0.7.1. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function load_weight_ckpt of the file lmdeploy/lmdeploy/vl/model/utils.py of the component PT File Handler. The manipulation leads to deserialization. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:21:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3160 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp File SceneCombiner.cpp AddNodeHashes out-of-bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3160</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function Assimp::SceneCombiner::AddNodeHashes of the file code/Common/SceneCombiner.cpp of the component File Handler. The manipulation leads to out-of-bounds read. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as a0993658f40d8e13ff5823990c30b43c82a5daf0. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3161 | Tenda AC10 ShutdownSetAdd stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3161</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function ShutdownSetAdd of the file /goform/ShutdownSetAdd. The manipulation of the argument list leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3159 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp ASE File ASEParser.cpp ParseLV4MeshBonesVertices heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3159</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. This affects the function Assimp::ASE::Parser::ParseLV4MeshBonesVertices of the file code/AssetLib/ASE/ASEParser.cpp of the component ASE File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of the patch is e8a6286542924e628e02749c4f5ac4f91fdae71b. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32051 | Libsoup: segmentation fault when parsing malformed data uri</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32051</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The libsoup soup_uri_decode_data_uri() function may crash when processing malformed data URI. This flaw allows an attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32052 | Libsoup: heap buffer overflow in sniff_unknown()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32052</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. A vulnerability in the sniff_unknown() function may lead to heap buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:52:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32053 | Libsoup: heap buffer overflows in sniff_feed_or_html() and skip_insignificant_space()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32053</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. A vulnerability in sniff_feed_or_html() and skip_insignificant_space() functions may lead to a heap buffer over-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22926 | An issue in OS4ED openSIS v8.0 through v9.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal by sending a crafted POST request to /Modules....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22926</link><description>An issue in OS4ED openSIS v8.0 through v9.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal by sending a crafted POST request to /Modules.php?modname=messaging/Inbox.php&amp;amp;modfunc=save&amp;amp;filename.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29369 | Code-Projects Matrimonial Site V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /view_profile.php?id=1.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29369</link><description>Code-Projects Matrimonial Site V1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in /view_profile.php?id=1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30596 | WordPress include-file &amp;lt;= 1 - Arbitrary File Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30596</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound include-file allows Path Traversal. This issue affects include-file: from n/a through 1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30611 | WordPress Wptobe-signinup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30611</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Wptobe-signinup allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Wptobe-signinup: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30616 | WordPress Latest Custom Post Type Updates plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30616</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Latest Custom Post Type Updates allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Latest Custom Post Type Updates: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30858 | WordPress Snow Storm plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30858</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tribulant Software Snow Storm allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Snow Storm: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30889 | WordPress Testimonial Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.13 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30889</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in PickPlugins Testimonial Slider allows Object Injection. This issue affects Testimonial Slider: from n/a through 2.0.13.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30908 | WordPress Web Directory Free plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30908</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Shamalli Web Directory Free allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Web Directory Free: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30915 | WordPress Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.19 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30915</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Small Package Quotes – Worldwide Express Edition: from n/a through 5.2.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30916 | WordPress Residential Address Detection plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30916</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in enituretechnology Residential Address Detection allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Residential Address Detection: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31091 | WordPress CM Header and Footer &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31091</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Header and Footer allows Stored XSS. This issue affects CM Header and Footer: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31098 | WordPress DeBounce Email Validator &amp;lt;= 5.7 - Local File Inclusion Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31098</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in debounce DeBounce Email Validator allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects DeBounce Email Validator: from n/a through 5.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31436 | WordPress Blubrry PowerPress Podcasting plugin MultiSite add-on plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31436</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Angelo Mandato Blubrry PowerPress Podcasting plugin MultiSite add-on allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Blubrry PowerPress Podcasting plugin MultiSite add-on: from n/a through 0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31442 | WordPress Search engine keywords highlighter plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31442</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Search engine keywords highlighter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Search engine keywords highlighter: from n/a through 0.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31467 | WordPress Flickr Photostream plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31467</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Flickr Photostream allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Flickr Photostream: from n/a through 3.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31468 | WordPress WP_Identicon plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31468</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP_Identicon allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP_Identicon: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31536 | WordPress CF7 Spreadsheets plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31536</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in moshensky CF7 Spreadsheets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CF7 Spreadsheets: from n/a through 2.3.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31541 | WordPress TuriTop Booking System plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31541</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in turitop TuriTop Booking System allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TuriTop Booking System: from n/a through 1.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31554 | WordPress Docxpresso plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31554</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in docxpresso Docxpresso allows Absolute Path Traversal. This issue affects Docxpresso: from n/a through 2.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31558 | WordPress TailPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.4.4 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31558</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Externally-Accessible File or Directory vulnerability in Greg TailPress allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects TailPress: from n/a through 0.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31573 | WordPress PeproDev CF7 Database plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31573</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pepro Dev. Group PeproDev CF7 Database allows Stored XSS. This issue affects PeproDev CF7 Database: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31581 | WordPress WP Video Playlist plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31581</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Sandeep Kumar WP Video Playlist allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WP Video Playlist: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31582 | WordPress Contact Form vCard Generator plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31582</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ashish Ajani Contact Form vCard Generator allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Contact Form vCard Generator: from n/a through 2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31622 | WordPress Advanced Typekit plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31622</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Utkarsh Kukreti Advanced Typekit allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Advanced Typekit: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31626 | WordPress Support Helpdesk Ticket System Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 4.5.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in M. Ali Saleem Support Helpdesk Ticket System Lite allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Support Helpdesk Ticket System Lite: from n/a through 4.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31729 | WordPress WooTumblog plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.4 - Content Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31729</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in jeffikus WooTumblog allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WooTumblog: from n/a through 2.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31736 | WordPress Rich Text Editor Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31736</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in richtexteditor Rich Text Editor allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Rich Text Editor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31739 | WordPress Minimalistic Event Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31739</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Manuel Schmalstieg Minimalistic Event Manager allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Minimalistic Event Manager: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31746 | WordPress Clients plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31746</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Think201 Clients allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Clients: from n/a through 1.1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31758 | WordPress Free Woocommerce Product Table View plugin &amp;lt;= 1.78 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31758</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BinaryCarpenter Free Woocommerce Product Table View allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Free Woocommerce Product Table View: from n/a through 1.78.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31768 | WordPress Widget Manager Light plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31768</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in OTWthemes Widget Manager Light allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Widget Manager Light: from n/a through 1.18.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31789 | WordPress TextMe SMS plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31789</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Matat Technologies TextMe SMS allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects TextMe SMS: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31794 | WordPress WR Price List Manager For Woocommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31794</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Web Ready Now WR Price List Manager For Woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects WR Price List Manager For Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31795 | WordPress Shopify to WooCommerce Migration plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Settings Change vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31795</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Plugin Devs Shopify to WooCommerce Migration allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Shopify to WooCommerce Migration: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31800 | WordPress Publitio plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Arbitrary File Read vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31800</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in publitio Publitio allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Publitio: from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31825 | WordPress Category Icon plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31825</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in pixelgrade Category Icon allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Category Icon: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31827 | WordPress Fonto plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Arbitrary File Download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31827</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in vlad.olaru Fonto allows Path Traversal. This issue affects Fonto: from n/a through 1.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31841 | WordPress FPW Category Thumbnails Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31841</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Frank P. Walentynowicz FPW Category Thumbnails allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects FPW Category Thumbnails: from n/a through 1.9.5.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31858 | WordPress Local Magic Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31858</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in matthewrubin Local Magic allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Local Magic: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31876 | WordPress Payday plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.12 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31876</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in gunnarpayday Payday allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Payday: from n/a through 3.3.12.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31893 | WordPress Botnet Attack Blocker plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31893</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in cheesefather Botnet Attack Blocker allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Botnet Attack Blocker: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31896 | WordPress GetBookingsWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.27 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31896</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in istmoplugins GetBookingsWP allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects GetBookingsWP: from n/a through 1.1.27.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31898 | WordPress MediaView plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31898</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MediaView allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MediaView: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31899 | WordPress Awesome Logos plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31899</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in wpshopee Awesome Logos allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Awesome Logos: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31900 | WordPress Lexicata plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.16 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31900</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in lexicata Lexicata allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Lexicata: from n/a through 1.0.16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31901 | WordPress Digihood HTML Sitemap Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31901</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Digihood Digihood HTML Sitemap allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Digihood HTML Sitemap: from n/a through 3.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31902 | WordPress Social Share And Social Locker Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31902</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Social Share And Social Locker allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Social Share And Social Locker: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31903 | WordPress XV Random Quotes Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.37 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31903</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound XV Random Quotes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XV Random Quotes: from n/a through 1.37.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31905 | WordPress Team Rosters Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31905</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Team Rosters allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Team Rosters: from n/a through 4.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31907 | WordPress Team Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31907</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Labib Ahmed Team Builder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Team Builder: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31909 | WordPress Apptivo Business Site CRM plugin &amp;lt;= 5.3 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31909</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Apptivo Business Site CRM allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Apptivo Business Site CRM: from n/a through 5.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31911 | WordPress Social Share And Social Locker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31911</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Social Share And Social Locker allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects Social Share And Social Locker: from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32049 | Libsoup: denial of service attack to websocket server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32049</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The SoupWebsocketConnection may accept a large WebSocket message, which may cause libsoup to allocate memory and lead to a denial of service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32050 | Libsoup: integer overflow in append_param_quoted</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32050</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The libsoup append_param_quoted() function may contain an overflow bug resulting in a buffer under-read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3155 | Yelp: arbitrary file read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3155</link><description>A flaw was found in Yelp. The Gnome user help application allows the help document to execute arbitrary scripts. This vulnerability allows malicious users to input help documents, which may exfiltrate user files to an external environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3157 | Intelbras WRN 150 Wireless Menu cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3157</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Intelbras WRN 150 1.0.15_pt_ITB01. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Wireless Menu. The manipulation of the argument SSID leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor was contacted early about this issue and explains that the latest version is not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3158 | Open Asset Import Library Assimp LWO File LWOAnimation.cpp UpdateAnimRangeSetup heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3158</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Open Asset Import Library Assimp 5.4.3. Affected by this issue is the function Assimp::LWO::AnimResolver::UpdateAnimRangeSetup of the file code/AssetLib/LWO/LWOAnimation.cpp of the component LWO File Handler. The manipulation leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22929 | OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the filter_id parameter at /students/StudentFilters.p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22929</link><description>OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the filter_id parameter at /students/StudentFilters.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22930 | OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the groupid parameter at /messaging/Group.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22930</link><description>OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the groupid parameter at /messaging/Group.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22931 | An insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in the component /assets/stafffiles of OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 allows unauthenticated attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22931</link><description>An insecure direct object reference (IDOR) in the component /assets/stafffiles of OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 allows unauthenticated attackers to access files uploaded by staff members.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:29:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22927 | An issue in OS4ED openSIS v8.0 through v9.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal by sending a crafted POST request to /Modules....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22927</link><description>An issue in OS4ED openSIS v8.0 through v9.1 allows attackers to execute a directory traversal by sending a crafted POST request to /Modules.php?modname=messaging/Inbox.php&amp;amp;modfunc=save&amp;amp;filename.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22928 | OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the cp_id parameter at /modules/messages/Inbox.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22928</link><description>OS4ED openSIS v7.0 to v9.1 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the cp_id parameter at /modules/messages/Inbox.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9416 | Modula Image Gallery &amp;lt;= 2.10.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via FancyBox 5 JavaScript Library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9416</link><description>The Modula Image Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's bundled FancyBox JavaScript library (versions &lt;= 5.0.36) due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2945 | pgAdmin 4: Remote Code Execution in Query Tool and Cloud Deployment</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2945</link><description>Remote Code Execution security vulnerability in pgAdmin 4  (Query Tool and Cloud Deployment modules).

The vulnerability is associated with the 2 POST endpoints; /sqleditor/query_tool/download, where the query_commited parameter and /cloud/deploy endpoint, where the high_availability parameter is unsafely passed to the Python eval() function, allowing arbitrary code execution.


This issue affects pgAdmin 4: before 9.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2946 | Cross-Site Vulnerability(XSS) due to arbitrary HTML/JavaScript gets executed while query result rendering in Query Tool and View/Edit Data Tool of pgAdmin 4</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2946</link><description>pgAdmin &lt;= 9.1 is affected by a security vulnerability with Cross-Site Scripting(XSS). If attackers execute any arbitrary HTML/JavaScript in a user's browser through query result rendering, then HTML/JavaScript runs on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2299 | LuckyWP Table of Contents &amp;lt;= 2.1.10 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2299</link><description>The LuckyWP Table of Contents plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.10. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'ajaxEdit' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 11:26:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53868 | Apache Traffic Server: Malformed chunked message body allows request smuggling</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53868</link><description>Apache Traffic Server allows request smuggling if chunked messages are malformed. 





This issue affects Apache Traffic Server: from 9.2.0 through 9.2.9, from 10.0.0 through 10.0.4.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 9.2.10 or 10.0.5, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 09:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3151 | SourceCodester Gym Management System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3151</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Gym Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:13:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3152 | caipeichao ThinkOX Search search.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3152</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in caipeichao ThinkOX 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /ThinkOX-master/index.php?s=/Weibo/Index/search.html of the component Search. The manipulation of the argument keywords leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:13:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3149 | itning Student Homework Management System Edit Job Page fileupload cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3149</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itning Student Homework Management System up to 1.2.7. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /shw_war/fileupload of the component Edit Job Page. The manipulation of the argument Course leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3150 | itning Student Homework Management System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3150</link><description>A vulnerability was found in itning Student Homework Management System up to 1.2.7. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple endpoints might be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:40:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13673 | Big Boom Directory &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13673</link><description>The Big Boom Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bbd-search' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1663 | Unlimited Elements For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.142 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1663</link><description>The Unlimited Elements For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.142 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21995 | drm/sched: Fix fence reference count leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21995</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/sched: Fix fence reference count leak

The last_scheduled fence leaks when an entity is being killed and adding
the cleanup callback fails.

Decrement the reference count of prev when dma_fence_add_callback()
fails, ensuring proper balance.

[phasta: add git tag info for stable kernel]</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21996 | drm/radeon: fix uninitialized size issue in radeon_vce_cs_parse()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21996</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/radeon: fix uninitialized size issue in radeon_vce_cs_parse()

On the off chance that command stream passed from userspace via
ioctl() call to radeon_vce_cs_parse() is weirdly crafted and
first command to execute is to encode (case 0x03000001), the function
in question will attempt to call radeon_vce_cs_reloc() with size
argument that has not been properly initialized. Specifically, 'size'
will point to 'tmp' variable before the latter had a chance to be
assigned any value.

Play it safe and init 'tmp' with 0, thus ensuring that
radeon_vce_cs_reloc() will catch an early error in cases like these.

Found by Linux Verification Center (linuxtesting.org) with static
analysis tool SVACE.

(cherry picked from commit 2d52de55f9ee7aaee0e09ac443f77855989c6b68)</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21997 | xsk: fix an integer overflow in xp_create_and_assign_umem()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21997</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

xsk: fix an integer overflow in xp_create_and_assign_umem()

Since the i and pool-&gt;chunk_size variables are of type 'u32',
their product can wrap around and then be cast to 'u64'.
This can lead to two different XDP buffers pointing to the same
memory area.

Found by InfoTeCS on behalf of Linux Verification Center
(linuxtesting.org) with SVACE.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21998 | firmware: qcom: uefisecapp: fix efivars registration race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21998</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

firmware: qcom: uefisecapp: fix efivars registration race

Since the conversion to using the TZ allocator, the efivars service is
registered before the memory pool has been allocated, something which
can lead to a NULL-pointer dereference in case of a racing EFI variable
access.

Make sure that all resources have been set up before registering the
efivars.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-21999 | proc: fix UAF in proc_get_inode()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-21999</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

proc: fix UAF in proc_get_inode()

Fix race between rmmod and /proc/XXX's inode instantiation.

The bug is that pde-&gt;proc_ops don't belong to /proc, it belongs to a
module, therefore dereferencing it after /proc entry has been registered
is a bug unless use_pde/unuse_pde() pair has been used.

use_pde/unuse_pde can be avoided (2 atomic ops!) because pde-&gt;proc_ops
never changes so information necessary for inode instantiation can be
saved _before_ proc_register() in PDE itself and used later, avoiding
pde-&gt;proc_ops-&gt;...  dereference.

      rmmod                         lookup
sys_delete_module
                         proc_lookup_de
			   pde_get(de);
			   proc_get_inode(dir-&gt;i_sb, de);
  mod-&gt;exit()
    proc_remove
      remove_proc_subtree
       proc_entry_rundown(de);
  free_module(mod);

                               if (S_ISREG(inode-&gt;i_mode))
	                         if (de-&gt;proc_ops-&gt;proc_read_iter)
                           --&gt; As module is already freed, will trigger UAF

BUG: unable to handle page fault for address: fffffbfff80a702b
PGD 817fc4067 P4D 817fc4067 PUD 817fc0067 PMD 102ef4067 PTE 0
Oops: Oops: 0000 [#1] PREEMPT SMP KASAN PTI
CPU: 26 UID: 0 PID: 2667 Comm: ls Tainted: G
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996)
RIP: 0010:proc_get_inode+0x302/0x6e0
RSP: 0018:ffff88811c837998 EFLAGS: 00010a06
RAX: dffffc0000000000 RBX: ffffffffc0538140 RCX: 0000000000000007
RDX: 1ffffffff80a702b RSI: 0000000000000001 RDI: ffffffffc0538158
RBP: ffff8881299a6000 R08: 0000000067bbe1e5 R09: 1ffff11023906f20
R10: ffffffffb560ca07 R11: ffffffffb2b43a58 R12: ffff888105bb78f0
R13: ffff888100518048 R14: ffff8881299a6004 R15: 0000000000000001
FS:  00007f95b9686840(0000) GS:ffff8883af100000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: fffffbfff80a702b CR3: 0000000117dd2000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
DR0: 0000000000000000 DR1: 0000000000000000 DR2: 0000000000000000
DR3: 0000000000000000 DR6: 00000000fffe0ff0 DR7: 0000000000000400
Call Trace:
 
 proc_lookup_de+0x11f/0x2e0
 __lookup_slow+0x188/0x350
 walk_component+0x2ab/0x4f0
 path_lookupat+0x120/0x660
 filename_lookup+0x1ce/0x560
 vfs_statx+0xac/0x150
 __do_sys_newstat+0x96/0x110
 do_syscall_64+0x5f/0x170
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

[adobriyan@gmail.com: don't do 2 atomic ops on the common path]</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22000 | mm/huge_memory: drop beyond-EOF folios with the right number of refs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22000</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mm/huge_memory: drop beyond-EOF folios with the right number of refs

When an after-split folio is large and needs to be dropped due to EOF,
folio_put_refs(folio, folio_nr_pages(folio)) should be used to drop all
page cache refs.  Otherwise, the folio will not be freed, causing memory
leak.

This leak would happen on a filesystem with blocksize &gt; page_size and a
truncate is performed, where the blocksize makes folios split to &gt;0 order
ones, causing truncated folios not being freed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22001 | accel/qaic: Fix integer overflow in qaic_validate_req()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22001</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

accel/qaic: Fix integer overflow in qaic_validate_req()

These are u64 variables that come from the user via
qaic_attach_slice_bo_ioctl().  Use check_add_overflow() to ensure that
the math doesn't have an integer wrapping bug.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22002 | netfs: Call `invalidate_cache` only if implemented</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22002</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: Call `invalidate_cache` only if implemented

Many filesystems such as NFS and Ceph do not implement the
`invalidate_cache` method.  On those filesystems, if writing to the
cache (`NETFS_WRITE_TO_CACHE`) fails for some reason, the kernel
crashes like this:

 BUG: kernel NULL pointer dereference, address: 0000000000000000
 #PF: supervisor instruction fetch in kernel mode
 #PF: error_code(0x0010) - not-present page
 PGD 0 P4D 0
 Oops: Oops: 0010 [#1] SMP PTI
 CPU: 9 UID: 0 PID: 3380 Comm: kworker/u193:11 Not tainted 6.13.3-cm4all1-hp #437
 Hardware name: HP ProLiant DL380 Gen9/ProLiant DL380 Gen9, BIOS P89 10/17/2018
 Workqueue: events_unbound netfs_write_collection_worker
 RIP: 0010:0x0
 Code: Unable to access opcode bytes at 0xffffffffffffffd6.
 RSP: 0018:ffff9b86e2ca7dc0 EFLAGS: 00010202
 RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: 0000000000000000 RCX: 7fffffffffffffff
 RDX: 0000000000000001 RSI: ffff89259d576a18 RDI: ffff89259d576900
 RBP: ffff89259d5769b0 R08: ffff9b86e2ca7d28 R09: 0000000000000002
 R10: ffff89258ceaca80 R11: 0000000000000001 R12: 0000000000000020
 R13: ffff893d158b9338 R14: ffff89259d576900 R15: ffff89259d5769b0
 FS:  0000000000000000(0000) GS:ffff893c9fa40000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
 CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
 CR2: ffffffffffffffd6 CR3: 000000054442e003 CR4: 00000000001706f0
 Call Trace:
  
  ? __die+0x1f/0x60
  ? page_fault_oops+0x15c/0x460
  ? try_to_wake_up+0x2d2/0x530
  ? exc_page_fault+0x5e/0x100
  ? asm_exc_page_fault+0x22/0x30
  netfs_write_collection_worker+0xe9f/0x12b0
  ? xs_poll_check_readable+0x3f/0x80
  ? xs_stream_data_receive_workfn+0x8d/0x110
  process_one_work+0x134/0x2d0
  worker_thread+0x299/0x3a0
  ? __pfx_worker_thread+0x10/0x10
  kthread+0xba/0xe0
  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
  ret_from_fork+0x30/0x50
  ? __pfx_kthread+0x10/0x10
  ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
  
 Modules linked in:
 CR2: 0000000000000000

This patch adds the missing `NULL` check.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22003 | can: ucan: fix out of bound read in strscpy() source</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22003</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

can: ucan: fix out of bound read in strscpy() source

Commit 7fdaf8966aae ("can: ucan: use strscpy() to instead of strncpy()")
unintentionally introduced a one byte out of bound read on strscpy()'s
source argument (which is kind of ironic knowing that strscpy() is meant
to be a more secure alternative :)).

Let's consider below buffers:

  dest[len + 1]; /* will be NUL terminated */
  src[len]; /* may not be NUL terminated */

When doing:

  strncpy(dest, src, len);
  dest[len] = '\0';

strncpy() will read up to len bytes from src.

On the other hand:

  strscpy(dest, src, len + 1);

will read up to len + 1 bytes from src, that is to say, an out of bound
read of one byte will occur on src if it is not NUL terminated. Note
that the src[len] byte is never copied, but strscpy() still needs to
read it to check whether a truncation occurred or not.

This exact pattern happened in ucan.

The root cause is that the source is not NUL terminated. Instead of
doing a copy in a local buffer, directly NUL terminate it as soon as
usb_control_msg() returns. With this, the local firmware_str[] variable
can be removed.

On top of this do a couple refactors:

  - ucan_ctl_payload-&gt;raw is only used for the firmware string, so
    rename it to ucan_ctl_payload-&gt;fw_str and change its type from u8 to
    char.

  - ucan_device_request_in() is only used to retrieve the firmware
    string, so rename it to ucan_get_fw_str() and refactor it to make it
    directly handle all the string termination logic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22004 | net: atm: fix use after free in lec_send()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22004</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: atm: fix use after free in lec_send()

The -&gt;send() operation frees skb so save the length before calling
-&gt;send() to avoid a use after free.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22005 | ipv6: Fix memleak of nhc_pcpu_rth_output in fib_check_nh_v6_gw().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22005</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

ipv6: Fix memleak of nhc_pcpu_rth_output in fib_check_nh_v6_gw().

fib_check_nh_v6_gw() expects that fib6_nh_init() cleans up everything
when it fails.

Commit 7dd73168e273 ("ipv6: Always allocate pcpu memory in a fib6_nh")
moved fib_nh_common_init() before alloc_percpu_gfp() within fib6_nh_init()
but forgot to add cleanup for fib6_nh-&gt;nh_common.nhc_pcpu_rth_output in
case it fails to allocate fib6_nh-&gt;rt6i_pcpu, resulting in memleak.

Let's call fib_nh_common_release() and clear nhc_pcpu_rth_output in the
error path.

Note that we can remove the fib6_nh_release() call in nh_create_ipv6()
later in net-next.git.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22006 | net: ethernet: ti: am65-cpsw: Fix NAPI registration sequence</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22006</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: ethernet: ti: am65-cpsw: Fix NAPI registration sequence

Registering the interrupts for TX or RX DMA Channels prior to registering
their respective NAPI callbacks can result in a NULL pointer dereference.
This is seen in practice as a random occurrence since it depends on the
randomness associated with the generation of traffic by Linux and the
reception of traffic from the wire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22007 | Bluetooth: Fix error code in chan_alloc_skb_cb()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22007</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Fix error code in chan_alloc_skb_cb()

The chan_alloc_skb_cb() function is supposed to return error pointers on
error.  Returning NULL will lead to a NULL dereference.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2874 | User Submitted Posts &amp;lt;= 20241026 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2874</link><description>The User Submitted Posts – Enable Users to Submit Posts from the Front End plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 20240319 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3147 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System add-subadmin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3147</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-subadmin.php. The manipulation of the argument sadminusername leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3148 | codeprojects Product Management System Login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3148</link><description>A vulnerability was found in codeprojects Product Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument Str1 leads to buffer overflow. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 07:22:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30485 | UNIX symbolic link (Symlink) following issue exists in FutureNet NXR series, VXR series and WXR series routers. Attaching to the affected pr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30485</link><description>UNIX symbolic link (Symlink) following issue exists in FutureNet NXR series, VXR series and WXR series routers. Attaching to the affected product an external storage containing malicious symbolic link files, a logged-in administrative user may obtain and/or destroy internal files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3145 | MindSpore mindspore.numpy.fft.rfft2 memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3145</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in MindSpore 2.5.0. Affected by this issue is the function mindspore.numpy.fft.rfft2. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3146 | PHPGurukul Bus Pass Management System view-pass-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3146</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Bus Pass Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /view-pass-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:44:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2055 | MapPress Maps for WordPress &amp;lt; 2.94.9 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2055</link><description>The MapPress Maps for WordPress plugin before 2.94.9 does not sanitise and escape some parameters when outputing them in the page, which could allow users with a role as low as contributor to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:22:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3143 | SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System visitor-entry.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3143</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /visitor-entry.php. The manipulation of the argument visname/address leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3144 | MindSpore mindspore.numpy.fft.hfftn memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3144</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in MindSpore 2.5.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function mindspore.numpy.fft.hfftn. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:22:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31334 | Issue that bypasses the "Mark of the Web" security warning function for files when opening a symbolic link that points to an executable file...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31334</link><description>Issue that bypasses the "Mark of the Web" security warning function for files when opening a symbolic link that points to an executable file exists in WinRAR versions prior to 7.11. If a symbolic link specially crafted by an attacker is opened on the affected product, arbitrary code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3142 | SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System add-apartment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3142</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Apartment Visitor Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add-apartment.php. The manipulation of the argument buildingno leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Multiple parameters might be affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:33:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3141 | SourceCodester Online Medicine Ordering System manage_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3141</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_category.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 05:15:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3140 | SourceCodester Online Medicine Ordering System view_category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3140</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Online Medicine Ordering System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /view_category.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3138 | PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System edit-guard-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3138</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-guard-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3139 | code-projects Bus Reservation System Login Form login buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3139</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Bus Reservation System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function Login of the component Login Form. The manipulation of the argument Str1 leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 04:17:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3136 | PyTorch CUDACachingAllocator.cpp torch.cuda.memory.caching_allocator_delete memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3136</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in PyTorch 2.6.0. This issue affects the function torch.cuda.memory.caching_allocator_delete of the file c10/cuda/CUDACachingAllocator.cpp. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3137 | PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3137</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Online Security Guards Hiring System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 03:47:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29991 | Yubico YubiKey 5.4.1 through 5.7.3 before 5.7.4 has an incorrect FIDO CTAP PIN/UV Auth Protocol Two implementation. It uses the signature le...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29991</link><description>Yubico YubiKey 5.4.1 through 5.7.3 before 5.7.4 has an incorrect FIDO CTAP PIN/UV Auth Protocol Two implementation. It uses the signature length from CTAP PIN/UV Auth Protocol One, even when CTAP PIN/UV Auth Protocol Two was chosen, resulting in a partial signature verification.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2784 | Libsoup: heap buffer over-read in `skip_insignificant_space` when sniffing content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2784</link><description>A flaw was found in libsoup. The package is vulnerable to a heap buffer over-read when sniffing content via the skip_insight_whitespace() function. Libsoup clients may read one byte out-of-bounds in response to a crafted HTTP response by an HTTP server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3134 | code-projects Payroll Management System add_overtime.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3134</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Payroll Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /add_overtime.php. The manipulation of the argument rate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3135 | fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System update sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3135</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in fcba_zzm ics-park Smart Park Management System 2.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/system/dept/update. The manipulation leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 02:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3153 | Concrete CMS version 9 below 9.4.0RC2 and versions below 8.5.20 - CSRF and XSS in Concrete CMS Custom Address attributeC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3153</link><description>Concrete CMS version 9 below 9.4.0RC2 and versions below 8.5.20 are vulnerable to CSRF and XSS in the Concrete CMS Address attribute because addresses are not properly sanitized in the output when a country is not specified.  Attackers are limited to individuals whom a site administrator has granted the ability to fill in an address attribute. It is possible for the attacker to glean limited information from the site but amount and type is restricted by mitigating controls and the level of access of the attacker. Limited data modification is possible. The dashboard page itself could be rendered unavailable. 
The fix only sanitizes new data uploaded post update to Concrete CMS 9.4.0RC2. Existing database entries added before the update will still be “live” if there were successful exploits added under previous versions; a database search is recommended. The Concrete CMS security team gave this vulnerability CVSS v.4.0 score of 5.1  with vector CVSS:4.0/AV:N/AC:L/AT:N/PR:L/UI:P/VC:L/VI:L/VA:L/SC:L/SI:L/SA:L Thanks Myq Larson for reporting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 01:14:02 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>