<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-8254 | Campcodes Courier Management System view_parcel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8254</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53159 | The openssl crate before 0.10.55 for Rust allows an out-of-bounds read via an empty string to X509VerifyParamRef::set_host.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53159</link><description>The openssl crate before 0.10.55 for Rust allows an out-of-bounds read via an empty string to X509VerifyParamRef::set_host.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53160 | The sequoia-openpgp crate before 1.16.0 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53160</link><description>The sequoia-openpgp crate before 1.16.0 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53161 | The buffered-reader crate before 1.1.5 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53161</link><description>The buffered-reader crate before 1.1.5 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8252 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8252</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s5.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8253 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s6.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8253</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/delete_s6.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50237 | The ed25519-dalek crate before 2 for Rust allows a double public key signing function oracle attack. The Keypair implementation leads to a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50237</link><description>The ed25519-dalek crate before 2 for Rust allows a double public key signing function oracle attack. The Keypair implementation leads to a simple computation for extracting a private key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8251 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8251</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s4.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8250 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8250</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update_s4.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53158 | The gix-transport crate before 0.36.1 for Rust allows command execution via the "gix clone 'ssh://-oProxyCommand=open$IFS" substring. NOTE: ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53158</link><description>The gix-transport crate before 0.36.1 for Rust allows command execution via the "gix clone 'ssh://-oProxyCommand=open$IFS" substring. NOTE: this was discovered before CVE-2024-32884, a similar vulnerability (involving a username field) that is more difficult to exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8248 | code-projects Online Ordering System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8248</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8249 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8249</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_s3.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53157 | The rosenpass crate before 0.2.1 for Rust allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (panic) via a one-byte UDP packet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53157</link><description>The rosenpass crate before 0.2.1 for Rust allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (panic) via a one-byte UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8247 | Projectworlds Online Admission System admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8247</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin.php. The manipulation of the argument markof leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8246 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formRoute buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8246</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formRoute of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8245 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMultiAPVLAN buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8245</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMultiAPVLAN of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8244 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMapDelDevice buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8244</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formMapDelDevice of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument macstr leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 22:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58266 | The shlex crate before 1.2.1 for Rust allows unquoted and unescaped instances of the { and \xa0 characters, which may facilitate command inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58266</link><description>The shlex crate before 1.2.1 for Rust allows unquoted and unescaped instances of the { and \xa0 characters, which may facilitate command injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8243 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMapDel buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8243</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formMapDel of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument devicemac1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58265 | The snow crate before 0.9.5 for Rust, when stateful TransportState is used, allows incrementing a nonce and thereby denying message delivery...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58265</link><description>The snow crate before 0.9.5 for Rust, when stateful TransportState is used, allows incrementing a nonce and thereby denying message delivery.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8242 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8242</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr/url/vpnPassword/vpnUser leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58264 | The serde-json-wasm crate before 1.0.1 for Rust allows stack consumption via deeply nested JSON data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58264</link><description>The serde-json-wasm crate before 1.0.1 for Rust allows stack consumption via deeply nested JSON data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53156 | The transpose crate before 0.2.3 for Rust allows an integer overflow via input_width and input_height arguments.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53156</link><description>The transpose crate before 0.2.3 for Rust allows an integer overflow via input_width and input_height arguments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8241 | 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8241</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /report.php. The manipulation of the argument From leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58263 | The cosmwasm-std crate before 2.0.2 for Rust allows integer overflows that cause incorrect contract calculations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58263</link><description>The cosmwasm-std crate before 2.0.2 for Rust allows integer overflows that cause incorrect contract calculations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58262 | The curve25519-dalek crate before 4.1.3 for Rust has a constant-time operation on elliptic curve scalars that is removed by LLVM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58262</link><description>The curve25519-dalek crate before 4.1.3 for Rust has a constant-time operation on elliptic curve scalars that is removed by LLVM.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8240 | code-projects Exam Form Submission dashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8240</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/dashboard.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58261 | The sequoia-openpgp crate 1.13.0 before 1.21.0 for Rust allows an infinite loop of "Reading a cert: Invalid operation: Not a Key packet" mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58261</link><description>The sequoia-openpgp crate 1.13.0 before 1.21.0 for Rust allows an infinite loop of "Reading a cert: Invalid operation: Not a Key packet" messages for RawCertParser operations that encounter an unsupported primary key type.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8239 | code-projects Exam Form Submission admin sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8239</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8238 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8238</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update_s2.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8237 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8237</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_s1.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8236 | code-projects Online Ordering System edit_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8236</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_product.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8235 | code-projects Online Ordering System product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8235</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/product.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 16:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8234 | code-projects Online Ordering System delete_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8234</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_member.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 15:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8233 | code-projects Online Ordering System user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8233</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument un leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8232 | code-projects Online Ordering System delete_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8232</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8231 | D-Link DIR-890L UART Port rgbin hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8231</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-890L up to 111b04. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rgbin of the component UART Port. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8230 | Campcodes Courier Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8230</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8229 | Campcodes Courier Management System parcel_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8229</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /parcel_list.php. The manipulation of the argument s leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8228 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS getPages server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8228</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function getPages of the file /cms/collect/getPages. The manipulation of the argument targetUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 09:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8227 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS getArticle deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /collect/getArticle. The manipulation of the argument taskUrl leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 33d9bb464353015aaaba84e27638ac9a3912795d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8226 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS find information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysApp/find. The manipulation of the argument accessKey/secretKey leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8225 | GNU Binutils DWARF Section dwarf.c process_debug_info memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8225</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNU Binutils 2.44 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function process_debug_info of the file binutils/dwarf.c of the component DWARF Section Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. Attacking locally is a requirement. The identifier of the patch is e51fdff7d2e538c0e5accdd65649ac68e6e0ddd4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5120 | Sandbox Escape Vulnerability in huggingface/smolagents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5120</link><description>A sandbox escape vulnerability was identified in huggingface/smolagents version 1.14.0, allowing attackers to bypass the restricted execution environment and achieve remote code execution (RCE). The vulnerability stems from the local_python_executor.py module, which inadequately restricts Python code execution despite employing static and dynamic checks. Attackers can exploit whitelisted modules and functions to execute arbitrary code, compromising the host system. This flaw undermines the core security boundary intended to isolate untrusted code, posing risks such as unauthorized code execution, data leakage, and potential integration-level compromise. The issue is resolved in version 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 07:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8224 | GNU Binutils BFD Library elf.c bfd_elf_get_str_section null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8224</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.44 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function bfd_elf_get_str_section of the file bfd/elf.c of the component BFD Library. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is db856d41004301b3a56438efd957ef5cabb91530. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8223 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 AdminTypeCustController.java cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8223</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. This affects an unknown part of the file AdminTypeCustController.java. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8104 | Memory Usage &amp;lt;= 3.98 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited Plugin Installation via wpmemory_install_plugin Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8104</link><description>The Memory Usage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.98. This is due to missing nonce validation in the wpmemory_install_plugin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to silently install one of the several whitelisted plugins via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8222 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 GoodsController.java cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8222</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file GoodsController.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8221 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 GoodsCustController.java goodsSearch cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8221</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. Affected by this vulnerability is the function goodsSearch of the file GoodsCustController.java. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8220 | Engeman Web Password Recovery Page RecoveryPass sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8220</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Engeman Web up to 12.0.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Login/RecoveryPass of the component Password Recovery Page. The manipulation of the argument LanguageCombobox leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54597 | LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.7.3 allows XSS via the q parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54597</link><description>LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.7.3 allows XSS via the q parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8219 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM HTTP POST Request tabdetail_moduleSave_dxkp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.4.7. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /crm/crmapi/erp/tabdetail_moduleSave_dxkp.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument getvaluestring leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.6.5.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor explains: "All SQL injection vectors were patched via parameterized queries and input sanitization in v8.6.5+. We strongly advise all customers to upgrade to the current version (v8.6.5.2), which includes this fix and additional security enhancements."</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6241 | CVE-2025-6241</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6241</link><description>LsiAgent.exe, a component of SysTrack from Lakeside Software, attempts to load several DLL files which are not present in the default installation. If a user-writable directory is present in the SYSTEM PATH environment variable, the user can write a malicious DLL to that directory with arbitrary code. This malicious DLL is executed in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM upon service start or restart, due to the Windows default dynamic-link library search order, resulting in local elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 02:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8211 | Roothub SystemConfigAdminController.java edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Roothub up to 2.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Edit of the file src/main/java/cn/roothub/web/admin/SystemConfigAdminController.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 21:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8210 | Yeelink Yeelight App com.yeelight.cherry AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yeelink Yeelight App up to 3.5.4 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.yeelight.cherry. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8207 | Canara ai1 Mobile Banking App com.canarabank.mobility AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Canara ai1 Mobile Banking App 3.6.23 on Android and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.canarabank.mobility. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8206 | Comodo Dragon IP DNS Leakage Detector cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8206</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. This affects an unknown part of the component IP DNS Leakage Detector. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8205 | Comodo Dragon IP DNS Leakage Detector cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8205</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component IP DNS Leakage Detector. The manipulation leads to cleartext transmission of sensitive information. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8204 | Comodo Dragon HSTS security check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8204</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HSTS Handler. The manipulation leads to security check for standard. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8203 | Jingmen Zeyou Large File Upload Control index.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8203</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Jingmen Zeyou Large File Upload Control up to 6.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.jsp. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8191 | macrozheng mall Swagger UI index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /swagger-ui/index.html of the component Swagger UI. The manipulation of the argument configUrl leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor deleted the GitHub issue for this vulnerability without any explanation. Afterwards the vendor was contacted early about this disclosure via email but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8190 | Campcodes Courier Management System print_pdets.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8190</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /print_pdets.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8189 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8189</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8188 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_staff.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit_staff.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8187 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_parcel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8186 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_branch.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit_branch.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8185 | 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System getbyid.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /getbyid.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8184 | D-Link DIR-513 HTTP POST Request formSetWanL2TPtriggers formSetWanL2TPcallback stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-513 up to 1.10 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetWanL2TPcallback of the file /goform/formSetWanL2TPtriggers of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8182 | Tenda AC18 Samba smb.conf weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8182</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /etc_ro/smb.conf of the component Samba. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5529 | Educenter &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5529</link><description>The Educenter theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Circle Counter Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6989 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.21.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Folder Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6989</link><description>The Kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary folder deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete_font() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.21.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary folders on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6991 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.21.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6991</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.21.0 via the 'TH_LatestPosts4` widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8181 | TOTOLINK N600R/X2000R FTP Service vsftpd.conf least privilege violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8181</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK N600R and X2000R 1.0.0.1. This affects an unknown part of the file vsftpd.conf of the component FTP Service. The manipulation leads to least privilege violation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6987 | Advanced iFrame &amp;lt;= 2025.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6987</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2025.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7501 | Wonder Slider Lite &amp;amp; Wonder Slider &amp;lt;= 14.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Dom-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7501</link><description>The Wonder Slider Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image title and description DOM in all versions up to, and including, 14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8097 | WoodMart - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Improper Input Validation Leading to Unauthenticated Cart Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8097</link><description>The WoodMart theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Input Validation in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.6. This is due to insufficient validation of the qty parameter in the woodmart_update_cart_item function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate cart quantities using fractional values, allowing them to obtain products for free by setting extremely small quantities (e.g., 0.00001) that round cart totals to $0.00, effectively bypassing payment requirements and allowing unauthorized acquisition of virtual or downloadable products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8180 | Tenda CH22 deleteUserName formdeleteUserName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8180</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. Affected by this issue is the function formdeleteUserName of the file /goform/deleteUserName. The manipulation of the argument old_account leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8198 | MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Unauthenticated Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8198</link><description>The MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to price manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.0. This is due to an insufficient check on quantity values when changing quantities in the cart. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add items to the cart and adjust the quantity to a fractional amount, causing the price to change based on the fractional amount. The vulnerability cannot be exploited if WooCommerce version 9.8.2+ is installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 05:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8179 | PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8179</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System 2.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 05:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6895 | MelaPress Login Security 2.1.0 - 2.1.1 - Authentication Bypass to Privilege Escalation via get_valid_user_based_on_token Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6895</link><description>The Melapress Login Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to missing authorization within the get_valid_user_based_on_token() function in versions 2.1.0 to 2.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers who know an arbitrary user meta value to bypass authentication checks and log in as that user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8178 | Tenda AC10 RequestsProcessLaid heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8178</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/RequestsProcessLaid. The manipulation of the argument device1D leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8177 | LibTIFF thumbnail.c setrow buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8177</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF up to 4.7.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setrow of the file tools/thumbnail.c. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The patch is named e8c9d6c616b19438695fd829e58ae4fde5bfbc22. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13507 | GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory &amp;lt;= 2.8.97 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13507</link><description>The GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the dist parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.97 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50184 | DbGate allows for File Traversal via file parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50184</link><description>DbGate is cross-platform database manager. In versions 6.4.3-premium-beta.5 and below, DbGate is vulnerable to a directory traversal flaw. The file parameter is not properly restricted to the intended uploads directory. As a result, the endpoint that lists files within the upload directory can be manipulated to access arbitrary files on the system. By supplying a crafted path to the file parameter, an attacker can read files outside the upload directory, potentially exposing sensitive system-level data. This is fixed in version 6.4.3-beta.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50185 | DbGate allows Unauthorized File Access via CSV Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50185</link><description>DbGate is cross-platform database manager. In versions 6.6.0 and below, DbGate allows unauthorized file access due to insufficient validation of file paths and types. A user with application-level access can retrieve data from arbitrary files on the system, regardless of their location or file type. The plugin fails to enforce proper checks on content type and file extension before reading a file. As a result, even sensitive files accessible only to the root user can be read through the application interface. There is currently no fix for this issue.






```
POST /runners/load-reader HTTP/1.1
Host: 
User-Agent: Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86_64; rv:138.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/138.0
Accept: */*
Accept-Language: en-US,en;q=0.5
Accept-Encoding: gzip, deflate, br
Referer: 
Content-Type: application/json
Authorization: Bearer 
Content-Length: 127
Origin: http://192.168.124.119:3000
Connection: keep-alive
Cookie: 
Priority: u=0
Cache-Control: max-age=0

{"functionName":"reader@dbgate-plugin-csv","props":{"fileName":"/etc\/shadow","limitRows":100}}

```



The request payload:
![Screenshot From 2025-05-31 22-54-49](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/28943ad7-14f8-432a-9836-cec5c3593c0a)


Lines of the file being returned:
![Screenshot From 2025-05-31 22-55-23](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/4fae4652-097d-4d39-9f7a-6ce39346ed1d)</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54366 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s deserialization of untrusted data leads to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54366</link><description>FreeScout is a lightweight free open source help desk and shared inbox built with PHP (Laravel framework). In versions 1.8.185 and below, there is a critical deserialization vulnerability in the /conversation/ajax endpoint that allows authenticated users with knowledge of the APP_KEY to achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability occurs when the application processes the attachments_all and attachments POST parameters through the insecure Helper::decrypt() function, which performs unsafe deserialization of user-controlled data without proper validation. This flaw enables attackers to create arbitrary objects and manipulate their properties, leading to complete compromise of the web application. This is fixed in version 1.8.186.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54378 | HAX CMS Backend Lacks Comprehensive Authorization Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54378</link><description>HAX CMS allows you to manage your microsite universe with PHP or NodeJs backends. In versions 11.0.13 and below of haxcms-nodejs and versions 11.0.8 and below of haxcms-php, API endpoints do not perform authorization checks when interacting with a resource. Both the JS and PHP versions of the CMS do not verify that a user has permission to interact with a resource before performing a given operation. The API endpoints within the HAX CMS application check if a user is authenticated, but don't check for authorization before performing an operation. This is fixed in versions 11.0.14 of haxcms-nodejs and 11.0.9 of haxcms-php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54380 | Opencast still publishes global system account credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54380</link><description>Opencast is a free, open-source platform to support the management of educational audio and video content. Prior to version 17.6, Opencast would incorrectly send the hashed global system account credentials (ie: org.opencastproject.security.digest.user and org.opencastproject.security.digest.pass) when attempting to fetch mediapackage elements included in a mediapackage XML file. A previous CVE prevented many cases where the credentials were inappropriately sent, but not all. Anyone with ingest permissions could cause Opencast to send its hashed global system account credentials to a url of their choosing. This issue is fixed in Opencast 17.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54385 | XWiki Platform&amp;#x27;s searchDocuments API allows for SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54385</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions between 17.0.0-rc1 to 17.2.2 and versions 16.10.5 and below, it's possible to execute any SQL query in Oracle by using the function like DBMS_XMLGEN or DBMS_XMLQUERY. The XWiki#searchDocuments APIs pass queries directly to Hibernate without sanitization. Even when these APIs enforce a specific SELECT clause, attackers can still inject malicious code through HQL's native function support in other parts of the query (such as the WHERE clause). This is fixed in versions 16.10.6 and 17.3.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54412 | skops&amp;#x27; Inconsistent Trusted Type Validation Enables Hidden `operator` Methods Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54412</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. Versions 0.11.0 and below contain a inconsistency in the OperatorFuncNode which can be exploited to hide the execution of untrusted operator methods. This can then be used in a code reuse attack to invoke seemingly safe functions and escalate to arbitrary code execution with minimal and misleading trusted types. This is fixed in version 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54413 | skops&amp;#x27; MethodNode can access unexpected object fields through dot notation, leading to arbitrary code execution at load time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54413</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. Versions 0.11.0 and below contain an inconsistency in MethodNode, which can be exploited to access unexpected object fields through dot notation. This can be used to achieve arbitrary code execution at load time. While this issue may seem similar to GHSA-m7f4-hrc6-fwg3, it is actually more severe, as it relies on fewer assumptions about trusted types. This is fixed in version 12.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54414 | Anubis accepts crafted redirect URLs in pass-challenge &amp;#x27;Try Again&amp;#x27; buttons</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54414</link><description>Anubis is a Web AI Firewall Utility that weighs the soul of users' connections using one or more challenges in order to protect upstream resources from scraper bots. In versions 1.21.2 and below, attackers can craft malicious pass-challenge pages that cause a user to execute arbitrary JavaScript code or trigger other nonstandard schemes. An incomplete version of this fix was tagged at 1.21.2 and then the release process was aborted upon final testing. To work around this issue: block any requests to the /.within.website/x/cmd/anubis/api/pass-challenge route with the ?redir= parameter set to anything that doesn't start with the URL scheme http, https, or no scheme (local path redirect). This was fixed in version 1.21.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54415 | dag-factory&amp;#x27;s CI/CD Workflow Allows for Repository Takeover and Secret Exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54415</link><description>dag-factory is a library for Apache Airflow® to construct DAGs declaratively via configuration files. In versions 0.23.0a8 and below, a high-severity vulnerability has been identified in the cicd.yml workflow within the astronomer/dag-factory GitHub repository. The workflow, specifically when triggered by pull_request_target, is susceptible to exploitation, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the GitHub Actions runner environment. This misconfiguration enables an attacker to establish a reverse shell, exfiltrate sensitive secrets, including the highly-privileged GITHUB_TOKEN, and ultimately gain full control over the repository. This is fixed in version 0.23.0a9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54416 | tj-actions/branch-names Contains Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54416</link><description>tj-actions/branch-names is a Github actions repository that contains workflows to retrieve branch or tag names with support for all events. In versions 8.2.1 and below, a critical vulnerability has been identified in the tj-actions/branch-names' GitHub Action workflow which allows arbitrary command execution in downstream workflows. This issue arises due to inconsistent input sanitization and unescaped output, enabling malicious actors to exploit specially crafted branch names or tags. While internal sanitization mechanisms have been implemented, the action outputs remain vulnerable, exposing consuming workflows to significant security risks. This is fixed in version 9.0.0</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8103 | WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher &amp;lt;= 2.8.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Deactivation via handle_feedback_submission Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8103</link><description>The WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This is due to missing nonce validation in the handle_feedback_submission() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate the plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8176 | LibTIFF tiffmedian.c get_histogram use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF up to 4.7.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_histogram of the file tools/tiffmedian.c. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as fe10872e53efba9cc36c66ac4ab3b41a839d5172. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8175 | D-Link DI-8400 jhttpd usb_paswd.asp null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8400 16.07.26A1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file usb_paswd.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument share_enable leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 03:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8174 | code-projects Voting System candidates_add.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8174</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Voting System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/candidates_add.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 01:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>