<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:31:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2022-48684 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.1.1. Template injection was seen in the search template. The search template uses jinja templat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48684</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint before 7.1.1. Template injection was seen in the search template. The search template uses jinja templating for generating dynamic data. This could be abused to achieve code execution. Any user with access to create a search template can leverage this to execute code as the loginspect user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48685 | An issue was discovered in Logpoint 7.1 before 7.1.2. The daily executed cron file clean_secbi_old_logs is writable by all users and is exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48685</link><description>An issue was discovered in Logpoint 7.1 before 7.1.2. The daily executed cron file clean_secbi_old_logs is writable by all users and is executed as root, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4293 | PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4293</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file appointment-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262225 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:39:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33851 | phpecc, as used in paragonie/phpecc before 2.0.1, has a branch-based timing leak in Point addition. (This is related to phpecc/phpecc on Git...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33851</link><description>phpecc, as used in paragonie/phpecc before 2.0.1, has a branch-based timing leak in Point addition. (This is related to phpecc/phpecc on GitHub, and the Matyas Danter ECC library.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4292 | Contemporary Controls BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B Device-Communication-Control Service denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4292</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Contemporary Controls BASrouter BACnet BASRT-B 2.7.2. Affected is an unknown function of the component Device-Communication-Control Service. The manipulation with the input 55ff0500370015f30104025506110afb7519035d0841e4bece257b6acfc71f leads to denial of service. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262224. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 20:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4291 | Tenda A301 setBlackRule formAddMacfilterRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4291</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda A301 15.13.08.12_multi_TDE01. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formAddMacfilterRule of the file /goform/setBlackRule. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262223. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4257 | BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System deleteStudy.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4257</link><description>A vulnerability was found in BlueNet Technology Clinical Browsing System 1.2.1. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /xds/deleteStudy.php. The manipulation of the argument documentUniqueId leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262149 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4256 | Techkshetra Info Solutions Savsoft Quiz Category Page editCategory cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4256</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Techkshetra Info Solutions Savsoft Quiz 6.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /public/index.php/Qbank/editCategory of the component Category Page. The manipulation of the argument category_name with the input &gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262148. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4255 | Ruijie RG-UAC gre_edit_commit.php os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4255</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Ruijie RG-UAC up to 20240419. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /view/network Config/GRE/gre_edit_commit.php. The manipulation of the argument name leads to os command injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262145 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4252 | Tenda i22 formSetUrlFilterRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4252</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda i22 1.0.0.3(4687). This affects the function formSetUrlFilterRule. The manipulation of the argument groupIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262143. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 13:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4251 | Tenda i21 DhcpSetSe fromDhcpSetSer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4251</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656). It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function fromDhcpSetSer of the file /goform/DhcpSetSe. The manipulation of the argument dhcpStartIp/dhcpEndIp/dhcpGw/dhcpMask/dhcpLeaseTime/dhcpDns1/dhcpDns2 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262142 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 13:18:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25048 | IBM MQ code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25048</link><description>IBM MQ Appliance 9.3 CD and LTS are vulnerable to a heap-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A remote authenticated attacker could overflow a buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system or cause the server to crash.  IBM X-Force ID:  283137.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4250 | Tenda i21 wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4250</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656). It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262141 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:28:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4249 | Tenda i21 wifiSSIDget formwrlSSIDget stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4249</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656). It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formwrlSSIDget of the file /goform/wifiSSIDget. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262140. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 11:38:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4248 | Tenda i21 formQosManage_user stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4248</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656) and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formQosManage_user. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262139. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 10:43:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3309 | The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Widget's attributes in all v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3309</link><description>The Qi Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Countdown Widget's attributes in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4247 | Tenda i21 formQosManage_auto stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4247</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656) and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formQosManage_auto. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. VDB-262138 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 09:40:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-1000 | cyanomiko dcnnt-py Notification notifications.py main command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-1000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in cyanomiko dcnnt-py up to 0.9.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function main of the file dcnnt/plugins/notifications.py of the component Notification Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 0.9.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as b4021d784a97e25151a5353aa763a741e9a148f5. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-262230 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 09:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3342 | The Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'events' attribute of the 'mp-time...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3342</link><description>The Timetable and Event Schedule by MotoPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'events' attribute of the 'mp-timetable' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.11 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 08:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4246 | Tenda i21 formQosManageDouble_auto stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4246</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656). This affects the function formQosManageDouble_auto. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The identifier VDB-262137 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 08:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4245 | Tenda i21 formQosManageDouble_user stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4245</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda i21 1.0.0.14(4656). Affected by this issue is the function formQosManageDouble_user. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262136. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3034 | The BackUpWordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.13 via the hmbkp_direc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3034</link><description>The BackUpWordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Directory Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 3.13 via the hmbkp_directory_browse parameter. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to traverse directories outside of the context in which the plugin should allow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 04:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2258 | The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2258</link><description>The Form Maker by 10Web – Mobile-Friendly Drag &amp; Drop Contact Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via a user's display name autofilled into forms in all versions up to, and including, 1.15.24 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 03:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2838 | The WPC Composite Products for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wooco_components[0][na...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2838</link><description>The WPC Composite Products for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'wooco_components[0][name]' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping and missing authorization on the ajax_save_components function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 03:43:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2859 | By default, SANnav OVA is shipped with root user login enabled (CVE-2024-2859)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2859</link><description>By default, SANnav OVA is shipped with root user login enabled.  While protected by a password, access to root could expose SANnav to a remote attacker should they gain access to the root account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28322 | SQL Injection vulnerability in /event-management-master/backend/register.php in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0 allows attackers to run ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28322</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in /event-management-master/backend/register.php in PuneethReddyHC Event Management 1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary SQL commands via the event_id parameter in a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 22:17:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31551 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in lib/admin/image.admin.php in cmseasy v7.7.7.9 20240105 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31551</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in lib/admin/image.admin.php in cmseasy v7.7.7.9 20240105 allows attackers to delete arbitrary files via crafted GET request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:57:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31741 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MiniCMS v.1.11 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted string in the URL after logi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31741</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in MiniCMS v.1.11 allows a remote attacker to run arbitrary code via crafted string in the URL after login.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31828 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Lavalite CMS v.10.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31828</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Lavalite CMS v.10.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via a crafted payload to the URL.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4243 | Tenda W9 wifiSSIDset formwrlSSIDset stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4243</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). Affected is the function formwrlSSIDset of the file /goform/wifiSSIDset. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262134 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4244 | Tenda W9 DhcpSetSer fromDhcpSetSer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4244</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromDhcpSetSer of the file /goform/DhcpSetSer. The manipulation of the argument dhcpStartIp/dhcpEndIp/dhcpGw/dhcpMask/dhcpLeaseTime/dhcpDns1/dhcpDns2 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262135. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3051 | Z/IP Gateway Device Reset Locally Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3051</link><description>Malformed Device Reset Locally command classes can be sent to temporarily deny service to an end device. Any frames sent by the end device will not be acknowledged by the gateway during this time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3052 | Z/IP Gateway S2 Nonce Get Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3052</link><description>Malformed S2 Nonce Get command classes can be sent to crash the gateway. A hard reset is required to recover the gateway.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30804 | An issue discovered in the DeviceIoControl component in ASUS Fan_Xpert before v.10013 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30804</link><description>An issue discovered in the DeviceIoControl component in ASUS Fan_Xpert before v.10013 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via crafted IOCTL requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32883 | MCUboot Injection attack of unprotected TLV values</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32883</link><description>MCUboot is a secure bootloader for 32-bits microcontrollers. MCUboot uses a TLV (tag-length-value) structure to represent the meta data associated with an image.  The TLVs themselves are divided into two sections, a protected and an unprotected section. The protected TLV entries are included as part of the image signature to avoid tampering. However, the code does not distinguish which TLV entries should be protected or not, so it is possible for an attacker to add unprotected TLV entries that should be protected. Currently, the primary protected TLV entries should be the dependency indication, and the boot record. An injected dependency value would primarily result in an otherwise acceptable image being rejected. A boot record injection could allow fields in a later attestation record to include data not intended, which could cause an image to appear to have properties that it should not have. As a workaround, disable the boot record functionality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32887 | Reflected XSS in sidekiq</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32887</link><description>Sidekiq is simple, efficient background processing for Ruby. Sidekiq is reflected XSS vulnerability. The value of substr parameter is reflected in the response without any encoding, allowing an attacker to inject Javascript code into the response of the application.  An attacker could exploit it to target users of the Sidekiq Web UI. Moreover, if other applications are deployed on the same domain or website as Sidekiq, users of those applications could also be affected, leading to a broader scope of compromise. Potentially compromising their accounts, forcing the users to perform sensitive actions, stealing sensitive data, performing CORS attacks, defacement of the web application, etc. This issue has been patched in version 7.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31601 | An issue in Beijing Panabit Network Software Co., Ltd Panalog big data analysis platform v. 20240323 and before allows attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31601</link><description>An issue in Beijing Panabit Network Software Co., Ltd Panalog big data analysis platform v. 20240323 and before allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via the exportpdf.php component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4241 | Tenda W9 formQosManageDouble_auto stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4241</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formQosManageDouble_auto. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262132. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4242 | Tenda W9 wifiSSIDget formwrlSSIDget stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4242</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formwrlSSIDget of the file /goform/wifiSSIDget. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262133 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32881 | Unauthorized access to GET/SET of Slack Bot Tokens in Danswer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32881</link><description>Danswer is the AI Assistant connected to company's docs, apps, and people. Danswer is vulnerable to unauthorized access to GET/SET of Slack Bot Tokens. Anyone with network access can steal slack bot tokens and set them. This implies full compromise of the customer's slack bot, leading to internal Slack access. This issue was patched in version 3.63.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:51:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31502 | An issue in Insurance Management System v.1.0.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted POST request to /ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31502</link><description>An issue in Insurance Management System v.1.0.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via a crafted POST request to /admin/core/new_staff.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32878 |  Use of Uninitialized Variable Vulnerability in llama.cpp</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32878</link><description>Llama.cpp is LLM inference in C/C++. There is a use of uninitialized heap variable vulnerability in gguf_init_from_file, the code will free this uninitialized variable later. In a simple POC, it will directly cause a crash. If the file is carefully constructed, it may be possible to control this uninitialized value and cause arbitrary address free problems. This may further lead to be exploited. Causes llama.cpp to crash (DoS) and may even lead to arbitrary code execution (RCE). This vulnerability has been patched in commit b2740.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4239 | Tenda AX1806 SetRebootTimer formSetRebootTimer stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4239</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AX1806 1.0.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function formSetRebootTimer of the file /goform/SetRebootTimer. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262130 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4240 | Tenda W9 formQosManageDouble_user stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4240</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda W9 1.0.0.7(4456). It has been classified as critical. This affects the function formQosManageDouble_user. The manipulation of the argument ssidIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262131. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4238 | Tenda AX1806 SetOnlineDevName formSetDeviceName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4238</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AX1806 1.0.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function formSetDeviceName of the file /goform/SetOnlineDevName. The manipulation of the argument devName leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-262129 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48611 | A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.12.4 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48611</link><description>A logic issue was addressed with improved checks. This issue is fixed in iTunes 12.12.4 for Windows. A local attacker may be able to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25343 | Tenda N300 F3 router vulnerability allows users to bypass intended security policy and create weak passwords.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25343</link><description>Tenda N300 F3 router vulnerability allows users to bypass intended security policy and create weak passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26603 | JumpCloud Agent before 1.178.0 Creates a Temporary File in a Directory with Insecure Permissions. This allows privilege escalation to SYSTEM...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26603</link><description>JumpCloud Agent before 1.178.0 Creates a Temporary File in a Directory with Insecure Permissions. This allows privilege escalation to SYSTEM via a repair action in the installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28326 | Incorrect Access Control in Asus RT-N12+ B1 routers allows local attackers to obtain root terminal access via the the UART interface.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28326</link><description>Incorrect Access Control in Asus RT-N12+ B1 routers allows local attackers to obtain root terminal access via the the UART interface.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28327 | Asus RT-N12+ B1 router stores user passwords in plaintext, which could allow local attackers to obtain unauthorized access and modify router...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28327</link><description>Asus RT-N12+ B1 router stores user passwords in plaintext, which could allow local attackers to obtain unauthorized access and modify router settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4237 | Tenda AX1806 execCommand R7WebsSecurityHandler stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4237</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AX1806 1.0.0.1. Affected is the function R7WebsSecurityHandler of the file /goform/execCommand. The manipulation of the argument password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262128. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:10:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28325 | Asus RT-N12+ B1 router stores credentials in cleartext, which could allow local attackers to obtain unauthorized access and modify router se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28325</link><description>Asus RT-N12+ B1 router stores credentials in cleartext, which could allow local attackers to obtain unauthorized access and modify router settings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:45:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32884 | gix-transport indirect code execution via malicious username</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32884</link><description>gitoxide is a pure Rust implementation of Git. `gix-transport` does not check the username part of a URL for text that the external `ssh` program would interpret as an option. A specially crafted clone URL can smuggle options to SSH. The possibilities are syntactically limited, but if a malicious clone URL is used by an application whose current working directory contains a malicious file, arbitrary code execution occurs. This is related to the patched vulnerability GHSA-rrjw-j4m2-mf34, but appears less severe due to a greater attack complexity. This issue has been patched in versions 0.35.0, 0.42.0 and 0.62.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 18:24:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32880 | pyLoad allows upload to arbitrary folder lead to RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32880</link><description>pyload is an open-source Download Manager written in pure Python. An authenticated user can change the download folder and upload a crafted template to the specified folder lead to remote code execution. There is no fix available at the time of publication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33342 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in SetPlcNetworkpwd function ofprog.cgi, which allows remote attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33342</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in SetPlcNetworkpwd function ofprog.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33343 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in ChgSambaUserSettings function of prog.cgi, which allows remote attackers ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33343</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in ChgSambaUserSettings function of prog.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33344 | D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in ftext function ofupload_firmware.cgi, which allows remote attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33344</link><description>D-Link DIR-822+ V1.0.5 was found to contain a command injection in ftext function ofupload_firmware.cgi, which allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary commands via shell.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4235 | Netgear DG834Gv5 Web Management Interface cleartext storage</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4235</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Netgear DG834Gv5 1.6.01.34. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Web Management Interface. The manipulation leads to cleartext storage of sensitive information. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-262126 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4236 | Tenda AX1803 SetDDNSCfg formSetSysToolDDNS stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4236</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda AX1803 1.0.0.1. This issue affects the function formSetSysToolDDNS of the file /goform/SetDDNSCfg. The manipulation of the argument serverName/ddnsUser/ddnsPwd/ddnsDomain leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-262127. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:39:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32730 | Missing authorization check in SAP Enable Now Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32730</link><description>SAP Enable Now Manager does not perform necessary authorization checks for an authenticated user, resulting in escalation of privileges. On successful exploitation, the attacker with the role 'Learner' could gain access to other user's data in manager which will lead to a high impact to the confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42955 | Claris International has successfully resolved an issue of potentially exposing password information to front-end websites when signed in to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42955</link><description>Claris International has successfully resolved an issue of potentially exposing password information to front-end websites when signed in to the Admin Console with an administrator role.  This issue has been fixed in FileMaker Server 20.3.1 by eliminating the send of Admin Role passwords in the Node.js socket.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27790 | Claris International has resolved an issue of potentially allowing unauthorized access to records stored in databases hosted on FileMaker Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27790</link><description>Claris International has resolved an issue of potentially allowing unauthorized access to records stored in databases hosted on FileMaker Server. This issue has been fixed in FileMaker Server 20.3.2 by validating transactions before replying to client requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32476 | Denial of Service via malicious jqPathExpressions in ignoreDifferences</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32476</link><description>Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. There is a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability via OOM using jq in ignoreDifferences. This vulnerability has been patched in version(s) 2.10.7, 2.9.12 and 2.8.16.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33263 | QuickJS commit 3b45d15 was discovered to contain an Assertion Failure via JS_FreeRuntime(JSRuntime *) at quickjs.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33263</link><description>QuickJS commit 3b45d15 was discovered to contain an Assertion Failure via JS_FreeRuntime(JSRuntime *) at quickjs.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:27:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41290 | QuFirewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41290</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect QuFirewall. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuFirewall 2.4.1 ( 2024/02/01 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41291 | QuFirewall</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41291</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect QuFirewall. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
QuFirewall 2.4.1 ( 2024/02/01 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47222 | Media Streaming add-on</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47222</link><description>An exposure of sensitive information vulnerability has been reported to affect Media Streaming add-on. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
Media Streaming add-on  500.1.1.5 ( 2024/01/22 ) and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50361 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50361</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50362 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50362</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50363 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50363</link><description>An incorrect authorization vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated users to bypass intended access restrictions via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50364 | QTS, QuTS hero</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50364</link><description>A buffer copy without checking size of input vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow authenticated administrators to execute code via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.6.2722 build 20240402 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.6.2734 build 20240414 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51364 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51364</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51365 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51365</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to read the contents of unexpected files and expose sensitive data via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.4.2596 build 20231128 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21905 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21905</link><description>An integer overflow or wraparound vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to compromise the security of the system via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-27124 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-27124</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28328 | CSV Injection vulnerability in the Asus RT-N12+ router allows administrator users to inject arbitrary commands or formulas in the client nam...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28328</link><description>CSV Injection vulnerability in the Asus RT-N12+ router allows administrator users to inject arbitrary commands or formulas in the client name parameter which can be triggered and executed in a different user session upon exporting to CSV format.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32764 | myQNAPcloud Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32764</link><description>A missing authentication for critical function vulnerability has been reported to affect myQNAPcloud Link. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users with the privilege level of some functionality via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following version:
myQNAPcloud Link 2.4.51 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32766 | QTS, QuTS hero, QuTScloud</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32766</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect several QNAP operating system versions. If exploited, the vulnerability could allow users to execute commands via a network.

We have already fixed the vulnerability in the following versions:
QTS 5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QTS 4.5.4.2627 build 20231225 and later
QuTS hero h5.1.3.2578 build 20231110 and later
QuTS hero h4.5.4.2626 build 20231225 and later
QuTScloud c5.1.5.2651 and later</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33255 | Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain an Assertion Failure via ECMA_STRING_IS_REF_EQUALS_TO_ONE (string_p) in ecma_free_strin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33255</link><description>Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain an Assertion Failure via ECMA_STRING_IS_REF_EQUALS_TO_ONE (string_p) in ecma_free_string_list.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33258 | Jerryscript commit ff9ff8f was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component vm_loop at jerry-core/vm/vm.c.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33258</link><description>Jerryscript commit ff9ff8f was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component vm_loop at jerry-core/vm/vm.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33259 | Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component scanner_seek at jerry-core/parser/js/js-scan...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33259</link><description>Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component scanner_seek at jerry-core/parser/js/js-scanner-util.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:57:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51794 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/af_stere...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51794</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Ffmpeg v.N113007-g8d24a28d06 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the libavfilter/af_stereowiden.c:120:69.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33260 | Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component parser_parse_class at jerry-core/parser/js/j...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33260</link><description>Jerryscript commit cefd391 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component parser_parse_class at jerry-core/parser/js/js-parser-expr.c</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-40975 | WordPress Post Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-40975</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Aazztech Post Slider.This issue affects Post Slider: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3076 | MM-email2image &amp;lt;= 0.2.5 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3076</link><description>The MM-email2image WordPress plugin through 0.2.5 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33688 | WordPress Teluro theme &amp;lt;= 1.0.31 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33688</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Extend Themes Teluro.This issue affects Teluro: from n/a through 1.0.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33689 | WordPress Radio Station plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.7 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33689</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Tony Zeoli, Tony Hayes Radio Station.This issue affects Radio Station: from n/a through 2.5.7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33690 | WordPress Financio theme &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33690</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jegstudio Financio.This issue affects Financio: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33691 | WordPress Popup Builder by OptinMonster plugin &amp;lt;= 2.15.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Notice Dismissal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33691</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in OptinMonster Popup Builder Team OptinMonster.This issue affects OptinMonster: from n/a through 2.15.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4234 | WordPress Filterable Portfolio plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4234</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sayful Islam Filterable Portfolio allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Filterable Portfolio: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33692 | WordPress Smart Recent Posts Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33692</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Satrya Smart Recent Posts Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Smart Recent Posts Widget: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33693 | WordPress Meks Smart Social Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33693</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Meks Meks Smart Social Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Meks Smart Social Widget: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33694 | WordPress Meks ThemeForest Smart Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33694</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Meks Meks ThemeForest Smart Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Meks ThemeForest Smart Widget: from n/a through 1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33695 | WordPress Fan Page Widget by ThemeNcode plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ThemeNcode Fan Page Widget by ThemeNcode allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Fan Page Widget by ThemeNcode: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:57:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33696 | WordPress WordPress Ad Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 2.20.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Broadstreet XPRESS WordPress Ad Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Ad Widget: from n/a through 2.20.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33697 | WordPress CF7 File Download plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rimes Gold CF7 File Download – File Download for CF7 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects CF7 File Download – File Download for CF7: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52646 | aio: fix mremap after fork null-deref</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52646</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

aio: fix mremap after fork null-deref

Commit e4a0d3e720e7 ("aio: Make it possible to remap aio ring") introduced
a null-deref if mremap is called on an old aio mapping after fork as
mm-&gt;ioctx_table will be set to NULL.

[jmoyer@redhat.com: fix 80 column issue]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 12:41:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32822 | WordPress Reviews Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32822</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in impleCode Reviews Plus.This issue affects Reviews Plus: from n/a through 1.3.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:32:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32826 | WordPress VK Block Patterns plugin &amp;lt;= 1.31.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32826</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Vektor,Inc. VK Block Patterns.This issue affects VK Block Patterns: from n/a through 1.31.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32828 | WordPress Table Rate Shipping Method for WooCommerce by Flexible Shipping plugin &amp;lt;= 4.24.15 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32828</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Octolize Flexible Shipping.This issue affects Flexible Shipping: from n/a through 4.24.15.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:12:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32829 | WordPress Data Tables Generator by Supsystic plugin &amp;lt;= 1.10.31 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32829</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Supsystic Data Tables Generator by Supsystic.This issue affects Data Tables Generator by Supsystic: from n/a through 1.10.31.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32957 | WordPress Page Builder: Live Composer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.38 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32957</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Live Composer Team Page Builder: Live Composer.This issue affects Page Builder: Live Composer: from n/a through 1.5.38.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:12:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33677 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.70 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33677</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Renzo Johnson Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp.This issue affects Contact Form 7 Extension For Mailchimp: from n/a through 0.5.70.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33678 | WordPress ClickCease Click Fraud Protection plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33678</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ClickCease ClickCease Click Fraud Protection.This issue affects ClickCease Click Fraud Protection: from n/a through 3.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33679 | WordPress FameTheme Demo Importer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33679</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in FameThemes FameTheme Demo Importer.This issue affects FameTheme Demo Importer: from n/a through 1.1.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33680 | WordPress MainWP Child Reports plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33680</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in MainWP MainWP Child Reports.This issue affects MainWP Child Reports: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33682 | WordPress WP GDPR Compliance  plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.23 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33682</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cookie Information A/S WP GDPR Compliance.This issue affects WP GDPR Compliance: from n/a through 2.0.23.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33683 | WordPress Hide Dashboard Notifications plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33683</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in WP Republic Hide Dashboard Notifications.This issue affects Hide Dashboard Notifications: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:46:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0740 | Eclipse Target Management &amp;lt;= 4.5.500 Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0740</link><description>Eclipse Target Management: Terminal and Remote System Explorer (RSE) version &lt;= 4.5.400 has a remote code execution vulnerability that does not require authentication. 





The fixed version is included in Eclipse IDE 2024-03</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 09:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3682 | The WP STAGING and WP STAGING Pro plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3682</link><description>The WP STAGING and WP STAGING Pro plugins for WordPress are vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in versions up to, and including, 3.4.3, and versions up to, and including, 5.4.3, respectively, via the ajaxSendReport function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from a log file, including system information and (in the Pro version) license keys. Successful exploitation requires an administrator to have used the 'Contact Us' functionality along with the "Enable this option to automatically submit the log files." option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 09:30:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1789 | The WP SMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search' parameter in versions 1.2 to 1.2.6 due to insufficient esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1789</link><description>The WP SMTP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'search' parameter in versions 1.2 to 1.2.6 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22091 | Excessive resource consumption due to lack to request path size limits</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22091</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.10, 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.2 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.11 fail to limit the size of a request path that includes user inputs which allows an attacker to cause excessive resource consumption, possibly leading to a DoS via sending large request paths</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32046 | Detailed error discloses full file path with dev mode off</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32046</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.6.x &lt;= 9.6.0, 9.5.x &lt;= 9.5.2, 9.4.x &lt;= 9.4.4 and 8.1.x &lt;= 8.1.11 fail to remove detailed error messages in API requests even if the developer mode is off which allows an attacker to get information about the server such as the full path were files are stored</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3962 | The Product Addons &amp; Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3962</link><description>The Product Addons &amp; Fields for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ppom_upload_file function in all versions up to, and including, 32.0.18. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Successful exploitation requires the PPOM Pro plugin to be installed along with a WooCommerce product that contains a file upload field to retrieve the correct nonce.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4182 | Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.5, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to handle JSON parsing errors in custom stat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4182</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.5, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to handle JSON parsing errors in custom status values, which allows an authenticated attacker to crash other users' web clients via a malformed custom status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4183 | Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.12, 9.6.x before 9.6.1, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.5 fail to limit the number of active sessi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4183</link><description>Mattermost versions 8.1.x before 8.1.12, 9.6.x before 9.6.1, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, 9.4.x before 9.4.5 fail to limit the number of active sessions, which allows an authenticated attacker to crash the server via repeated requests to the getSessions API after flooding the sessions table.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4195 | Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to fully validate role changes, which allows an attacker authent...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4195</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to fully validate role changes, which allows an attacker authenticated as a team admin to promote guests to team admins via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4198 | Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to fully validate role changes which allows an attacker authenti...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4198</link><description>Mattermost versions 9.6.0, 9.5.x before 9.5.3, and 8.1.x before 8.1.12 fail to fully validate role changes which allows an attacker authenticated as team admin to demote users to guest via crafted HTTP requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 08:40:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6116 | Remote Code Execution without authentication using stack overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6116</link><description>Team ENVY, a Security Research TEAM has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the camera. An attacker could inject malicious into http request packets to execute arbitrary code. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2920 | The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.3 du...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2920</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.9.3 due to the plugin uploading user supplied files to a publicly accessible directory in wp-content without any restrictions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view files uploaded by other users which may contain sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3678 | The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3678</link><description>The Blog2Social: Social Media Auto Post &amp; Scheduler plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.4.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to view limited information from password protected posts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3890 | The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Calendly widget in all versions up ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3890</link><description>The Happy Addons for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Calendly widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.10.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6096 | using a inappropriate encryption logic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6096</link><description>Vladimir Kononovich, a Security Researcher has found a flaw that using a inappropriate encryption logic on the DVR. firmware encryption is broken and allows to decrypt. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33598 | WordPress Annual Archive plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33598</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Twinpictures Annual Archive allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Annual Archive: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33639 | WordPress PopupAlly plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33639</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AccessAlly PopupAlly allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PopupAlly: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33642 | WordPress Advanced Post List plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.6.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33642</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in EkoJR Advanced Post List allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Advanced Post List: from n/a through 0.5.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6095 | Remote Code Execution without authentication using memory overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6095</link><description>Vladimir Kononovich, a Security Researcher has found a flaw that allows for a remote code execution on the DVR. An attacker could inject malicious HTTP headers into request packets to execute arbitrary code. The manufacturer has released patch firmware for the flaw, please refer to the manufacturer's report for details and workarounds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33638 | WordPress Smart Maintenance Mode plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33638</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Brijesh Kothari Smart Maintenance Mode.This issue affects Smart Maintenance Mode: from n/a through 1.4.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33650 | WordPress Serious Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33650</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Cryout Creations Serious Slider.This issue affects Serious Slider: from n/a through 1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33651 | WordPress MF Gig Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33651</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Matthew Fries MF Gig Calendar.This issue affects MF Gig Calendar : from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:25:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4056 | Denial of service condition in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4056</link><description>Denial of service condition in M-Files Server in versions before 24.4.13592.4 and after 23.11 (excluding 24.2 LTS) allows unauthenticated user to consume computing resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:24:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0905 | Fancy Product Designer &amp;lt; 6.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0905</link><description>The Fancy Product Designer WordPress plugin before 6.1.8 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against unauthenticated and admin-level users</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2159 | Sassy Social Share &amp;lt; 3.3.61 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2159</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin  WordPress plugin before 3.3.61 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2310 | WP Google Review Slider &amp;lt; 13.6 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2310</link><description>The WP Google Review Slider WordPress plugin before 13.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2429 | Salon booking system &amp;lt;= 9.6.5 - Settings Update via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2429</link><description>The Salon booking system WordPress plugin through 9.6.5 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2439 | Salon booking system &amp;lt;= 9.6.5 - Editor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2439</link><description>The Salon booking system WordPress plugin through 9.6.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as Editor to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2603 | Salon booking system &amp;lt;= 9.6.5 - Editor+ Stored XSS via Email Settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2603</link><description>The Salon booking system WordPress plugin through 9.6.5 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin (or editor depending on Salon booking system WordPress plugin through 9.6.5 configuration) to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2837 | WP Chat App &amp;lt; 3.6.4 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2837</link><description>The WP Chat App WordPress plugin before 3.6.4 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admins to perform Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when unfiltered_html is disallowed</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2908 | Call Now Button &amp;lt; 1.4.7 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2908</link><description>The Call Now Button  WordPress plugin before 1.4.7 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3048 | Bannerlid &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3048</link><description>The Bannerlid WordPress plugin through 1.1.0 does not escape generated URLs before outputting them in attributes, leading to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as administrators</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3058 | ENL Newsletter &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Stored XSS via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3058</link><description>The ENL Newsletter WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not have CSRF check in some places, and is missing sanitisation as well as escaping, which could allow attackers to make logged in admin add Stored XSS payloads via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3059 | ENL Newsletter &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Campaign Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3059</link><description>The ENL Newsletter WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not have CSRF checks in some places, which could allow attackers to make logged in admins delete arbitrary Campaigns via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3060 | ENL Newsletter &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3060</link><description>The ENL Newsletter WordPress plugin through 1.0.1 does not sanitize and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, allowing admin+ to perform SQL injection attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3075 | MM-email2image &amp;lt;= 0.2.5 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3075</link><description>The MM-email2image WordPress plugin through 0.2.5 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3188 | Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt; 7.1.0 - Contributor+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3188</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate WordPress plugin before 7.1.0 does not validate and escape some of its shortcode attributes before outputting them back in a page/post where the shortcode is embed, which could allow users with the contributor role and above to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32406 | Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32406</link><description>Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Batch-Issue Exam Tickets function.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 04:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22632 | Setor Informatica Sistema Inteligente para Laboratorios (S.I.L.) 388 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22632</link><description>Setor Informatica Sistema Inteligente para Laboratorios (S.I.L.) 388 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the hmsg parameter. This vulnerability is triggered via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 03:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22633 | Setor Informatica Sistema Inteligente para Laboratorios (S.I.L.) 388 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22633</link><description>Setor Informatica Sistema Inteligente para Laboratorios (S.I.L.) 388 was discovered to contain a remote code execution (RCE) vulnerability via the hprinter parameter. This vulnerability is triggered via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 03:52:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32404 | Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32404</link><description>Server-Side Template Injection (SSTI) vulnerability in inducer relate before v.2024.1, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the Markup Sandbox feature.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 03:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3154 | Cri-o: arbitrary command injection via pod annotation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3154</link><description>A flaw was found in cri-o, where an arbitrary systemd property can be injected via a Pod annotation. Any user who can create a pod with an arbitrary annotation may perform an arbitrary action on the host system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 03:22:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47252 | An issue was discovered in PnpSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.6. There is a possible out-of-bounds access in the SMM commu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47252</link><description>An issue was discovered in PnpSmm in Insyde InsydeH2O with kernel 5.0 through 5.6. There is a possible out-of-bounds access in the SMM communication buffer, leading to tampering. The PNP-related SMI sub-functions do not verify data size before getting it from the communication buffer, which could lead to possible circumstances where the data immediately following the command buffer could be destroyed with a fixed value. This is fixed in kernel 5.2 v05.28.45, kernel 5.3 v05.37.45, kernel 5.4 v05.45.45, kernel 5.5 v05.53.45, and kernel 5.6 v05.60.45.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:50:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31755 | cJSON v1.7.17 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation, which can trigger through the second parameter of function cJSON_SetValues...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31755</link><description>cJSON v1.7.17 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation, which can trigger through the second parameter of function cJSON_SetValuestring at cJSON.c.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4163 | Privilege Escalation on Skylab IIoT Gateway (IGX)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4163</link><description>The Skylab IGX IIoT Gateway allowed users to connect to it via a limited shell terminal (IGX). However, it was discovered that the process was running under root privileges. This allowed the attacker to read, write, and modify any file in the operating system by utilizing the limited shell file exec and download functions. By replacing the /etc/passwd file with a new root user entry, the attacker was able to breakout from the limited shell and login to a unrestricted shell with root access. With the root access, the attacker will be able take full control of the IIoT Gateway.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33671 | An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. The Backup Exec Deduplication Multi-threaded Streaming Agent can b...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33671</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. The Backup Exec Deduplication Multi-threaded Streaming Agent can be leveraged to perform arbitrary file deletion on protected files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33672 | An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.4. The Multi-Threaded Agent used in NetBackup can be leveraged to perform arbitrary f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33672</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas NetBackup before 10.4. The Multi-Threaded Agent used in NetBackup can be leveraged to perform arbitrary file deletion on protected files.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33673 | An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. Improper access controls allow for DLL Hijacking in the Windows DL...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33673</link><description>An issue was discovered in Veritas Backup Exec before 22.2 HotFix 917391. Improper access controls allow for DLL Hijacking in the Windows DLL Search path.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48682 | In deletefiles in FDUPES before 2.2.0, a TOCTOU race condition allows arbitrary file deletion via a symlink.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48682</link><description>In deletefiles in FDUPES before 2.2.0, a TOCTOU race condition allows arbitrary file deletion via a symlink.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33669 | An issue was discovered in Passbolt Browser Extension before 4.6.2. It can send multiple requests to HaveIBeenPwned while a password is bein...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33669</link><description>An issue was discovered in Passbolt Browser Extension before 4.6.2. It can send multiple requests to HaveIBeenPwned while a password is being typed, which results in an information leak. This allows an attacker capable of observing Passbolt's HTTPS queries to the Pwned Password API to more easily brute force passwords that are manually typed by the user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33670 | Passbolt API before 4.6.2 allows HTML injection in a URL parameter, resulting in custom content being displayed when a user visits the craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33670</link><description>Passbolt API before 4.6.2 allows HTML injection in a URL parameter, resulting in custom content being displayed when a user visits the crafted URL. Although the injected content is not executed as JavaScript due to Content Security Policy (CSP) restrictions, it may still impact the appearance and user interaction of the page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33666 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. Users with customer access to a ticket could have accessed time accounting details of this t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33666</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. Users with customer access to a ticket could have accessed time accounting details of this ticket via the API. This data should be available only to agents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33667 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. An authenticated agent could perform a remote Denial of Service attack by calling an endpoin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33667</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. An authenticated agent could perform a remote Denial of Service attack by calling an endpoint that accepts a generic method name, which was not properly sanitized against an allowlist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33668 | An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. The Zammad Upload Cache uses insecure, partially guessable FormIDs to identify content. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33668</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zammad before 6.3.0. The Zammad Upload Cache uses insecure, partially guessable FormIDs to identify content. An attacker could try to brute force them to upload malicious content to article drafts they have no access to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33665 | angular-translate through 2.19.1 allows XSS via a crafted key that is used by the translate directive. NOTE: the vendor indicates that there...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33665</link><description>angular-translate through 2.19.1 allows XSS via a crafted key that is used by the translate directive. NOTE: the vendor indicates that there is no documentation indicating that a key is supposed to be safe against XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:20:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32868 | ZITADEL&amp;#x27;s Improper Lockout Mechanism Leads to MFA Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32868</link><description>ZITADEL provides users the possibility to use Time-based One-Time-Password (TOTP) and One-Time-Password (OTP) through SMS and Email. While ZITADEL already gives administrators the option to define a `Lockout Policy` with a maximum amount of failed password check attempts, there was no such mechanism for (T)OTP checks. This issue has been patched in version 2.50.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:59:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32651 | Server Side Template Injection in Jinja2 allows Remote Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32651</link><description>changedetection.io is an open source web page change detection, website watcher, restock monitor and notification service. There is a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI) in Jinja2 that allows Remote Command Execution on the server host. Attackers can run any system command without any restriction and they could use a reverse shell. The impact is critical as the attacker can completely takeover the server machine. This can be reduced if changedetection is behind a login page, but this isn't required by the application (not by default and not enforced).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:59:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33661 | Portainer before 2.20.0 allows redirects when the target is not index.yaml.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33661</link><description>Portainer before 2.20.0 allows redirects when the target is not index.yaml.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33663 | python-jose through 3.3.0 has algorithm confusion with OpenSSH ECDSA keys and other key formats. This is similar to CVE-2022-29217.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33663</link><description>python-jose through 3.3.0 has algorithm confusion with OpenSSH ECDSA keys and other key formats. This is similar to CVE-2022-29217.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33664 | python-jose through 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) during a decode via a crafted JSON Web Encryp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33664</link><description>python-jose through 3.3.0 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (resource consumption) during a decode via a crafted JSON Web Encryption (JWE) token with a high compression ratio, aka a "JWT bomb." This is similar to CVE-2024-21319.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:49:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0916 | Unauthenticated Remote Code Execution in UvDesk Community</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0916</link><description>Unauthenticated file upload allows remote code execution.
This issue affects UvDesk Community: from 1.0.0 through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 23:19:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3265 | WP Advanced Search &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Admin+ SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3265</link><description>The Advanced Search WordPress plugin through 1.1.6 does not properly escape parameters appended to an SQL query, making it possible for users with the administrator role to conduct SQL Injection attacks in the context of a multisite WordPress configurations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:38:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31609 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BOSSCMS v3.10 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the header code and footer code fields ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31609</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BOSSCMS v3.10 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via the header code and footer code fields in code configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31610 | File Upload vulnerability in the function for employees to upload avatars in Code-Projects Simple School Management System v1.0 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31610</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in the function for employees to upload avatars in Code-Projects Simple School Management System v1.0 allows attackers to run arbitrary code via upload of crafted file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36029 | BigBlueButton Greenlight Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36029</link><description>Greenlight is an end-user interface for BigBlueButton servers. Versions prior to 2.13.0 have an open redirect vulnerability in the Login page due to unchecked the value of the `return_to` cookie. Versions 2.13.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-36028 | BigBlueButton Greenlight Open Redirect vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-36028</link><description>Greenlight is an end-user interface for BigBlueButton servers. Versions prior to 2.13.0 have an open redirect vulnerability in the Login page due to unchecked the value of the `return_to` cookie. Versions 2.13.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32324 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v.3.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32324</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Shenzhen Libituo Technology Co., Ltd LBT-T300-T400 v.3.2 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the vpn_client_ip variable of the config_vpn_pptp function in rc program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 19:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31615 | ThinkCMF 6.0.9 is vulnerable to File upload via UeditorController.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31615</link><description>ThinkCMF 6.0.9 is vulnerable to File upload via UeditorController.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 19:47:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30939 | An issue discovered in Yealink VP59 Teams Editions with firmware version 91.15.0.118 allows a physically proximate attacker to gain control ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30939</link><description>An issue discovered in Yealink VP59 Teams Editions with firmware version 91.15.0.118 allows a physically proximate attacker to gain control of an account via a flaw in the factory reset procedure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32649 | vyper performs double eval of the argument of sqrt</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32649</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `sqrt` builtin can result in double eval vulnerability when the argument has side-effects. It can be seen that the `build_IR` function of the `sqrt` builtin doesn't cache the argument to the stack. As such, it can be evaluated multiple times (instead of retrieving the value from the stack). No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32648 | vyper default functions don&amp;#x27;t respect nonreentrancy keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32648</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. Prior to version 0.3.0, default functions don't respect nonreentrancy keys and the lock isn't emitted. No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, using a lock on a `default` function is a very sparsely used pattern. As such, the impact is low. Version 0.3.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3623 | Mirror-registry: default database secret key stored in plain-text on initial configuration file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3623</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default database secret key, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same database secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to access sensitive information from Quay's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3624 | Mirror-registry: database user and password stored in plain-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3624</link><description>A flaw was found in how Quay's database is stored in plain-text in mirror-registry on the jinja's config.yaml file. This flaw allows a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3625 | Mirror-registry: redis password stored in plain-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3625</link><description>A flaw was found in Quay, where Quay's database is stored in plain text in mirror-registry on Jinja's config.yaml file. This issue leaves the possibility of a malicious actor with access to this file to gain access to Quay's Redis instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2905 | Rpm-ostree: world-readable /etc/shadow file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2905</link><description>A security vulnerability has been discovered within rpm-ostree, pertaining to the /etc/shadow file in default builds having the world-readable bit enabled. This issue arises from the default permissions being set at a higher level than recommended, potentially exposing sensitive authentication data to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32647 | vyper performs double eval of raw_args in create_from_blueprint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32647</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `create_from_blueprint` builtin can result in a double eval vulnerability when `raw_args=True` and the `args` argument has side-effects. It can be seen that the `_build_create_IR` function of the `create_from_blueprint` builtin doesn't cache the mentioned `args` argument to the stack. As such, it can be evaluated multiple times (instead of retrieving the value from the stack). No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions exist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3508 | Bzip2: compressed content bomb leads to denial of service of bombastic api</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3508</link><description>A flaw was found in Bombastic, which allows authenticated users to upload compressed (bzip2 or zstd) SBOMs. The API endpoint verifies the presence of some fields and values in the JSON. To perform this verification, the uploaded file must first be decompressed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3622 | Mirror-registry: plain-text default csrf secret key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3622</link><description>A flaw was found when using mirror-registry to install Quay. It uses a default secret, which is stored in plain-text format in one of the configuration template files. This issue may lead to all instances of Quay deployed using mirror-registry to have the same secret key. This flaw allows a malicious actor to craft session cookies and as a consequence, it may lead to gaining access to the affected Quay instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32646 | vyper performs double eval of the slice args when buffer from adhoc locations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32646</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.3.10 and prior, using the `slice` builtin can result in a double eval vulnerability when the buffer argument is either `msg.data`, `self.code` or `&lt;address&gt;.code` and either the `start` or `length` arguments have side-effects. It can be easily triggered only with the versions `&lt;0.3.4` as `0.3.4` introduced the unique symbol fence. No vulnerable production contracts were found. Additionally, double evaluation of side-effects should be easily discoverable in client tests. As such, the impact is low. As of time of publication, no fixed versions are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32645 | vyper performs incorrect topic logging in raw_log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32645</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. In versions 0.13.0 and prior, incorrect values can be logged when `raw_log` builtin is called with memory or storage arguments to be used as topics. A contract search was performed and no vulnerable contracts were found in production. The `build_IR` function of the `RawLog` class fails to properly unwrap the variables provided as topics. Consequently, incorrect values are logged as topics. As of time of publication, no fixed version is available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32481 | vyper&amp;#x27;s range(start, start + N) reverts for negative numbers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32481</link><description>Vyper is a pythonic Smart Contract Language for the Ethereum virtual machine. Starting in version 0.3.8 and prior to version 0.4.0b1, when looping over a `range` of the form `range(start, start + N)`, if `start` is negative, the execution will always revert. This issue is caused by an incorrect assertion inserted by the code generation of the range `stmt.parse_For_range()`. The issue arises when `start` is signed, instead of using `sle`, `le` is used and `start` is interpreted as an unsigned integer for the comparison. If it is a negative number, its 255th bit is set to `1` and is hence interpreted as a very large unsigned integer making the assertion always fail. Any contract having a `range(start, start + N)` where `start` is a signed integer with the possibility for `start` to be negative is affected. If a call goes through the loop while supplying a negative `start` the execution will revert. Version 0.4.0b1 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32467 | Meteraphsere vulnerable to unauthorized viewing by workspace members</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32467</link><description>MeterSphere is an open source continuous testing platform. Prior to version 2.10.14-lts, members without space permissions can view member information from other workspaces beyond their authority. Version 2.10.14-lts fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:09:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28241 | GlPI-Agent MSI package installation doesn&amp;#x27;t update folder security profile when using non default installation folder</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28241</link><description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. Prior to version 1.7.2, a local user can modify GLPI-Agent code or used DLLs to modify agent logic and even gain higher privileges. Users should upgrade to GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 to receive a patch. As a workaround, use the default installation folder which involves installed folder is automatically secured by the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2467 | Perl-crypt-openssl-rsa: side-channel attack in pkcs#1 v1.5 padding mode (marvin attack)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2467</link><description>A timing-based side-channel flaw exists in the perl-Crypt-OpenSSL-RSA package, which could be sufficient to recover plaintext across a network in a Bleichenbacher-style attack. To achieve successful decryption, an attacker would have to be able to send a large number of trial messages. The vulnerability affects the legacy PKCS#1v1.5 RSA encryption padding mode.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-28240 | GLPI-Agent&amp;#x27;s MSI package installation permits local users to change Agent configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-28240</link><description>The GLPI Agent is a generic management agent. A vulnerability that only affects GLPI-Agent installed on windows via MSI packaging can allow a local user to cause denial of agent service by replacing GLPI server url with a wrong url or disabling the service. Additionally, in the case the Deploy task is installed, a local malicious user can trigger privilege escalation configuring a malicious server providing its own deploy task payload. GLPI-Agent 1.7.2 contains a patch for this issue. As a workaround, edit GLPI-Agent related key under `HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Uninstall` and add `SystemComponent` DWORD value setting it to `1` to hide GLPI-Agent from installed applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1657 | Ansible automation platform: insecure websocket used when interacting with eda server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1657</link><description>A flaw was found in the ansible automation platform. An insecure WebSocket connection was being used in installation from the Ansible rulebook EDA server. An attacker that has access to any machine in the CIDR block could download all rulebook data from the WebSocket, resulting in loss of confidentiality and integrity of the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1726 | Quarkus: security checks for some inherited endpoints performed after serialization in resteasy reactive may trigger a denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1726</link><description>A flaw was discovered in the RESTEasy Reactive implementation in Quarkus. Due to security checks for some JAX-RS endpoints being performed after serialization, more processing resources are consumed while the HTTP request is checked. In certain configurations, if an attacker has knowledge of any POST, PUT, or PATCH request paths, they can potentially identify vulnerable endpoints and trigger excessive resource usage as the endpoints process the requests. This can result in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25624 | iris-web vulnerable to Server Side Template Injection in reports</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25624</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform aiming to help incident responders sharing technical details during investigations. Due to an improper setup of Jinja2 environment, reports generation in `iris-web` is prone to a Server Side Template Injection (SSTI). Successful exploitation of the vulnerability can lead to an arbitrary Remote Code Execution. An authenticated administrator has to upload a crafted report template containing the payload. Upon generation of a report based on the weaponized report, any user can trigger the vulnerability.  The vulnerability is patched in IRIS v2.4.6. No workaround is available. It is recommended to update as soon as possible. Until patching, review the report templates and keep the administrative privileges that include the upload of report templates limited to dedicated users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31574 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TWCMS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31574</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in TWCMS v.2.6 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0874 | Coredns: cd bit response is cached and served later</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0874</link><description>A flaw was found in coredns. This issue could lead to invalid cache entries returning due to incorrectly implemented caching.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1102 | Jberet: jberet-core logging database credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1102</link><description>A vulnerability was found in jberet-core logging. An exception in 'dbProperties' might display user credentials such as the username and password for the database-connection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1139 | Cluster-monitoring-operator: credentials leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1139</link><description>A credentials leak vulnerability was found in the cluster monitoring operator in OCP.  This issue may allow a remote attacker who has basic login credentials to check the pod manifest to discover a repository pull secret.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-29660 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the stepselec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-29660</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in DedeCMS v.5.7 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to the stepselect_main.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32358 | An issue in Jpress v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the custom plug-in module function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32358</link><description>An issue in Jpress v.5.1.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the custom plug-in module function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30890 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ED01-CMS v.1.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the categories.php component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30890</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in ED01-CMS v.1.0 allows an attacker to obtain sensitive information via the categories.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32236 | An issue in CmsEasy v.7.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the update function in the index.php compo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32236</link><description>An issue in CmsEasy v.7.7 and before allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via the update function in the index.php component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6717 | Keycloak: xss via assertion consumer service url in saml post-binding flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6717</link><description>A flaw was found in the SAML client registration in Keycloak that could allow an administrator to register malicious JavaScript URIs as Assertion Consumer Service POST Binding URLs (ACS), posing a Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) risk. This issue may allow a malicious admin in one realm or a client with registration access to target users in different realms or applications, executing arbitrary JavaScript in their contexts upon form submission. This can enable unauthorized access and harmful actions, compromising the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the complete KC instance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6787 | Keycloak: session hijacking via re-authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6787</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak that occurs from an error in the re-authentication mechanism within org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows hijacking an active Keycloak session by triggering a new authentication process with the query parameter "prompt=login," prompting the user to re-enter their credentials. If the user cancels this re-authentication by selecting "Restart login," an account takeover may occur, as the new session, with a different SUB, will possess the same SID as the previous session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6484 | Keycloak: log injection during webauthn authentication or registration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6484</link><description>A log injection flaw was found in Keycloak. A text string may be injected through the authentication form when using the WebAuthn authentication mode. This issue may have a minor impact to the logs integrity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6544 | Keycloak: authorization bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6544</link><description>A flaw was found in the Keycloak package. This issue occurs due to a permissive regular expression hardcoded for filtering which allows hosts to register a dynamic client. A malicious user with enough information about the environment could jeopardize an environment with this specific Dynamic Client Registration and TrustedDomain configuration previously unauthorized.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6596 | Openshift: incomplete fix for rapid reset (cve-2023-44487/cve-2023-39325)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6596</link><description>An incomplete fix was shipped for the Rapid Reset (CVE-2023-44487/CVE-2023-39325) vulnerability for an OpenShift Containers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5675 | Quarkus: authorization flaw in quarkus resteasy reactive and classic when &amp;quot;quarkus.security.jaxrs.deny-unannotated-endpoints&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;quarkus.security.jaxrs.default-roles-allowed&amp;quot; properties are used.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5675</link><description>A flaw was found in Quarkus. When a Quarkus RestEasy Classic or Reactive JAX-RS endpoint has its methods declared in the abstract Java class or customized by Quarkus extensions using the annotation processor, the authorization of these methods will not be enforced if it is enabled by either 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.deny-unannotated-endpoints' or 'quarkus.security.jaxrs.default-roles-allowed' properties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33592 | WordPress Radio Player plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.73 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33592</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in SoftLab Radio Player.This issue affects Radio Player: from n/a through 2.0.73.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:09:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22373 | An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the JPEG2000Codec::DecodeByStreamsCommon functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22373</link><description>An out-of-bounds write vulnerability exists in the JPEG2000Codec::DecodeByStreamsCommon functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted DICOM file can lead to a heap buffer overflow. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22391 | A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LookupTable::SetLUT functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22391</link><description>A heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the LookupTable::SetLUT functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted malformed file can lead to memory corruption. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25569 | An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the RAWCodec::DecodeBytes functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A special...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25569</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability exists in the RAWCodec::DecodeBytes functionality of Mathieu Malaterre Grassroot DICOM 3.0.23. A specially crafted DICOM file can lead to an out-of-bounds read. An attacker can provide a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4172 | idcCMS cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4172</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in idcCMS 1.35. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_cl.php?mudi=revPwd. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261991.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4006 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4006</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.7 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1 where personal access scopes were not honored by GraphQL subscriptions</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4024 | Improper Authentication in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4024</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 7.8 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker with their Bitbucket account credentials may be able to take over a GitLab account linked to another user's Bitbucket account, if Bitbucket is used as an OAuth 2.0 provider on GitLab.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4171 | Tenda W30E WizardHandle fromWizardHandle stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4171</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda W30E 1.0/1.0.1.25. Affected is the function fromWizardHandle of the file /goform/WizardHandle. The manipulation of the argument PPW leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-261990 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4170 | Tenda 4G300 sub_429A30 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4170</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function sub_429A30. The manipulation of the argument list1 leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The identifier VDB-261989 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:17:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33247 | Sourcecodester Employee Task Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin-manage-user.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33247</link><description>Sourcecodester Employee Task Management System v1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via admin-manage-user.php.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4169 | Tenda 4G300 sub_4279CC stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4169</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function sub_42775C/sub_4279CC. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261988. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3597 | Keycloak: secondary factor bypass in step-up authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3597</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak, where it does not correctly validate its client step-up authentication in org.keycloak.authentication. This flaw allows a remote user authenticated with a password to register a false second authentication factor along with an existing one and bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25026 | IBM WebSphere Application Server denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25026</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5, 9.0 and IBM WebSphere Application Server Liberty 17.0.0.3 through 24.0.0.4 are vulnerable to a denial of service, caused by sending a specially crafted request.  A remote attacker could exploit this vulnerability to cause the server to consume memory resources.  IBM X-Force ID:  281516.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4167 | Tenda 4G300 sub_422AA4 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4167</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_422AA4. The manipulation of the argument year/month/day/hour/minute/second leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. VDB-261986 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4168 | Tenda 4G300 sub_4260F0 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4168</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function sub_4260F0. The manipulation of the argument upfilen leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261987. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4175 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4175</link><description>Unicode transformation vulnerability in Hyperion affecting version 2.0.15. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to send a malicious payload with Unicode characters that will be replaced by ASCII characters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:56:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4174 | Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4174</link><description>Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Hyperion Web Server affecting version 2.0.15. This vulnerability could allow an attacker to execute malicious Javascript code on the client by injecting that code into the URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4165 | Tenda G3 modifyDhcpRule stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4165</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda G3 15.11.0.17(9502). Affected is the function modifyDhcpRule of the file /goform/modifyDhcpRule. The manipulation of the argument bindDhcpIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261984. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4166 | Tenda 4G300 sub_41E858 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4166</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda 4G300 1.01.42 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_41E858. The manipulation of the argument GO/page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The identifier VDB-261985 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1347 | Improper Authentication in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1347</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. Under certain conditions, an attacker through a crafted email address may be able to bypass domain based restrictions on an instance or a group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2434 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory (&amp;#x27;Path Traversal&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2434</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab affecting all versions of GitLab CE/EE  16.9 prior to 16.9.6, 16.10 prior to 16.10.4, and 16.11 prior to 16.11.1 where path traversal could lead to DoS and restricted file read.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2829 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2829</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.5 before 16.9.6, all versions starting from 16.10 before 16.10.4, all versions starting from 16.11 before 16.11.1. A crafted wildcard filter in FileFinder may lead to a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3730 | The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'swpm_paypal_subscription_cancel_li...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3730</link><description>The Simple Membership plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'swpm_paypal_subscription_cancel_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:16:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32676 | WordPress LoginPress Pro plugin &amp;lt; 3.0.0 - Captcha Bypass vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32676</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in LoginPress LoginPress Pro.This issue affects LoginPress Pro: from n/a before 3.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4164 | Tenda G3 ModifyPppAuthWhiteMac formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4164</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda G3 15.11.0.17(9502). This issue affects the function formModifyPppAuthWhiteMac of the file /goform/ModifyPppAuthWhiteMac. The manipulation of the argument pppoeServerWhiteMacIndex leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-261983. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:40:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25583 | Crafted responses can lead to a denial of service in Recursor if recursive forwarding is configured</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25583</link><description>A crafted response from an upstream server the recursor has been configured to forward-recurse to can cause a Denial of Service in the Recursor. The default configuration of the Recursor does not use recursive forwarding and is not affected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52220 | WordPress MonsterInsights plugin &amp;lt;= 8.21.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52220</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in MonsterInsights Google Analytics by Monster Insights.This issue affects Google Analytics by Monster Insights: from n/a through 8.21.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3994 | The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3994</link><description>The Tutor LMS – eLearning and online course solution plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'tutor_instructor_list' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4035 | The Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4035</link><description>The Photo Gallery – GT3 Image Gallery &amp; Gutenberg Block Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image alt text in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.7.21 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-32961 | WordPress Blocksy theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.33 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-32961</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Creative Themes HQ Blocksy allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Blocksy: from n/a through 2.0.33.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4077 | WordPress UDesign theme &amp;lt;= 4.7.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4077</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AndonDesign UDesign allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects UDesign: from n/a through 4.7.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:23:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-30560 | WordPress DX-Watermark plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.4 - CSRF to Arbitrary File Upload and XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-30560</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in 大侠WP DX-Watermark.This issue affects DX-Watermark: from n/a through 1.0.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31266 | WordPress Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.4 - Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31266</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in AlgolPlus Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce allows Code Injection.This issue affects Advanced Order Export For WooCommerce: from n/a through 3.4.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:52:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25917 | WordPress WP Setup Wizard plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8.1 - Auth. Full Database Download Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25917</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in CodeRevolution WP Setup Wizard.This issue affects WP Setup Wizard: from n/a through 1.0.8.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3733 | The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3733</link><description>The Essential Addons for Elementor – Best Elementor Templates, Widgets, Kits &amp; WooCommerce Builders plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 5.9.15 via the ajax_load_more() , eael_woo_pagination_product_ajax(), and ajax_eael_product_gallery() functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract posts that may be in private or draft status.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:42:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51484 | WordPress Login as User or Customer plugin &amp;lt;= 3.8 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51484</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in wp-buy Login as User or Customer (User Switching) allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Login as User or Customer (User Switching): from n/a through 3.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22144 | WordPress Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall plugin &amp;lt;= 4.21.96 - Unauthenticated Predictable Nonce Brute-Force Leading to RCE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22144</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Eli Scheetz Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall gotmls allows Code Injection.This issue affects Anti-Malware Security and Brute-Force Firewall: from n/a through 4.21.96.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51482 | WordPress Eazy Plugin Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1.2 - Auth. Arbitrary Options Update lead to RCE vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51482</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in EazyPlugins Eazy Plugin Manager allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs.This issue affects Eazy Plugin Manager: from n/a through 4.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51478 | WordPress Build App Online plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Unauthenticated Account Takeover vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51478</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Abdul Hakeem Build App Online allows Privilege Escalation.This issue affects Build App Online: from n/a through 1.0.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:19:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3893 | The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3893</link><description>The Classified Listing – Classified ads &amp; Business Directory Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the rtcl_fb_gallery_image_delete AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.10.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3929 | The Content Views – Post Grid &amp; Filter, Recent Posts, Category Posts, &amp; More (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulner...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3929</link><description>The Content Views – Post Grid &amp; Filter, Recent Posts, Category Posts, &amp; More (Gutenberg Blocks and Shortcode) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the  Widget Post Overlay block in all versions up to, and including, 3.7.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3988 | The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plu...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3988</link><description>The Sina Extension for Elementor (Slider, Gallery, Form, Modal, Data Table, Tab, Particle, Free Elementor Widgets &amp; Elementor Templates) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Sina Fancy Text Widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4173 | Inconsistent firewall rules</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4173</link><description>A vulnerability in Brocade SANnav ova versions before Brocade SANnav v2.3.1 and v2.3.0a exposes Kafka in the wan interface due to inconsistent firewall rules.

The vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform various attacks, including DOS, the Brocade SANnav appliance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:37:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6237 | Excessive time spent checking invalid RSA public keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6237</link><description>Issue summary: Checking excessively long invalid RSA public keys may take
a long time.

Impact summary: Applications that use the function EVP_PKEY_public_check()
to check RSA public keys may experience long delays. Where the key that
is being checked has been obtained from an untrusted source this may lead
to a Denial of Service.

When function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is called on RSA public keys,
a computation is done to confirm that the RSA modulus, n, is composite.
For valid RSA keys, n is a product of two or more large primes and this
computation completes quickly. However, if n is an overly large prime,
then this computation would take a long time.

An application that calls EVP_PKEY_public_check() and supplies an RSA key
obtained from an untrusted source could be vulnerable to a Denial of Service
attack.

The function EVP_PKEY_public_check() is not called from other OpenSSL
functions however it is called from the OpenSSL pkey command line
application. For that reason that application is also vulnerable if used
with the '-pubin' and '-check' options on untrusted data.

The OpenSSL SSL/TLS implementation is not affected by this issue.

The OpenSSL 3.0 and 3.1 FIPS providers are affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-2907 | AGCA – Custom Dashboard &amp;amp; Login Page &amp;lt; 7.2.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS via Image URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-2907</link><description>The AGCA  WordPress plugin before 7.2.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 05:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4161 | Syslog traffic sent in clear-text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4161</link><description>In Brocade SANnav, before Brocade SANnav v2.3.0, syslog traffic received
 clear text. This could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to 
capture sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:35:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-4159 | Protection mechanisms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-4159</link><description>Brocade SANnav before Brocade SANnav v2.3.1 lacks protection mechanisms on port 2377/TCP and 7946/TCP, which could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to reach Kafka APIs and send malicious data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:16:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>