<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 13:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-12015 | SQL Injection in WordPress Project Manager Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12015</link><description>The 'Project Manager' WordPress Plugin is affected by an authenticated SQL injection vulnerability in the 'orderby' parameter in the '/pm/v2/activites' route.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 13:34:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33036 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33036</link><description>Memory corruption while parsing sensor packets in camera driver, user-space variable is used while allocating memory in kernel and parsing which can lead to huge allocation or invalid memory access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33037 | Buffer Over-read in Neural Processing Unit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33037</link><description>Information disclosure as NPU firmware can send invalid IPC message to NPU driver as the driver doesn`t validate the IPC message received from the firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33039 | Untrusted Pointer Dereference in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33039</link><description>Memory corruption when PAL client calls PAL service APIs by passing a random value as handle and the handle is not validated by the service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33040 | Use After Free in Camera Driver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33040</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking redundant release command to release one buffer from user space as race condition can occur in kernel space between buffer release and buffer access.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33044 | Improper Validation of Array Index in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33044</link><description>Memory corruption while Configuring the SMR/S2CR register in Bypass mode.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33053 | Use After Free in Video</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33053</link><description>Memory corruption when multiple threads try to unregister the CVP buffer at the same time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33056 | Buffer Over-read in MProc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33056</link><description>Memory corruption when allocating and accessing an entry in an SMEM partition continuously.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33063 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in WLAN Host Communication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33063</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing the ML IE when a beacon with common info length of the ML IE greater than the ML IE inside which this element is present.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43048 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in Performance</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43048</link><description>Memory corruption when invalid input is passed to invoke GPU Headroom API call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43049 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43049</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from user space to set generic private command inside WLAN driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43050 | Stack-based Buffer Overflow in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43050</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from user space to issue factory test command inside WLAN driver.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43052 | Improper Input Validation in Video Analytics and Processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43052</link><description>Memory corruption while processing API calls to NPU with invalid input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43053 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in WLAN Windows Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43053</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTL calls from user space to read WLAN target diagnostic information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:39:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10490 | Authentication bypass flaw in several mapp components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10490</link><description>An “Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel” vulnerability in the OPC UA Server configuration required for B&amp;amp;R mapp Cockpit before 6.0, B&amp;amp;R mapp View before 6.0, B&amp;amp;R mapp Services before 6.0, B&amp;amp;R mapp Motion before 6.0 and B&amp;amp;R mapp Vision before 6.0 may be used by an unauthenticated network-based attacker to cause information disclosure, unintended change of data, or denial of service conditions.
B&amp;amp;R mapp Services is only affected, when mpUserX or mpCodeBox are used in the Automation Studio project.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53103 | hv_sock: Initializing vsk-&amp;gt;trans to NULL to prevent a dangling pointer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53103</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

hv_sock: Initializing vsk-&gt;trans to NULL to prevent a dangling pointer

When hvs is released, there is a possibility that vsk-&gt;trans may not
be initialized to NULL, which could lead to a dangling pointer.
This issue is resolved by initializing vsk-&gt;trans to NULL.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 07:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53104 | media: uvcvideo: Skip parsing frames of type UVC_VS_UNDEFINED in uvc_parse_format</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53104</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

media: uvcvideo: Skip parsing frames of type UVC_VS_UNDEFINED in uvc_parse_format

This can lead to out of bounds writes since frames of this type were not
taken into account when calculating the size of the frames buffer in
uvc_parse_streaming.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 07:42:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20116 | In cmdq, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20116</link><description>In cmdq, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09057438; Issue ID: MSV-1696.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20125 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20125</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09046782; Issue ID: MSV-1728.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20127 | In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20127</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09289881; Issue ID: MSV-2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20128 | In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20128</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09289881; Issue ID: MSV-2024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20129 | In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20129</link><description>In Telephony, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09289881; Issue ID: MSV-2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20130 | In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20130</link><description>In power, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09193374; Issue ID: MSV-1982.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20131 | In Modem, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20131</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01395886; Issue ID: MSV-1873.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20132 | In Modem, there is a possible out of bonds write due to a mission bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20132</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible out of bonds write due to a mission bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00957388; Issue ID: MSV-1872.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20133 | In Modem, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20133</link><description>In Modem, there is a possible escalation of privilege due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01395886; Issue ID: MSV-1871.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20134 | In ril, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20134</link><description>In ril, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09154589; Issue ID: MSV-1866.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20135 | In soundtrigger, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20135</link><description>In soundtrigger, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09142526; Issue ID: MSV-1841.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20136 | In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20136</link><description>In da, there is a possible out of bounds read due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09121847; Issue ID: MSV-1821.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20137 | In wlan driver, there is a possible client disconnection due to improper handling of exceptional conditions. This could lead to remote denia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20137</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible client disconnection due to improper handling of exceptional conditions. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00384543; Issue ID: MSV-1727.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20138 | In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bound read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20138</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible out of bound read due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08998291; Issue ID: MSV-1604.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20139 | In Bluetooth firmware, there is a possible firmware asssert due to improper handling of exceptional conditions. This could lead to local den...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20139</link><description>In Bluetooth firmware, there is a possible firmware asssert due to improper handling of exceptional conditions. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS09001270; Issue ID: MSV-1600.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11856 | HPE IceWall Products, Remote Unauthorized Data Modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11856</link><description>A security vulnerability in HPE IceWall products could be exploited remotely to cause Unauthorized Data Modification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 03:26:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53605 | Incorrect access control in the component content://com.handcent.messaging.provider.MessageProvider/ of Handcent NextSMS v10.9.9.7 allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53605</link><description>Incorrect access control in the component content://com.handcent.messaging.provider.MessageProvider/ of Handcent NextSMS v10.9.9.7 allows attackers to access sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12007 | code-projects Farmacia visualizar-produto.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12007</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /visualizar-produto.php. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53742 | WordPress Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.27 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53742</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Prism I.T. Systems Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS.This issue affects Multilevel Referral Affiliate Plugin for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.27.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53743 | WordPress Countdown Timer for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53743</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FlickDevs Countdown Timer for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Countdown Timer for Elementor: from n/a through 1.3.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53744 | WordPress Elementor Image Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53744</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Skybootstrap Elementor Image Gallery Plugin allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Image Gallery Plugin: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53745 | WordPress  Social Sharing Buttons By Cosmos Farm  plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53745</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in 코스모스팜 – Cosmosfarm 소셜 공유 버튼 By 코스모스팜 allows Stored XSS.This issue affects 소셜 공유 버튼 By 코스모스팜: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53746 | WordPress Elementor Button Plus plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53746</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in FlickDevs Elementor Button Plus allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Button Plus: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:33:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53747 | WordPress Video Player for WPBakery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53747</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NuttTaro Video Player for WPBakery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Video Player for WPBakery: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53748 | WordPress WP Mermaid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Terry Lin WP Mermaid allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Mermaid: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:25:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53749 | WordPress Post Carousel Slider for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53749</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Plugin Devs Post Carousel Slider for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Post Carousel Slider for Elementor: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53750 | WordPress PayPal Responder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53750</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Maeve Lander PayPal Responder allows Stored XSS.This issue affects PayPal Responder: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:25:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53752 | WordPress Stripe Donation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53752</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Berg Informatik Stripe Donation allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Stripe Donation: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 21:25:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45520 | WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 1.0.35-1 allows a remote Denial of Service because of memory corruption during scanning of a PE...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45520</link><description>WithSecure Atlant (formerly F-Secure Atlant) 1.0.35-1 allows a remote Denial of Service because of memory corruption during scanning of a PE32 file.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53756 | WordPress Vertical Carousel plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53756</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Aftab Husain Vertical Carousel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Vertical Carousel: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 22:14:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53757 | WordPress  WP Find Your Nearest plugin &amp;lt;= 0.3.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53757</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SocialEvolution WP Find Your Nearest allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP Find Your Nearest: from n/a through 0.3.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:58:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53758 | WordPress WP MathJax plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53758</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Terry Lin WP MathJax allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP MathJax: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53760 | WordPress Capitalize My Title WordPress plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53760</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Capitalize My Title allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Capitalize My Title: from n/a through 0.5.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:58:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53763 | WordPress Best Addons for Elementor plugin  &amp;lt;=1.0.5 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53763</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rejuan Ahamed Best Addons for Elementor allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Best Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:58:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53764 | WordPress Softtemplates For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53764</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SoftHopper Softtemplates For Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Softtemplates For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53766 | WordPress Devnex Addons For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53766</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Devnex Devnex Addons For Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Devnex Addons For Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53767 | WordPress Pixobe Cartography plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Pixobe Pixobe Cartography allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Pixobe Cartography: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:37:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53771 | WordPress SimpleSchema plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53771</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sergio Micó SimpleSchema allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects SimpleSchema: from n/a through 1.7.6.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53772 | WordPress Mail Picker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53772</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in PickPlugins Mail Picker allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Mail Picker: from n/a through 1.0.14.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53773 | WordPress Znajdź Pracę z Praca.pl plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53773</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Praca.Pl sp. Z o.O. Znajdź Pracę z Praca.Pl allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Znajdź Pracę z Praca.Pl: from n/a through 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53774 | WordPress Sparkle Elementor Kit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53774</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sparkle WP Sparkle Elementor Kit allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Sparkle Elementor Kit: from n/a through 2.0.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:29:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53778 | WordPress Essential Breadcrumbs plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53778</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Essential Marketer Essential Breadcrumbs allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Essential Breadcrumbs: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53786 | WordPress Cowidgets – Elementor Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53786</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Codeless Cowidgets – Elementor Addons allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Cowidgets – Elementor Addons: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53783 | WordPress Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53783</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Anzia Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Ni WooCommerce Cost Of Goods: from n/a through 3.2.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53787 | WordPress Random Banner plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.9 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53787</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in vinoth06 Random Banner allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Random Banner: from n/a through 4.2.9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:18:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53788 | WordPress WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53788</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Portfoliohub WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WordPress Portfolio Builder – Portfolio Gallery: from n/a through 1.1.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53739 | WordPress Cryptocurrency Widgets For Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53739</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Cool Plugins Cryptocurrency Widgets For Elementor allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Cryptocurrency Widgets For Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53768 | WordPress Content Audit Exporter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53768</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive System Information to an Unauthorized Control Sphere vulnerability in IDE Interactive Content Audit Exporter allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Content Audit Exporter: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:18:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53738 | WordPress Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster plugin &amp;lt;=1.3.9.8 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53738</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Gabe Livan Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects Asset CleanUp: Page Speed Booster: from n/a through 1.3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12002 | Tenda FH451/FH1201/FH1202/FH1206 GetIPTV websReadEvent null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12002</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Tenda FH451, FH1201, FH1202 and FH1206 up to 20241129. Affected by this vulnerability is the function websReadEvent of the file /goform/GetIPTV. The manipulation of the argument Content-Length leads to null pointer dereference. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 13:26:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12001 | code-projects Wazifa System Setting updatesettings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12001</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 13:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12000 | code-projects Blood Bank System Setting updatesettings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12000</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Blood Bank System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11998 | code-projects Farmacia visualizer-forneccedor.chp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11998</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /visualizer-forneccedor.chp. The manipulation of the argument id leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 09:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11997 | code-projects Farmacia vendas.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11997</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /vendas.php. The manipulation of the argument notaFiscal leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 08:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11996 | code-projects Farmacia editar-fornecedor.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11996</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Farmacia 1.0 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /editar-fornecedor.php. The manipulation of the argument cidade leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 07:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11252 | Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share &amp;lt;= 3.3.69 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via heateor_mastodon_share Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11252</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin – Sassy Social Share plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the heateor_mastodon_share parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.3.69 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 05:50:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43702 | GPU DDK - MLIST/PM render state buffers writable allowing arbitrary writes to kernel memory pages</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43702</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to allow unprivileged access to arbitrary physical memory page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 03:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43703 | GPU DDK - Duplicate calls to RGXCreateFreeList on the same reservation leads to GPU UAF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43703</link><description>Software installed and run as a non-privileged user may conduct improper GPU system calls to achieve unauthorised reads and writes of physical memory from the GPU HW.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 03:02:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>