<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:20:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-12595 | Tenda AC23 SetVirtualServerCfg formSetVirtualSer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12595</link><description>A weakness has been identified in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52. This impacts the function formSetVirtualSer of the file /goform/SetVirtualServerCfg. This manipulation of the argument list causes buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been made available to the public and could be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12594 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System add_account.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12594</link><description>A security flaw has been discovered in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. This affects an unknown function of the file /admin/add_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Name results in sql injection. The attack may be performed from remote. The exploit has been released to the public and may be exploited.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 08:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12593 | code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System Photo edit_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12593</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in code-projects Simple Online Hotel Reservation System 2.0. The impacted element is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_room.php of the component Photo Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack is possible to be carried out remotely. The exploit is publicly available and might be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 06:18:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12602 | /etc/avahi/services/z9.service can be Arbitrarily Written</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12602</link><description>/etc/avahi/services/z9.service can be Arbitrarily Written.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12603 | /etc/timezone can be Arbitrarily Written</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12603</link><description>/etc/timezone can be Arbitrarily Written.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12600 | Web UI Malfunction</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12600</link><description>Web UI Malfunction when setting unexpected locale via API.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12601 | Denial of Service Due to SlowLoris</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12601</link><description>Denial of Service Due to SlowLoris.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12599 | Multiple Devices are Sharing the Same Secrets for SDKSocket (TCP/5000)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12599</link><description>Multiple Devices are Sharing the Same Secrets for SDKSocket (TCP/5000).This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36367 | IBM i is affected by a privilege escalation in IBM i SQL services []</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36367</link><description>IBM i 7.6, 7.5, 7.4, 7.3, and 7.2 is vulnerable to privilege escalation caused by an invalid IBM i SQL services authorization check.  A malicious actor can use the elevated privileges of another user profile to gain root access to the host operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 12:14:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6988 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.23.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6988</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via several of the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 4.23.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 07:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6990 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.24.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6990</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 4.24.0 via the  `TH_PhpCode` pagebuilder widget. This is due to the theme not restricting access to the code editor widget for non-administrators. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 07:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10487 | Advanced Ads &amp;lt;= 2.0.12 - Unauthenticated Limited Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10487</link><description>The Advanced Ads – Ad Manager &amp; AdSense plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.12 via the select_one() function. This is due to the endpoint not properly restricting access to the AJAX endpoint or limiting the functions that can be called to safe functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to call arbitrary functions beginning with get_the_ like get_the_excerpt which can make information exposure possible.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11499 | Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent &amp;lt;= 1.1.32 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11499</link><description>The Tablesome Table – Contact Form DB – WPForms, CF7, Gravity, Forminator, Fluent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the set_featured_image_from_external_url() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.32. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible in configurations where unauthenticated users have been provided with a method for adding featured images, and the workflow trigger is created.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11755 | Delicious Recipes &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11755</link><description>The WP Delicious – Recipe Plugin for Food Bloggers (formerly Delicious Recipes) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads when importing recipes via CSV in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0. This flaw allows an attacker with at least Contributor-level permissions to upload a malicious PHP file by providing a remote URL during a recipe import process, leading to Remote Code Execution (RCE).</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12137 | Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress &amp;lt;= 2.14.16 - Authenticated (Admin+) Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12137</link><description>The Import WP – Export and Import CSV and XML files to WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Arbitrary File Read in all versions up to, and including, 2.14.16. This is due to the plugin's REST API endpoint accepting arbitrary absolute file paths without proper validation in the 'attach_file()' function when handling 'file_local' actions. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to read arbitrary files on the server's filesystem, including sensitive configuration files and system files via the 'local_url' parameter.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12171 | RESTful Content Syndication 1.1.0 - 1.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12171</link><description>The RESTful Content Syndication plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ingest_image() function in versions 1.1.0 to 1.5.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. This requires the attacker have access to a defined third-party server as specified in the settings, so it is unlikely that this will be exploitable by contributor-level users, and more likely to be exploited by administrators who also have access to the plugin's settings.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6574 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt; 6.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via Account Takeover</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6574</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and excluding, 6.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their details like email. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's email addresses, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 06:53:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11502 | Schema &amp;amp; Structured Data for WP &amp;amp; AMP &amp;lt;= 1.51 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11502</link><description>The Schema &amp; Structured Data for WP &amp; AMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'saswp_tiny_multiple_faq' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.51 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11740 | wpForo Forum &amp;lt;= 2.4.9 - Authenticated (Susbscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11740</link><description>The wpForo Forum plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the Subscriptions Manager in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11983 | WP Discourse &amp;lt;= 2.5.9 - Authenticated (Author+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11983</link><description>The WP Discourse plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.5.9. This is due to the plugin unconditionally sending Discourse API credentials (Api-Key and Api-Username headers) to any host specified in a post's discourse_permalink custom field during comment synchronization. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with author-level access and above, to exfiltrate sensitive Discourse API credentials to attacker-controlled servers, as well as query internal services and potentially perform further attacks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12038 | Folderly &amp;lt;= 0.3 - Incorrect Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Term Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12038</link><description>The Folderly plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to an insufficient capability check on the /wp-json/folderly/v1/config/clear-all-data REST API endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 0.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to clear all data like terms and categories.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12090 | Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp;amp; Meet the Team Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12090</link><description>The Employee Spotlight – Team Member Showcase &amp; Meet the Team Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Social URLs in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12180 | Qi Blocks &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12180</link><description>The Qi Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.3. This is due to the plugin storing arbitrary CSS styles submitted via the `qi-blocks/v1/update-styles` REST API endpoint without proper sanitization in the `update_global_styles_callback()` function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary CSS, which can be used to perform actions such as hiding content, overlaying fake UI elements, or exfiltrating sensitive information via CSS injection techniques.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11377 | List category posts &amp;lt;= 0.92.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11377</link><description>The List category posts plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 0.92.0 via the 'catlist' shortcode due to insufficient restrictions on which posts can be included. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to extract data from password protected, private, or draft posts that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11927 | Flying Images: Optimize and Lazy Load Images for Faster Page Speed &amp;lt;= 2.4.14 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11927</link><description>The Flying Images: Optimize and Lazy Load Images for Faster Page Speed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.14 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11995 | Community Events &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11995</link><description>The Community Events plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via event details parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12118 | Schema Scalpel &amp;lt;= 1.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Post Title in JSON-LD Schema</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12118</link><description>The Schema Scalpel plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the post title in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping when outputting user-supplied data into JSON-LD schema markup. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5949 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via change_candidate_password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5949</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to processing a password change request. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with subscriber access or higher to reset other users' passwords, including those of admins.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11833 | Post SMTP – Complete SMTP Solution with Logs, Alerts, Backup SMTP &amp;amp; Mobile App &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Missing Authorization to Account Takeover via Unauthenticated Email Log Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11833</link><description>The Post SMTP – Complete SMTP Solution with Logs, Alerts, Backup SMTP &amp; Mobile App plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the __construct function in all versions up to, and including, 3.6.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary logged emails sent through the Post SMTP plugin, including password reset emails containing password reset links, which can lead to account takeover.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11928 | CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript Toolbox &amp;lt;= 12.0.5 - Authenticated (Admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11928</link><description>The CSS &amp; JavaScript Toolbox plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via admin settings in all versions up to, and including, 12.0.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level permissions and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12367 | SiteSEO – SEO Simplified &amp;lt;= 1.3.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Author+) Plugin Settings Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12367</link><description>The SiteSEO – SEO Simplified plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Missing Authorization in versions up to, and including, 1.3.1. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying that a user is authorized to perform an action. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to enable or disable arbitrary SiteSEO features that they should not have access to.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:47:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62275 | Blogs in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 thr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62275</link><description>Blogs in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions does not check permission of images in a blog entry, which allows remote attackers to view the images in a blog entry via crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11174 | Document Library Lite &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11174</link><description>The Document Library Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Authorization in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.6. This is due to the plugin exposing an unauthenticated AJAX action dll_load_posts which returns a JSON table of document data without performing nonce or capability checks. The handler accepts an attacker-controlled args array where the status option explicitly allows draft, pending, future, and any. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve unpublished document titles and content via the AJAX endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11816 | Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp;amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages &amp;lt;= 3.5.1 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated API Disconnect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11816</link><description>The Privacy Policy Generator, Terms &amp; Conditions Generator WordPress Plugin : WP Legal Pages plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the disconnect_account_request() function in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to disconnect the site from its API plan.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11920 | WPCOM Member &amp;lt;= 1.7.14 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11920</link><description>The WPCOM Member plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.14 via the action parameter in one of its shortcodes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11922 | Inactive Logout &amp;lt;= 3.5.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11922</link><description>The Inactive Logout plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ina_redirect_page_individual_user' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 03:03:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62276 | The Document Library and the Adaptive Media modules in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay D...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62276</link><description>The Document Library and the Adaptive Media modules in Liferay Portal 7.4.0 through 7.4.3.111, and older unsupported versions, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 GA through update 92, and older unsupported versions uses an incorrect cache-control header, which allows local users to obtain access to downloaded files via the browser's cache.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 23:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12464 | Qemu-kvm: stack buffer overflow in e1000 device via short frames in loopback mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12464</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow was found in the QEMU e1000 network device. The code for padding short frames was dropped from individual network devices and moved to the net core code. The issue stems from the device's receive code still being able to process a short frame in loopback mode. This could lead to a buffer overrun in the e1000_receive_iov() function via the loopback code path. A malicious guest user could use this vulnerability to crash the QEMU process on the host, resulting in a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63563 | Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to v1.0.2 does not properly invalidate active user sessions after a password ch...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63563</link><description>Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to v1.0.2 does not properly invalidate active user sessions after a password change. This allows an attacker with a valid session token to maintain access to the account even after the legitimate user changes their password.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:34:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63561 | Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to 1.0.2 is susceptible to a Slowloris-style Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63561</link><description>Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to 1.0.2 is susceptible to a Slowloris-style Denial-of-Service (DoS) condition in the HTTP connection handling layer, where an attacker that opens and maintains many slow or partially-completed HTTP connections can exhaust the server’s connection pool and worker capacity, preventing legitimate users and APIs from accessing the service.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63562 | Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to v1.0.2 suffers from insufficient server-side authorization. Authenticated at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63562</link><description>Summer Pearl Group Vacation Rental Management Platform prior to v1.0.2 suffers from insufficient server-side authorization. Authenticated attackers can call several endpoints and perform create/update/delete actions on resources owned by arbitrary users by manipulating request parameters (e.g., owner or resource id).</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:54:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60711 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60711</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10693 | Silicon Labs Z-Wave PIR Sensor Joins Network as Non-Secure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10693</link><description>When SmartStart Inclusion fails during the onboarding of a Z-Wave PIR sensor, the sensor will join the network as a non-secure device. This vulnerability exists in Silicon Labs' Z-Wave PIR Sensor Reference design delivered as part of SiSDK v2025.6.0 and v2025.6.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63458 | Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the timeZone parameter in the form_fast_setting_wifi_set function. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63458</link><description>Tenda AX-1803 v1.0.0.1 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the timeZone parameter in the form_fast_setting_wifi_set function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63454 | Tenda AX-3 v16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the deviceId parameter in the get_parentControl_list_Info function...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63454</link><description>Tenda AX-3 v16.03.12.10_CN was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the deviceId parameter in the get_parentControl_list_Info function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12546 | LogicalDOC Community Edition API Key creation UI cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12546</link><description>A vulnerability was determined in LogicalDOC Community Edition up to 9.2.1. This affects an unknown part of the component API Key creation UI. This manipulation causes cross site scripting. Remote exploitation of the attack is possible. The exploit has been publicly disclosed and may be utilized. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12547 | LogicalDOC Community Edition Admin Login login.jsp excessive authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12547</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in LogicalDOC Community Edition up to 9.2.1. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /login.jsp of the component Admin Login Page. Such manipulation leads to improper restriction of excessive authentication attempts. The attack can be executed remotely. This attack is characterized by high complexity. It is stated that the exploitability is difficult. The exploit is publicly available and might be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62618 | ELOG file upload stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62618</link><description>ELOG allows an authenticated user to upload arbitrary HTML files. The HTML content is executed in the context of other users when they open the file. Because ELOG includes usernames and password hashes in certain HTTP requests, an attacker can obtain the target's credentials and replay them or crack the password hash offline. In ELOG 3.1.5-20251014 release, HTML files are rendered as plain text.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:45:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64348 | ELOG configuration file authorization bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64348</link><description>ELOG allows an authenticated user to modify or overwrite the configuration file, resulting in denial of service. If the execute facility is specifically enabled with the "-x" command line flag, attackers could execute OS commands on the host machine. By default, ELOG is not configured to allow shell commands or self-registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64349 | ELOG user profile missing authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64349</link><description>ELOG allows an authenticated user to modify another user's profile. An attacker can edit a target user's email address, then request a password reset, and take control of the target account. By default, ELOG is not configured to allow self-registration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:45:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62267 | Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in web content template’s select structure page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62267</link><description>Multiple cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in web content template’s select structure page in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.35 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, 7.4 update 35 through update 92 allow remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via a crafted payload injected into a user’s (1) First Name, (2) Middle Name, or (3) Last Name text field.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62264 | Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Languauge Override in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62264</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Languauge Override in Liferay Portal 7.4.3.8 through 7.4.3.111, and Liferay DXP 2023.Q4.0 through 2023.Q4.10, 2023.Q3.1 through 2023.Q3.10, and 7.4 update 4 through update 92 allows remote attackers to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via the `_com_liferay_portal_language_override_web_internal_portlet_PLOPortlet_selectedLanguageId` parameter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:44:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63459 | Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the sub_421CF0 function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63459</link><description>Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the sub_421CF0 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63460 | Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the sub_4222E0 function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63460</link><description>Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the sub_4222E0 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:18:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-59501 | Microsoft Configuration Manager Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-59501</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63461 | Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the urldecode function. This v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63461</link><description>Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid5g parameter in the urldecode function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:57:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63462 | Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wifiOff parameter in the sub_421A04 function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63462</link><description>Totolink A7000R v9.1.0u.6115_B20201022 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wifiOff parameter in the sub_421A04 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63463 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wifiOff parameter in the sub_4232EC function. This ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63463</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the wifiOff parameter in the sub_4232EC function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63464 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_42396C function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63464</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_42396C function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63465 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_422880 function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63465</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_422880 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6075 | Quadratic complexity in os.path.expandvars() with user-controlled template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6075</link><description>If the value passed to os.path.expandvars() is user-controlled a 
performance degradation is possible when expanding environment 
variables.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12507 | Insecure service configuration – unquoted path</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12507</link><description>The service Bizerba Communication Server (BCS) has an unquoted service path. Due to the way Windows searches the executable for the BCS service, malicious programs can be executed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12508 | Unencrypted communication to Active Directory services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12508</link><description>When using domain users as BRAIN2 users, communication with Active Directory services is unencrypted. This can lead to the interception of authentication data and compromise confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12509 | Scripts for the module Global_Shipping executable on BRAIN2 Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12509</link><description>On a client with an admin user, a Global_Shipping script can be implemented. The script could later be executed on the BRAIN2 server with administrator rights.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12553 | Server Certificate Verification Disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12553</link><description>Email Server Certificate Verification Disabled.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12554 | Missing Security Headers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12554</link><description>Missing Security Headers.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63469 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_421BAC function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63469</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_421BAC function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:56:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12552 | Insufficient Password Policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12552</link><description>Insufficient Password Policy.This issue affects BLU-IC2: through 1.19.5; BLU-IC4: through 1.19.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12357 | International Standards Organization ISO 15118-2 Improper Restriction of Communication Channel to Intended Endpoints</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12357</link><description>By manipulating the Signal Level Attenuation Characterization (SLAC) 
protocol with spoofed measurements, an attacker can stage a 
man-in-the-middle attack between an electric vehicle and chargers that 
comply with the ISO 15118-2 part. This vulnerability may be exploitable 
wirelessly, within close proximity, via electromagnetic induction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63466 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the sub_426EF8 function. This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63466</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the password parameter in the sub_426EF8 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63468 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the http_host parameter in the sub_426EF8 function. Thi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63468</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the http_host parameter in the sub_426EF8 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29270 | Incorrect access control in the realtime.cgi endpoint of Deep Sea Electronics devices DSE855 v1.1.0 to v1.1.26 allows attackers to gain acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29270</link><description>Incorrect access control in the realtime.cgi endpoint of Deep Sea Electronics devices DSE855 v1.1.0 to v1.1.26 allows attackers to gain access to the admin panel and complete control of the device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63467 | Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_425400 function. This vul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63467</link><description>Totolink LR350 v9.3.5u.6369_B20220309 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the ssid parameter in the sub_425400 function. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:37:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57108 | Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) through 9.5.0 contains a heap use-after-free vulnerability in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. The vulnerability m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57108</link><description>Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) through 9.5.0 contains a heap use-after-free vulnerability in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. The vulnerability manifests during mesh object copy operations where vector members are accessed after the underlying memory has been freed, specifically when handling GLTF files with corrupted or invalid mesh reference structures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57106 | Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) up to 9.5.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. The vulnerability occurs in the B...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57106</link><description>Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) up to 9.5.0 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. The vulnerability occurs in the BufferDataExtractionWorker template function when processing GLTF accessor data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64168 | Agno session state overwrites between different sessions/users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64168</link><description>Agno is a multi-agent framework, runtime and control plane. From 2.0.0 to before 2.2.2, under high concurrency, when session_state is passed to Agent or Team during run or arun calls, a race condition can occur, causing a session_state to be assigned and persisted to the incorrect session. This may result in user data from one session being exposed to another user. This has been patched in version 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-57107 | Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) through 9.5.0 contains a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. When processing sp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-57107</link><description>Kitware VTK (Visualization Toolkit) through 9.5.0 contains a heap buffer overflow vulnerability in vtkGLTFDocumentLoader. When processing specially crafted GLTF files, the copy constructor of Accessor objects fails to properly validate buffer boundaries before performing memory read operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:57:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-60749 | DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Trimble SketchUp desktop 2025 via crafted libcef.dll used by sketchup_webhelper.exe.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-60749</link><description>DLL Hijacking vulnerability in Trimble SketchUp desktop 2025 via crafted libcef.dll used by sketchup_webhelper.exe.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:49:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-61427 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BEO GmbH BEO Atlas Einfuhr Ausfuhr 3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-61427</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in BEO GmbH BEO Atlas Einfuhr Ausfuhr 3.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code in the context of a user's browser via injecting a crafted payload into the userid and password parameters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64385 | INCORRECT SECURITY VALIDATION IN SENDING UDP FRAMES</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64385</link><description>The equipment initially can be configured using the manufacturer's application, by Wi-Fi, by the web server or with the manufacturer’s software.
Using the manufacturer's software, the device can be configured via UDP. Analyzing this communication, it has been observed that any aspect of the initial configuration can be changed by means of the device's MAC without the need for authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64389 | EXCHANGE OF SENSITIVE INFORMATION IN CLEAR TEXT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64389</link><description>The web server of the device performs exchanges of sensitive information in clear text through an insecure protocol.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12501 | Integer overflow in GameMaker IDE below 2024.14.0 version can lead to can lead to application crashes through denial-of-service attacks (DoS...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12501</link><description>Integer overflow in GameMaker IDE below 2024.14.0 version can lead to can lead to application crashes through denial-of-service attacks (DoS). GameMaker users who use the network_create_server() function in their projects  are urged to update and recompile immediately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64387 | CLICKJACKING</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64387</link><description>The web application is vulnerable to a so-called ‘clickjacking’ attack. In this type of attack, the vulnerable page is inserted into a page controlled by the attacker in order to deceive the victim. This deception can range from making the victim click on a button to making them enter their login credentials in a form that, a priori, appears legitimate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64388 | Denial of service through specific packets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64388</link><description>Denial of service of the web server through specific requests to this protocol</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:35:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12460 | Stored XSS vulnerability in Afterlogic Aurora webmail</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12460</link><description>An XSS issue was discovered in Afterlogic Aurora webmail version 9.8.3 and below. An attacker can send a specially crafted HTML e-mail message with JavaScript in an img HTML tag. This could allow a remote attacker to load arbitrary JavaScript code in the context of a webmail user's browser window, and access user data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:11:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12521 | Analytify Pro &amp;lt;= 7.0.3 - Unauthenticated Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12521</link><description>The Analytify Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 7.0.3 via the Analytify Tag HTML details. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract usernames from source code. While we generally do not assign CVE IDs to username exposure issues, this vendor has specifically requested we consider it a vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:54:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64386 | Denial of service through specific requests.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64386</link><description>The device's web server stops working after suffering a DoS attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33003 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server is vulnerable to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33003</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7.0.0 through 11.7.1.6 could allow a non-root user to gain higher privileges/capabilities within the scope of a container due to execution with unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36249 | IBM Jazz for Service Management is vulnerable to &amp;quot;filter&amp;quot; cookie not sent over SSL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36249</link><description>IBM Jazz for Service Management 1.1.3.0 through 1.1.3.25 does not set the secure attribute on authorization tokens or session cookies. Attackers may be able to get the cookie values by sending a http:// link to a user or by planting this link in a site the user goes to. The cookie will be sent to the insecure link and the attacker can then obtain the cookie value by snooping the traffic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13992 | Nagios XI &amp;lt; 2024R1.1 XSS via Missing Page / 404</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13992</link><description>Nagios XI versions prior to &lt; 2024R1.1 is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting (XSS) when a user visits the "missing page" (404) page after following a link from another website. The vulnerable component, page-missing.php, fails to properly validate or escape user-supplied input, allowing an attacker to craft a malicious link that, when visited by a victim, executes arbitrary JavaScript in the victim’s browser within the Nagios XI domain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:21:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4952 | Denial-of-service vulnerability in ESET security products for Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4952</link><description>Tampering of the registry entries might have led to preventing the ESET security products from starting correctly on the next system startup or to unauthorized changes in the product's configuration.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58147 | x86: Incorrect input sanitisation in Viridian hypercalls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58147</link><description>[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

Some Viridian hypercalls can specify a mask of vCPU IDs as an input, in
one of three formats.  Xen has boundary checking bugs with all three
formats, which can cause out-of-bounds reads and writes while processing
the inputs.

 * CVE-2025-58147.  Hypercalls using the HV_VP_SET Sparse format can
   cause vpmask_set() to write out of bounds when converting the bitmap
   to Xen's format.

 * CVE-2025-58148.  Hypercalls using any input format can cause
   send_ipi() to read d-&gt;vcpu[] out-of-bounds, and operate on a wild
   vCPU pointer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:58:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58148 | x86: Incorrect input sanitisation in Viridian hypercalls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58148</link><description>[This CNA information record relates to multiple CVEs; the
text explains which aspects/vulnerabilities correspond to which CVE.]

Some Viridian hypercalls can specify a mask of vCPU IDs as an input, in
one of three formats.  Xen has boundary checking bugs with all three
formats, which can cause out-of-bounds reads and writes while processing
the inputs.

 * CVE-2025-58147.  Hypercalls using the HV_VP_SET Sparse format can
   cause vpmask_set() to write out of bounds when converting the bitmap
   to Xen's format.

 * CVE-2025-58148.  Hypercalls using any input format can cause
   send_ipi() to read d-&gt;vcpu[] out-of-bounds, and operate on a wild
   vCPU pointer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58149 | Incorrect removal of permissions on PCI device unplug</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58149</link><description>When passing through PCI devices, the detach logic in libxl won't remove
access permissions to any 64bit memory BARs the device might have.  As a
result a domain can still have access any 64bit memory BAR when such
device is no longer assigned to the domain.

For PV domains the permission leak allows the domain itself to map the memory
in the page-tables.  For HVM it would require a compromised device model or
stubdomain to map the leaked memory into the HVM domain p2m.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:58:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64350 | WordPress Rank Math SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.252.1 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64350</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Rank Math SEO Rank Math SEO seo-by-rank-math allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Rank Math SEO: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.252.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64351 | WordPress Rank Math SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.252.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64351</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in Rank Math SEO Rank Math SEO seo-by-rank-math allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects Rank Math SEO: from n/a through &lt;= 1.0.252.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64352 | WordPress Essential Addons for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.4 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64352</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WPDeveloper Essential Addons for Elementor essential-addons-for-elementor-lite allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Essential Addons for Elementor: from n/a through &lt;= 6.2.4.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64353 | WordPress Polylang plugin &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64353</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Chouby Polylang polylang allows Object Injection.This issue affects Polylang: from n/a through &lt;= 3.7.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64354 | WordPress Gutenberg plugin &amp;lt;= 21.8.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64354</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matias Ventura Gutenberg gutenberg allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Gutenberg: from n/a through &lt;= 21.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64356 | WordPress Insert PHP Code Snippet plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64356</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in f1logic Insert PHP Code Snippet insert-php-code-snippet allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Insert PHP Code Snippet: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64357 | WordPress Advanced Database Cleaner plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64357</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Younes JFR. Advanced Database Cleaner advanced-database-cleaner allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Advanced Database Cleaner: from n/a through &lt;= 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64358 | WordPress Smart Coupons for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64358</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WebToffee Smart Coupons for WooCommerce wt-smart-coupons-for-woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Smart Coupons for WooCommerce: from n/a through &lt;= 2.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64359 | WordPress Consulting theme &amp;lt; 6.7.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64359</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting consulting allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting: from n/a through &lt; 6.7.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64360 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64360</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets consulting-elementor-widgets allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64361 | WordPress Consulting Elementor Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64361</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Consulting Elementor Widgets consulting-elementor-widgets allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Consulting Elementor Widgets: from n/a through &lt;= 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64362 | WordPress K Elements plugin &amp;lt; 5.5.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64362</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SeventhQueen K Elements k-elements allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects K Elements: from n/a through &lt; 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64363 | WordPress Kleo theme &amp;lt; 5.5.0 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64363</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in SeventhQueen Kleo kleo allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Kleo: from n/a through &lt; 5.5.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64364 | WordPress Masterstudy theme &amp;lt; 4.8.126 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64364</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in StylemixThemes Masterstudy masterstudy allows PHP Local File Inclusion.This issue affects Masterstudy: from n/a through &lt; 4.8.126.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64365 | WordPress Ohio Extra plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64365</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in colabrio Ohio Extra ohio-extra allows DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Ohio Extra: from n/a through &lt;= 3.6.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64366 | WordPress MasterStudy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.6.27 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64366</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Stylemix MasterStudy LMS masterstudy-lms-learning-management-system allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects MasterStudy LMS: from n/a through &lt;= 3.6.27.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64367 | WordPress Groundhogg plugin &amp;lt;= 4.2.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64367</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Adrian Tobey Groundhogg groundhogg allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Groundhogg: from n/a through &lt;= 4.2.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-64368 | WordPress Bard theme &amp;lt;= 1.6 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-64368</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Mikado-Themes Bard bardwp allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Bard: from n/a through &lt;= 1.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:50:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40603 | A potential exposure of sensitive information in log files in SonicWall SMA100 Series appliances may allow a remote, authenticated administr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40603</link><description>A potential exposure of sensitive information in log files in SonicWall SMA100 Series appliances may allow a remote, authenticated administrator, under certain conditions to view partial users credential data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11602 | Untargeted information leak in Bolt protocol handshake</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11602</link><description>Potential information leak in bolt protocol handshake in Neo4j Enterprise and Community editions allows attacker to obtain one byte of information from previous connections. The attacker has no control over the information leaked in server responses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:39:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11843 | Therefore™ Online and Therefore™ On-Premises contains an account impersonation issue, which could potentially allow the attacker to access all the stored data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11843</link><description>Therefore Corporation GmbH has recently become aware that Therefore™ Online and Therefore™ On-Premises contain an account impersonation vulnerability. A malicious user may potentially be able to impersonate the web service account or the account of a service using the API when connecting to the Therefore™ Server. If the malicious user gains this impersonation user access, then it is possible for them to access the documents stored in Therefore™. This impersonation is at application level (Therefore access level), not the operating system level.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:55:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40106 | comedi: fix divide-by-zero in comedi_buf_munge()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40106</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: fix divide-by-zero in comedi_buf_munge()

The comedi_buf_munge() function performs a modulo operation
`async-&gt;munge_chan %= async-&gt;cmd.chanlist_len` without first
checking if chanlist_len is zero. If a user program submits a command with
chanlist_len set to zero, this causes a divide-by-zero error when the device
processes data in the interrupt handler path.

Add a check for zero chanlist_len at the beginning of the
function, similar to the existing checks for !map and
CMDF_RAWDATA flag. When chanlist_len is zero, update
munge_count and return early, indicating the data was
handled without munging.

This prevents potential kernel panics from malformed user commands.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12041 | ERI File Library &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Protected File Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12041</link><description>The ERI File Library plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the 'erifl_file' AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to download files restricted to specific user roles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12115 | WPC Name Your Price for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 - Unauthenticated Price Alteration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12115</link><description>The WPC Name Your Price for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized price alteration in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.9. This is due to the plugin not disabling the ability to name a custom price when it has been specifically disabled for a product. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to purchase products at prices less than they should be able to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:34:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30189 | When cache is enabled, some passdb/userdb drivers incorrectly cache all users with same cache key, causing wrong cached information to be us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30189</link><description>When cache is enabled, some passdb/userdb drivers incorrectly cache all users with same cache key, causing wrong cached information to be used for these users. After cached login, all subsequent logins are for same user. Install fixed version or disable caching either globally or for the impacted passdb/userdb drivers. No publicly available exploits are known.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30188 | Malicious or unintentional API requests can be used to add significant amount of data to caches. Caches may evict information that is requir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30188</link><description>Malicious or unintentional API requests can be used to add significant amount of data to caches. Caches may evict information that is required to operate the web frontend, which leads to unavailability of the component. Please deploy the provided updates and patch releases. No publicly available exploits are known</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:14:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30191 | Malicious content from E-Mail can be used to perform a redressing attack. Users can be tricked to perform unintended actions or provide sens...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30191</link><description>Malicious content from E-Mail can be used to perform a redressing attack. Users can be tricked to perform unintended actions or provide sensitive information to a third party which would enable further threats. Attribute values containing HTML fragments are now denied by the sanitization procedure. No publicly available exploits are known</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-62232 | Apache APISIX: basic-auth logs plaintext credentials at info level</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-62232</link><description>Sensitive data exposure via logging in basic-auth leads to plaintext usernames and passwords written to error logs and forwarded to log sinks when log level is INFO/DEBUG. This creates a high risk of credential compromise through log access.
It has been fixed in the following commit:  https://github.com/apache/apisix/pull/12629 
Users are recommended to upgrade to version 3.14, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12094 | OOPSpam Anti-Spam: Spam Protection for WordPress Forms &amp;amp; Comments (No CAPTCHA) &amp;lt;= 1.2.53 - Unauthenticated IP Header Spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12094</link><description>The OOPSpam Anti-Spam: Spam Protection for WordPress Forms &amp; Comments (No CAPTCHA) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to IP Header Spoofing in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.53. This is due to the plugin trusting client-controlled forwarded headers (such as CF-Connecting-IP, X-Forwarded-For, and others) without verifying that those headers originate from legitimate, trusted proxies. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to spoof their IP address and bypass IP-based security controls, including blocked IP lists and rate limiting protections, by sending arbitrary HTTP headers with their requests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 08:41:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-12175 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.15.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Draft Event Title/QR Code Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-12175</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'tec_qr_code_modal' AJAX endpoint in all versions up to, and including, 6.15.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to view draft event names and generate/view QR codes for them.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 08:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8383 | Depicter &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8383</link><description>The Depicter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions less than, or equal to, 4.0.4. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the depicter-document-rules-store function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to modify document rules via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 08:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6520 | SQLi in Abis Technology&amp;#x27;s BAPSIS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6520</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Abis Technology BAPSIS allows Blind SQL Injection.This issue affects BAPSIS: before 202510271606.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:53:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-10897 | WooCommerce Designer Pro &amp;lt;= 1.9.28 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-10897</link><description>The WooCommerce Designer Pro theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file read in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.28. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the server, which can expose DB credentials when the wp-config.php file is read.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:36:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8385 | Zombify &amp;lt;= 1.7.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Path Traversal to Arbitrary File Read</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8385</link><description>The Zombify plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.5. This is due to insufficient input validation in the zf_get_file_by_url function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to read arbitrary files on the server, including sensitive system files like /etc/passwd, via a forged request. It's worth noting that successfully exploiting this vulnerability relies on a race condition as the file generated will be deleted immediately.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:36:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-63675 | cryptidy through 1.2.4 allows code execution via untrusted data because pickle.loads is used. This occurs in aes_decrypt_message in symmetri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-63675</link><description>cryptidy through 1.2.4 allows code execution via untrusted data because pickle.loads is used. This occurs in aes_decrypt_message in symmetric_encryption.py.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5397 | Jobmonster - Job Board WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.8.1 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5397</link><description>The Noo JobMonster theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 4.8.1. This is due to the check_login() function not properly verifying a user's identity prior to successfully authenticating them  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to bypass standard authentication and access administrative user accounts. Please note social login needs to be enabled in order for a site to be impacted by this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7846 | WordPress User Extra Fields &amp;lt;= 16.7 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion via save_fields Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7846</link><description>The WordPress User Extra Fields plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the save_fields() function in all versions up to, and including, 16.7. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8489 | King Addons for Elementor – Free Elements, Widgets, Templates, and Features for Elementor 24.12.92 - 51.1.14 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8489</link><description>The King Addons for Elementor – Free Elements, Widgets, Templates, and Features for Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in versions 24.12.92 to 51.1.14 . This is due to the plugin not properly restricting the roles that users can register with. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register with administrator-level user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11191 | RealPress &amp;lt; 1.1.0 - Unauthenticated Content Creation/Email Sending via REST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11191</link><description>The RealPress  WordPress plugin before 1.1.0 registers the REST routes without proper permission checks, allowing the creation of pages and sending of emails from the site.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 06:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54763 | FutureNet MA and IP-K series provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. contain an OS command Injection vulnerability. A user who logs in to the ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54763</link><description>FutureNet MA and IP-K series provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. contain an OS command Injection vulnerability. A user who logs in to the Web UI of the product may execute an arbitrary OS command.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 06:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-58152 | FutureNet MA and IP-K series provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. put the firmware version and the garbage collection information on the in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-58152</link><description>FutureNet MA and IP-K series provided by Century Systems Co., Ltd. put the firmware version and the garbage collection information on the internal web page. With some crafted HTTP request, they can be accessed without authentication.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 06:28:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11806 | Qzzr Shortcode Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11806</link><description>The Qzzr Shortcode Plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'qzzr' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on the 'quiz' attribute. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-11975 | FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp;amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) &amp;lt;= 1.1.23.0 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sync Rule Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-11975</link><description>The FuseWP – WordPress User Sync to Email List &amp; Marketing Automation (Mailchimp, Constant Contact, ActiveCampaign etc.) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the save_changes() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.23.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add and edit sync rules.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:04:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23050 | QLowEnergyController in Qt before 6.8.2 mishandles malformed Bluetooth ATT commands, leading to an out-of-bounds read (or division by zero)....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23050</link><description>QLowEnergyController in Qt before 6.8.2 mishandles malformed Bluetooth ATT commands, leading to an out-of-bounds read (or division by zero). This is fixed in 5.15.19, 6.5.9, and 6.8.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6176 | Brotli decompression bomb DoS in scrapy/scrapy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6176</link><description>Scrapy versions up to 2.13.2 are vulnerable to a denial of service (DoS) attack due to a flaw in its brotli decompression implementation. The protection mechanism against decompression bombs fails to mitigate the brotli variant, allowing remote servers to crash clients with less than 80GB of available memory. This occurs because brotli can achieve extremely high compression ratios for zero-filled data, leading to excessive memory consumption during decompression.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>