<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:37:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-6259 | Local Access to Sensitive Data in Brivo ACS100 and ACS300 </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6259</link><description>Insufficiently Protected Credentials, : Improper Access Control vulnerability in Brivo ACS100, ACS300 allows Password Recovery Exploitation, Bypassing Physical Security.This issue affects ACS100, ACS300: from 5.2.4 before 6.2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6260 | Web UI OS Command Injection in Brivo ACS100, ACS300</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6260</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in Brivo ACS100, ACS300 allows OS Command Injection, Bypassing Physical Security.This issue affects ACS100 (Network Adjacent Access), ACS300 (Physical Access): from 5.2.4 before 6.2.4.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1635 | Undertow: out-of-memory error after several closed connections with wildfly-http-client protocol</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1635</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Undertow. This vulnerability impacts a server that supports the wildfly-http-client protocol. Whenever a malicious user opens and closes a connection with the HTTP port of the server and then closes the connection immediately, the server will end with both memory and open file limits exhausted at some point, depending on the amount of memory available. &#13;
&#13;
At HTTP upgrade to remoting, the WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit leaks connections if RemotingConnection is closed by Remoting ServerConnectionOpenListener. Because the remoting connection originates in Undertow as part of the HTTP upgrade, there is an external layer to the remoting connection. This connection is unaware of the outermost layer when closing the connection during the connection opening procedure. Hence, the Undertow WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit is not notified of the closed connection in this scenario. Because WriteTimeoutStreamSinkConduit creates a timeout task, the whole dependency tree leaks via that task, which is added to XNIO WorkerThread. So, the workerThread points to the Undertow conduit, which contains the connections and causes the leak.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1638 | Bluetooth characteristic LESC security requirement not enforced without additional flags</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1638</link><description>The documentation specifies that the BT_GATT_PERM_READ_LESC and BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_LESC defines for a Bluetooth characteristic: Attribute read/write permission with LE Secure Connection encryption. If set, requires that LE Secure Connections is used for read/write access, however this is only true when it is combined with other permissions, namely BT_GATT_PERM_READ_ENCRYPT/BT_GATT_PERM_READ_AUTHEN (for read) or BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_ENCRYPT/BT_GATT_PERM_WRITE_AUTHEN (for write), if these additional permissions are not set (even in secure connections only mode) then the stack does not perform any permission checks on these characteristics and they can be freely written/read.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 21:27:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25640 | Improper Neutralization of Alternate XSS Syntax in iris-web</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25640</link><description>Iris is a web collaborative platform that helps incident responders share technical details during investigations. A stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been identified in iris-web, affecting multiple locations in versions prior to v2.4.0. The vulnerability may allow an attacker to inject malicious scripts into the application, which could then be executed when a user visits the affected locations. This could lead to unauthorized access, data theft, or other related malicious activities. An attacker need to be authenticated on the application to exploit this vulnerability. The issue is fixed in version v2.4.0 of iris-web. No workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 20:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25634 | IDOR make user can read e-mail log sent by other events</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25634</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system. Prior to version 2.0-Mr-2402, an attacker can access data from other organizers. The attacker can use a specially crafted request to receive the e-mail log sent by other events. Version 2.0-M4-2402 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25635 | IDOR Vulnerability: Allowing Organization Owner to view the other Organizations API KEY and USERS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25635</link><description>alf.io is an open source ticket reservation system. Prior to version 2.0-Mr-2402, organization owners can view the generated API KEY and USERS of other organization owners using the `http://192.168.26.128:8080/admin/api/users/&lt;user_id&gt;` endpoint, which exposes the details of the provided user ID. This may also expose the API KEY in the username of the user. Version 2.0-M4-2402 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:52:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25636 | Lack of media type verification of Activity Streams objects allows impersonation and takeover of remote accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25636</link><description>Misskey is an open source, decentralized social media platform with ActivityPub support. Prior to version 2024.2.0, when fetching remote Activity Streams objects, Misskey doesn't check that the response from the remote server has a `Content-Type` header value of the Activity Streams media type, which allows a threat actor to upload a crafted Activity Streams document to a remote server and make a Misskey instance fetch it, if the remote server accepts arbitrary user uploads. The vulnerability allows a threat actor to impersonate and take over an account on a remote server that satisfies all of the following properties: allows the threat actor to register an account; accepts arbitrary user-uploaded documents and places them on the same domain as legitimate Activity Streams actors; and serves user-uploaded document in response to requests with an `Accept` header value of the Activity Streams media type. Version 2024.2.0 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25626 | Yocto Project Security Advisory - BitBake/Toaster</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25626</link><description>Yocto Project is an open source collaboration project that helps developers create custom Linux-based systems regardless of the hardware architecture. In Yocto Projects Bitbake before 2.6.2 (before and included Yocto Project 4.3.1), with the Toaster server (included in bitbake) running, missing input validation allows an attacker to perform a remote code execution in the server's shell via a crafted HTTP request. Authentication is not necessary. Toaster server execution has to be specifically run and is not the default for Bitbake command line builds, it is only used for the Toaster web based user interface to Bitbake. The fix has been backported to the bitbake included with Yocto Project 5.0, 3.1.31, 4.0.16, and 4.3.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50257 | Disconnect Vulnerability in RTPS Packets Used by SROS2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50257</link><description>eProsima Fast DDS (formerly Fast RTPS) is a C++ implementation of the Data Distribution Service standard of the Object Management Group. Even with the application of SROS2, due to the issue where the data (`p[UD]`) and `guid` values used to disconnect between nodes are not encrypted, a vulnerability has been discovered where a malicious attacker can forcibly disconnect a Subscriber and can deny a Subscriber attempting to connect. Afterwards, if the attacker sends the packet for disconnecting, which is data (`p[UD]`), to the Global Data Space (`239.255.0.1:7400`) using the said Publisher ID, all the Subscribers (Listeners) connected to the Publisher (Talker) will not receive any data and their connection will be disconnected. Moreover, if this disconnection packet is sent continuously, the Subscribers (Listeners) trying to connect will not be able to do so. Since the initial commit of the `SecurityManager.cpp` code (`init`, `on_process_handshake`) on Nov 8, 2016, the Disconnect Vulnerability in RTPS Packets Used by SROS2 has been present prior to versions 2.13.0, 2.12.2, 2.11.3, 2.10.3, and 2.6.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 19:32:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1633 | FIP Header Integer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1633</link><description>During the secure boot, bl2 (the second stage of
the bootloader) loops over images defined in the table “bl2_mem_params_descs”.
For each image, the bl2 reads the image length and destination from the image’s
certificate. Because of the way of reading from the image, which base on 32-bit unsigned integer value, it can result to an integer overflow. An attacker can bypass memory range restriction and write data out of buffer bounds, which could result in bypass of secure boot.

 Affected git version from c2f286820471ed276c57e603762bd831873e5a17 until (not</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25981 | Msa-24-0004: forum export did not respect activity group settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25981</link><description>Separate Groups mode restrictions were not honored when performing a forum export, which would export forum data for all groups. By default this only provided additional access to non-editing teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25982 | Msa-24-0005: csrf risk in language import utility</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25982</link><description>The link to update all installed language packs did not include the necessary token to prevent a CSRF risk.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25983 | Msa-24-0006: idor on dashboard comments block</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25983</link><description>Insufficient checks in a web service made it possible to add comments to the comments block on another user's dashboard when it was not otherwise available (e.g., on their profile page).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:45:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25978 | Msa-24-0001: denial of service risk in file picker unzip functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25978</link><description>Insufficient file size checks resulted in a denial of service risk in the file picker's unzip functionality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25979 | Msa-24-0002: forum search accepted random parameters in its url</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25979</link><description>The URL parameters accepted by forum search were not limited to the allowed parameters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25980 | Msa-24-0003: h5p attempts report did not respect activity group settings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25980</link><description>Separate Groups mode restrictions were not honored in the H5P attempts report, which would display users from other groups. By default this only provided additional access to non-editing teachers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25625 | Pimcore Host Header Injection in user invitation link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25625</link><description>Pimcore's Admin Classic Bundle provides a Backend UI for Pimcore. A potential security vulnerability has been discovered in `pimcore/admin-ui-classic-bundle` prior to version 1.3.4. The vulnerability involves a Host Header Injection in the `invitationLinkAction` function of the UserController, specifically in the way `$loginUrl` trusts user input.  The host header from incoming HTTP requests is used unsafely when generating URLs. An attacker can manipulate the HTTP host header in requests to the /admin/user/invitationlink endpoint, resulting in the generation of URLs with the attacker's domain. In fact, if a host header is injected in the POST request, the $loginURL parameter is constructed with this unvalidated host header. It is then used to send an invitation email to the provided user. This vulnerability can be used to perform phishing attacks by making the URLs in the invitation links emails point to an attacker-controlled domain. Version 1.3.4 contains a patch for the vulnerability. The maintainers recommend validating the host header and ensuring it matches the application's domain. It would also be beneficial to use a default trusted host or hostname if the incoming host header is not recognized or is absent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25623 | Lack of media type verification of Activity Streams objects allows impersonation of remote accounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25623</link><description>Mastodon is a free, open-source social network server based on ActivityPub. Prior to versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19, when fetching remote statuses, Mastodon doesn't check that the response from the remote server has a `Content-Type` header value of the Activity Streams media type, which allows a threat actor to upload a crafted Activity Streams document to a remote server and make a Mastodon server fetch it, if the remote server accepts arbitrary user uploads. The vulnerability allows a threat actor to impersonate an account on a remote server that satisfies all of the following properties: allows the attacker to register an account; accepts arbitrary user-uploaded documents and places them on the same domain as the ActivityPub actors; and serves user-uploaded document in response to requests with an `Accept` header value of the Activity Streams media type. Versions 4.2.7, 4.1.15, 4.0.15, and 3.5.19 contain a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1597 | pgjdbc SQL Injection via line comment generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1597</link><description>pgjdbc, the PostgreSQL JDBC Driver, allows attacker to inject SQL if using PreferQueryMode=SIMPLE. Note this is not the default. In the default mode there is no vulnerability. A placeholder for a numeric value must be immediately preceded by a minus. There must be a second placeholder for a string value after the first placeholder; both must be on the same line. By constructing a matching string payload, the attacker can inject SQL to alter the query,bypassing the protections that parameterized queries bring against SQL Injection attacks. Versions before 42.7.2, 42.6.1, 42.5.5, 42.4.4, 42.3.9, and 42.2.8 are affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1346 | Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1346</link><description>Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree affects version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to calculate the root password of the MySQL database used by LaborOfficeFree using two constants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1343 | Weak permission vulnerability in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1343</link><description>A weak permission was found in the backup directory in LaborOfficeFree affecting version 19.10. This vulnerability allows any authenticated user to read backup files in the directory '%programfiles(x86)% LaborOfficeFree BackUp'.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1344 | Encrypted database credentials in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1344</link><description>Encrypted database credentials in LaborOfficeFree affecting version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to read and extract the username and password from the database of 'LOF_service.exe' and 'LaborOfficeFree.exe' located in the '%programfiles(x86)%\LaborOfficeFree\' directory. This user can log in remotely and has root-like privileges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1345 | Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1345</link><description>Weak MySQL database root password in LaborOfficeFree affects version 19.10. This vulnerability allows an attacker to perform a brute force attack and easily discover the root password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1580 | Integer overflow in VideoLAN dav1d</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1580</link><description>An integer overflow in dav1d AV1 decoder that can occur when decoding videos with large frame size. This can lead to memory corruption within the AV1 decoder. We recommend upgrading past version 1.4.0 of dav1d.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 10:43:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25710 | Apache Commons Compress: Denial of service caused by an infinite loop for a corrupted DUMP file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25710</link><description>Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition ('Infinite Loop') vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.3 through 1.25.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26.0 which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26308 | Apache Commons Compress: OutOfMemoryError unpacking broken Pack200 file</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26308</link><description>Allocation of Resources Without Limits or Throttling vulnerability in Apache Commons Compress.This issue affects Apache Commons Compress: from 1.21 before 1.26.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.26, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24722 | An unquoted service path vulnerability in the 12d Synergy Server and File Replication Server components may allow an attacker to gain elevat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24722</link><description>An unquoted service path vulnerability in the 12d Synergy Server and File Replication Server components may allow an attacker to gain elevated privileges via the 12d Synergy Server and/or 12d Synergy File Replication Server executable service path. This is fixed in 4.3.10.192, 5.1.5.221, and 5.1.6.235.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 06:19:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26327 | An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c mishandles the situation where a guest writes NumVF...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26327</link><description>An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c mishandles the situation where a guest writes NumVFs greater than TotalVFs, leading to a buffer overflow in VF implementations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26328 | An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c does not set NumVFs to PCI_SRIOV_TOTAL_VF, and thus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26328</link><description>An issue was discovered in QEMU 7.1.0 through 8.2.1. register_vfs in hw/pci/pcie_sriov.c does not set NumVFs to PCI_SRIOV_TOTAL_VF, and thus interaction with hw/nvme/ctrl.c is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 04:48:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-26318 | Serenity before 6.8.0 allows XSS via an email link because LoginPage.tsx permits return URLs that do not begin with a / character.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-26318</link><description>Serenity before 6.8.0 allows XSS via an email link because LoginPage.tsx permits return URLs that do not begin with a / character.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 03:51:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36774 | plugins/gtk+/glade-gtk-box.c in GNOME Glade before 3.38.1 and 3.39.x before 3.40.0 mishandles widget rebuilding for GladeGtkBox, leading to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36774</link><description>plugins/gtk+/glade-gtk-box.c in GNOME Glade before 3.38.1 and 3.39.x before 3.40.0 mishandles widget rebuilding for GladeGtkBox, leading to a denial of service (application crash).</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 01:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48624 | close_altfile in filename.c in less before 606 omits shell_quote calls for LESSCLOSE.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48624</link><description>close_altfile in filename.c in less before 606 omits shell_quote calls for LESSCLOSE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 01:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5779 | can: out of bounds in remove_rx_filter function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5779</link><description>can: out of bounds in remove_rx_filter function</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:50:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6249 | ipm: signed to unsigned conversion problem in esp32_ipm_send</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6249</link><description>Signed to unsigned conversion esp32_ipm_send</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6749 | Unchecked user input length in the Zephyr Settings Shell</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6749</link><description>Unchecked length coming from user input in settings shell</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 07:11:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48621 | Vulnerability of missing authentication for critical functions in the Wi-Fi module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48621</link><description>Vulnerability of missing authentication for critical functions in the Wi-Fi module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52378 | Vulnerability of incorrect service logic in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause feature...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52378</link><description>Vulnerability of incorrect service logic in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52379 | Permission control vulnerability in the calendarProvider module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52379</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the calendarProvider module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52380 | Vulnerability of improper access control in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentialit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52380</link><description>Vulnerability of improper access control in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52381 | Script injection vulnerability in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52381</link><description>Script injection vulnerability in the email module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52375 | Permission control vulnerability in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52375</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the WindowManagerServices module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52376 | Information management vulnerability in the Gallery module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52376</link><description>Information management vulnerability in the Gallery module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52377 | Vulnerability of input data not being verified in the cellular data module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause out-of-bo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52377</link><description>Vulnerability of input data not being verified in the cellular data module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause out-of-bounds access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52374 | Permission control vulnerability in the package management module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confident...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52374</link><description>Permission control vulnerability in the package management module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 04:12:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52372 | Vulnerability of input parameter verification in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52372</link><description>Vulnerability of input parameter verification in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:57:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52373 | Vulnerability of permission verification in the content sharing pop-up module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52373</link><description>Vulnerability of permission verification in the content sharing pop-up module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file sharing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:57:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52369 | Stack overflow vulnerability in the NFC module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52369</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in the NFC module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52370 | Stack overflow vulnerability in the network acceleration module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file ac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52370</link><description>Stack overflow vulnerability in the network acceleration module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause unauthorized file access.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52371 | Vulnerability of null references in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52371</link><description>Vulnerability of null references in the motor module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:50:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52368 | Input verification vulnerability in the account module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormall...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52368</link><description>Input verification vulnerability in the account module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52366 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52366</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52367 | Vulnerability of improper access control in the media library module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52367</link><description>Vulnerability of improper access control in the media library module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service availability and integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52365 | Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52365</link><description>Out-of-bounds read vulnerability in the smart activity recognition module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause features to perform abnormally.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:21:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52358 | Vulnerability of configuration defects in some APIs of the audio module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52358</link><description>Vulnerability of configuration defects in some APIs of the audio module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52360 | Logic vulnerabilities in the baseband.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52360</link><description>Logic vulnerabilities in the baseband.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52361 | The VerifiedBoot module has a vulnerability that may cause authentication errors.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52361</link><description>The VerifiedBoot module has a vulnerability that may cause authentication errors.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect integrity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52362 | Permission management vulnerability in the lock screen module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52362</link><description>Permission management vulnerability in the lock screen module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52363 | Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the Control Panel module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52363</link><description>Vulnerability of defects introduced in the design process in the Control Panel module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause app processes to be started by mistake.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52097 | Vulnerability of foreground service restrictions being bypassed in the NMS module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52097</link><description>Vulnerability of foreground service restrictions being bypassed in the NMS module.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52357 | Vulnerability of serialization/deserialization mismatch in the vibration framework.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52357</link><description>Vulnerability of serialization/deserialization mismatch in the vibration framework.Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52387 | Resource reuse vulnerability in the GPU module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52387</link><description>Resource reuse vulnerability in the GPU module. Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41737 | IBM Spectrum Scale security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41737</link><description>IBM Storage Scale Container Native Storage Access 5.1.2.1 through 5.1.7.0 could allow a local attacker to initiate connections from a container outside the current namespace.  IBM X-Force ID:  237811.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:25:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-41738 | IBM Spectrum Scale security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-41738</link><description>IBM Storage Scale Container Native Storage Access 5.1.2.1 -through 5.1.7.0 could allow an attacker to initiate connections to containers from external networks.  IBM X-Force ID:  237812.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-42443 | Trusteer for mobile file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-42443</link><description>An undisclosed issue in Trusteer iOS SDK for mobile versions prior to 5.7 and Trusteer Android SDK for mobile versions prior to 5.7 may allow uploading of files.  IBM X-Force ID:  238535.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50951 | IBM QRadar Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50951</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.17.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 in some circumstances will log some sensitive information about invalid authorization attempts.  IBM X-Force ID:  275747.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 16:09:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22336 | IBM QRadar Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22336</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.17.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  279976.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 15:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22337 | IBM QRadar Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22337</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.17.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  279977.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 15:48:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22335 | IBM QRadar Suite information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22335</link><description>IBM QRadar Suite 1.10.12.0 through 1.10.17.0 and IBM Cloud Pak for Security 1.10.0.0 through 1.10.11.0 stores potentially sensitive information in log files that could be read by a local user.  IBM X-Force ID:  279975.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0610 | The Piraeus Bank WooCommerce Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'MerchantReference...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0610</link><description>The Piraeus Bank WooCommerce Payment Gateway plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based blind SQL Injection via the 'MerchantReference' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.5.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-1512 | The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union based SQL Injection via ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-1512</link><description>The MasterStudy LMS WordPress Plugin – for Online Courses and Education plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to union based SQL Injection via the 'user' parameter of the /lms/stm-lms/order/items REST route in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.5 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 07:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25297 | Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bludit CMS version 3.15, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25297</link><description>Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bludit CMS version 3.15, allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via edit-content.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 06:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25298 | An issue was discovered in REDAXO version 5.15.1, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via modules.mo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25298</link><description>An issue was discovered in REDAXO version 5.15.1, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and obtain sensitive information via modules.modules.php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:53:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25468 | An issue in TOTOLINK X5000R V.9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the host_time parameter of the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25468</link><description>An issue in TOTOLINK X5000R V.9.1.0u.6369_B20230113 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the host_time parameter of the NTPSyncWithHost component.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:45:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21492 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Insufficient Session Expiration due to improper user sessio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21492</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Insufficient Session Expiration due to improper user session invalidation upon clicking the "Sign Out" button. User sessions remain valid even after requests are sent to /logout and /oauth2/google/logout. Attackers who gain access to an active but supposedly logged-out session can perform unauthorized actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21493 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Array Index when parsing a Caddyfile...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21493</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Validation of Array Index when parsing a Caddyfile. Multiple parsing functions in the affected library do not validate whether their input values are nil before attempting to access elements, which can lead to a panic (index out of range). Panics during the parsing of a configuration file may introduce ambiguity and vulnerabilities, hindering the correct interpretation and configuration of the web server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21494 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass by Spoofing via the X-Forwarded-For h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21494</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Authentication Bypass by Spoofing via the X-Forwarded-For header due to improper input sanitization. An attacker can spoof an IP address used in the user identity module (/whoami API endpoint). This could lead to unauthorized access if the system trusts this spoofed IP address.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21495 | Versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security before 1.0.42 are vulnerable to Insecure Randomness due to using an insecure rand...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21495</link><description>Versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security before 1.0.42 are vulnerable to Insecure Randomness due to using an insecure random number generation library which could possibly be predicted via a brute-force search. Attackers could use the potentially predictable nonce value used for authentication purposes in the OAuth flow to conduct OAuth replay attacks. In addition, insecure randomness is used while generating multifactor authentication (MFA) secrets and creating API keys in the database package.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21496 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Referer header, due to i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21496</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting (XSS) via the Referer header, due to improper input sanitization. Although the Referer header is sanitized by escaping some characters that can allow XSS (e.g., [&amp;], [&lt;], [&gt;], ["], [']), it does not account for the attack based on the JavaScript URL scheme (e.g., javascript:alert(document.domain)// payload). Exploiting this vulnerability may not be trivial, but it could lead to the execution of malicious scripts in the context of the target user’s browser, compromising user sessions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21497 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Open Redirect via the redirect_url parameter. An attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21497</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Open Redirect via the redirect_url parameter. An attacker could perform a phishing attack and trick users into visiting a malicious website by crafting a convincing URL with this parameter. To exploit this vulnerability, the user must take an action, such as clicking on a portal button or using the browser’s back button, to trigger the redirection.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21498 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) via X-Forwarded-Host hea...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21498</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Server-side Request Forgery (SSRF) via X-Forwarded-Host header manipulation. An attacker can expose sensitive information, interact with internal services, or exploit other vulnerabilities within the network by exploiting this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21499 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to HTTP Header Injection via the X-Forwarded-Proto header due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21499</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to HTTP Header Injection via the X-Forwarded-Proto header due to redirecting to the injected protocol.Exploiting this vulnerability could lead to bypass of security mechanisms or confusion in handling TLS.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21500 | All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21500</link><description>All versions of the package github.com/greenpau/caddy-security are vulnerable to Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts via the two-factor authentication (2FA). Although the application blocks the user after several failed attempts to provide 2FA codes, attackers can bypass this blocking mechanism by automating the application’s full multistep 2FA process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 05:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22727 | Teltonika TRB1-series devices with firmware before TRB1_R_00.07.05.2 allow attackers to exploit a firmware vulnerability via Ethernet LAN or...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22727</link><description>Teltonika TRB1-series devices with firmware before TRB1_R_00.07.05.2 allow attackers to exploit a firmware vulnerability via Ethernet LAN or USB.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-31728 | Teltonika RUT240 devices with firmware before 07.04.2, when bridge mode is used, sometimes make SSH and HTTP services available on the IPv6 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-31728</link><description>Teltonika RUT240 devices with firmware before 07.04.2, when bridge mode is used, sometimes make SSH and HTTP services available on the IPv6 WAN interface even though the UI shows that they are only available on the LAN interface.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 04:17:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20915 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20915</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20917 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20917</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20919 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20919</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20921 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20921</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20923 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20923</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20925 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20925</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20927 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20927</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20929 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20929</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20931 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20931</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20933 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20933</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20935 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20935</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20937 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20937</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20939 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20939</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20941 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20941</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20943 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20943</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20945 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20945</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20947 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20947</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20949 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20949</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20951 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20951</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20953 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20953</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20956 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20956</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20958 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20958</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20960 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20960</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20962 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20962</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20964 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20964</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20966 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20966</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20968 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20968</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20970 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20970</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20972 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20972</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20974 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20974</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20976 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20976</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20978 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20978</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20980 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20980</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20982 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20982</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20984 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20984</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20986 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20986</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21833 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21833</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20903 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20903</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20905 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20905</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20907 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20907</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20909 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20909</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20911 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20911</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-20913 | No english description</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-20913</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:52:14 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>