<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 23:18:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2023-49554 | Use After Free vulnerability in YASM 1.3.0.86.g9def allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the do_directive function in t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49554</link><description>Use After Free vulnerability in YASM 1.3.0.86.g9def allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the do_directive function in the modules/preprocs/nasm/nasm-pp.c component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 23:18:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49552 | An Out of Bounds Write in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_op_json_stringify function in...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49552</link><description>An Out of Bounds Write in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_op_json_stringify function in the msj.c file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49553 | An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_destroy function in the msj.c file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49553</link><description>An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_destroy function in the msj.c file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:49:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49551 | An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_op_json_parse function in the msj.c file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49551</link><description>An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_op_json_parse function in the msj.c file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48418 | User Build misconfiguration resulting in local escalation of privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48418</link><description>In checkDebuggingDisallowed of DeviceVersionFragment.java, there is a
    possible way to access adb before SUW completion due to an insecure default
    value. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional
    execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for
    exploitation</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:32:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49549 | An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_getretvalpos function in the msj.c file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49549</link><description>An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs_getretvalpos function in the msj.c file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:32:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49550 | An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs+0x4ec508 component.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49550</link><description>An issue in Cesanta mjs 2.20.0 allows a remote attacker to cause a denial of service via the mjs+0x4ec508 component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:32:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0196 | Magic-Api code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0196</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Magic-Api up to 2.0.1 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /resource/file/api/save?auto=1. The manipulation leads to code injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249511.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21632 | omniauth-microsoft_graph vulnerable to account takeover (nOAuth)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21632</link><description>omniauth-microsoft_graph provides an Omniauth strategy for the Microsoft Graph API. Prior to versions 2.0.0, the implementation did not validate the legitimacy of the `email` attribute of the user nor did it give/document an option to do so, making it susceptible to nOAuth misconfiguration in cases when the `email` is used as a trusted user identifier. This could lead to account takeover. Version 2.0.0 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 22:15:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50020 | An issue was discovered in open5gs v2.6.6. SIGPIPE can be used to crash AMF.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50020</link><description>An issue was discovered in open5gs v2.6.6. SIGPIPE can be used to crash AMF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6339 | Google Nest WiFi Pro root code-execution &amp;amp; user-data compromise</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6339</link><description>Google Nest WiFi Pro root code-execution &amp; user-data compromise</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:55:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50019 | An issue was discovered in open5gs v2.6.6. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect err...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50019</link><description>An issue was discovered in open5gs v2.6.6. InitialUEMessage, Registration request sent at a specific time can crash AMF due to incorrect error handling of Nudm_UECM_Registration response.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:45:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26624 | A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26624</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts via the ID parameter after the login portal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26625 | A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26625</link><description>A SQL injection vulnerability was discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier which allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts via the 'user_id' parameter after the login portal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:45:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-26623 | SQL Injection vulnerability discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts via the Area...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-26623</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability discovered in Gila CMS 1.15.4 and earlier allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary web scripts via the Area parameter under the Administration&gt;Widget tab after the login portal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21629 | Erroneous handling of `record_external_operation` error return</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21629</link><description>Rust EVM is an Ethereum Virtual Machine interpreter. In `rust-evm`, a feature called `record_external_operation` was introduced, allowing library users to record custom gas changes. This feature can have some bogus interactions with the call stack. In particular, during finalization of a `CREATE` or `CREATE2`, in the case that the substack execution happens successfully, `rust-evm` will first commit the substate, and then call `record_external_operation(Write(out_code.len()))`. If `record_external_operation` later fails, this error is returned to the parent call stack, instead of `Succeeded`. Yet, the substate commitment already happened. This causes smart contracts able to commit state changes, when the parent caller contract receives zero address (which usually indicates that the execution has failed). This issue only impacts library users with custom `record_external_operation` that returns errors. The issue is patched in release 0.41.1. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:35:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4164 | There is a possible information disclosure due to a missing permission check in Pixel Watch</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4164</link><description>There is a possible information disclosure due to a missing permission check. This could lead to local information disclosure of health data with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21628 | XSS can be stored in DB from &amp;quot;add a message form&amp;quot; in order detail page (FO)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21628</link><description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Prior to version 8.1.3, the isCleanHtml method is not used on this this form, which makes it possible to store a cross-site scripting payload in the database. The impact is low because the HTML is not interpreted in BO, thanks to twig's escape mechanism. In FO, the cross-site scripting attack is effective, but only impacts the customer sending it, or the customer session from which it was sent. This issue affects those who have a module fetching these messages from the DB and displaying it without escaping HTML. Version 8.1.3 contains a patch for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0195 | spider-flow FunctionController.java FunctionService.saveFunction code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0195</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in spider-flow 0.4.3. Affected is the function FunctionService.saveFunction of the file src/main/java/org/spiderflow/controller/FunctionController.java. The manipulation leads to code injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249510 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21627 | Some attribute not escaped in Validate::isCleanHTML method</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21627</link><description>PrestaShop is an open-source e-commerce platform. Prior to versions 8.1.3 and 1.7.8.11, some event attributes are not detected by the `isCleanHTML` method. Some modules using the `isCleanHTML` method could be vulnerable to cross-site scripting. Versions 8.1.3 and 1.7.8.11 contain a patch for this issue. The best workaround is to use the `HTMLPurifier` library to sanitize html input coming from users. The library is already available as a dependency in the PrestaShop project. Beware though that in legacy object models, fields of `HTML` type will call `isCleanHTML`.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:13:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45561 | An issue in A-WORLD OIRASE BEER_waiting Line v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45561</link><description>An issue in A-WORLD OIRASE BEER_waiting Line v.13.6.1 allows attackers to send crafted notifications via leakage of the channel access token.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:56:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45893 | An indirect Object Reference (IDOR) in the Order and Invoice pages in Floorsight Customer Portal Q3 2023 allows an unauthenticated remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45893</link><description>An indirect Object Reference (IDOR) in the Order and Invoice pages in Floorsight Customer Portal Q3 2023 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to view sensitive customer information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45892 | An issue discovered in the Order and Invoice pages in Floorsight Insights Q3 2023 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to view sensitiv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45892</link><description>An issue discovered in the Order and Invoice pages in Floorsight Insights Q3 2023 allows an unauthenticated remote attacker to view sensitive customer information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0194 | CodeAstro Internet Banking System Profile Picture pages_account.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0194</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeAstro Internet Banking System up to 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file pages_account.php of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249509 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:37:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21623 | Arbitrary Expression Injection in github workflow leads to Command execution &amp;amp; leaking secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21623</link><description>OTCLient is an alternative tibia client for otserv. Prior to commit db560de0b56476c87a2f967466407939196dd254, the /mehah/otclient "`Analysis - SonarCloud`" workflow is vulnerable to an expression injection in Actions, allowing an attacker to run commands remotely on the runner, leak secrets, and alter the repository using this workflow. Commit db560de0b56476c87a2f967466407939196dd254 contains a fix for this issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:37:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47458 | An issue in SpringBlade v.3.7.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the lack of permissions control framework.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47458</link><description>An issue in SpringBlade v.3.7.0 and before allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the lack of permissions control framework.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50711 | `serde` deserialization for `FamStructWrapper` lacks bound checks that could potentially lead to out-of-bounds memory access</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50711</link><description>vmm-sys-util is a collection of modules that provides helpers and utilities used by multiple rust-vmm components. Starting in version 0.5.0 and prior to version 0.12.0, an issue in the `FamStructWrapper::deserialize` implementation provided by the crate for `vmm_sys_util::fam::FamStructWrapper` can lead to out of bounds memory accesses. The deserialization does not check that the length stored in the header matches the flexible array length. Mismatch in the lengths might allow out of bounds memory access through Rust-safe methods. The issue was corrected in version 0.12.0 by inserting a check that verifies the lengths of compared flexible arrays are equal for any deserialized header and aborting deserialization otherwise. Moreover, the API was changed so that header length can only be modified through Rust-unsafe code. This ensures that users cannot trigger out-of-bounds memory access from Rust-safe code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:11:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51652 | OWASP.AntiSamy mXSS when preserving comments</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51652</link><description>OWASP AntiSamy .NET is a library for performing cleansing of HTML coming from untrusted sources. Prior to version 1.2.0, there is a potential for a mutation cross-site scripting (mXSS) vulnerability in AntiSamy caused by flawed parsing of the HTML being sanitized. To be subject to this vulnerability the `preserveComments` directive must be enabled in your policy file and also allow for certain tags at the same time. As a result, certain crafty inputs can result in elements in comment tags being interpreted as executable when using AntiSamy's sanitized output. This is patched in OWASP AntiSamy .NET 1.2.0 and later. See important remediation details in the reference given below. As a workaround, manually edit the AntiSamy policy file (e.g., antisamy.xml) by deleting the `preserveComments` directive or setting its value to `false`,  if present. Also it would be useful to make AntiSamy remove the `noscript` tag by adding a line described in the GitHub Security Advisory to the tag definitions under the `&lt;tagrules&gt;` node, or deleting it entirely if present. As the previously mentioned policy settings are preconditions for the mXSS attack to work, changing them as recommended should be sufficient to protect you against this vulnerability when using a vulnerable version of this library. However, the existing bug would still be present in AntiSamy or its parser dependency (HtmlAgilityPack). The safety of this workaround relies on configurations that may change in the future and don't address the root cause of the vulnerability. As such, it is strongly recommended to upgrade to a fixed version of AntiSamy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0192 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Add Downloadable downloadable.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0192</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file downloadable.php of the component Add Downloadable. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249505 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:11:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49794 | The logic of get apk path in KernelSU module can be bypassed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49794</link><description>KernelSU is a Kernel-based root solution for Android devices. In versions 0.7.1 and prior, the logic of get apk path in KernelSU kernel module can be bypassed, which causes any malicious apk named `me.weishu.kernelsu` get root permission. If a KernelSU module installed device try to install any not checked apk which package name equal to the official KernelSU Manager, it can take over root privileges on the device. As of time of publication, a patched version is not available.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:11:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0191 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal file information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0191</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/uploads/. The manipulation leads to file and directory information exposure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249504.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 19:43:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7192 | Kernel: refcount leak in ctnetlink_create_conntrack()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7192</link><description>A memory leak problem was found in ctnetlink_create_conntrack in net/netfilter/nf_conntrack_netlink.c in the Linux Kernel. This issue may allow a local attacker with CAP_NET_ADMIN privileges to cause a denial of service (DoS) attack due to a refcount overflow.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 19:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48419 | An attacker in the wifi vicinity of a target Google Home can spy on the victim, resulting in EoP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48419</link><description>An attacker in the wifi vicinity of a target Google Home can spy on the victim, resulting in Elevation of Privilege</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:57:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-3010 | Predictable SSH credentials in Priva TopControl Suite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-3010</link><description>The Priva TopControl Suite contains predictable credentials for the SSH service, based on the Serial number. Which makes it possible for an attacker to calculate the login credentials for the Priva TopControll suite.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:36:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0190 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Quiz add_quiz.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0190</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file add_quiz.php of the component Quiz Handler. The manipulation of the argument Quiz Title/Quiz Description with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249503.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:36:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0193 | Kernel: netfilter: use-after-free in nft_trans_gc_catchall_sync leads to privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0193</link><description>A use-after-free flaw was found in the netfilter subsystem of the Linux kernel. If the catchall element is garbage-collected when the pipapo set is removed, the element can be deactivated twice. This can cause a use-after-free issue on an NFT_CHAIN object or NFT_OBJECT object, allowing a local unprivileged user to escalate their privileges on the system.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:25:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0189 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Create Message teacher_message.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0189</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file teacher_message.php of the component Create Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content with the input &lt;/title&gt;&lt;scRipt&gt;alert(x)&lt;/scRipt&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249502 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 18:25:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4280 | Unvalidated input in Silicon Labs TrustZone implementation leads to accessing Trusted memory region</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4280</link><description>An unvalidated input in Silicon Labs TrustZone implementation in v4.3.x and earlier of the Gecko SDK allows an attacker to access the trusted region of memory from the untrusted region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 16:58:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25097 | Acumos Design Studio cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25097</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Acumos Design Studio up to 2.0.7. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 2.0.8 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is 0df8a5e8722188744973168648e4c74c69ce67fd. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249420.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 15:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0188 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal change_password_teacher.php weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0188</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file change_password_teacher.php. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249501 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 15:18:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20188 | Zimbra zm-ajax XFormItem.js XFormItem.prototype.setError cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20188</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Zimbra zm-ajax up to 8.8.1 and classified as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function XFormItem.prototype.setError of the file WebRoot/js/ajax/dwt/xforms/XFormItem.js. The manipulation of the argument message leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. Upgrading to version 8.8.2 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is 8d039d6efe80780adc40c6f670c06d21de272105. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-249421 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10128 | rt-prettyphoto Plugin rt-prettyphoto.php royal_prettyphoto_plugin_links cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10128</link><description>A vulnerability was found in rt-prettyphoto Plugin up to 1.2 on WordPress and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is the function royal_prettyphoto_plugin_links of the file rt-prettyphoto.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. Upgrading to version 1.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 0d3d38cfa487481b66869e4212df1cefc281ecb7. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-249422 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6436 | SQLi in Ekol Bilisim Website Template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6436</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ekol Informatics Website Template allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Website Template: through 20231215.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 12:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47858 | Details of archived public channels are leaked to members of another team</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47858</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly verify the permissions needed for viewing archived public channels,  allowing a member of one team to get details about the archived public channels of another team via the GET /api/v4/teams/&lt;team-id&gt;/channels/deleted endpoint.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 10:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48732 | Keywords that trigger mentions are leaked to other users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48732</link><description>Mattermost fails to scope the WebSocket response around notified users to a each user separately resulting in the WebSocket broadcasting the information about who was notified about a post to everyone else in the channel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 10:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50333 | Lack of restriction to manage group names for freshly demoted guests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50333</link><description>Mattermost fails to update the permissions of the current session for a user who was just demoted to guest, allowing freshly demoted guests to change group names.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 10:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6693 | Qemu: virtio-net: stack buffer overflow in virtio_net_flush_tx()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6693</link><description>A stack based buffer overflow was found in the virtio-net device of QEMU. This issue occurs when flushing TX in the virtio_net_flush_tx function if guest features VIRTIO_NET_F_HASH_REPORT, VIRTIO_F_VERSION_1 and VIRTIO_NET_F_MRG_RXBUF are enabled. This could allow a malicious user to overwrite local variables allocated on the stack. Specifically, the `out_sg` variable could be used to read a part of process memory and send it to the wire, causing an information leak.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47216 | Liteos-A has a missing release of resource vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47216</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause DOS through occupy all resources</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47857 | multimedia camera has a UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47857</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause multimedia camera crash through modify a released pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-48360 | multimedia player has a UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-48360</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause multimedia player crash through modify a released pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49135 | multimedia player has a UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49135</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause multimedia player crash through modify a released pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:32:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49142 | multimedia audio has a UAF vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49142</link><description>in OpenHarmony v3.2.2 and prior versions allow a local attacker cause multimedia audio crash through modify a released pointer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 07:32:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28583 | Double Free in Data Network Stack &amp;amp; Connectivity</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28583</link><description>Memory corruption when IPv6 prefix timer object`s lifetime expires which are created while Netmgr daemon gets an IPv6 address.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33014 | Improper Input Validation in Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33014</link><description>Information disclosure in Core services while processing a Diag command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33025 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input in Data Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33025</link><description>Memory corruption in Data Modem when a non-standard SDP body, during a VOLTE call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33030 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33030</link><description>Memory corruption in HLOS while running playready use-case.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33032 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33032</link><description>Memory corruption in TZ Secure OS while requesting a memory allocation from TA region.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33033 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33033</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio during playback with speaker protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33036 | NULL Pointer Dereference in Hypervisor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33036</link><description>Permanent DOS in Hypervisor while untrusted VM without PSCI support makes a PSCI call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33037 | Cryptographic Issues in Automotive</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33037</link><description>Cryptographic issue in Automotive while unwrapping the key secs2d and verifying with RPMB data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33038 | Integer Overflow or Wraparound in Radio Interface Layer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33038</link><description>Memory corruption while receiving a message in Bus Socket Transport Server.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33040 | Buffer Over-read in Data Modem</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33040</link><description>Transient DOS in Data Modem during DTLS handshake.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33062 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33062</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware while parsing a BTM request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33085 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (Classic Buffer Overflow) in Wearables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33085</link><description>Memory corruption in wearables while processing data from AON.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33094 | Use After Free in Linux Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33094</link><description>Memory corruption while running VK synchronization with KASAN enabled.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33108 | Use After Free in Graphics</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33108</link><description>Memory corruption in Graphics Driver when destroying a context with KGSL_GPU_AUX_COMMAND_TIMELINE objects queued.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33109 | NULL Pointer Dereference in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33109</link><description>Transient DOS while processing a WMI P2P listen start command (0xD00A) sent from host.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33110 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33110</link><description>The session index variable in PCM host voice audio driver initialized before PCM open, accessed during event callback from ADSP and reset during PCM close may lead to race condition between event callback - PCM close and reset session index causing memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33112 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33112</link><description>Transient DOS when WLAN firmware receives "reassoc response" frame including RIC_DATA element.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33113 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input (`Classic Buffer Overflow`) in Kernel</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33113</link><description>Memory corruption when resource manager sends the host kernel a reply message with multiple fragments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33114 | Use after free in Neural Processing Unit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33114</link><description>Memory corruption while running NPU, when NETWORK_UNLOAD and (NETWORK_UNLOAD or NETWORK_EXECUTE_V2) commands are submitted at the same time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33116 | Buffer over-read without Checking Size of Input in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33116</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing ieee80211_parse_mscs_ie in WIN WLAN driver.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33117 | Use After Free in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33117</link><description>Memory corruption when HLOS allocates the response payload buffer to copy the data received from ADSP in response to AVCS_LOAD_MODULE command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33118 | Use After Free in Automotive Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33118</link><description>Memory corruption while processing Listen Sound Model client payload buffer when there is a request for Listen Sound session get parameter from ST HAL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33120 | Use After Free in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33120</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio when memory map command is executed consecutively in ADSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43511 | Loop with Unreachable Exit Condition (Infinite Loop) in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43511</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing IPv6 extension header when WLAN firmware receives an IPv6 packet that contains `IPPROTO_NONE` as the next header.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43512 | Buffer Over-read in Qualcomm ESL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43512</link><description>Transient DOS while parsing GATT service data when the total amount of memory that is required by the multiple services is greater than the actual size of the services buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43514 | Use After Free in DSP Services</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43514</link><description>Memory corruption while invoking IOCTLs calls from user space for internal mem MAP and internal mem UNMAP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47039 | Perl: perl for windows binary hijacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47039</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Perl. This security issue occurs while Perl for Windows relies on the system path environment variable to find the shell (`cmd.exe`). When running an executable that uses the Windows Perl interpreter, Perl attempts to find and execute `cmd.exe` within the operating system. However, due to path search order issues, Perl initially looks for cmd.exe in the current working directory. This flaw allows an attacker with limited privileges to place`cmd.exe` in locations with weak permissions, such as `C:\ProgramData`. By doing so, arbitrary code can be executed when an administrator attempts to use this executable from these compromised locations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26157 | Versions of the package libredwg before 0.12.5.6384 are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to an out-of-bounds read involving section...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26157</link><description>Versions of the package libredwg before 0.12.5.6384 are vulnerable to Denial of Service (DoS) due to an out-of-bounds read involving section-&gt;num_pages in decode_r2007.c.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:08:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-26159 | Versions of the package follow-redirects before 1.15.4 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to the improper handling of URLs by t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-26159</link><description>Versions of the package follow-redirects before 1.15.4 are vulnerable to Improper Input Validation due to the improper handling of URLs by the url.parse() function. When new URL() throws an error, it can be manipulated to misinterpret the hostname. An attacker could exploit this weakness to redirect traffic to a malicious site, potentially leading to information disclosure, phishing attacks, or other security breaches.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 05:08:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32831 | In wlan driver, there is a possible PIN crack due to use of insufficiently random values. This could lead to local information disclosure wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32831</link><description>In wlan driver, there is a possible PIN crack due to use of insufficiently random values. This could lead to local information disclosure with no execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: WCNCR00325055; Issue ID: MSV-868.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32872 | In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32872</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308607; Issue ID: ALPS08308607.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32874 | In Modem IMS Stack, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32874</link><description>In Modem IMS Stack, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote code execution with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01161803; Issue ID: MOLY01161803 (MSV-893).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32875 | In keyInstall, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32875</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308607; Issue ID: ALPS08304217.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32876 | In keyInstall, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32876</link><description>In keyInstall, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308612; Issue ID: ALPS08308612.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32877 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32877</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08308070.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32878 | In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32878</link><description>In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08307992.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32879 | In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Sys...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32879</link><description>In battery, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08308064.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32880 | In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32880</link><description>In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08308076.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32881 | In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with Syst...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32881</link><description>In battery, there is a possible information disclosure due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local information disclosure with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08308080.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32882 | In battery, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with Syste...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32882</link><description>In battery, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08308070; Issue ID: ALPS08308616.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32883 | In Engineer Mode, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32883</link><description>In Engineer Mode, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08282249; Issue ID: ALPS08282249.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32884 | In netdagent, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32884</link><description>In netdagent, there is a possible information disclosure due to an incorrect bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07944011; Issue ID: ALPS07944011.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32885 | In display drm, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32885</link><description>In display drm, there is a possible memory corruption due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07780685; Issue ID: ALPS07780685.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32886 | In Modem IMS SMS UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32886</link><description>In Modem IMS SMS UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00730807; Issue ID: MOLY00730807.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32887 | In Modem IMS Stack, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no addi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32887</link><description>In Modem IMS Stack, there is a possible system crash due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01161837; Issue ID: MOLY01161837 (MSV-892).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32888 | In Modem IMS Call UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32888</link><description>In Modem IMS Call UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01161830; Issue ID: MOLY01161830 (MSV-894).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32889 | In Modem IMS Call UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service wit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32889</link><description>In Modem IMS Call UA, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01161825; Issue ID: MOLY01161825 (MSV-895).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32890 | In modem EMM, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32890</link><description>In modem EMM, there is a possible system crash due to improper input validation. This could lead to remote denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY01183647; Issue ID: MOLY01183647 (MSV-963).</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32891 | In bluetooth service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32891</link><description>In bluetooth service, there is a possible out of bounds write due to improper input validation. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07933038; Issue ID: MSV-559.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0186 | HuiRan Host Reseller System HTTP POST Request password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0186</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in HuiRan Host Reseller System up to 2.0.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/index/findpass?do=4 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249444.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 01:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0185 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Avatar dasboard_teacher.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file dasboard_teacher.php of the component Avatar Handler. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249443.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 01:17:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0184 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Add Enginer edit_teacher.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_teacher.php of the component Add Enginer. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249442 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0183 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal NIA Office students.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0183</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/students.php of the component NIA Office. The manipulation leads to basic cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249441 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:16:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0182 | SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal Admin Login sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0182</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Engineers Online Portal 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ of the component Admin Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249440.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:10:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50094 | reNgine through 2.0.2 allows OS Command Injection if an adversary has a valid session ID. The attack places shell metacharacters in an api/t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50094</link><description>reNgine through 2.0.2 allows OS Command Injection if an adversary has a valid session ID. The attack places shell metacharacters in an api/tools/waf_detector/?url= string. The commands are executed as root via subprocess.check_output.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:23:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50096 | STMicroelectronics STSAFE-A1xx middleware before 3.3.7 allows MCU code execution if an adversary has the ability to read from and write to t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50096</link><description>STMicroelectronics STSAFE-A1xx middleware before 3.3.7 allows MCU code execution if an adversary has the ability to read from and write to the I2C bus. This is caused by an StSafeA_ReceiveBytes buffer overflow in the X-CUBE-SAFEA1 Software Package for STSAFE-A sample applications (1.2.0), and thus can affect user-written code that was derived from a published sample application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-0181 | RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal Admin Panel admin_user.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-0181</link><description>A vulnerability was found in RRJ Nueva Ecija Engineer Online Portal 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/admin_user.php of the component Admin Panel. The manipulation of the argument Firstname/Lastname/Username leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249433 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 16:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5877 | affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt; 3.4.3 - Unauthenticated SSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5877</link><description>The affiliate-toolkit WordPress plugin before 3.4.3 lacks authorization and authentication for requests to it's affiliate-toolkit-starter/tools/atkp_imagereceiver.php endpoint, allowing unauthenticated visitors to make requests to arbitrary URL's, including RFC1918 private addresses, leading to a Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6000 | Popup Builder &amp;lt; 4.2.3 - Unauthenticated Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6000</link><description>The Popup Builder WordPress plugin before 4.2.3 does not prevent simple visitors from updating existing popups, and injecting raw JavaScript in them, which could lead to Stored XSS attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6037 | WP TripAdvisor Review Slider &amp;lt; 11.9 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6037</link><description>The WP TripAdvisor Review Slider WordPress plugin before 11.9 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6064 | PayHere Payment Gateway &amp;lt; 2.2.12 - Unauthenticated Log Data Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6064</link><description>The PayHere Payment Gateway WordPress plugin before 2.2.12 automatically creates publicly-accessible log files containing sensitive information when transactions occur.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6113 | WP Staging (Free &amp;lt; 3.1.3, Pro &amp;lt; 5.1.3) - Unauthenticated Backup Download</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6113</link><description>The WP STAGING WordPress Backup Plugin before 3.1.3 and WP STAGING Pro WordPress Backup Plugin before 5.1.3 do not prevent visitors from leaking key information about ongoing backups processes, allowing unauthenticated attackers to download said backups later.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6271 | Backup Migration Staging &amp;lt; 1.3.6 - Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6271</link><description>The Backup Migration WordPress plugin before 1.3.6 stores in-progress backups information in easy to find, publicly-accessible files, which may allow attackers monitoring those to leak sensitive information from the site's backups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6421 | Download Manager &amp;lt; 3.2.83 - Unauthenticated Protected File Download Password Leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6421</link><description>The Download Manager WordPress plugin before 3.2.83 does not protect file download's passwords, leaking it upon receiving an invalid one.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6485 | Html5 Video Player &amp;lt; 2.5.19 - Subscriber+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6485</link><description>The Html5 Video Player WordPress plugin before 2.5.19 does not sanitise and escape some of its player settings, which combined with missing capability checks around the plugin could allow any authenticated users, such as low as subscribers to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks against high privilege users like admins</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-21732 | FlyCms through abbaa5a allows XSS via the permission management feature.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-21732</link><description>FlyCms through abbaa5a allows XSS via the permission management feature.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 07:39:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51503 | WordPress WooCommerce Payments Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.6.2 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object References (IDOR)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51503</link><description>Authorization Bypass Through User-Controlled Key vulnerability in Automattic WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo.This issue affects WooPayments – Fully Integrated Solution Built and Supported by Woo: from n/a through 6.9.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:20:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51423 | WordPress WebinarIgnition Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.05.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51423</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Saleswonder Team Webinar Plugin: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition.This issue affects Webinar Plugin: Create live/evergreen/automated/instant webinars, stream &amp; Zoom Meetings | WebinarIgnition: from n/a through 3.05.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:58:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51469 | WordPress Checkout Mestres WP Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.9.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51469</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Mestres do WP Checkout Mestres WP.This issue affects Checkout Mestres WP: from n/a through 7.1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-51547 | WordPress Fluent Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-51547</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WPManageNinja LLC Fluent Support – WordPress Helpdesk and Customer Support Ticket Plugin.This issue affects Fluent Support – WordPress Helpdesk and Customer Support Ticket Plugin: from n/a through 1.7.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52131 | WordPress Page Generator Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52131</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WP Zinc Page Generator.This issue affects Page Generator: from n/a through 1.7.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52132 | WordPress WP Adminify Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52132</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jewel Theme WP Adminify.This issue affects WP Adminify: from n/a through 3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52133 | WordPress Most And Least Read Posts Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.16 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52133</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WhileTrue Most And Least Read Posts Widget.This issue affects Most And Least Read Posts Widget: from n/a through 2.5.16.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52134 | WordPress GEO my WordPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52134</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Eyal Fitoussi GEO my WordPress.This issue affects GEO my WordPress: from n/a through 4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52185 | WordPress Everest Backup Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.9 is vulnerable to Sensitive Data Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52185</link><description>Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability in Everestthemes Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin.This issue affects Everest Backup – WordPress Cloud Backup, Migration, Restore &amp; Cloning Plugin: from n/a through 2.1.9.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7193 | MTab Bookmark Installation install.php access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7193</link><description>A vulnerability was found in MTab Bookmark up to 1.2.6 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file public/install.php of the component Installation. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249395. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:36:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7191 | S-CMS reg.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. This affects an unknown part of the file member/reg.php. The manipulation of the argument M_login/M_email leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249393 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7190 | S-CMS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7190</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /member/ad.php?action=ad. The manipulation of the argument A_text/A_url/A_contact leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249392. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:38:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7189 | S-CMS sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7189</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in S-CMS up to 2.0_build20220529-20231006. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /s/index.php?action=statistics. The manipulation of the argument lid leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249391. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:18:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7188 | Shipping 100 Fahuo100 login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shipping 100 Fahuo100 up to 1.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file member/login.php. The manipulation of the argument M_pwd leads to sql injection. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249390 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:39:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7187 | Totolink N350RT HTTP POST Request stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Totolink N350RT 9.3.5u.6139_B20201216. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi?action=login&amp;flag=ie8 of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249389 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7186 | 7-card Fakabao notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file member/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249388. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 13:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7185 | 7-card Fakabao wxpay_notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file shop/wxpay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-249387. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:35:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7184 | 7-card Fakabao notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file shop/notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-249386 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7183 | 7-card Fakabao alipay_notify.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7183</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in 7-card Fakabao up to 1.0_build20230805 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file shop/alipay_notify.php. The manipulation of the argument out_trade_no leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249385 was assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:37:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-49777 | WordPress YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.3.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-49777</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in YITH YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons.This issue affects YITH WooCommerce Product Add-Ons: from n/a through 4.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52180 | WordPress Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes Plugin &amp;lt;= 8.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52180</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Really Simple Plugins Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes.This issue affects Recipe Maker For Your Food Blog from Zip Recipes: from n/a through 8.1.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39157 | WordPress JetElements For Elementor Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.10 is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution (RCE)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39157</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Crocoblock JetElements For Elementor.This issue affects JetElements For Elementor: from n/a through 2.6.10.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52181 | WordPress Theme per user Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52181</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in Presslabs Theme per user.This issue affects Theme per user: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:27:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52182 | WordPress ARI Stream Quiz Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52182</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in ARI Soft ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder.This issue affects ARI Stream Quiz – WordPress Quizzes Builder: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6094 | OnCell G3150A-LTE Series: Web Server Transmits Cleartext Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6094</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OnCell G3150A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.3 and prior.  The vulnerability results from a lack of protection for sensitive information during transmission. An attacker eavesdropping on the traffic between the web browser and server may obtain sensitive information. 

This type of attack could be executed to gather sensitive information or to facilitate a subsequent attack against the target.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-6093 | OnCell G3150A-LTE Series: clickhacking vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-6093</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in OnCell G3150A-LTE Series firmware versions v1.3 and prior.  The vulnerability result from incorrectly restricts frame objects, which lead to user confusion about which interface the user is interacting with.

This vulnerability may lead attacker to trick user into interacting with the application.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 10:09:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-7130 | code-projects College Notes Gallery login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-7130</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects College Notes Gallery 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file login.php. The manipulation of the argument user leads to sql injection. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The identifier VDB-249133 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 09:10:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46901 | examples/6lbr/apps/6lbr-webserver/httpd.c in CETIC-6LBR (aka 6lbr) 1.5.0 has a strcat stack-based buffer overflow via a request for a long U...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46901</link><description>examples/6lbr/apps/6lbr-webserver/httpd.c in CETIC-6LBR (aka 6lbr) 1.5.0 has a strcat stack-based buffer overflow via a request for a long URL over a 6LoWPAN network.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 07:13:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52286 | Tencent tdsqlpcloud through 1.8.5 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to discover database credentials via an index.php/api/install/get_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52286</link><description>Tencent tdsqlpcloud through 1.8.5 allows unauthenticated remote attackers to discover database credentials via an index.php/api/install/get_db_info request, a related issue to CVE-2023-42387.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 07:13:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52284 | Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime (aka WebAssembly Micro Runtime or WAMR) before 1.3.0 can have an "double free or corruption" error for ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52284</link><description>Bytecode Alliance wasm-micro-runtime (aka WebAssembly Micro Runtime or WAMR) before 1.3.0 can have an "double free or corruption" error for a valid WebAssembly module because push_pop_frame_ref_offset is mishandled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 06:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-46900 | Sympa before 6.2.62 relies on a cookie parameter for certain security objectives, but does not ensure that this parameter exists and has an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-46900</link><description>Sympa before 6.2.62 relies on a cookie parameter for certain security objectives, but does not ensure that this parameter exists and has an unpredictable value. Specifically, the cookie parameter is both a salt for stored passwords and an XSS protection mechanism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 04:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52277 | Royal RoyalTSX before 6.0.2.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (Heap Memory Corruption and application crash) or possibly have ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52277</link><description>Royal RoyalTSX before 6.0.2.1 allows attackers to cause a denial of service (Heap Memory Corruption and application crash) or possibly have unspecified other impact via a long hostname in an RTSZ file, if the victim clicks on Test Connection. This occurs during SecureGatewayHost object processing in RAPortCheck.createNWConnection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 03:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52275 | Gallery3d on Tecno Camon X CA7 devices allows attackers to view hidden images by navigating to data/com.android.gallery3d/.privatealbum/.enc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52275</link><description>Gallery3d on Tecno Camon X CA7 devices allows attackers to view hidden images by navigating to data/com.android.gallery3d/.privatealbum/.encryptfiles and guessing the correct image file extension.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 02:33:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-52269 | MDaemon SecurityGateway through 9.0.3 allows XSS via a crafted Message Content Filtering rule. This might allow domain administrators to con...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-52269</link><description>MDaemon SecurityGateway through 9.0.3 allows XSS via a crafted Message Content Filtering rule. This might allow domain administrators to conduct attacks against global administrators.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 01:17:55 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>