<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-54427 | Polkadot Frontier contains missing `check_inherent` for `note_min_gas_price_target` inflates gas price</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54427</link><description>Polkadot Frontier is an Ethereum and EVM compatibility layer for Polkadot and Substrate. The extrinsic note_min_gas_price_target is an inherent extrinsic, meaning only the block producer can call it. To ensure correctness, the ProvideInherent trait should be implemented for each inherent, which includes the check_inherent call. This allows other nodes to verify if the input (in this case, the target value) is correct. However, prior to commit a754b3d, the check_inherent function has not been implemented for note_min_gas_price_target. This lets the block producer set the target value without verification. The target is then used to set the MinGasPrice, which has an upper and lower bound defined in the on_initialize hook. The block producer can set the target to the upper bound. Which also increases the upper and lower bounds for the next block. Over time, this could result in continuously raising the gas price, making contract execution too expensive and ineffective for users. An attacker could use this flaw to manipulate the gas price, potentially leading to significantly inflated transaction fees. Such manipulation could render contract execution prohibitively expensive for users, effectively resulting in a denial-of-service condition for the network. This is fixed in version a754b3d.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54428 | RevelaCode exposes Sensitive MongoDB Atlas URI in .env (potential credential leak)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54428</link><description>RevelaCode is an AI-powered faith-tech project that decodes biblical verses, prophecies and global events into accessible language. In versions below 1.0.1, a valid MongoDB Atlas URI with embedded username and password was accidentally committed to the public repository. This could allow unauthorized access to production or staging databases, potentially leading to data exfiltration, modification, or deletion. This is fixed in version 1.0.1. Workarounds include: immediately rotating credentials for the exposed database user, using a secret manager (like Vault, Doppler, AWS Secrets Manager, etc.) instead of storing secrets directly in code, or auditing recent access logs for suspicious activity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54426 | Polkadot Frontier contains silent failure in Curve25519 arithmetic precompiles with malformed points</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54426</link><description>Polkadot Frontier is an Ethereum and EVM compatibility layer for Polkadot and Substrate. In versions prior to commit 36f70d1, the Curve25519Add and Curve25519ScalarMul precompiles incorrectly handle invalid Ristretto point representations. Instead of returning an error, they silently treat invalid input bytes as the Ristretto identity element, leading to potentially incorrect cryptographic results. This is fixed in commit 36f70d1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54423 | copyparty has a DOM-Based XSS vulnerability when displaying multimedia metadata</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54423</link><description>copyparty is a portable file server. In versions up to and including versions 1.18.4, an unauthenticated attacker is able to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in a victim's browser due to improper sanitization of multimedia tags in music files, including m3u files. This is fixed in version 1.18.5.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29534 | An authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in PowerStick Wave Dual-Band Wifi Extender V1.0 allows an attacker with valid credentia...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29534</link><description>An authenticated remote code execution vulnerability in PowerStick Wave Dual-Band Wifi Extender V1.0 allows an attacker with valid credentials to execute arbitrary commands with root privileges. The issue stems from insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in the /cgi-bin/cgi_vista.cgi executable, which is passed to a system-level function call.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50485 | Improper session invalidation in the component /crm/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Online Course Registration v3.1 allows attackers to ex...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50485</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /crm/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Online Course Registration v3.1 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50486 | Improper session invalidation in the component /carrental/update-password.php of PHPGurukul Car Rental Project v3.0 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50486</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /carrental/update-password.php of PHPGurukul Car Rental Project v3.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50487 | Improper session invalidation in the component /bbdms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Blood Bank &amp; Donor Management System v2.4 allows att...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50487</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /bbdms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Blood Bank &amp; Donor Management System v2.4 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50484 | Improper session invalidation in the component /crm/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Small CRM v3.0 allows attackers to execute a session h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50484</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /crm/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Small CRM v3.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8194 | Tarfile infinite loop during parsing with negative member offset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8194</link><description>There is a defect in the CPython “tarfile” module affecting the “TarFile” extraction and entry enumeration APIs. The tar implementation would process tar archives with negative offsets without error, resulting in an infinite loop and deadlock during the parsing of maliciously crafted tar archives. 

This vulnerability can be mitigated by including the following patch after importing the “tarfile” module:



import tarfile

def _block_patched(self, count):
    if count &lt; 0:  # pragma: no cover
        raise tarfile.InvalidHeaderError("invalid offset")
    return _block_patched._orig_block(self, count)

_block_patched._orig_block = tarfile.TarInfo._block
tarfile.TarInfo._block = _block_patched</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:56:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8283 | Netavark: podman: netavark may resolve hostnames to unexpected hosts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8283</link><description>A vulnerability was found in the netavark package, a network stack for containers used with Podman. Due to dns.podman search domain being removed, netavark may return external servers if a valid A/AAAA record is sent as a response. When creating a container with a given name, this name will be used as the hostname for the container itself, as the podman's search domain is not added anymore the container is using the host's resolv.conf, and the DNS resolver will try to look into the search domains contained on it. If one of the domains contain a name with the same hostname as the running container, the connection will forward to unexpected external servers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50491 | Improper session invalidation in the component /banker/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System v1 allows attackers t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50491</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /banker/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Bank Locker Management System v1 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:29:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43023 | HP Linux Imaging and Printing Software - Use of DSA Key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43023</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Linux Imaging and Printing Software documentation. This potential vulnerability is due to the use of a weak code signing key, Digital Signature Algorithm (DSA).</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:56:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50489 | Improper session invalidation in the component /srms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Student Result Management System v2.0 allows attacker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50489</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /srms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Student Result Management System v2.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50492 | Improper session invalidation in the component /edms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System v1 allows attackers to exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50492</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /edms/change-password.php of PHPGurukul e-Diary Management System v1 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54298 | Extension - firecoders.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in CommentBox component 1.0.0-1.1.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54298</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in CommentBox component 1.0.0-1.1.0 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:45:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54299 | Extension - nobossextensions.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in No Boss Testimonials component 1.0.0-3.0.0 and 4.0.0-4.0.2 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54299</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in No Boss Testimonials component 1.0.0-3.0.0 and 4.0.0-4.0.2 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:45:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50488 | Improper session invalidation in the component /library/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Online Library Management System v3.0 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50488</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /library/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Online Library Management System v3.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50494 | Improper session invalidation in the component /doctor/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Car Washing Management System v1.0 allows attackers...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50494</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /doctor/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Car Washing Management System v1.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50490 | Improper session invalidation in the component /elms/emp-changepassword.php of PHPGurukul Student Result Management System v2.0 allows attac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50490</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /elms/emp-changepassword.php of PHPGurukul Student Result Management System v2.0 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50493 | Improper session invalidation in the component /doctor/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System v1 allows atta...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50493</link><description>Improper session invalidation in the component /doctor/change-password.php of PHPGurukul Doctor Appointment Management System v1 allows attackers to execute a session hijacking attack.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:59:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7676 | DLL hijacking of all PE32 executables on Windows 11 for ARM CPUs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7676</link><description>DLL hijacking of all PE32 executables when run on Windows for ARM64 CPU architecture. This allows an attacker to execute code, if the attacker can plant a DLL in the same directory as the executable. Vulnerable versions of Windows 11 for ARM attempt to load Base DLLs that would ordinarily not be loaded from the application directory. Fixed in release 24H2, but present in all earlier versions of Windows 11 for ARM CPUs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54527 | In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.2.86935, 
2025.2.87167, 
2025.3.87341, 
2025.3.87344 improper iframe configuration in widget sandbox allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54527</link><description>In JetBrains YouTrack before 2025.2.86935, 
2025.2.87167, 
2025.3.87341, 
2025.3.87344 improper iframe configuration in widget sandbox allows popups to bypass security restrictions</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54528 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible in GitHub App connection flow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54528</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible in GitHub App connection flow</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54529 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible in external OAuth login integration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54529</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible in external OAuth login integration</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54530 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 privilege escalation was possible due to incorrect directory permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54530</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 privilege escalation was possible due to incorrect directory permissions</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54531 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 path traversal was possible via plugin unpacking on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54531</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 path traversal was possible via plugin unpacking on Windows</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54532 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 improper access control allowed disclosure of build settings via snapshot dependencies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54532</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 improper access control allowed disclosure of build settings via snapshot dependencies</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54533 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 improper access control allowed disclosure of build settings via VCS configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54533</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 improper access control allowed disclosure of build settings via VCS configuration</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54534 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 reflected XSS was possible on the agentpushPreset page</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54534</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 reflected XSS was possible on the agentpushPreset page</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54535 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 password reset and email verification tokens were using weak hashing algorithms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54535</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 password reset and email verification tokens were using weak hashing algorithms</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54536 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible on GraphQL endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54536</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 a CSRF was possible on GraphQL endpoint</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54537 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 user credentials were stored in plain text in memory snapshots</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54537</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 user credentials were stored in plain text in memory snapshots</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54538 | In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 password exposure was possible via command line in the "hg pull" command</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54538</link><description>In JetBrains TeamCity before 2025.07 password exposure was possible via command line in the "hg pull" command</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:38:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2297 | Privilege Management for Windows - Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2297</link><description>Prior to version 25.4.270.0, a local authenticated attacker can manipulate user profile files to add illegitimate challenge response codes into the local user registry under certain conditions. This allows users with the ability to edit their user profile files to elevate their privileges to administrator.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6250 | Privilege Management for Windows - Elevation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6250</link><description>Prior to 25.4.270.0, when wmic.exe is elevated with a full admin token the user can stop the Defendpoint service, bypassing anti-tamper protections. Once the service is disabled, the malicious user can add themselves to Administrators group and run any process with elevated permissions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49342 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49342</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 12.10 and 14.10 uses an inadequate account lockout setting that could allow a remote attacker to brute force account credentials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-49343 | IBM Informix Dynamic Server HTML injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-49343</link><description>IBM Informix Dynamic Server 12.10 and 14.10 is vulnerable to HTML injection. A remote attacker could inject malicious HTML code, which when viewed, would be executed in the victim's Web browser within the security context of the hosting site.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54418 | CodeIgniter4&amp;#x27;s ImageMagick Handler has Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54418</link><description>CodeIgniter is a PHP full-stack web framework. A command injection vulnerability present in versions prior to 4.6.2 affects applications that use the ImageMagick handler for image processing (`imagick` as the image library) and either allow file uploads with user-controlled filenames and process uploaded images using the `resize()` method or use the `text()` method with user-controlled text content or options. An attacker can upload a file with a malicious filename containing shell metacharacters that get executed when the image is processed or provide malicious text content or options that get executed when adding text to images Users should upgrade to v4.6.2 or later to receive a patch. As a workaround, switch to the GD image handler (`gd`, the default handler), which is not affected by either vulnerability. For file upload scenarios, instead of using user-provided filenames, generate random names to eliminate the attack vector with `getRandomName()` when using the `move()` method, or use the `store()` method, which automatically generates safe filenames. For text operations, if one must use ImageMagick with user-controlled text, sanitize the input to only allow safe characters and validate/restrict text options.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53696 | iSTAR Ultra performs a firmware verification on boot, however the verification does not inspect certain portions of the firmware. These firm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53696</link><description>iSTAR Ultra performs a firmware verification on boot, however the verification does not inspect certain portions of the firmware. These firmware parts may contain malicious code. Tested up to firmware 6.9.2, later firmwares are also possibly affected.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30125 | An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. All dashcams were shipped with the same default credentials of 12345678, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30125</link><description>An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. All dashcams were shipped with the same default credentials of 12345678, which creates an insecure-by-default condition. For users who change their passwords, it's limited to 8 characters. These short passwords can be cracked in 8 hours via low-end commercial cloud resources.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30124 | An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. When a new SD card is inserted into the dashcam, the existing password is...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30124</link><description>An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. When a new SD card is inserted into the dashcam, the existing password is written onto the SD card in cleartext automatically. An attacker with temporary access to the dashcam can switch the SD card to steal this password.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53695 | OS Command Injection in iSTAR Ultra products web application allows an authenticated attacker to gain even more privileged access ('root' us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53695</link><description>OS Command Injection in iSTAR Ultra products web application allows an authenticated attacker to gain even more privileged access ('root' user) to the device firmware.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8279 | Missing Authentication for Critical Function in GitLab Language Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8279</link><description>Insufficient input validation within GitLab Language Server 7.6.0 and later before 7.30.0 allows arbitrary GraphQL query execution</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30133 | An issue was discovered on IROAD Dashcam FX2 devices. Bypass of Device Pairing/Registration can occur. It requires device registration via t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30133</link><description>An issue was discovered on IROAD Dashcam FX2 devices. Bypass of Device Pairing/Registration can occur. It requires device registration via the "IROAD X View" app for authentication, but its HTTP server lacks this restriction. Once connected to the dashcam's Wi-Fi network via the default password ("qwertyuiop"), an attacker can directly access the HTTP server at http://192.168.10.1 without undergoing the pairing process. Additionally, no alert is triggered on the device when an attacker connects, making this intrusion completely silent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24485 | A server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in the cecho.php functionality of MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.5.860. A specially crafted HT...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24485</link><description>A server-side request forgery vulnerability exists in the cecho.php functionality of MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.5.860. A specially crafted HTTP request can lead to SSRF. An attacker can make an unauthenticated HTTP request to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26469 | An incorrect default permissions vulnerability exists in the CServerSettings::SetRegistryValues functionality of MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.3...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26469</link><description>An incorrect default permissions vulnerability exists in the CServerSettings::SetRegistryValues functionality of MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.3.840.
A specially crafted application can decrypt credentials stored in a configuration-related registry key.
An attacker can execute a malicious script or application to exploit this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:58:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27724 | A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the login.php functionality of meddream MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.3.840. A specially crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27724</link><description>A privilege escalation vulnerability exists in the login.php functionality of meddream MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.3.840. A specially crafted .php file can lead to elevated capabilities. An attacker can upload a malicious file to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30126 | An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. Via port 7777 without any need to pair or press a physical button, a remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30126</link><description>An issue was discovered on Marbella KR8s Dashcam FF 2.0.8 devices. Via port 7777 without any need to pair or press a physical button, a remote attacker can disable recording, delete recordings, or even disable battery protection to cause a flat battery to essentially disable the car from being used. During the process of changing these settings, there are no indications or sounds on the dashcam to alert the dashcam owner that someone else is making those changes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:58:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32731 | A reflected cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the radiationDoseReport.php functionality of meddream MedDream PACS Premium 7...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32731</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (xss) vulnerability exists in the radiationDoseReport.php functionality of meddream MedDream PACS Premium 7.3.5.860. A specially crafted malicious url can lead to arbitrary javascript code execution. An attacker can provide a crafted URL to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:58:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4056 | Glib: glib crash after long command line</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4056</link><description>A flaw was found in GLib. A denial of service on Windows platforms may occur if an application attempts to spawn a program using long command lines.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:28:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54569 | In Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.16.0.0, the installer is vulnerable to local privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54569</link><description>In Malwarebytes Binisoft Windows Firewall Control before 6.16.0.0, the installer is vulnerable to local privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:42:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8275 | bsc Peru Cocktails App bsc.devy.peru_cocktails AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8275</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in bsc Peru Cocktails App 1.0.0 on Android. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component bsc.devy.peru_cocktails. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8274 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8274</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_recruitment_status. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:48:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5997 | Privilege Escalation in Beamsec PhishPro</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5997</link><description>Incorrect Use of Privileged APIs vulnerability in Beamsec PhishPro allows Privilege Abuse.This issue affects PhishPro: before 7.5.4.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38468 | net/sched: Return NULL when htb_lookup_leaf encounters an empty rbtree</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38468</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: Return NULL when htb_lookup_leaf encounters an empty rbtree

htb_lookup_leaf has a BUG_ON that can trigger with the following:

tc qdisc del dev lo root
tc qdisc add dev lo root handle 1: htb default 1
tc class add dev lo parent 1: classid 1:1 htb rate 64bit
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 1:1 handle 2: netem
tc qdisc add dev lo parent 2:1 handle 3: blackhole
ping -I lo -c1 -W0.001 127.0.0.1

The root cause is the following:

1. htb_dequeue calls htb_dequeue_tree which calls the dequeue handler on
   the selected leaf qdisc
2. netem_dequeue calls enqueue on the child qdisc
3. blackhole_enqueue drops the packet and returns a value that is not
   just NET_XMIT_SUCCESS
4. Because of this, netem_dequeue calls qdisc_tree_reduce_backlog, and
   since qlen is now 0, it calls htb_qlen_notify -&gt; htb_deactivate -&gt;
   htb_deactiviate_prios -&gt; htb_remove_class_from_row -&gt; htb_safe_rb_erase
5. As this is the only class in the selected hprio rbtree,
   __rb_change_child in __rb_erase_augmented sets the rb_root pointer to
   NULL
6. Because blackhole_dequeue returns NULL, netem_dequeue returns NULL,
   which causes htb_dequeue_tree to call htb_lookup_leaf with the same
   hprio rbtree, and fail the BUG_ON

The function graph for this scenario is shown here:
 0)               |  htb_enqueue() {
 0) + 13.635 us   |    netem_enqueue();
 0)   4.719 us    |    htb_activate_prios();
 0) # 2249.199 us |  }
 0)               |  htb_dequeue() {
 0)   2.355 us    |    htb_lookup_leaf();
 0)               |    netem_dequeue() {
 0) + 11.061 us   |      blackhole_enqueue();
 0)               |      qdisc_tree_reduce_backlog() {
 0)               |        qdisc_lookup_rcu() {
 0)   1.873 us    |          qdisc_match_from_root();
 0)   6.292 us    |        }
 0)   1.894 us    |        htb_search();
 0)               |        htb_qlen_notify() {
 0)   2.655 us    |          htb_deactivate_prios();
 0)   6.933 us    |        }
 0) + 25.227 us   |      }
 0)   1.983 us    |      blackhole_dequeue();
 0) + 86.553 us   |    }
 0) # 2932.761 us |    qdisc_warn_nonwc();
 0)               |    htb_lookup_leaf() {
 0)               |      BUG_ON();
 ------------------------------------------

The full original bug report can be seen here [1].

We can fix this just by returning NULL instead of the BUG_ON,
as htb_dequeue_tree returns NULL when htb_lookup_leaf returns
NULL.

[1] https://lore.kernel.org/netdev/pF5XOOIim0IuEfhI-SOxTgRvNoDwuux7UHKnE_Y5-zVd4wmGvNk2ceHjKb8ORnzw0cGwfmVu42g9dL7XyJLf1NEzaztboTWcm0Ogxuojoeo=@willsroot.io/</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38469 | KVM: x86/xen: Fix cleanup logic in emulation of Xen schedop poll hypercalls</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38469</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

KVM: x86/xen: Fix cleanup logic in emulation of Xen schedop poll hypercalls

kvm_xen_schedop_poll does a kmalloc_array() when a VM polls the host
for more than one event channel potr (nr_ports &gt; 1).

After the kmalloc_array(), the error paths need to go through the
"out" label, but the call to kvm_read_guest_virt() does not.

[Adjusted commit message. - Paolo]</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38470 | net: vlan: fix VLAN 0 refcount imbalance of toggling filtering during runtime</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38470</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: vlan: fix VLAN 0 refcount imbalance of toggling filtering during runtime

Assuming the "rx-vlan-filter" feature is enabled on a net device, the
8021q module will automatically add or remove VLAN 0 when the net device
is put administratively up or down, respectively. There are a couple of
problems with the above scheme.

The first problem is a memory leak that can happen if the "rx-vlan-filter"
feature is disabled while the device is running:

 # ip link add bond1 up type bond mode 0
 # ethtool -K bond1 rx-vlan-filter off
 # ip link del dev bond1

When the device is put administratively down the "rx-vlan-filter"
feature is disabled, so the 8021q module will not remove VLAN 0 and the
memory will be leaked [1].

Another problem that can happen is that the kernel can automatically
delete VLAN 0 when the device is put administratively down despite not
adding it when the device was put administratively up since during that
time the "rx-vlan-filter" feature was disabled. null-ptr-unref or
bug_on[2] will be triggered by unregister_vlan_dev() for refcount
imbalance if toggling filtering during runtime:

$ ip link add bond0 type bond mode 0
$ ip link add link bond0 name vlan0 type vlan id 0 protocol 802.1q
$ ethtool -K bond0 rx-vlan-filter off
$ ifconfig bond0 up
$ ethtool -K bond0 rx-vlan-filter on
$ ifconfig bond0 down
$ ip link del vlan0

Root cause is as below:
step1: add vlan0 for real_dev, such as bond, team.
register_vlan_dev
    vlan_vid_add(real_dev,htons(ETH_P_8021Q),0) //refcnt=1
step2: disable vlan filter feature and enable real_dev
step3: change filter from 0 to 1
vlan_device_event
    vlan_filter_push_vids
        ndo_vlan_rx_add_vid //No refcnt added to real_dev vlan0
step4: real_dev down
vlan_device_event
    vlan_vid_del(dev, htons(ETH_P_8021Q), 0); //refcnt=0
        vlan_info_rcu_free //free vlan0
step5: delete vlan0
unregister_vlan_dev
    BUG_ON(!vlan_info); //vlan_info is null

Fix both problems by noting in the VLAN info whether VLAN 0 was
automatically added upon NETDEV_UP and based on that decide whether it
should be deleted upon NETDEV_DOWN, regardless of the state of the
"rx-vlan-filter" feature.

[1]
unreferenced object 0xffff8880068e3100 (size 256):
  comm "ip", pid 384, jiffies 4296130254
  hex dump (first 32 bytes):
    00 20 30 0d 80 88 ff ff 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  . 0.............
    00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00  ................
  backtrace (crc 81ce31fa):
    __kmalloc_cache_noprof+0x2b5/0x340
    vlan_vid_add+0x434/0x940
    vlan_device_event.cold+0x75/0xa8
    notifier_call_chain+0xca/0x150
    __dev_notify_flags+0xe3/0x250
    rtnl_configure_link+0x193/0x260
    rtnl_newlink_create+0x383/0x8e0
    __rtnl_newlink+0x22c/0xa40
    rtnl_newlink+0x627/0xb00
    rtnetlink_rcv_msg+0x6fb/0xb70
    netlink_rcv_skb+0x11f/0x350
    netlink_unicast+0x426/0x710
    netlink_sendmsg+0x75a/0xc20
    __sock_sendmsg+0xc1/0x150
    ____sys_sendmsg+0x5aa/0x7b0
    ___sys_sendmsg+0xfc/0x180

[2]
kernel BUG at net/8021q/vlan.c:99!
Oops: invalid opcode: 0000 [#1] SMP KASAN PTI
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 382 Comm: ip Not tainted 6.16.0-rc3 #61 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996),
BIOS rel-1.13.0-0-gf21b5a4aeb02-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
RIP: 0010:unregister_vlan_dev (net/8021q/vlan.c:99 (discriminator 1))
RSP: 0018:ffff88810badf310 EFLAGS: 00010246
RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff88810da84000 RCX: ffffffffb47ceb9a
RDX: dffffc0000000000 RSI: 0000000000000008 RDI: ffff88810e8b43c8
RBP: 0000000000000000 R08: 0000000000000000 R09: fffffbfff6cefe80
R10: ffffffffb677f407 R11: ffff88810badf3c0 R12: ffff88810e8b4000
R13: 0000000000000000 R14: ffff88810642a5c0 R15: 000000000000017e
FS:  00007f1ff68c20c0(0000) GS:ffff888163a24000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
CR2: 00007f1ff5dad240 CR3: 0000000107e56000 CR4: 00000000000006f0
Call Trace:
 &lt;TASK
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38471 | tls: always refresh the queue when reading sock</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38471</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tls: always refresh the queue when reading sock

After recent changes in net-next TCP compacts skbs much more
aggressively. This unearthed a bug in TLS where we may try
to operate on an old skb when checking if all skbs in the
queue have matching decrypt state and geometry.

    BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in tls_strp_check_rcv+0x898/0x9a0 [tls]
    (net/tls/tls_strp.c:436 net/tls/tls_strp.c:530 net/tls/tls_strp.c:544)
    Read of size 4 at addr ffff888013085750 by task tls/13529

    CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 13529 Comm: tls Not tainted 6.16.0-rc5-virtme
    Call Trace:
     kasan_report+0xca/0x100
     tls_strp_check_rcv+0x898/0x9a0 [tls]
     tls_rx_rec_wait+0x2c9/0x8d0 [tls]
     tls_sw_recvmsg+0x40f/0x1aa0 [tls]
     inet_recvmsg+0x1c3/0x1f0

Always reload the queue, fast path is to have the record in the queue
when we wake, anyway (IOW the path going down "if !strp-&gt;stm.full_len").</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38472 | netfilter: nf_conntrack: fix crash due to removal of uninitialised entry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38472</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_conntrack: fix crash due to removal of uninitialised entry

A crash in conntrack was reported while trying to unlink the conntrack
entry from the hash bucket list:
    [exception RIP: __nf_ct_delete_from_lists+172]
    [..]
 #7 [ff539b5a2b043aa0] nf_ct_delete at ffffffffc124d421 [nf_conntrack]
 #8 [ff539b5a2b043ad0] nf_ct_gc_expired at ffffffffc124d999 [nf_conntrack]
 #9 [ff539b5a2b043ae0] __nf_conntrack_find_get at ffffffffc124efbc [nf_conntrack]
    [..]

The nf_conn struct is marked as allocated from slab but appears to be in
a partially initialised state:

 ct hlist pointer is garbage; looks like the ct hash value
 (hence crash).
 ct-&gt;status is equal to IPS_CONFIRMED|IPS_DYING, which is expected
 ct-&gt;timeout is 30000 (=30s), which is unexpected.

Everything else looks like normal udp conntrack entry.  If we ignore
ct-&gt;status and pretend its 0, the entry matches those that are newly
allocated but not yet inserted into the hash:
  - ct hlist pointers are overloaded and store/cache the raw tuple hash
  - ct-&gt;timeout matches the relative time expected for a new udp flow
    rather than the absolute 'jiffies' value.

If it were not for the presence of IPS_CONFIRMED,
__nf_conntrack_find_get() would have skipped the entry.

Theory is that we did hit following race:

cpu x 			cpu y			cpu z
 found entry E		found entry E
 E is expired		
 nf_ct_delete()
 return E to rcu slab
					init_conntrack
					E is re-inited,
					ct-&gt;status set to 0
					reply tuplehash hnnode.pprev
					stores hash value.

cpu y found E right before it was deleted on cpu x.
E is now re-inited on cpu z.  cpu y was preempted before
checking for expiry and/or confirm bit.

					-&gt;refcnt set to 1
					E now owned by skb
					-&gt;timeout set to 30000

If cpu y were to resume now, it would observe E as
expired but would skip E due to missing CONFIRMED bit.

					nf_conntrack_confirm gets called
					sets: ct-&gt;status |= CONFIRMED
					This is wrong: E is not yet added
					to hashtable.

cpu y resumes, it observes E as expired but CONFIRMED:
			
			nf_ct_expired()
			 -&gt; yes (ct-&gt;timeout is 30s)
			confirmed bit set.

cpu y will try to delete E from the hashtable:
			nf_ct_delete() -&gt; set DYING bit
			__nf_ct_delete_from_lists

Even this scenario doesn't guarantee a crash:
cpu z still holds the table bucket lock(s) so y blocks:

			wait for spinlock held by z

					CONFIRMED is set but there is no
					guarantee ct will be added to hash:
					"chaintoolong" or "clash resolution"
					logic both skip the insert step.
					reply hnnode.pprev still stores the
					hash value.

					unlocks spinlock
					return NF_DROP
			

In case CPU z does insert the entry into the hashtable, cpu y will unlink
E again right away but no crash occurs.

Without 'cpu y' race, 'garbage' hlist is of no consequence:
ct refcnt remains at 1, eventually skb will be free'd and E gets
destroyed via: nf_conntrack_put -&gt; nf_conntrack_destroy -&gt; nf_ct_destroy.

To resolve this, move the IPS_CONFIRMED assignment after the table
insertion but before the unlock.

Pablo points out that the confirm-bit-store could be reordered to happen
before hlist add resp. the timeout fixup, so switch to set_bit and
before_atomic memory barrier to prevent this.

It doesn't matter if other CPUs can observe a newly inserted entry right
before the CONFIRMED bit was set:

Such event cannot be distinguished from above "E is the old incarnation"
case: the entry will be skipped.

Also change nf_ct_should_gc() to first check the confirmed bit.

The gc sequence is:
 1. Check if entry has expired, if not skip to next entry
 2. Obtain a reference to the expired entry.
 3. Call nf_ct_should_gc() to double-check step 1.

nf_ct_should_gc() is thus called only for entries that already failed an
expiry check. After this patch, once the confirmed bit check pas
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38473 | Bluetooth: Fix null-ptr-deref in l2cap_sock_resume_cb()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38473</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

Bluetooth: Fix null-ptr-deref in l2cap_sock_resume_cb()

syzbot reported null-ptr-deref in l2cap_sock_resume_cb(). [0]

l2cap_sock_resume_cb() has a similar problem that was fixed by commit
1bff51ea59a9 ("Bluetooth: fix use-after-free error in lock_sock_nested()").

Since both l2cap_sock_kill() and l2cap_sock_resume_cb() are executed
under l2cap_sock_resume_cb(), we can avoid the issue simply by checking
if chan-&gt;data is NULL.

Let's not access to the killed socket in l2cap_sock_resume_cb().

[0]:
BUG: KASAN: null-ptr-deref in instrument_atomic_write include/linux/instrumented.h:82 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: null-ptr-deref in clear_bit include/asm-generic/bitops/instrumented-atomic.h:41 [inline]
BUG: KASAN: null-ptr-deref in l2cap_sock_resume_cb+0xb4/0x17c net/bluetooth/l2cap_sock.c:1711
Write of size 8 at addr 0000000000000570 by task kworker/u9:0/52

CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 52 Comm: kworker/u9:0 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc4-syzkaller-g7482bb149b9f #0 PREEMPT
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 05/07/2025
Workqueue: hci0 hci_rx_work
Call trace:
 show_stack+0x2c/0x3c arch/arm64/kernel/stacktrace.c:501 (C)
 __dump_stack+0x30/0x40 lib/dump_stack.c:94
 dump_stack_lvl+0xd8/0x12c lib/dump_stack.c:120
 print_report+0x58/0x84 mm/kasan/report.c:524
 kasan_report+0xb0/0x110 mm/kasan/report.c:634
 check_region_inline mm/kasan/generic.c:-1 [inline]
 kasan_check_range+0x264/0x2a4 mm/kasan/generic.c:189
 __kasan_check_write+0x20/0x30 mm/kasan/shadow.c:37
 instrument_atomic_write include/linux/instrumented.h:82 [inline]
 clear_bit include/asm-generic/bitops/instrumented-atomic.h:41 [inline]
 l2cap_sock_resume_cb+0xb4/0x17c net/bluetooth/l2cap_sock.c:1711
 l2cap_security_cfm+0x524/0xea0 net/bluetooth/l2cap_core.c:7357
 hci_auth_cfm include/net/bluetooth/hci_core.h:2092 [inline]
 hci_auth_complete_evt+0x2e8/0xa4c net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:3514
 hci_event_func net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7511 [inline]
 hci_event_packet+0x650/0xe9c net/bluetooth/hci_event.c:7565
 hci_rx_work+0x320/0xb18 net/bluetooth/hci_core.c:4070
 process_one_work+0x7e8/0x155c kernel/workqueue.c:3238
 process_scheduled_works kernel/workqueue.c:3321 [inline]
 worker_thread+0x958/0xed8 kernel/workqueue.c:3402
 kthread+0x5fc/0x75c kernel/kthread.c:464
 ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20 arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:847</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38474 | usb: net: sierra: check for no status endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38474</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: net: sierra: check for no status endpoint

The driver checks for having three endpoints and
having bulk in and out endpoints, but not that
the third endpoint is interrupt input.
Rectify the omission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38475 | smc: Fix various oops due to inet_sock type confusion.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38475</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smc: Fix various oops due to inet_sock type confusion.

syzbot reported weird splats [0][1] in cipso_v4_sock_setattr() while
freeing inet_sk(sk)-&gt;inet_opt.

The address was freed multiple times even though it was read-only memory.

cipso_v4_sock_setattr() did nothing wrong, and the root cause was type
confusion.

The cited commit made it possible to create smc_sock as an INET socket.

The issue is that struct smc_sock does not have struct inet_sock as the
first member but hijacks AF_INET and AF_INET6 sk_family, which confuses
various places.

In this case, inet_sock.inet_opt was actually smc_sock.clcsk_data_ready(),
which is an address of a function in the text segment.

  $ pahole -C inet_sock vmlinux
  struct inet_sock {
  ...
          struct ip_options_rcu *    inet_opt;             /*   784     8 */

  $ pahole -C smc_sock vmlinux
  struct smc_sock {
  ...
          void                       (*clcsk_data_ready)(struct sock *); /*   784     8 */

The same issue for another field was reported before. [2][3]

At that time, an ugly hack was suggested [4], but it makes both INET
and SMC code error-prone and hard to change.

Also, yet another variant was fixed by a hacky commit 98d4435efcbf3
("net/smc: prevent NULL pointer dereference in txopt_get").

Instead of papering over the root cause by such hacks, we should not
allow non-INET socket to reuse the INET infra.

Let's add inet_sock as the first member of smc_sock.

[0]:
kvfree_call_rcu(): Double-freed call. rcu_head 000000006921da73
WARNING: CPU: 0 PID: 6718 at mm/slab_common.c:1956 kvfree_call_rcu+0x94/0x3f0 mm/slab_common.c:1955
Modules linked in:
CPU: 0 UID: 0 PID: 6718 Comm: syz.0.17 Tainted: G        W           6.16.0-rc4-syzkaller-g7482bb149b9f #0 PREEMPT
Tainted: [W]=WARN
Hardware name: Google Google Compute Engine/Google Compute Engine, BIOS Google 05/07/2025
pstate: 60400005 (nZCv daif +PAN -UAO -TCO -DIT -SSBS BTYPE=--)
pc : kvfree_call_rcu+0x94/0x3f0 mm/slab_common.c:1955
lr : kvfree_call_rcu+0x94/0x3f0 mm/slab_common.c:1955
sp : ffff8000a03a7730
x29: ffff8000a03a7730 x28: 00000000fffffff5 x27: 1fffe000184823d3
x26: dfff800000000000 x25: ffff0000c2411e9e x24: ffff0000dd88da00
x23: ffff8000891ac9a0 x22: 00000000ffffffea x21: ffff8000891ac9a0
x20: ffff8000891ac9a0 x19: ffff80008afc2480 x18: 00000000ffffffff
x17: 0000000000000000 x16: ffff80008ae642c8 x15: ffff700011ede14c
x14: 1ffff00011ede14c x13: 0000000000000004 x12: ffffffffffffffff
x11: ffff700011ede14c x10: 0000000000ff0100 x9 : 5fa3c1ffaf0ff000
x8 : 5fa3c1ffaf0ff000 x7 : 0000000000000001 x6 : 0000000000000001
x5 : ffff8000a03a7078 x4 : ffff80008f766c20 x3 : ffff80008054d360
x2 : 0000000000000000 x1 : 0000000000000201 x0 : 0000000000000000
Call trace:
 kvfree_call_rcu+0x94/0x3f0 mm/slab_common.c:1955 (P)
 cipso_v4_sock_setattr+0x2f0/0x3f4 net/ipv4/cipso_ipv4.c:1914
 netlbl_sock_setattr+0x240/0x334 net/netlabel/netlabel_kapi.c:1000
 smack_netlbl_add+0xa8/0x158 security/smack/smack_lsm.c:2581
 smack_inode_setsecurity+0x378/0x430 security/smack/smack_lsm.c:2912
 security_inode_setsecurity+0x118/0x3c0 security/security.c:2706
 __vfs_setxattr_noperm+0x174/0x5c4 fs/xattr.c:251
 __vfs_setxattr_locked+0x1ec/0x218 fs/xattr.c:295
 vfs_setxattr+0x158/0x2ac fs/xattr.c:321
 do_setxattr fs/xattr.c:636 [inline]
 file_setxattr+0x1b8/0x294 fs/xattr.c:646
 path_setxattrat+0x2ac/0x320 fs/xattr.c:711
 __do_sys_fsetxattr fs/xattr.c:761 [inline]
 __se_sys_fsetxattr fs/xattr.c:758 [inline]
 __arm64_sys_fsetxattr+0xc0/0xdc fs/xattr.c:758
 __invoke_syscall arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:35 [inline]
 invoke_syscall+0x98/0x2b8 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:49
 el0_svc_common+0x130/0x23c arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:132
 do_el0_svc+0x48/0x58 arch/arm64/kernel/syscall.c:151
 el0_svc+0x58/0x180 arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:879
 el0t_64_sync_handler+0x84/0x12c arch/arm64/kernel/entry-common.c:898
 el0t_64_sync+0x198/0x19c arch/arm64/kernel/entry.S:600

[
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38476 | rpl: Fix use-after-free in rpl_do_srh_inline().</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38476</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

rpl: Fix use-after-free in rpl_do_srh_inline().

Running lwt_dst_cache_ref_loop.sh in selftest with KASAN triggers
the splat below [0].

rpl_do_srh_inline() fetches ipv6_hdr(skb) and accesses it after
skb_cow_head(), which is illegal as the header could be freed then.

Let's fix it by making oldhdr to a local struct instead of a pointer.

[0]:
[root@fedora net]# ./lwt_dst_cache_ref_loop.sh
...
TEST: rpl (input)
[   57.631529] ==================================================================
BUG: KASAN: slab-use-after-free in rpl_do_srh_inline.isra.0 (net/ipv6/rpl_iptunnel.c:174)
Read of size 40 at addr ffff888122bf96d8 by task ping6/1543

CPU: 50 UID: 0 PID: 1543 Comm: ping6 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc5-01302-gfadd1e6231b1 #23 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl (lib/dump_stack.c:122)
 print_report (mm/kasan/report.c:409 mm/kasan/report.c:521)
 kasan_report (mm/kasan/report.c:221 mm/kasan/report.c:636)
 kasan_check_range (mm/kasan/generic.c:175 (discriminator 1) mm/kasan/generic.c:189 (discriminator 1))
 __asan_memmove (mm/kasan/shadow.c:94 (discriminator 2))
 rpl_do_srh_inline.isra.0 (net/ipv6/rpl_iptunnel.c:174)
 rpl_input (net/ipv6/rpl_iptunnel.c:201 net/ipv6/rpl_iptunnel.c:282)
 lwtunnel_input (net/core/lwtunnel.c:459)
 ipv6_rcv (./include/net/dst.h:471 (discriminator 1) ./include/net/dst.h:469 (discriminator 1) net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:79 (discriminator 1) ./include/linux/netfilter.h:317 (discriminator 1) ./include/linux/netfilter.h:311 (discriminator 1) net/ipv6/ip6_input.c:311 (discriminator 1))
 __netif_receive_skb_one_core (net/core/dev.c:5967)
 process_backlog (./include/linux/rcupdate.h:869 net/core/dev.c:6440)
 __napi_poll.constprop.0 (net/core/dev.c:7452)
 net_rx_action (net/core/dev.c:7518 net/core/dev.c:7643)
 handle_softirqs (kernel/softirq.c:579)
 do_softirq (kernel/softirq.c:480 (discriminator 20))
 
 
 __local_bh_enable_ip (kernel/softirq.c:407)
 __dev_queue_xmit (net/core/dev.c:4740)
 ip6_finish_output2 (./include/linux/netdevice.h:3358 ./include/net/neighbour.h:526 ./include/net/neighbour.h:540 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:141)
 ip6_finish_output (net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:215 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:226)
 ip6_output (./include/linux/netfilter.h:306 net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:248)
 ip6_send_skb (net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1983)
 rawv6_sendmsg (net/ipv6/raw.c:588 net/ipv6/raw.c:918)
 __sys_sendto (net/socket.c:714 (discriminator 1) net/socket.c:729 (discriminator 1) net/socket.c:2228 (discriminator 1))
 __x64_sys_sendto (net/socket.c:2231)
 do_syscall_64 (arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:63 (discriminator 1) arch/x86/entry/syscall_64.c:94 (discriminator 1))
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe (arch/x86/entry/entry_64.S:130)
RIP: 0033:0x7f68cffb2a06
Code: 5d e8 41 8b 93 08 03 00 00 59 5e 48 83 f8 fc 75 19 83 e2 39 83 fa 08 75 11 e8 26 ff ff ff 66 0f 1f 44 00 00 48 8b 45 10 0f 05 &lt;48&gt; 8b 5d f8 c9 c3 0f 1f 40 00 f3 0f 1e fa 55 48 89 e5 48 83 ec 08
RSP: 002b:00007ffefb7c53d0 EFLAGS: 00000202 ORIG_RAX: 000000000000002c
RAX: ffffffffffffffda RBX: 0000564cd69f10a0 RCX: 00007f68cffb2a06
RDX: 0000000000000040 RSI: 0000564cd69f10a4 RDI: 0000000000000003
RBP: 00007ffefb7c53f0 R08: 0000564cd6a032ac R09: 000000000000001c
R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000202 R12: 0000564cd69f10a4
R13: 0000000000000040 R14: 00007ffefb7c66e0 R15: 0000564cd69f10a0
 

Allocated by task 1543:
 kasan_save_stack (mm/kasan/common.c:48)
 kasan_save_track (mm/kasan/common.c:60 (discriminator 1) mm/kasan/common.c:69 (discriminator 1))
 __kasan_slab_alloc (mm/kasan/common.c:319 mm/kasan/common.c:345)
 kmem_cache_alloc_node_noprof (./include/linux/kasan.h:250 mm/slub.c:4148 mm/slub.c:4197 mm/slub.c:4249)
 kmalloc_reserve (net/core/skbuff.c:581 (discriminator 88))
 __alloc_skb (net/core/skbuff.c:669)
 __ip6_append_data (net/ipv6/ip6_output.c:1672 (discriminator 1))
 ip6_
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38477 | net/sched: sch_qfq: Fix race condition on qfq_aggregate</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38477</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net/sched: sch_qfq: Fix race condition on qfq_aggregate

A race condition can occur when 'agg' is modified in qfq_change_agg
(called during qfq_enqueue) while other threads access it
concurrently. For example, qfq_dump_class may trigger a NULL
dereference, and qfq_delete_class may cause a use-after-free.

This patch addresses the issue by:

1. Moved qfq_destroy_class into the critical section.

2. Added sch_tree_lock protection to qfq_dump_class and
qfq_dump_class_stats.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38478 | comedi: Fix initialization of data for instructions that write to subdevice</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38478</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: Fix initialization of data for instructions that write to subdevice

Some Comedi subdevice instruction handlers are known to access
instruction data elements beyond the first `insn-&gt;n` elements in some
cases.  The `do_insn_ioctl()` and `do_insnlist_ioctl()` functions
allocate at least `MIN_SAMPLES` (16) data elements to deal with this,
but they do not initialize all of that.  For Comedi instruction codes
that write to the subdevice, the first `insn-&gt;n` data elements are
copied from user-space, but the remaining elements are left
uninitialized.  That could be a problem if the subdevice instruction
handler reads the uninitialized data.  Ensure that the first
`MIN_SAMPLES` elements are initialized before calling these instruction
handlers, filling the uncopied elements with 0.  For
`do_insnlist_ioctl()`, the same data buffer elements are used for
handling a list of instructions, so ensure the first `MIN_SAMPLES`
elements are initialized for each instruction that writes to the
subdevice.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38480 | comedi: Fix use of uninitialized data in insn_rw_emulate_bits()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38480</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: Fix use of uninitialized data in insn_rw_emulate_bits()

For Comedi `INSN_READ` and `INSN_WRITE` instructions on "digital"
subdevices (subdevice types `COMEDI_SUBD_DI`, `COMEDI_SUBD_DO`, and
`COMEDI_SUBD_DIO`), it is common for the subdevice driver not to have
`insn_read` and `insn_write` handler functions, but to have an
`insn_bits` handler function for handling Comedi `INSN_BITS`
instructions.  In that case, the subdevice's `insn_read` and/or
`insn_write` function handler pointers are set to point to the
`insn_rw_emulate_bits()` function by `__comedi_device_postconfig()`.

For `INSN_WRITE`, `insn_rw_emulate_bits()` currently assumes that the
supplied `data[0]` value is a valid copy from user memory.  It will at
least exist because `do_insnlist_ioctl()` and `do_insn_ioctl()` in
"comedi_fops.c" ensure at lease `MIN_SAMPLES` (16) elements are
allocated.  However, if `insn-&gt;n` is 0 (which is allowable for
`INSN_READ` and `INSN_WRITE` instructions, then `data[0]` may contain
uninitialized data, and certainly contains invalid data, possibly from a
different instruction in the array of instructions handled by
`do_insnlist_ioctl()`.  This will result in an incorrect value being
written to the digital output channel (or to the digital input/output
channel if configured as an output), and may be reflected in the
internal saved state of the channel.

Fix it by returning 0 early if `insn-&gt;n` is 0, before reaching the code
that accesses `data[0]`.  Previously, the function always returned 1 on
success, but it is supposed to be the number of data samples actually
read or written up to `insn-&gt;n`, which is 0 in this case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38481 | comedi: Fail COMEDI_INSNLIST ioctl if n_insns is too large</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38481</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: Fail COMEDI_INSNLIST ioctl if n_insns is too large

The handling of the `COMEDI_INSNLIST` ioctl allocates a kernel buffer to
hold the array of `struct comedi_insn`, getting the length from the
`n_insns` member of the `struct comedi_insnlist` supplied by the user.
The allocation will fail with a WARNING and a stack dump if it is too
large.

Avoid that by failing with an `-EINVAL` error if the supplied `n_insns`
value is unreasonable.

Define the limit on the `n_insns` value in the `MAX_INSNS` macro.  Set
this to the same value as `MAX_SAMPLES` (65536), which is the maximum
allowed sum of the values of the member `n` in the array of `struct
comedi_insn`, and sensible comedi instructions will have an `n` of at
least 1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38482 | comedi: das6402: Fix bit shift out of bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38482</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: das6402: Fix bit shift out of bounds

When checking for a supported IRQ number, the following test is used:

	/* IRQs 2,3,5,6,7, 10,11,15 are valid for "enhanced" mode */
	if ((1 &lt;&lt; it-&gt;options[1]) &amp; 0x8cec) {

However, `it-&gt;options[i]` is an unchecked `int` value from userspace, so
the shift amount could be negative or out of bounds.  Fix the test by
requiring `it-&gt;options[1]` to be within bounds before proceeding with
the original test.  Valid `it-&gt;options[1]` values that select the IRQ
will be in the range [1,15]. The value 0 explicitly disables the use of
interrupts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38483 | comedi: das16m1: Fix bit shift out of bounds</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38483</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

comedi: das16m1: Fix bit shift out of bounds

When checking for a supported IRQ number, the following test is used:

	/* only irqs 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 10, 11, 12, 14, and 15 are valid */
	if ((1 &lt;&lt; it-&gt;options[1]) &amp; 0xdcfc) {

However, `it-&gt;options[i]` is an unchecked `int` value from userspace, so
the shift amount could be negative or out of bounds.  Fix the test by
requiring `it-&gt;options[1]` to be within bounds before proceeding with
the original test.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38484 | iio: backend: fix out-of-bound write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38484</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iio: backend: fix out-of-bound write

The buffer is set to 80 character. If a caller write more characters,
count is truncated to the max available space in "simple_write_to_buffer".
But afterwards a string terminator is written to the buffer at offset count
without boundary check. The zero termination is written OUT-OF-BOUND.

Add a check that the given buffer is smaller then the buffer to prevent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38485 | iio: accel: fxls8962af: Fix use after free in fxls8962af_fifo_flush</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38485</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

iio: accel: fxls8962af: Fix use after free in fxls8962af_fifo_flush

fxls8962af_fifo_flush() uses indio_dev-&gt;active_scan_mask (with
iio_for_each_active_channel()) without making sure the indio_dev
stays in buffer mode.
There is a race if indio_dev exits buffer mode in the middle of the
interrupt that flushes the fifo. Fix this by calling
synchronize_irq() to ensure that no interrupt is currently running when
disabling buffer mode.

Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 00000000 when read
[...]
_find_first_bit_le from fxls8962af_fifo_flush+0x17c/0x290
fxls8962af_fifo_flush from fxls8962af_interrupt+0x80/0x178
fxls8962af_interrupt from irq_thread_fn+0x1c/0x7c
irq_thread_fn from irq_thread+0x110/0x1f4
irq_thread from kthread+0xe0/0xfc
kthread from ret_from_fork+0x14/0x2c</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:36:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38486 | soundwire: Revert &amp;quot;soundwire: qcom: Add set_channel_map api support&amp;quot;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38486</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

soundwire: Revert "soundwire: qcom: Add set_channel_map api support"

This reverts commit 7796c97df6b1b2206681a07f3c80f6023a6593d5.

This patch broke Dragonboard 845c (sdm845). I see:

    Unexpected kernel BRK exception at EL1
    Internal error: BRK handler: 00000000f20003e8 [#1]  SMP
    pc : qcom_swrm_set_channel_map+0x7c/0x80 [soundwire_qcom]
    lr : snd_soc_dai_set_channel_map+0x34/0x78
    Call trace:
     qcom_swrm_set_channel_map+0x7c/0x80 [soundwire_qcom] (P)
     sdm845_dai_init+0x18c/0x2e0 [snd_soc_sdm845]
     snd_soc_link_init+0x28/0x6c
     snd_soc_bind_card+0x5f4/0xb0c
     snd_soc_register_card+0x148/0x1a4
     devm_snd_soc_register_card+0x50/0xb0
     sdm845_snd_platform_probe+0x124/0x148 [snd_soc_sdm845]
     platform_probe+0x6c/0xd0
     really_probe+0xc0/0x2a4
     __driver_probe_device+0x7c/0x130
     driver_probe_device+0x40/0x118
     __device_attach_driver+0xc4/0x108
     bus_for_each_drv+0x8c/0xf0
     __device_attach+0xa4/0x198
     device_initial_probe+0x18/0x28
     bus_probe_device+0xb8/0xbc
     deferred_probe_work_func+0xac/0xfc
     process_one_work+0x244/0x658
     worker_thread+0x1b4/0x360
     kthread+0x148/0x228
     ret_from_fork+0x10/0x20
    Kernel panic - not syncing: BRK handler: Fatal exception

Dan has also reported following issues with the original patch
https://lore.kernel.org/all/33fe8fe7-719a-405a-9ed2-d9f816ce1d57@sabinyo.mountain/

Bug #1:
The zeroeth element of ctrl-&gt;pconfig[] is supposed to be unused.  We
start counting at 1.  However this code sets ctrl-&gt;pconfig[0].ch_mask = 128.

Bug #2:
There are SLIM_MAX_TX_PORTS (16) elements in tx_ch[] array but only
QCOM_SDW_MAX_PORTS + 1 (15) in the ctrl-&gt;pconfig[] array so it corrupts
memory like Yongqin Liu pointed out.

Bug 3:
Like Jie Gan pointed out, it erases all the tx information with the rx
information.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38487 | soc: aspeed: lpc-snoop: Don&amp;#x27;t disable channels that aren&amp;#x27;t enabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38487</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

soc: aspeed: lpc-snoop: Don't disable channels that aren't enabled

Mitigate e.g. the following:

    # echo 1e789080.lpc-snoop &gt; /sys/bus/platform/drivers/aspeed-lpc-snoop/unbind
    ...
    [  120.363594] Unable to handle kernel NULL pointer dereference at virtual address 00000004 when write
    [  120.373866] [00000004] *pgd=00000000
    [  120.377910] Internal error: Oops: 805 [#1] SMP ARM
    [  120.383306] CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 315 Comm: sh Not tainted 6.15.0-rc1-00009-g926217bc7d7d-dirty #20 NONE
    ...
    [  120.679543] Call trace:
    [  120.679559]  misc_deregister from aspeed_lpc_snoop_remove+0x84/0xac
    [  120.692462]  aspeed_lpc_snoop_remove from platform_remove+0x28/0x38
    [  120.700996]  platform_remove from device_release_driver_internal+0x188/0x200
    ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38488 | smb: client: fix use-after-free in crypt_message when using async crypto</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38488</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

smb: client: fix use-after-free in crypt_message when using async crypto

The CVE-2024-50047 fix removed asynchronous crypto handling from
crypt_message(), assuming all crypto operations are synchronous.
However, when hardware crypto accelerators are used, this can cause
use-after-free crashes:

  crypt_message()
    // Allocate the creq buffer containing the req
    creq = smb2_get_aead_req(..., &amp;amp;req);

    // Async encryption returns -EINPROGRESS immediately
    rc = enc ? crypto_aead_encrypt(req) : crypto_aead_decrypt(req);

    // Free creq while async operation is still in progress
    kvfree_sensitive(creq, ...);

Hardware crypto modules often implement async AEAD operations for
performance. When crypto_aead_encrypt/decrypt() returns -EINPROGRESS,
the operation completes asynchronously. Without crypto_wait_req(),
the function immediately frees the request buffer, leading to crashes
when the driver later accesses the freed memory.

This results in a use-after-free condition when the hardware crypto
driver later accesses the freed request structure, leading to kernel
crashes with NULL pointer dereferences.

The issue occurs because crypto_alloc_aead() with mask=0 doesn't
guarantee synchronous operation. Even without CRYPTO_ALG_ASYNC in
the mask, async implementations can be selected.

Fix by restoring the async crypto handling:
- DECLARE_CRYPTO_WAIT(wait) for completion tracking
- aead_request_set_callback() for async completion notification
- crypto_wait_req() to wait for operation completion

This ensures the request buffer isn't freed until the crypto operation
completes, whether synchronous or asynchronous, while preserving the
CVE-2024-50047 fix.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38489 | s390/bpf: Fix bpf_arch_text_poke() with new_addr == NULL again</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38489</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

s390/bpf: Fix bpf_arch_text_poke() with new_addr == NULL again

Commit 7ded842b356d ("s390/bpf: Fix bpf_plt pointer arithmetic") has
accidentally removed the critical piece of commit c730fce7c70c
("s390/bpf: Fix bpf_arch_text_poke() with new_addr == NULL"), causing
intermittent kernel panics in e.g. perf's on_switch() prog to reappear.

Restore the fix and add a comment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38490 | net: libwx: remove duplicate page_pool_put_full_page()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38490</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

net: libwx: remove duplicate page_pool_put_full_page()

page_pool_put_full_page() should only be invoked when freeing Rx buffers
or building a skb if the size is too short. At other times, the pages
need to be reused. So remove the redundant page put. In the original
code, double free pages cause kernel panic:

[  876.949834]  __irq_exit_rcu+0xc7/0x130
[  876.949836]  common_interrupt+0xb8/0xd0
[  876.949838]  
[  876.949838]  
[  876.949840]  asm_common_interrupt+0x22/0x40
[  876.949841] RIP: 0010:cpuidle_enter_state+0xc2/0x420
[  876.949843] Code: 00 00 e8 d1 1d 5e ff e8 ac f0 ff ff 49 89 c5 0f 1f 44 00 00 31 ff e8 cd fc 5c ff 45 84 ff 0f 85 40 02 00 00 fb 0f 1f 44 00 00 &lt;45&gt; 85 f6 0f 88 84 01 00 00 49 63 d6 48 8d 04 52 48 8d 04 82 49 8d
[  876.949844] RSP: 0018:ffffaa7340267e78 EFLAGS: 00000246
[  876.949845] RAX: ffff9e3f135be000 RBX: 0000000000000002 RCX: 0000000000000000
[  876.949846] RDX: 000000cc2dc4cb7c RSI: ffffffff89ee49ae RDI: ffffffff89ef9f9e
[  876.949847] RBP: ffff9e378f940800 R08: 0000000000000002 R09: 00000000000000ed
[  876.949848] R10: 000000000000afc8 R11: ffff9e3e9e5a9b6c R12: ffffffff8a6d8580
[  876.949849] R13: 000000cc2dc4cb7c R14: 0000000000000002 R15: 0000000000000000
[  876.949852]  ? cpuidle_enter_state+0xb3/0x420
[  876.949855]  cpuidle_enter+0x29/0x40
[  876.949857]  cpuidle_idle_call+0xfd/0x170
[  876.949859]  do_idle+0x7a/0xc0
[  876.949861]  cpu_startup_entry+0x25/0x30
[  876.949862]  start_secondary+0x117/0x140
[  876.949864]  common_startup_64+0x13e/0x148
[  876.949867]  
[  876.949868] ---[ end trace 0000000000000000 ]---
[  876.949869] ------------[ cut here ]------------
[  876.949870] list_del corruption, ffffead40445a348-&gt;next is NULL
[  876.949873] WARNING: CPU: 14 PID: 0 at lib/list_debug.c:52 __list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x67/0x120
[  876.949875] Modules linked in: snd_hrtimer(E) bnep(E) binfmt_misc(E) amdgpu(E) squashfs(E) vfat(E) loop(E) fat(E) amd_atl(E) snd_hda_codec_realtek(E) intel_rapl_msr(E) snd_hda_codec_generic(E) intel_rapl_common(E) snd_hda_scodec_component(E) snd_hda_codec_hdmi(E) snd_hda_intel(E) edac_mce_amd(E) snd_intel_dspcfg(E) snd_hda_codec(E) snd_hda_core(E) amdxcp(E) kvm_amd(E) snd_hwdep(E) gpu_sched(E) drm_panel_backlight_quirks(E) cec(E) snd_pcm(E) drm_buddy(E) snd_seq_dummy(E) drm_ttm_helper(E) btusb(E) kvm(E) snd_seq_oss(E) btrtl(E) ttm(E) btintel(E) snd_seq_midi(E) btbcm(E) drm_exec(E) snd_seq_midi_event(E) i2c_algo_bit(E) snd_rawmidi(E) bluetooth(E) drm_suballoc_helper(E) irqbypass(E) snd_seq(E) ghash_clmulni_intel(E) sha512_ssse3(E) drm_display_helper(E) aesni_intel(E) snd_seq_device(E) rfkill(E) snd_timer(E) gf128mul(E) drm_client_lib(E) drm_kms_helper(E) snd(E) i2c_piix4(E) joydev(E) soundcore(E) wmi_bmof(E) ccp(E) k10temp(E) i2c_smbus(E) gpio_amdpt(E) i2c_designware_platform(E) gpio_generic(E) sg(E)
[  876.949914]  i2c_designware_core(E) sch_fq_codel(E) parport_pc(E) drm(E) ppdev(E) lp(E) parport(E) fuse(E) nfnetlink(E) ip_tables(E) ext4 crc16 mbcache jbd2 sd_mod sfp mdio_i2c i2c_core txgbe ahci ngbe pcs_xpcs libahci libwx r8169 phylink libata realtek ptp pps_core video wmi
[  876.949933] CPU: 14 UID: 0 PID: 0 Comm: swapper/14 Kdump: loaded Tainted: G        W   E       6.16.0-rc2+ #20 PREEMPT(voluntary)
[  876.949935] Tainted: [W]=WARN, [E]=UNSIGNED_MODULE
[  876.949936] Hardware name: Micro-Star International Co., Ltd. MS-7E16/X670E GAMING PLUS WIFI (MS-7E16), BIOS 1.90 12/31/2024
[  876.949936] RIP: 0010:__list_del_entry_valid_or_report+0x67/0x120
[  876.949938] Code: 00 00 00 48 39 7d 08 0f 85 a6 00 00 00 5b b8 01 00 00 00 5d 41 5c e9 73 0d 93 ff 48 89 fe 48 c7 c7 a0 31 e8 89 e8 59 7c b3 ff &lt;0f&gt; 0b 31 c0 5b 5d 41 5c e9 57 0d 93 ff 48 89 fe 48 c7 c7 c8 31 e8
[  876.949940] RSP: 0018:ffffaa73405d0c60 EFLAGS: 00010282
[  876.949941] RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffffead40445a348 RCX: 0000000000000000
[  876.949942] RDX: 0000000000000105 RSI: 00000
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38491 | mptcp: make fallback action and fallback decision atomic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38491</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

mptcp: make fallback action and fallback decision atomic

Syzkaller reported the following splat:

  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 7704 at net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 __mptcp_do_fallback net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 [inline]
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 7704 at net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 mptcp_do_fallback net/mptcp/protocol.h:1244 [inline]
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 7704 at net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 check_fully_established net/mptcp/options.c:982 [inline]
  WARNING: CPU: 1 PID: 7704 at net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 mptcp_incoming_options+0x21a8/0x2510 net/mptcp/options.c:1153
  Modules linked in:
  CPU: 1 UID: 0 PID: 7704 Comm: syz.3.1419 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc3-gbd5ce2324dba #20 PREEMPT(voluntary)
  Hardware name: QEMU Ubuntu 24.04 PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS 1.16.3-debian-1.16.3-2 04/01/2014
  RIP: 0010:__mptcp_do_fallback net/mptcp/protocol.h:1223 [inline]
  RIP: 0010:mptcp_do_fallback net/mptcp/protocol.h:1244 [inline]
  RIP: 0010:check_fully_established net/mptcp/options.c:982 [inline]
  RIP: 0010:mptcp_incoming_options+0x21a8/0x2510 net/mptcp/options.c:1153
  Code: 24 18 e8 bb 2a 00 fd e9 1b df ff ff e8 b1 21 0f 00 e8 ec 5f c4 fc 44 0f b7 ac 24 b0 00 00 00 e9 54 f1 ff ff e8 d9 5f c4 fc 90 &lt;0f&gt; 0b 90 e9 b8 f4 ff ff e8 8b 2a 00 fd e9 8d e6 ff ff e8 81 2a 00
  RSP: 0018:ffff8880a3f08448 EFLAGS: 00010246
  RAX: 0000000000000000 RBX: ffff8880180a8000 RCX: ffffffff84afcf45
  RDX: ffff888090223700 RSI: ffffffff84afdaa7 RDI: 0000000000000001
  RBP: ffff888017955780 R08: 0000000000000001 R09: 0000000000000000
  R10: 0000000000000000 R11: 0000000000000000 R12: 0000000000000000
  R13: ffff8880180a8910 R14: ffff8880a3e9d058 R15: 0000000000000000
  FS:  00005555791b8500(0000) GS:ffff88811c495000(0000) knlGS:0000000000000000
  CS:  0010 DS: 0000 ES: 0000 CR0: 0000000080050033
  CR2: 000000110c2800b7 CR3: 0000000058e44000 CR4: 0000000000350ef0
  Call Trace:
   
   tcp_reset+0x26f/0x2b0 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:4432
   tcp_validate_incoming+0x1057/0x1b60 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:5975
   tcp_rcv_established+0x5b5/0x21f0 net/ipv4/tcp_input.c:6166
   tcp_v4_do_rcv+0x5dc/0xa70 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:1925
   tcp_v4_rcv+0x3473/0x44a0 net/ipv4/tcp_ipv4.c:2363
   ip_protocol_deliver_rcu+0xba/0x480 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:205
   ip_local_deliver_finish+0x2f1/0x500 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:233
   NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:317 [inline]
   NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:311 [inline]
   ip_local_deliver+0x1be/0x560 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:254
   dst_input include/net/dst.h:469 [inline]
   ip_rcv_finish net/ipv4/ip_input.c:447 [inline]
   NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:317 [inline]
   NF_HOOK include/linux/netfilter.h:311 [inline]
   ip_rcv+0x514/0x810 net/ipv4/ip_input.c:567
   __netif_receive_skb_one_core+0x197/0x1e0 net/core/dev.c:5975
   __netif_receive_skb+0x1f/0x120 net/core/dev.c:6088
   process_backlog+0x301/0x1360 net/core/dev.c:6440
   __napi_poll.constprop.0+0xba/0x550 net/core/dev.c:7453
   napi_poll net/core/dev.c:7517 [inline]
   net_rx_action+0xb44/0x1010 net/core/dev.c:7644
   handle_softirqs+0x1d0/0x770 kernel/softirq.c:579
   do_softirq+0x3f/0x90 kernel/softirq.c:480
   
   
   __local_bh_enable_ip+0xed/0x110 kernel/softirq.c:407
   local_bh_enable include/linux/bottom_half.h:33 [inline]
   inet_csk_listen_stop+0x2c5/0x1070 net/ipv4/inet_connection_sock.c:1524
   mptcp_check_listen_stop.part.0+0x1cc/0x220 net/mptcp/protocol.c:2985
   mptcp_check_listen_stop net/mptcp/mib.h:118 [inline]
   __mptcp_close+0x9b9/0xbd0 net/mptcp/protocol.c:3000
   mptcp_close+0x2f/0x140 net/mptcp/protocol.c:3066
   inet_release+0xed/0x200 net/ipv4/af_inet.c:435
   inet6_release+0x4f/0x70 net/ipv6/af_inet6.c:487
   __sock_release+0xb3/0x270 net/socket.c:649
   sock_close+0x1c/0x30 net/socket.c:1439
   __fput+0x402/0xb70 fs/file_table.c:465
   task_work_run+0x150/0x240 kernel/task_work.c:227
   resume_user_mode_work include/linux/resume_user_mode.h:50 [inline]
   exit_to_user_mode_loop+0xd4
---truncated---</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38492 | netfs: Fix race between cache write completion and ALL_QUEUED being set</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38492</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfs: Fix race between cache write completion and ALL_QUEUED being set

When netfslib is issuing subrequests, the subrequests start processing
immediately and may complete before we reach the end of the issuing
function.  At the end of the issuing function we set NETFS_RREQ_ALL_QUEUED
to indicate to the collector that we aren't going to issue any more subreqs
and that it can do the final notifications and cleanup.

Now, this isn't a problem if the request is synchronous
(NETFS_RREQ_OFFLOAD_COLLECTION is unset) as the result collection will be
done in-thread and we're guaranteed an opportunity to run the collector.

However, if the request is asynchronous, collection is primarily triggered
by the termination of subrequests queuing it on a workqueue.  Now, a race
can occur here if the app thread sets ALL_QUEUED after the last subrequest
terminates.

This can happen most easily with the copy2cache code (as used by Ceph)
where, in the collection routine of a read request, an asynchronous write
request is spawned to copy data to the cache.  Folios are added to the
write request as they're unlocked, but there may be a delay before
ALL_QUEUED is set as the write subrequests may complete before we get
there.

If all the write subreqs have finished by the ALL_QUEUED point, no further
events happen and the collection never happens, leaving the request
hanging.

Fix this by queuing the collector after setting ALL_QUEUED.  This is a bit
heavy-handed and it may be sufficient to do it only if there are no extant
subreqs.

Also add a tracepoint to cross-reference both requests in a copy-to-request
operation and add a trace to the netfs_rreq tracepoint to indicate the
setting of ALL_QUEUED.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38493 | tracing/osnoise: Fix crash in timerlat_dump_stack()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38493</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

tracing/osnoise: Fix crash in timerlat_dump_stack()

We have observed kernel panics when using timerlat with stack saving,
with the following dmesg output:

memcpy: detected buffer overflow: 88 byte write of buffer size 0
WARNING: CPU: 2 PID: 8153 at lib/string_helpers.c:1032 __fortify_report+0x55/0xa0
CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 8153 Comm: timerlatu/2 Kdump: loaded Not tainted 6.15.3-200.fc42.x86_64 #1 PREEMPT(lazy)
Call Trace:
 
 ? trace_buffer_lock_reserve+0x2a/0x60
 __fortify_panic+0xd/0xf
 __timerlat_dump_stack.cold+0xd/0xd
 timerlat_dump_stack.part.0+0x47/0x80
 timerlat_fd_read+0x36d/0x390
 vfs_read+0xe2/0x390
 ? syscall_exit_to_user_mode+0x1d5/0x210
 ksys_read+0x73/0xe0
 do_syscall_64+0x7b/0x160
 ? exc_page_fault+0x7e/0x1a0
 entry_SYSCALL_64_after_hwframe+0x76/0x7e

__timerlat_dump_stack() constructs the ftrace stack entry like this:

struct stack_entry *entry;
...
memcpy(&amp;amp;entry-&gt;caller, fstack-&gt;calls, size);
entry-&gt;size = fstack-&gt;nr_entries;

Since commit e7186af7fb26 ("tracing: Add back FORTIFY_SOURCE logic to
kernel_stack event structure"), struct stack_entry marks its caller
field with __counted_by(size). At the time of the memcpy, entry-&gt;size
contains garbage from the ringbuffer, which under some circumstances is
zero, triggering a kernel panic by buffer overflow.

Populate the size field before the memcpy so that the out-of-bounds
check knows the correct size. This is analogous to
__ftrace_trace_stack().</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38494 | HID: core: do not bypass hid_hw_raw_request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38494</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: core: do not bypass hid_hw_raw_request

hid_hw_raw_request() is actually useful to ensure the provided buffer
and length are valid. Directly calling in the low level transport driver
function bypassed those checks and allowed invalid paramto be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38495 | HID: core: ensure the allocated report buffer can contain the reserved report ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38495</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

HID: core: ensure the allocated report buffer can contain the reserved report ID

When the report ID is not used, the low level transport drivers expect
the first byte to be 0. However, currently the allocated buffer not
account for that extra byte, meaning that instead of having 8 guaranteed
bytes for implement to be working, we only have 7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38496 | dm-bufio: fix sched in atomic context</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38496</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

dm-bufio: fix sched in atomic context

If "try_verify_in_tasklet" is set for dm-verity, DM_BUFIO_CLIENT_NO_SLEEP
is enabled for dm-bufio. However, when bufio tries to evict buffers, there
is a chance to trigger scheduling in spin_lock_bh, the following warning
is hit:

BUG: sleeping function called from invalid context at drivers/md/dm-bufio.c:2745
in_atomic(): 1, irqs_disabled(): 0, non_block: 0, pid: 123, name: kworker/2:2
preempt_count: 201, expected: 0
RCU nest depth: 0, expected: 0
4 locks held by kworker/2:2/123:
 #0: ffff88800a2d1548 ((wq_completion)dm_bufio_cache){....}-{0:0}, at: process_one_work+0xe46/0x1970
 #1: ffffc90000d97d20 ((work_completion)(&amp;amp;dm_bufio_replacement_work)){....}-{0:0}, at: process_one_work+0x763/0x1970
 #2: ffffffff8555b528 (dm_bufio_clients_lock){....}-{3:3}, at: do_global_cleanup+0x1ce/0x710
 #3: ffff88801d5820b8 (&amp;amp;c-&gt;spinlock){....}-{2:2}, at: do_global_cleanup+0x2a5/0x710
Preemption disabled at:
[&lt;0000000000000000&gt;] 0x0
CPU: 2 UID: 0 PID: 123 Comm: kworker/2:2 Not tainted 6.16.0-rc3-g90548c634bd0 #305 PREEMPT(voluntary)
Hardware name: QEMU Standard PC (i440FX + PIIX, 1996), BIOS rel-1.16.3-0-ga6ed6b701f0a-prebuilt.qemu.org 04/01/2014
Workqueue: dm_bufio_cache do_global_cleanup
Call Trace:
 
 dump_stack_lvl+0x53/0x70
 __might_resched+0x360/0x4e0
 do_global_cleanup+0x2f5/0x710
 process_one_work+0x7db/0x1970
 worker_thread+0x518/0xea0
 kthread+0x359/0x690
 ret_from_fork+0xf3/0x1b0
 ret_from_fork_asm+0x1a/0x30
 

That can be reproduced by:

  veritysetup format --data-block-size=4096 --hash-block-size=4096 /dev/vda /dev/vdb
  SIZE=$(blockdev --getsz /dev/vda)
  dmsetup create myverity -r --table "0 $SIZE verity 1 /dev/vda /dev/vdb 4096 4096  1 sha256   1 try_verify_in_tasklet"
  mount /dev/dm-0 /mnt -o ro
  echo 102400 &gt; /sys/module/dm_bufio/parameters/max_cache_size_bytes
  [read files in /mnt]</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38497 | usb: gadget: configfs: Fix OOB read on empty string write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38497</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

usb: gadget: configfs: Fix OOB read on empty string write

When writing an empty string to either 'qw_sign' or 'landingPage'
sysfs attributes, the store functions attempt to access page[l - 1]
before validating that the length 'l' is greater than zero.

This patch fixes the vulnerability by adding a check at the beginning
of os_desc_qw_sign_store() and webusb_landingPage_store() to handle
the zero-length input case gracefully by returning immediately.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6918 | SQLi in Ncvav&amp;#x27;s Virtual PBX Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6918</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Ncvav Virtual PBX Software allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Virtual PBX Software: before 09.07.2025.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:20:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8273 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s8.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8273</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update_s8.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40730 | HTML injection in Vox Media&amp;#x27;s Chorus CMS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40730</link><description>HTML injection in Vox Media's Chorus CMS. This vulnerability allows an attacker to execute JavaScript code in the victim's browser by sending them a malicious URL using the 'q' parameter in '/search'. This vulnerability can be exploited to steal sensitive user data, such as session cookies, or to perform actions on behalf of the user.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8272 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_fst.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8272</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_fst.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:44:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8271 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8271</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/delete_s3.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:44:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8270 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8270</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/delete_s2.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8269 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8269</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s1.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:32:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27802 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Episerver Content Management System (CMS) Edit Preview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27802</link><description>The Episerver Content Management System (CMS) by Optimizely was affected by multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. This allowed an authenticated attacker to execute malicious JavaScript code in the victim's browser.

RTE properties (text fields), which could be used in the "Edit" section of the CMS,
allowed the input of arbitrary text. It was possible to input malicious JavaScript 
code in these properties that would be executed if a user visits the previewed 
page. Attackers needed at least the role "WebEditor" in order to exploit this issue.

Affected products: Version 11.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;11.21.4) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.5), Version 12.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;12.22.1) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.3)</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27800 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Episerver Content Management System (CMS) Admin Dashboard</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27800</link><description>The Episerver Content Management System (CMS) by Optimizely was affected by multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. This allowed an authenticated attacker to execute malicious JavaScript code in the victim's browser.



The Admin dashboard offered the functionality to add gadgets to the dashboard.
This included the "Notes" gadget. An authenticated attacker with the corresponding
access rights (such as "WebAdmin") that was impersonating the victim could insert
malicious JavaScript code in these notes that would be executed if the victim
visited the dashboard.

Affected products: Version 11.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;11.21.4) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.5), Version 12.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;12.22.1) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.3)</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:58:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27801 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Episerver Content Management System (CMS) Media Selection Preview</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27801</link><description>The Episerver Content Management System (CMS) by Optimizely was affected by multiple Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities. This allowed an authenticated attacker to execute malicious JavaScript code in the victim's browser.



ContentReference properties, which could be used in the "Edit" section of the CMS, offered an upload functionality for documents. These documents could later be used as displayed content on the page. It was possible to upload SVG files that include malicious JavaScript code that would be executed if a user visited the direct URL of the preview image. Attackers needed at least the role "WebEditor" in order to exploit this issue.







Affected products: Version 11.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;11.21.4) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.5), Version 12.X: EPiServer.CMS.Core (&lt;12.22.1) with EPiServer.CMS.UI (&lt;11.37.3)</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8266 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS collect.js getArticle deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8266</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function getArticle of the file app/modules/cms/controller/collect.js. The manipulation of the argument targetUrl leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8265 | 299Ko CMS File Management view unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8265</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in 299Ko CMS 2.0.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/filemanager/view of the component File Management. The manipulation leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8263 | prettier parser-postcss.js parseNestedCSS redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8263</link><description>A vulnerability was found in prettier up to 3.6.2. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function parseNestedCSS of the file src/language-css/parser-postcss.js. The manipulation of the argument node leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:49:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8262 | yarnpkg Yarn hosted-git-resolver.js explodeHostedGitFragment redos</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8262</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yarnpkg Yarn up to 1.22.22. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function explodeHostedGitFragment of the file src/resolvers/exotics/hosted-git-resolver.js. The manipulation leads to inefficient regular expression complexity. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The patch is identified as 97731871e674bf93bcbf29e9d3258da8685f3076. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 07:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8261 | Vaelsys User Creation vgrid_server.php improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8261</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Vaelsys 4.1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /grid/vgrid_server.php of the component User Creation Handler. The manipulation leads to improper authorization. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 06:35:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8260 | Vaelsys MD4 Hash vgrid_server.php weak hash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8260</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Vaelsys 4.1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /grid/vgrid_server.php of the component MD4 Hash Handler. The manipulation of the argument xajaxargs leads to use of weak hash. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 06:35:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8259 | Vaelsys vgrid_server.php execute_DataObjectProc os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8259</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Vaelsys 4.1.0. This affects the function execute_DataObjectProc of the file /grid/vgrid_server.php. The manipulation of the argument xajaxargs leads to os command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8258 | Cool Mo Maigcal Number App com.sdmagic.number AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8258</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Cool Mo Maigcal Number App up to 1.0.3 on Android. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.sdmagic.number. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. An attack has to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8267 | Versions of the package ssrfcheck before 1.2.0 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) due to an incomplete denylist of IP addr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8267</link><description>Versions of the package ssrfcheck before 1.2.0 are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) due to an incomplete denylist of IP address ranges. Specifically, the package fails to classify the reserved IP address space 224.0.0.0/4 (Multicast) as invalid. This oversight allows attackers to craft requests targeting these multicast addresses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8257 | Lobby Universe Lobby App com.maverick.lobby AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8257</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Lobby Universe Lobby App up to 2.8.0 on Android. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.maverick.lobby. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:05:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8256 | code-projects Online Ordering System product.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8256</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/product.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:31:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8255 | code-projects Exam Form Submission register.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8255</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:31:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8254 | Campcodes Courier Management System view_parcel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8254</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /view_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53159 | The openssl crate before 0.10.55 for Rust allows an out-of-bounds read via an empty string to X509VerifyParamRef::set_host.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53159</link><description>The openssl crate before 0.10.55 for Rust allows an out-of-bounds read via an empty string to X509VerifyParamRef::set_host.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53160 | The sequoia-openpgp crate before 1.16.0 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53160</link><description>The sequoia-openpgp crate before 1.16.0 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53161 | The buffered-reader crate before 1.1.5 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53161</link><description>The buffered-reader crate before 1.1.5 for Rust allows out-of-bounds array access and a panic.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8252 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8252</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s5.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8253 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s6.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8253</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/delete_s6.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-50237 | The ed25519-dalek crate before 2 for Rust allows a double public key signing function oracle attack. The Keypair implementation leads to a s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-50237</link><description>The ed25519-dalek crate before 2 for Rust allows a double public key signing function oracle attack. The Keypair implementation leads to a simple computation for extracting a private key.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8251 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8251</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s4.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8250 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s4.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8250</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update_s4.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53158 | The gix-transport crate before 0.36.1 for Rust allows command execution via the "gix clone 'ssh://-oProxyCommand=open$IFS" substring. NOTE: ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53158</link><description>The gix-transport crate before 0.36.1 for Rust allows command execution via the "gix clone 'ssh://-oProxyCommand=open$IFS" substring. NOTE: this was discovered before CVE-2024-32884, a similar vulnerability (involving a username field) that is more difficult to exploit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8248 | code-projects Online Ordering System signup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8248</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /signup.php. The manipulation of the argument firstname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8249 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8249</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_s3.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:50:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53157 | The rosenpass crate before 0.2.1 for Rust allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (panic) via a one-byte UDP packet.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53157</link><description>The rosenpass crate before 0.2.1 for Rust allows remote attackers to cause a denial of service (panic) via a one-byte UDP packet.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8247 | Projectworlds Online Admission System admin.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8247</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin.php. The manipulation of the argument markof leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:34:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8246 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formRoute buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8246</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formRoute of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:14:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8245 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMultiAPVLAN buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8245</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formMultiAPVLAN of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 22:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8244 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMapDelDevice buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8244</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formMapDelDevice of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument macstr leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 22:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58266 | The shlex crate before 1.2.1 for Rust allows unquoted and unescaped instances of the { and \xa0 characters, which may facilitate command inj...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58266</link><description>The shlex crate before 1.2.1 for Rust allows unquoted and unescaped instances of the { and \xa0 characters, which may facilitate command injection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:57:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8243 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formMapDel buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8243</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formMapDel of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument devicemac1 leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58265 | The snow crate before 0.9.5 for Rust, when stateful TransportState is used, allows incrementing a nonce and thereby denying message delivery...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58265</link><description>The snow crate before 0.9.5 for Rust, when stateful TransportState is used, allows incrementing a nonce and thereby denying message delivery.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8242 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8242</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument ip6addr/url/vpnPassword/vpnUser leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58264 | The serde-json-wasm crate before 1.0.1 for Rust allows stack consumption via deeply nested JSON data.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58264</link><description>The serde-json-wasm crate before 1.0.1 for Rust allows stack consumption via deeply nested JSON data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:23:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-53156 | The transpose crate before 0.2.3 for Rust allows an integer overflow via input_width and input_height arguments.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-53156</link><description>The transpose crate before 0.2.3 for Rust allows an integer overflow via input_width and input_height arguments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8241 | 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System report.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8241</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /report.php. The manipulation of the argument From leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58263 | The cosmwasm-std crate before 2.0.2 for Rust allows integer overflows that cause incorrect contract calculations.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58263</link><description>The cosmwasm-std crate before 2.0.2 for Rust allows integer overflows that cause incorrect contract calculations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58262 | The curve25519-dalek crate before 4.1.3 for Rust has a constant-time operation on elliptic curve scalars that is removed by LLVM.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58262</link><description>The curve25519-dalek crate before 4.1.3 for Rust has a constant-time operation on elliptic curve scalars that is removed by LLVM.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8240 | code-projects Exam Form Submission dashboard.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8240</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/dashboard.php. The manipulation of the argument phone leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58261 | The sequoia-openpgp crate 1.13.0 before 1.21.0 for Rust allows an infinite loop of "Reading a cert: Invalid operation: Not a Key packet" mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58261</link><description>The sequoia-openpgp crate 1.13.0 before 1.21.0 for Rust allows an infinite loop of "Reading a cert: Invalid operation: Not a Key packet" messages for RawCertParser operations that encounter an unsupported primary key type.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8239 | code-projects Exam Form Submission admin sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8239</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:23:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8238 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8238</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/update_s2.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8237 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8237</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/update_s1.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:14:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8236 | code-projects Online Ordering System edit_product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8236</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit_product.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8235 | code-projects Online Ordering System product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8235</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/product.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 16:29:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8234 | code-projects Online Ordering System delete_member.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8234</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_member.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 15:22:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8233 | code-projects Online Ordering System user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8233</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/user.php. The manipulation of the argument un leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:36:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8232 | code-projects Online Ordering System delete_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8232</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Ordering System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:15:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8231 | D-Link DIR-890L UART Port rgbin hard-coded credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8231</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in D-Link DIR-890L up to 111b04. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file rgbin of the component UART Port. The manipulation leads to hard-coded credentials. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:45:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8230 | Campcodes Courier Management System manage_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8230</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 12:42:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8229 | Campcodes Courier Management System parcel_list.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8229</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /parcel_list.php. The manipulation of the argument s leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 10:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8228 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS getPages server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8228</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function getPages of the file /cms/collect/getPages. The manipulation of the argument targetUrl leads to server-side request forgery. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 09:45:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8227 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS getArticle deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8227</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /collect/getArticle. The manipulation of the argument taskUrl leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 33d9bb464353015aaaba84e27638ac9a3912795d. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 09:29:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8226 | yanyutao0402 ChanCMS find information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8226</link><description>A vulnerability was found in yanyutao0402 ChanCMS up to 3.1.2. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysApp/find. The manipulation of the argument accessKey/secretKey leads to information disclosure. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 3.1.3 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:50:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8225 | GNU Binutils DWARF Section dwarf.c process_debug_info memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8225</link><description>A vulnerability was found in GNU Binutils 2.44 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function process_debug_info of the file binutils/dwarf.c of the component DWARF Section Handler. The manipulation leads to memory leak. Attacking locally is a requirement. The identifier of the patch is e51fdff7d2e538c0e5accdd65649ac68e6e0ddd4. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:29:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5120 | Sandbox Escape Vulnerability in huggingface/smolagents</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5120</link><description>A sandbox escape vulnerability was identified in huggingface/smolagents version 1.14.0, allowing attackers to bypass the restricted execution environment and achieve remote code execution (RCE). The vulnerability stems from the local_python_executor.py module, which inadequately restricts Python code execution despite employing static and dynamic checks. Attackers can exploit whitelisted modules and functions to execute arbitrary code, compromising the host system. This flaw undermines the core security boundary intended to isolate untrusted code, posing risks such as unauthorized code execution, data leakage, and potential integration-level compromise. The issue is resolved in version 1.17.0.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 07:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8224 | GNU Binutils BFD Library elf.c bfd_elf_get_str_section null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8224</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in GNU Binutils 2.44 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function bfd_elf_get_str_section of the file bfd/elf.c of the component BFD Library. The manipulation leads to null pointer dereference. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The name of the patch is db856d41004301b3a56438efd957ef5cabb91530. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:53:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8223 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 AdminTypeCustController.java cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8223</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. This affects an unknown part of the file AdminTypeCustController.java. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:36:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8104 | Memory Usage &amp;lt;= 3.98 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Limited Plugin Installation via wpmemory_install_plugin Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8104</link><description>The Memory Usage plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 3.98. This is due to missing nonce validation in the wpmemory_install_plugin() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to silently install one of the several whitelisted plugins via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:04:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8222 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 GoodsController.java cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8222</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file GoodsController.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available. Multiple endpoints are affected.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 05:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8221 | jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 GoodsCustController.java goodsSearch cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8221</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in jerryshensjf JPACookieShop 蛋糕商城JPA版 up to 24a15c02b4f75042c9f7f615a3fed2ec1cefb999. Affected by this vulnerability is the function goodsSearch of the file GoodsCustController.java. The manipulation of the argument keyword leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 04:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8220 | Engeman Web Password Recovery Page RecoveryPass sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8220</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Engeman Web up to 12.0.0.1. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Login/RecoveryPass of the component Password Recovery Page. The manipulation of the argument LanguageCombobox leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54597 | LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.7.3 allows XSS via the q parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54597</link><description>LinuxServer.io Heimdall before 2.7.3 allows XSS via the q parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8219 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM HTTP POST Request tabdetail_moduleSave_dxkp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8219</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.4.7. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /crm/crmapi/erp/tabdetail_moduleSave_dxkp.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument getvaluestring leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 8.6.5.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The vendor explains: "All SQL injection vectors were patched via parameterized queries and input sanitization in v8.6.5+. We strongly advise all customers to upgrade to the current version (v8.6.5.2), which includes this fix and additional security enhancements."</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 03:52:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6241 | CVE-2025-6241</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6241</link><description>LsiAgent.exe, a component of SysTrack from Lakeside Software, attempts to load several DLL files which are not present in the default installation. If a user-writable directory is present in the SYSTEM PATH environment variable, the user can write a malicious DLL to that directory with arbitrary code. This malicious DLL is executed in the context of NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM upon service start or restart, due to the Windows default dynamic-link library search order, resulting in local elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 02:09:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8211 | Roothub SystemConfigAdminController.java edit cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8211</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Roothub up to 2.6. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Edit of the file src/main/java/cn/roothub/web/admin/SystemConfigAdminController.java. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 21:10:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8210 | Yeelink Yeelight App com.yeelight.cherry AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8210</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Yeelink Yeelight App up to 3.5.4 on Android. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.yeelight.cherry. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Attacking locally is a requirement. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8207 | Canara ai1 Mobile Banking App com.canarabank.mobility AndroidManifest.xml improper export of android application components</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8207</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Canara ai1 Mobile Banking App 3.6.23 on Android and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file AndroidManifest.xml of the component com.canarabank.mobility. The manipulation leads to improper export of android application components. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8206 | Comodo Dragon IP DNS Leakage Detector cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8206</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. This affects an unknown part of the component IP DNS Leakage Detector. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 19:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8205 | Comodo Dragon IP DNS Leakage Detector cleartext transmission</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8205</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component IP DNS Leakage Detector. The manipulation leads to cleartext transmission of sensitive information. The attack may be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:45:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8204 | Comodo Dragon HSTS security check</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8204</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Comodo Dragon up to 134.0.6998.179. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component HSTS Handler. The manipulation leads to security check for standard. The attack can be launched remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:46:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8203 | Jingmen Zeyou Large File Upload Control index.jsp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8203</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Jingmen Zeyou Large File Upload Control up to 6.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.jsp. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8191 | macrozheng mall Swagger UI index.html cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8191</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in macrozheng mall up to 1.0.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /swagger-ui/index.html of the component Swagger UI. The manipulation of the argument configUrl leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor deleted the GitHub issue for this vulnerability without any explanation. Afterwards the vendor was contacted early about this disclosure via email but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8190 | Campcodes Courier Management System print_pdets.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8190</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /print_pdets.php. The manipulation of the argument ids leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8189 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_user.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8189</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit_user.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8188 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_staff.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8188</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /edit_staff.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:55:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8187 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_parcel.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8187</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /edit_parcel.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:43:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8186 | Campcodes Courier Management System edit_branch.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8186</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Courier Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /edit_branch.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8185 | 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System getbyid.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8185</link><description>A vulnerability was found in 1000 Projects ABC Courier Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /getbyid.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8184 | D-Link DIR-513 HTTP POST Request formSetWanL2TPtriggers formSetWanL2TPcallback stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8184</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-513 up to 1.10 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function formSetWanL2TPcallback of the file /goform/formSetWanL2TPtriggers of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 09:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8182 | Tenda AC18 Samba smb.conf weak password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8182</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.19 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /etc_ro/smb.conf of the component Samba. The manipulation leads to weak password requirements. The attack can be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:50:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5529 | Educenter &amp;lt;= 1.6.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5529</link><description>The Educenter theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Circle Counter Block in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6989 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.21.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Arbitrary Folder Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6989</link><description>The Kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary folder deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete_font() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.21.0. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary folders on the server.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6991 | Kallyas &amp;lt;= 4.21.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6991</link><description>The kallyas theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 4.21.0 via the 'TH_LatestPosts4` widget. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary .php files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where .php file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:41:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8181 | TOTOLINK N600R/X2000R FTP Service vsftpd.conf least privilege violation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8181</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK N600R and X2000R 1.0.0.1. This affects an unknown part of the file vsftpd.conf of the component FTP Service. The manipulation leads to least privilege violation. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6987 | Advanced iFrame &amp;lt;= 2025.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6987</link><description>The Advanced iFrame plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'advanced_iframe' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2025.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7501 | Wonder Slider Lite &amp;amp; Wonder Slider &amp;lt;= 14.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Dom-based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7501</link><description>The Wonder Slider Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via image title and description DOM in all versions up to, and including, 14.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8097 | WoodMart - Multipurpose WooCommerce Theme &amp;lt;= 8.2.6 - Improper Input Validation Leading to Unauthenticated Cart Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8097</link><description>The WoodMart theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Improper Input Validation in all versions up to, and including, 8.2.6. This is due to insufficient validation of the qty parameter in the woodmart_update_cart_item function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to manipulate cart quantities using fractional values, allowing them to obtain products for free by setting extremely small quantities (e.g., 0.00001) that round cart totals to $0.00, effectively bypassing payment requirements and allowing unauthorized acquisition of virtual or downloadable products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8180 | Tenda CH22 deleteUserName formdeleteUserName buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8180</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. Affected by this issue is the function formdeleteUserName of the file /goform/deleteUserName. The manipulation of the argument old_account leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8198 | MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 3.9.0 - Unauthenticated Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8198</link><description>The MinimogWP – The High Converting eCommerce WordPress Theme theme for WordPress is vulnerable to price manipulation in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.0. This is due to an insufficient check on quantity values when changing quantities in the cart. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to add items to the cart and adjust the quantity to a fractional amount, causing the price to change based on the fractional amount. The vulnerability cannot be exploited if WooCommerce version 9.8.2+ is installed.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 05:53:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8179 | PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8179</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Local Services Search Engine Management System 2.1. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 05:12:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6895 | MelaPress Login Security 2.1.0 - 2.1.1 - Authentication Bypass to Privilege Escalation via get_valid_user_based_on_token Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6895</link><description>The Melapress Login Security plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass due to missing authorization within the get_valid_user_based_on_token() function in versions 2.1.0 to 2.1.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers who know an arbitrary user meta value to bypass authentication checks and log in as that user.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:48:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8178 | Tenda AC10 RequestsProcessLaid heap-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8178</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC10 16.03.10.13. Affected is an unknown function of the file /goform/RequestsProcessLaid. The manipulation of the argument device1D leads to heap-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:48:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8177 | LibTIFF thumbnail.c setrow buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8177</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF up to 4.7.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function setrow of the file tools/thumbnail.c. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. An attack has to be approached locally. The patch is named e8c9d6c616b19438695fd829e58ae4fde5bfbc22. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13507 | GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory &amp;lt;= 2.8.97 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13507</link><description>The GeoDirectory – WP Business Directory Plugin and Classified Listings Directory plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the dist parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.97 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50184 | DbGate allows for File Traversal via file parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50184</link><description>DbGate is cross-platform database manager. In versions 6.4.3-premium-beta.5 and below, DbGate is vulnerable to a directory traversal flaw. The file parameter is not properly restricted to the intended uploads directory. As a result, the endpoint that lists files within the upload directory can be manipulated to access arbitrary files on the system. By supplying a crafted path to the file parameter, an attacker can read files outside the upload directory, potentially exposing sensitive system-level data. This is fixed in version 6.4.3-beta.8.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50185 | DbGate allows Unauthorized File Access via CSV Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50185</link><description>DbGate is cross-platform database manager. In versions 6.6.0 and below, DbGate allows unauthorized file access due to insufficient validation of file paths and types. A user with application-level access can retrieve data from arbitrary files on the system, regardless of their location or file type. The plugin fails to enforce proper checks on content type and file extension before reading a file. As a result, even sensitive files accessible only to the root user can be read through the application interface. There is currently no fix for this issue.






```
POST /runners/load-reader HTTP/1.1
Host: 
User-Agent: Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86_64; rv:138.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/138.0
Accept: */*
Accept-Language: en-US,en;q=0.5
Accept-Encoding: gzip, deflate, br
Referer: 
Content-Type: application/json
Authorization: Bearer 
Content-Length: 127
Origin: http://192.168.124.119:3000
Connection: keep-alive
Cookie: 
Priority: u=0
Cache-Control: max-age=0

{"functionName":"reader@dbgate-plugin-csv","props":{"fileName":"/etc\/shadow","limitRows":100}}

```



The request payload:
![Screenshot From 2025-05-31 22-54-49](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/28943ad7-14f8-432a-9836-cec5c3593c0a)


Lines of the file being returned:
![Screenshot From 2025-05-31 22-55-23](https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/4fae4652-097d-4d39-9f7a-6ce39346ed1d)</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54366 | FreeScout&amp;#x27;s deserialization of untrusted data leads to Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54366</link><description>FreeScout is a lightweight free open source help desk and shared inbox built with PHP (Laravel framework). In versions 1.8.185 and below, there is a critical deserialization vulnerability in the /conversation/ajax endpoint that allows authenticated users with knowledge of the APP_KEY to achieve remote code execution. The vulnerability occurs when the application processes the attachments_all and attachments POST parameters through the insecure Helper::decrypt() function, which performs unsafe deserialization of user-controlled data without proper validation. This flaw enables attackers to create arbitrary objects and manipulate their properties, leading to complete compromise of the web application. This is fixed in version 1.8.186.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54378 | HAX CMS Backend Lacks Comprehensive Authorization Checks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54378</link><description>HAX CMS allows you to manage your microsite universe with PHP or NodeJs backends. In versions 11.0.13 and below of haxcms-nodejs and versions 11.0.8 and below of haxcms-php, API endpoints do not perform authorization checks when interacting with a resource. Both the JS and PHP versions of the CMS do not verify that a user has permission to interact with a resource before performing a given operation. The API endpoints within the HAX CMS application check if a user is authenticated, but don't check for authorization before performing an operation. This is fixed in versions 11.0.14 of haxcms-nodejs and 11.0.9 of haxcms-php.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54380 | Opencast still publishes global system account credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54380</link><description>Opencast is a free, open-source platform to support the management of educational audio and video content. Prior to version 17.6, Opencast would incorrectly send the hashed global system account credentials (ie: org.opencastproject.security.digest.user and org.opencastproject.security.digest.pass) when attempting to fetch mediapackage elements included in a mediapackage XML file. A previous CVE prevented many cases where the credentials were inappropriately sent, but not all. Anyone with ingest permissions could cause Opencast to send its hashed global system account credentials to a url of their choosing. This issue is fixed in Opencast 17.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54385 | XWiki Platform&amp;#x27;s searchDocuments API allows for SQL injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54385</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. In versions between 17.0.0-rc1 to 17.2.2 and versions 16.10.5 and below, it's possible to execute any SQL query in Oracle by using the function like DBMS_XMLGEN or DBMS_XMLQUERY. The XWiki#searchDocuments APIs pass queries directly to Hibernate without sanitization. Even when these APIs enforce a specific SELECT clause, attackers can still inject malicious code through HQL's native function support in other parts of the query (such as the WHERE clause). This is fixed in versions 16.10.6 and 17.3.0-rc-1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54412 | skops&amp;#x27; Inconsistent Trusted Type Validation Enables Hidden `operator` Methods Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54412</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. Versions 0.11.0 and below contain a inconsistency in the OperatorFuncNode which can be exploited to hide the execution of untrusted operator methods. This can then be used in a code reuse attack to invoke seemingly safe functions and escalate to arbitrary code execution with minimal and misleading trusted types. This is fixed in version 0.12.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54413 | skops&amp;#x27; MethodNode can access unexpected object fields through dot notation, leading to arbitrary code execution at load time</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54413</link><description>skops is a Python library which helps users share and ship their scikit-learn based models. Versions 0.11.0 and below contain an inconsistency in MethodNode, which can be exploited to access unexpected object fields through dot notation. This can be used to achieve arbitrary code execution at load time. While this issue may seem similar to GHSA-m7f4-hrc6-fwg3, it is actually more severe, as it relies on fewer assumptions about trusted types. This is fixed in version 12.0.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54414 | Anubis accepts crafted redirect URLs in pass-challenge &amp;#x27;Try Again&amp;#x27; buttons</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54414</link><description>Anubis is a Web AI Firewall Utility that weighs the soul of users' connections using one or more challenges in order to protect upstream resources from scraper bots. In versions 1.21.2 and below, attackers can craft malicious pass-challenge pages that cause a user to execute arbitrary JavaScript code or trigger other nonstandard schemes. An incomplete version of this fix was tagged at 1.21.2 and then the release process was aborted upon final testing. To work around this issue: block any requests to the /.within.website/x/cmd/anubis/api/pass-challenge route with the ?redir= parameter set to anything that doesn't start with the URL scheme http, https, or no scheme (local path redirect). This was fixed in version 1.21.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54415 | dag-factory&amp;#x27;s CI/CD Workflow Allows for Repository Takeover and Secret Exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54415</link><description>dag-factory is a library for Apache Airflow® to construct DAGs declaratively via configuration files. In versions 0.23.0a8 and below, a high-severity vulnerability has been identified in the cicd.yml workflow within the astronomer/dag-factory GitHub repository. The workflow, specifically when triggered by pull_request_target, is susceptible to exploitation, allowing an attacker to execute arbitrary code within the GitHub Actions runner environment. This misconfiguration enables an attacker to establish a reverse shell, exfiltrate sensitive secrets, including the highly-privileged GITHUB_TOKEN, and ultimately gain full control over the repository. This is fixed in version 0.23.0a9.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54416 | tj-actions/branch-names Contains Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54416</link><description>tj-actions/branch-names is a Github actions repository that contains workflows to retrieve branch or tag names with support for all events. In versions 8.2.1 and below, a critical vulnerability has been identified in the tj-actions/branch-names' GitHub Action workflow which allows arbitrary command execution in downstream workflows. This issue arises due to inconsistent input sanitization and unescaped output, enabling malicious actors to exploit specially crafted branch names or tags. While internal sanitization mechanisms have been implemented, the action outputs remain vulnerable, exposing consuming workflows to significant security risks. This is fixed in version 9.0.0</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8103 | WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher &amp;lt;= 2.8.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Deactivation via handle_feedback_submission Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8103</link><description>The WPeMatico RSS Feed Fetcher plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.7. This is due to missing nonce validation in the handle_feedback_submission() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to deactivate the plugin via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8176 | LibTIFF tiffmedian.c get_histogram use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8176</link><description>A vulnerability was found in LibTIFF up to 4.7.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function get_histogram of the file tools/tiffmedian.c. The manipulation leads to use after free. The attack needs to be approached locally. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is identified as fe10872e53efba9cc36c66ac4ab3b41a839d5172. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 04:08:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8175 | D-Link DI-8400 jhttpd usb_paswd.asp null pointer dereference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8175</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DI-8400 16.07.26A1. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file usb_paswd.asp of the component jhttpd. The manipulation of the argument share_enable leads to null pointer dereference. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 03:19:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8174 | code-projects Voting System candidates_add.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8174</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Voting System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/candidates_add.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 01:46:39 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>