<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:18:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-8442 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide cussignup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8442</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /cussignup.php. The manipulation of the argument uname leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8441 | code-projects Online Medicine Guide pharsignup.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8441</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Online Medicine Guide 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /pharsignup.php. The manipulation of the argument phuname leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:41:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8439 | code-projects Wazifa System updatesettings.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8439</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /controllers/updatesettings.php. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:14:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7646 | The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 6.3.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7646</link><description>The The Plus Addons for Elementor – Elementor Addons, Page Templates, Widgets, Mega Menu, WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the custom script parameter in all versions up to, and including, 6.3.10 even when the user does not have the unfiltered_html capability. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8438 | code-projects Wazifa System postpublish.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8438</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Wazifa System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /controllers/postpublish.php. The manipulation of the argument post leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8437 | code-projects Kitchen Treasure userregistration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8437</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Kitchen Treasure 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /userregistration.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31716 | In bootloader, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no add...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31716</link><description>In bootloader, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local denial of service with no additional execution privileges needed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5921 | SureForms &amp;lt; 1.7.2 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5921</link><description>The SureForms  WordPress plugin before 1.7.2 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against both authenticated and unauthenticated users.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8454 | It was discovered that uscan, a tool to scan/watch upstream sources for new releases of software, included in devscripts (a collection of sc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8454</link><description>It was discovered that uscan, a tool to scan/watch upstream sources for new releases of software, included in devscripts (a collection of scripts to make the life of a Debian Package maintainer easier), skips OpenPGP verification for files already downloaded even if a previous verification did fail.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 06:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8436 | projectworlds Online Admission System viewdoc.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8436</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /viewdoc.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54939 | LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.3.1 has an lsquic_engine_packet_in memory leak.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54939</link><description>LiteSpeed QUIC (LSQUIC) Library before 4.3.1 has an lsquic_engine_packet_in memory leak.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 05:48:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4523 | IDonate 2.0.0 - 2.1.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Sensitive Information Disclosure via admin_donor_profile_view Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4523</link><description>The IDonate – Blood Donation, Request And Donor Management System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the admin_donor_profile_view() function in versions 2.0.0 to 2.1.9. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to expose an administrator’s username, email address, and all donor fields.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7443 | BerqWP &amp;lt;= 2.2.42 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7443</link><description>The BerqWP – Automated All-In-One Page Speed Optimization for Core Web Vitals, Cache, CDN, Images, CSS, and JavaScript plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation via the store_javascript_cache.php file in all versions up to, and including, 2.2.42. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7725 | Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal or Stripe, Social Share Buttons, OpenAI &amp;lt;= 26.1.0 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7725</link><description>The Photos, Files, YouTube, Twitter, Instagram, TikTok, Ecommerce Contest Gallery – Upload, Vote, Sell via PayPal or Stripe, Social Share Buttons, OpenAI plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the comment feature in all versions up to, and including, 26.1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7845 | Stratum – Elementor Widgets &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Advanced Google Maps and Image Hotspot Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7845</link><description>The Stratum – Elementor Widgets plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's Advanced Google Maps and Image Hotspot widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8435 | code-projects Online Movie Streaming admin-control.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8435</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Movie Streaming 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-control.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to missing authorization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8434 | code-projects Online Movie Streaming admin.php authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8434</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Movie Streaming 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to missing authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-19145 | Quantum SuperLoader 3 V94.0 005E.0h devices allow attackers to access the hardcoded fa account because there are only 65536 possible passwor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-19145</link><description>Quantum SuperLoader 3 V94.0 005E.0h devices allow attackers to access the hardcoded fa account because there are only 65536 possible passwords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53399 | In Sipwise rtpengine before 13.4.1.1, an origin-validation error in the endpoint-learning logic of the media-relay core allows remote attack...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53399</link><description>In Sipwise rtpengine before 13.4.1.1, an origin-validation error in the endpoint-learning logic of the media-relay core allows remote attackers to inject or intercept RTP/SRTP media streams via RTP packets (except when the relay is configured for strict source and learning disabled). Version 13.4.1.1 fixes the heuristic mode by limiting exposure to the first five packets, and introduces a recrypt flag that fully prevents SRTP attacks when both mitigations are enabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5947 | Service Finder Bookings &amp;lt;= 6.0 - Authentication Bypass via User Switch Cookie</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5947</link><description>The Service Finder Bookings plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 6.0. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's cookie value prior to logging them in through the service_finder_switch_back() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to login as any user including admins.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8433 | code-projects Document Management System dell.php unlink path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8433</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Document Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function unlink of the file /dell.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 04:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5954 | Service Finder SMS System &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5954</link><description>The Service Finder SMS System plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 2.0.0. This is due to the plugin not restricting user role selection at the time of registration through the aonesms_fn_savedata_after_signup() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to register as an administrator user.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8431 | PHPGurukul Boat Booking System add-boat.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8431</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Boat Booking System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add-boat.php. The manipulation of the argument boatname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 03:24:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32251 | Kernel: ksmbd brute force delay bypass via asynchronous requests</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32251</link><description>A vulnerability has been identified in the Linux kernel's ksmbd component (kernel SMB/CIFS server). A security control designed to prevent dictionary attacks, which introduces a 5-second delay during session setup, can be bypassed through the use of asynchronous requests. This bypass negates the intended anti-brute-force protection, potentially allowing attackers to conduct dictionary attacks more efficiently against user credentials or other authentication mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23289 | NVIDIA Omniverse Launcher for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the launcher logs, where a user could cause sensitive informatio...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23289</link><description>NVIDIA Omniverse Launcher for Windows and Linux contains a vulnerability in the launcher logs, where a user could cause sensitive information to be written to the log files through proxy servers. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to information disclosure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:49:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48072 | OpenEXR&amp;#x27;s Inaccurate Pointer Arithmetic can Cause an Out of Bounds Heap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48072</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. Version 3.3.2 is vulnerable to a heap-based buffer overflow during a read operation due to bad pointer math when decompressing DWAA-packed scan-line EXR files with a maliciously forged chunk. This is fixed in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:32:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48073 | OpenEXR ScanLineProcess::run_fill NULL Pointer Write In &amp;quot;reduceMemory&amp;quot; Mode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48073</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In version 3.3.2, when reading a deep scanline image with a large sample count in reduceMemory mode, it is possible to crash a target application with a NULL pointer dereference in a write operation. This is fixed in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45768 | pyjwt v2.10.1 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45768</link><description>pyjwt v2.10.1 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48071 | OpenEXR&amp;#x27;s Forged Unpacked Size can Lead to Heap-Based Buffer Overflow in Deep Scanline Parsing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48071</link><description>OpenEXR provides the specification and reference implementation of the EXR file format, an image storage format for the motion picture industry. In versions 3.3.2 through 3.3.0, there is a heap-based buffer overflow during a write operation when decompressing ZIPS-packed deep scan-line EXR files with a maliciously forged chunk header. This is fixed in version 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:32:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45769 | php-jwt v6.11.0 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45769</link><description>php-jwt v6.11.0 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37110 | Sensitive Credential Information stored insecurely in System Database</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37110</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the storage policy for certain sets of sensitive credential information in the HPE Telco Network Function Virtual Orchestrator. Successful Exploitation could lead to unauthorized parties gaining access to sensitive system information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37111 | Hard-Coded Authentication Keys found in System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37111</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the storage policy for certain sets of authentication keys in the HPE Telco Network Function Virtual Orchestrator. Successful Exploitation could lead to unauthorized parties gaining access to sensitive system information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37112 | Hard-Coded Encryption Keys found in System</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37112</link><description>A vulnerability was discovered in the storage policy for certain sets of encryption keys in the HPE Telco Network Function Virtual Orchestrator. Successful Exploitation could lead to unauthorized parties gaining access to sensitive system information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45770 | jwt v5.4.3 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45770</link><description>jwt v5.4.3 was discovered to contain weak encryption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50572 | An issue was discovered in Archer Technology RSA Archer 6.11.00204.10014 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted system inp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50572</link><description>An issue was discovered in Archer Technology RSA Archer 6.11.00204.10014 allowing attackers to execute arbitrary code via crafted system inputs that would be exported into the CSV and be executed after the user opened the file with compatible applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8286 | Güralp Systems Güralp FMUS series Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8286</link><description>Güralp FMUS series seismic monitoring devices expose an unauthenticated Telnet-based command line interface that 
could allow an attacker to modify hardware configurations, manipulate 
data, or factory reset the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37108 | HPE Telco Service Activator, Protection Mechanism Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37108</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability have been identified in HPE Telco Service Activator product</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-37109 | HPE Telco Service Activator, Protection Mechanism Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-37109</link><description>Cross-site scripting vulnerability has been identified in HPE Telco Service Activator product</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26062 | An access control issue in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows unauthenticated attackers to access the router's settings file ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26062</link><description>An access control issue in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows unauthenticated attackers to access the router's settings file and obtain potentially sensitive information from the current settings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26063 | An issue in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted pa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26063</link><description>An issue in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code via injecting a crafted payload into the ESSID name when creating a network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:52:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26064 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts o...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26064</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Intelbras RX1500 v2.2.9 and RX3000 v1.0.11 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into the name of a connnected device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:52:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51503 | A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Microweber CMS 2.0 allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into user profile field...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51503</link><description>A Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Microweber CMS 2.0 allows attackers to inject malicious scripts into user profile fields, leading to arbitrary JavaScript execution in admin browsers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8426 | Marvell QConvergeConsole compressConfigFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8426</link><description>Marvell QConvergeConsole compressConfigFiles Directory Traversal Information Disclosure and Denial-of-Service Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows remote attackers to disclose sensitive information or to create a denial-of-service condition on affected installations of Marvell QConvergeConsole. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the implementation of the compressConfigFiles method. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of a user-supplied path prior to using it in file operations. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to disclose sensitive information or to create a denial-of-service condition on the system. Was ZDI-CAN-24915.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51383 | D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the ipsec_road_asp function via the host_ip parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51383</link><description>D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the ipsec_road_asp function via the host_ip parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:54:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51384 | D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the ipsec_net_asp function via the remot_ip parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51384</link><description>D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the ipsec_net_asp function via the remot_ip parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51385 | D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the yyxz_dlink_asp function via the id parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51385</link><description>D-LINK DI-8200 16.07.26A1 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in the yyxz_dlink_asp function via the id parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54832 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) state and territory list unauthorized modification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54832</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL), version v11.1.0, allows an authenticated user to add entries to the list of states and territories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54833 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) account-lockout and CAPTCHA protection bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54833</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) version v11.1.0 allows attackers to bypass account-lockout and CAPTCHA protections. Unauthenticated remote attackers can more easily brute force passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54834 | OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) unauthenticated username enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54834</link><description>OPEXUS FOIAXpress Public Access Link (PAL) version v11.1.0 allows an unauthenticated, remote attacker to query the /App/CreateRequest.aspx endpoint to check for the existence of valid usernames. There are no rate-limiting mechanisms in place.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50866 | CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0 contains a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the email parameter of the postquerypublic e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50866</link><description>CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0 contains a reflected Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the email parameter of the postquerypublic endpoint. Improper sanitization allows an attacker to inject arbitrary JavaScript code that executes in the context of the user s browser, potentially leading to session hijacking or phishing attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:57:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34327 | Sielox AnyWare v2.1.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email address field of the password reset form.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34327</link><description>Sielox AnyWare v2.1.2 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability via the email address field of the password reset form.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29556 | ExaGrid EX10 6.3 - 7.0.1.P08 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Since version 6.3, ExaGrid enforces restrictions preventing users wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29556</link><description>ExaGrid EX10 6.3 - 7.0.1.P08 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control. Since version 6.3, ExaGrid enforces restrictions preventing users with the Admin role from creating or modifying users with the Security Officer role without approval. However, a flaw in the account creation process allows an attacker to bypass these restrictions via API request manipulation. An attacker with an Admin access can intercept and modify the API request during user creation, altering the parameters to assign the new account to the ExaGrid Security Officers group without the required approval.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:35:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50867 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the takeassessment2.php endpoint of the CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0, where the Q5 POST parameter ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50867</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the takeassessment2.php endpoint of the CloudClassroom-PHP-Project 1.0, where the Q5 POST parameter is directly embedded in SQL statements without sanitization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50848 | A file upload vulnerability was discovered in CS Cart 4.18.3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. CS Cart 4.18.3 allows unrestricted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50848</link><description>A file upload vulnerability was discovered in CS Cart 4.18.3, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code. CS Cart 4.18.3 allows unrestricted upload of HTML files, which are rendered directly in the browser when accessed. This allows an attacker to upload a crafted HTML file containing malicious content, such as a fake login form for credential harvesting or scripts for Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attacks. Since the content is served from a trusted domain, it significantly increases the likelihood of successful phishing or script execution against other users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:35:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50847 | Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CS Cart 4.18.3, allows attackers to add products to a user's comparison list via a crafte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50847</link><description>Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CS Cart 4.18.3, allows attackers to add products to a user's comparison list via a crafted HTTP request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50850 | An issue was discovered in CS Cart 4.18.3 allows the vendor login functionality lacks essential security controls such as CAPTCHA verificati...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50850</link><description>An issue was discovered in CS Cart 4.18.3 allows the vendor login functionality lacks essential security controls such as CAPTCHA verification and rate limiting. This allows an attacker to systematically attempt various combinations of usernames and passwords (brute-force attack) to gain unauthorized access to vendor accounts. The absence of any blocking mechanism makes the login endpoint susceptible to automated attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8409 | code-projects Vehicle Management filter.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8409</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /filter.php. The manipulation of the argument from leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46809 | Plain text HTTP Proxy user and password in repolog accessible from the Multi Linux Manager UI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46809</link><description>A Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability in SUSE Multi Linux Manager exposes the HTTP proxy credentials. This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 5.0.27-150600.3.33.1; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS: from ? before 4.3.87-150400.3.110.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-Azure: from ? before 4.3.87-150400.3.110.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-EC2: from ? before 4.3.87-150400.3.110.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-GCE: from ? before 4.3.87-150400.3.110.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.87-150400.3.110.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52203 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in DevaslanPHP project-management v1.2.4. The vulnerability resides in the Ticket N...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52203</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in DevaslanPHP project-management v1.2.4. The vulnerability resides in the Ticket Name field, which fails to properly sanitize user-supplied input. An authenticated attacker can inject malicious JavaScript payloads into this field, which are subsequently stored in the database. When a legitimate user logs in and is redirected to the Dashboard panel "automatically upon authentication the malicious script executes in the user's browser context.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50475 | An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Russound MBX-PRE-D67F firmware version 3.1.6, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50475</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in Russound MBX-PRE-D67F firmware version 3.1.6, allowing unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary commands as root via crafted input to the hostname parameter in network configuration requests. This vulnerability stems from improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command within the network configuration handler, enabling remote code execution with the highest privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50849 | CS Cart 4.18.3 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR). The user profile functionality allows enabling or disabling sticker...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50849</link><description>CS Cart 4.18.3 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR). The user profile functionality allows enabling or disabling stickers through a parameter (company_id) sent in the request. However, this operation is not properly validated on the server side. An authenticated user can manipulate the request to target other users' accounts and toggle the sticker setting by modifying the company_id or other object identifiers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10008 | MPlayer Lite r33064 M3U Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10008</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in MPlayer Lite r33064 due to improper bounds checking when handling M3U playlist files containing long http:// URL entries. An attacker can craft a malicious .m3u file with a specially formatted URL that triggers a stack overflow when processed by the player, particularly via drag-and-drop interaction. This flaw allows for control of the execution flow through SEH overwrite and a DEP bypass using a ROP chain that leverages known gadgets in loaded DLLs. Successful exploitation may result in arbitrary code execution with the privileges of the current user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10035 | ProcessMaker Open Source &amp;lt; 2.5.2 neoclassic Skin PHP Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10035</link><description>A code injection vulnerability exists in ProcessMaker Open Source versions 2.x when using the default 'neoclassic' skin. An authenticated user can execute arbitrary PHP code via multiple endpoints, including appFolderAjax.php, casesStartPage_Ajax.php, and cases_SchedulerGetPlugins.php, by supplying crafted POST requests to parameters such as action and params. These endpoints fail to validate user input and directly invoke PHP functions like system() with user-supplied parameters, enabling remote code execution. The vulnerability affects both Linux and Windows installations and is present in default configurations of versions including 2.0.23 through 2.5.1. The vulnerable skin cannot be removed through the web interface, and exploitation requires only valid user credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10037 | WebTester 5.x install2.php Unauthenticated Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10037</link><description>An OS command injection vulnerability exists in WebTester version 5.x via the install2.php installation script. The parameters cpusername, cppassword, and cpdomain are passed directly to shell commands without sanitization. A remote unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw by sending a crafted HTTP POST request, resulting in arbitrary command execution on the underlying system with web server privileges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125122 | Linksys WRT120N tmUnblock.cgi Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Admin Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125122</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the tmUnblock.cgi endpoint of the Linksys WRT120N wireless router. The vulnerability is triggered by sending a specially crafted HTTP POST request with an overly long TM_Block_URL parameter to the endpoint. By exploiting this flaw, an unauthenticated remote attacker can overwrite memory in a controlled manner, enabling them to temporarily reset the administrator password of the device to a blank value. This grants unauthorized access to the router’s web management interface without requiring valid credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125123 | Kloxo &amp;lt; 6.1.12 Unauthenticated SQL Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125123</link><description>An unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in the Kloxo web hosting control panel (developed by LXCenter) prior to version 6.1.12. The flaw resides in the login-name parameter passed to lbin/webcommand.php, which fails to properly sanitize input, allowing an attacker to extract the administrator’s password from the backend database. After recovering valid credentials, the attacker can authenticate to the Kloxo control panel and leverage the Command Center feature (display.php) to execute arbitrary operating system commands as root on the underlying host system. This vulnerability was reported to be exploited in the wild in January 2014.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125124 | Pandora FMS &amp;lt;= 5.0RC1 Anyterm Unauthenticated Command Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125124</link><description>An unauthenticated remote command execution vulnerability exists in Pandora FMS versions up to and including 5.0RC1 via the Anyterm web interface, which listens on TCP port 8023. The anyterm-module endpoint accepts unsanitized user input via the p parameter and directly injects it into a shell command, allowing arbitrary command execution as the pandora user. In certain versions (notably 4.1 and 5.0RC1), the pandora user can elevate privileges to root without a password using a chain involving the artica user account. This account is typically installed without a password and is configured to run sudo without authentication. Therefore, full system compromise is possible without any credentials.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125126 | Simple E-Document Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125126</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability exists in Simple E-Document versions 3.0 to 3.1 that allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication by sending a specific cookie header (access=3) with HTTP requests. The application’s upload mechanism fails to restrict file types and does not validate or sanitize user-supplied input, allowing attackers to upload malicious .php scripts. Authentication can be bypassed entirely by supplying a specially crafted cookie (access=3), granting access to the upload functionality without valid credentials. If file uploads are enabled on the server, the attacker can upload a web shell and gain remote code execution with the privileges of the web server user, potentially leading to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34146 | nyariv sandboxjs 0.8.23 Prototype Pollution Sandbox Escape DoS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34146</link><description>A prototype pollution vulnerability exists in @nyariv/sandboxjs versions &lt;= 0.8.23, allowing attackers to inject arbitrary properties into Object.prototype via crafted JavaScript code. This can result in a denial-of-service (DoS) condition or, under certain conditions, escape the sandboxed environment intended to restrict code execution. The vulnerability stems from insufficient prototype access checks in the sandbox’s executor logic, particularly in the handling of JavaScript function objects returned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8408 | code-projects Vehicle Management filter1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8408</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /filter1.php. The manipulation of the argument vehicle leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:28:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10021 | D-Link DIR-605L Captcha Handling Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10021</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in D-Link DIR-605L Wireless N300 Cloud Router firmware versions 1.12 and 1.13 via the getAuthCode() function. The flaw arises from unsafe usage of sprintf() when processing user-supplied CAPTCHA data via the FILECODE parameter in /goform/formLogin. A remote unauthenticated attacker can exploit this to execute arbitrary code with root privileges on the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10033 | Kimai 0.9.2 db_restore.php SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10033</link><description>An unauthenticated SQL injection vulnerability exists in Kimai version 0.9.2.x via the db_restore.php endpoint. The flaw allows attackers to inject arbitrary SQL queries into the dates[] POST parameter, enabling file write via INTO OUTFILE under specific environmental conditions. This can lead to remote code execution by writing a PHP payload to the web-accessible temporary directory. The vulnerability has been confirmed in versions including 0.9.2.beta, 0.9.2.1294.beta, and 0.9.2.1306-3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10034 | Kaseya &amp;lt; 6.3.0.2 uploadImage.asp Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10034</link><description>An unrestricted file upload vulnerability exists in Kaseya KServer versions prior to 6.3.0.2. The uploadImage.asp endpoint allows unauthenticated users to upload files to arbitrary paths via a crafted filename parameter in a multipart/form-data POST request. Due to the lack of authentication and input sanitation, an attacker can upload a file with an .asp extension to a web-accessible directory, which can then be invoked to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the IUSR account. The vulnerability enables remote code execution without prior authentication and was resolved in version 6.3.0.2 by removing the vulnerable uploadImage.asp endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10036 | Beetel Connection Manager NetConfig.ini Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10036</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in Beetel Connection Manager version PCW_BTLINDV1.0.0B04 when parsing the UserName parameter in the NetConfig.ini configuration file. A crafted .ini file containing an overly long UserName value can overwrite the Structured Exception Handler (SEH), leading to arbitrary code execution when the application processes the file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10038 | FlashChat Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10038</link><description>An unauthenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in FlashChat versions 6.0.2 and 6.0.4 through 6.0.8. The upload.php endpoint fails to properly validate file types and authentication, allowing attackers to upload malicious PHP scripts. Once uploaded, these scripts can be executed remotely, resulting in arbitrary code execution as the web server user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10039 | GestioIP 3.0 ip_checkhost.cgi RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10039</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists in GestioIP 3.0 commit ac67be and earlier in ip_checkhost.cgi. Crafted input to the 'ip' parameter allows attackers to execute arbitrary shell commands on the server via embedded base64-encoded payloads. Authentication may be required depending on deployment configuration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10040 | ClipBucket &amp;lt;= 2.6 ofc_upload_image.php Arbitrary File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10040</link><description>ClipBucket version 2.6 and earlier contains a critical vulnerability in the ofc_upload_image.php script located at /admin_area/charts/ofc-library/. This endpoint allows unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files, including executable PHP scripts. Once uploaded, the attacker can access the file via a predictable path and trigger remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10042 | freeFTPd &amp;lt;= 1.0.10 PASS Command Stack-Based Buffer Overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10042</link><description>A stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability exists in freeFTPd version 1.0.10 and earlier in the handling of the FTP PASS command. When an attacker sends a specially crafted password string, the application fails to validate input length, resulting in memory corruption. This can lead to denial of service or arbitrary code execution. Exploitation requires the anonymous user account to be enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2013-10043 | Astium VOIP PBX &amp;lt;= 2.1 SQL Injection File Upload RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2013-10043</link><description>A vulnerability exists in OAstium VoIP PBX astium-confweb-2.1-25399 and earlier, where improper input validation in the logon.php script allows an attacker to bypass authentication via SQL injection. Once authenticated as an administrator, the attacker can upload arbitrary PHP code through the importcompany field in import.php, resulting in remote code execution. The malicious payload is injected into /usr/local/astium/web/php/config.php and executed with root privileges by triggering a configuration reload via sudo /sbin/service astcfgd reload. Successful exploitation leads to full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125121 | Array Networks vAPV and vxAG Default Credential Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125121</link><description>Array Networks vAPV (version 8.3.2.17) and vxAG (version 9.2.0.34) appliances are affected by a privilege escalation vulnerability caused by a combination of hardcoded SSH credentials (or SSH private key) and insecure permissions on a startup script. The devices ship with a default SSH login or a hardcoded DSA private key, allowing an attacker to authenticate remotely with limited privileges.


Once authenticated, an attacker can overwrite the world-writable /ca/bin/monitor.sh script with arbitrary commands. Since this script is executed with elevated privileges through the backend binary, enabling the debug monitor via backend -c "debug monitor on" triggers execution of the attacker's payload as root. This allows full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2014-125125 | A10 Networks AX Loadbalancer Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2014-125125</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in A10 Networks AX Loadbalancer versions 2.6.1-GR1-P5, 2.7.0, and earlier. The vulnerability resides in the handling of the filename parameter in the /xml/downloads endpoint, which fails to properly sanitize user input. An unauthenticated attacker can exploit this flaw by sending crafted HTTP requests containing directory traversal sequences to read arbitrary files outside the intended directory. The files returned by the vulnerable endpoint are deleted from the system after retrieval. This can lead to unauthorized disclosure of sensitive information such as SSL certificates and private keys, as well as unintended file deletion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51569 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the LB-Link BL-CPE300M 01.01.02P42U14_06 router's web interface. The /goform/goform_get...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51569</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the LB-Link BL-CPE300M 01.01.02P42U14_06 router's web interface. The /goform/goform_get_cmd_process endpoint fails to sanitize user input in the cmd parameter before reflecting it into a text/html response. This allows unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary JavaScript, which is executed in the context of the router's origin when the crafted URL is accessed. The issue requires user interaction to exploit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34328 | An open redirect in Sielox AnyWare v2.1.2 allows attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via a crafted URL.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34328</link><description>An open redirect in Sielox AnyWare v2.1.2 allows attackers to execute a man-in-the-middle attack via a crafted URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29557 | ExaGrid EX10 6.3 - 7.0.1.P08 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the MailConfiguration API endpoint, where users with operator-leve...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29557</link><description>ExaGrid EX10 6.3 - 7.0.1.P08 is vulnerable to Incorrect Access Control in the MailConfiguration API endpoint, where users with operator-level privileges can issue an HTTP request to retrieve SMTP credentials, including plaintext passwords.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50270 | A stored Cross Site Scripting (xss) vulnerability in the "content management" feature in AnQiCMS v.3.4.11 allows a remote attacker to execut...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50270</link><description>A stored Cross Site Scripting (xss) vulnerability in the "content management" feature in AnQiCMS v.3.4.11 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script to the title, categoryTitle, and tmpTag parameters.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52289 | A Broken Access Control vulnerability in MagnusBilling v7.8.5.3 allows newly registered users to gain escalated privileges by sending a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52289</link><description>A Broken Access Control vulnerability in MagnusBilling v7.8.5.3 allows newly registered users to gain escalated privileges by sending a crafted request to /mbilling/index.php/user/save to set their account status fom "pending" to "active" without requiring administrator approval.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7738 | Python3.11-django-ansible-base: sensitive authenticator secrets returned in clear text via api in aap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7738</link><description>A flaw was found in Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) where the Gateway API returns the client secret for certain GitHub Enterprise authenticators in clear text. This vulnerability affects administrators or auditors accessing authenticator configurations. While access is limited to privileged users, the clear text exposure of sensitive credentials increases the risk of accidental leaks or misuse.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8407 | code-projects Vehicle Management filter2.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8407</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /filter2.php. The manipulation of the argument from leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54589 | copyparty Reflected XSS via Filter Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54589</link><description>Copyparty is a portable file server. In versions 1.18.6 and below, when accessing the recent uploads page at `/?ru`, users can filter the results using an input field at the top. This field appends a filter parameter to the URL, which reflects its value directly into a `</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8213 | NinjaScanner – Virus &amp;amp; Malware scan &amp;lt;= 3.2.5 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8213</link><description>The NinjaScanner – Virus &amp; Malware scan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'nscan_ajax_quarantine' and 'nscan_quarantine_select' functions in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, including files outside the WordPress root directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8382 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System edit_room.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8382</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit_room.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8381 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System add_reserve.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8381</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /add_reserve.php. The manipulation of the argument room_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:48:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8068 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Improper Authorization to Authenticated (Contributor+) Limited Administrator Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8068</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification and loss of data due to an improper capability check on the 'ajax_trash_templates' function in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to delete arbitrary attachment files, and move arbitrary posts, pages, and templates to the Trash.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8151 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Path Traversal to Limited Arbitrary CSS File Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8151</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Path Traversal in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 via the 'save_block_css' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to create CSS files in any directory, and delete CSS files in any directory in a Windows environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:36:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8401 | HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor &amp;lt;= 2.9.1 - Authenticated (Author+) Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8401</link><description>The HT Mega – Absolute Addons For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 2.9.1 via the 'get_post_data' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to extract sensitive data including the content of private, password-protected, and draft posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:36:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8380 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System add_query_account.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8380</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/add_query_account.php. The manipulation of the argument Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8379 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System edit_room.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8379</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit_room.php. The manipulation of the argument photo leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2813 | HTTP Service DoS Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2813</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker can cause a Denial of Service by sending a large number of requests to the http service on port 80.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41688 | High Privilege RCE via LUA Sandbox Escape</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41688</link><description>A high privileged remote attacker can execute arbitrary OS commands using an undocumented method allowing to escape the implemented LUA sandbox.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8378 | Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System Login index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8378</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Hotel Reservation System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/index.php of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40980 | ddd</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40980</link><description>A Stored Cross Site Scripting vulnerability has been found in UltimatePOS by UltimateFosters. This vulnerability is due to the lack of proper validation of user inputs via ‘/products//edit’, affecting to ‘name’ parameter via POST. The vulnerability could allow a remote attacker to send a specially crafted query to an authenticated user and steal his/her session cookies details.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8376 | code-projects Vehicle Management updatebal.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8376</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /updatebal.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8375 | code-projects Vehicle Management addvehicle.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8375</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /addvehicle.php. The manipulation of the argument vehicle leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 09:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24853 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in JSPWiki Header Link processing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24853</link><description>A carefully crafted request when creating a header link using the 
wiki markup syntax, which could allow the attacker to execute javascript
 in the victim's browser and get some sensitive information about the 
victim.



Further research by the JSPWiki team showed that the markdown parser allowed this kind of attack too.

Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.3 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24854 | Apache JSPWiki: Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in JSPWiki Image plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24854</link><description>A carefully crafted request using the Image plugin could trigger an XSS 
vulnerability on Apache JSPWiki, which could allow the attacker to 
execute javascript in the victim's browser and get some sensitive 
information about the victim.





Apache JSPWiki users should upgrade to 2.12.3 or later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8374 | code-projects Vehicle Management addcompany.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8374</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /addcompany.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8192 | Race condition in AndroidTV TvSettings</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8192</link><description>There exists a TOCTOU race condition in TvSettings AppRestrictionsFragment.java that lead to start of attacker supplied activity in Settings’ context, i.e. system-uid context, thus lead to launchAnyWhere. The core idea is to utilize the time window between the check of Intent and the use to Intent to change the target component’s state, thus bypass the original security sanitize function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:47:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8373 | code-projects Vehicle Management print.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8373</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /print.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36563 | Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product administrator accesses a crafted URL, an ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36563</link><description>Reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product administrator accesses a crafted URL, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41391 | Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product user accesses a malicious page, an arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41391</link><description>Stored cross-site scripting vulnerability exists in multiple versions of PowerCMS. If a product user accesses a malicious page, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41396 | A path traversal issue exists in file uploading feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. Arbitrary files may be overwritten by a product us...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41396</link><description>A path traversal issue exists in file uploading feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. Arbitrary files may be overwritten by a product user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46359 | A path traversal issue exists in backup and restore feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. A product administrator may execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46359</link><description>A path traversal issue exists in backup and restore feature of multiple versions of PowerCMS. A product administrator may execute arbitrary code by restoring a crafted backup file.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54752 | Multiple versions of PowerCMS improperly neutralize formula elements in a CSV file.  If a product user creates a malformed entry and a victi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54752</link><description>Multiple versions of PowerCMS improperly neutralize formula elements in a CSV file.  If a product user creates a malformed entry and a victim user downloads it as a CSV file and opens it in the user's environment, the embedded code may be executed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7205 | GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (GiveWP worker+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7205</link><description>The GiveWP – Donation Plugin and Fundraising Platform plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the donor notes parameter in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with GiveWP worker-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. Additionally, they need to trick an administrator into visiting the legacy version of the site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8372 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s7.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8372</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_s7.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54757 | Multiple versions of PowerCMS allow unrestricted upload of dangerous files. If a product administrator accesses a malicious file uploaded by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54757</link><description>Multiple versions of PowerCMS allow unrestricted upload of dangerous files. If a product administrator accesses a malicious file uploaded by a product user, an arbitrary script may be executed on the browser.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8371 | code-projects Exam Form Submission update_s5.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8371</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/update_s5.php. The manipulation of the argument credits leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8370 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_escolaridade_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8370</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. Affected is an unknown function of the file /intranet/educar_escolaridade_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument descricao leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:56:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8369 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_avaliacao_desempenho_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8369</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /intranet/educar_avaliacao_desempenho_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument titulo_avaliacao leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:25:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53558 | ZXHN-F660T and ZXHN-F660A provided by ZTE Japan K.K. use a common credential for all installations. With the knowledge of the credential, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53558</link><description>ZXHN-F660T and ZXHN-F660A provided by ZTE Japan K.K. use a common credential for all installations. With the knowledge of the credential, an attacker may log in to the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:55:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8368 | Portabilis i-Educar pesquisa_pessoa_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8368</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /intranet/pesquisa_pessoa_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument campo_busca/cpf leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:55:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8367 | Portabilis i-Educar funcionario_vinculo_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8367</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. This affects an unknown part of the file /intranet/funcionario_vinculo_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument nome leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8366 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_servidor_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8366</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.9. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /intranet/educar_servidor_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument nome/matricula_servidor leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:03:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5720 | Customer Reviews for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 5.80.2 - Unauthenticated Stored Cross-Site Scripting via `author` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5720</link><description>The Customer Reviews for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘author’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 5.80.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7847 | AI Engine 2.9.3 - 2.9.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7847</link><description>The AI Engine plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the rest_simpleFileUpload() function in versions 2.9.3 and 2.9.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server when the REST API is enabled, which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8365 | Portabilis i-Educar atendidos_cad.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8365</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.10. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file atendidos_cad.php. The manipulation of the argument nome/nome_social/email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:32:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8348 | Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform home improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8348</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /home. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8347 | Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform findAllTask sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8347</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Kehua Charging Pile Cloud Platform 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/task/findAllTask. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8345 | Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM yunzhijiaApi.php delete_user sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8345</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Shanghai Lingdang Information Technology Lingdang CRM up to 8.6.4.7. Affected by this vulnerability is the function delete_user of the file crm/WeiXinApp/yunzhijia/yunzhijiaApi.php. The manipulation of the argument function leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 8.6.5.2 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8346 | Portabilis i-Educar educar_aluno_lst.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8346</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Portabilis i-Educar 2.10. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /educar_aluno_lst.php. The manipulation of the argument ref_cod_matricula with the input "&gt;&lt;img /&gt; leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:51:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8344 | openviglet shio ShStaticFileAPI.java shStaticFileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8344</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in openviglet shio up to 0.3.8. Affected is the function shStaticFileUpload of the file shio-app/src/main/java/com/viglet/shio/api/staticfile/ShStaticFileAPI.java. The manipulation of the argument filename leads to unrestricted upload. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8343 | openviglet shio ShStaticFileAPI.java shStaticFilePreUpload path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8343</link><description>A vulnerability was found in openviglet shio up to 0.3.8. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function shStaticFilePreUpload of the file shio-app/src/main/java/com/viglet/shio/api/staticfile/ShStaticFileAPI.java. The manipulation of the argument fileName leads to path traversal. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8339 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System student_login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8339</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /student_login.php. The manipulation of the argument user_name/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8340 | code-projects Intern Membership Management System Error Message fill_details.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8340</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Intern Membership Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file fill_details.php of the component Error Message Handler. The manipulation of the argument email leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 02:28:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36039 | IBM Aspera Faspex bypass security</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36039</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12.1 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to client-side enforcement of sever side security mechanisms,</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36040 | IBM Aspera Faspex session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36040</link><description>IBM Aspera Faspex 5.0.0 through 5.0.12.1 could allow an authenticated user to perform unauthorized actions due to client-side enforcement of sever side security mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49082 | Permissions bypass vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49082</link><description>CVE-2025-49082 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of permissions
can bypass those permissions to improperly read other settings. The attack
complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack requirements; the privileges
required are high, and there is no user interaction required. The impact to
system confidentiality is low, there is no impact to system availability or
integrity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54085 | Elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54085</link><description>CVE-2025-54085 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access to the console and who have been assigned a certain set of permissions
can bypass those permissions to improperly read or change other settings. The
attack complexity is low, there are no preexisting attack requirements; the
privileges required are high, and there is no user interaction required. The
impact to system confidentiality and integrity is low, there is no impact to
system availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:52:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49083 | Data deserialization vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49083</link><description>CVE-2025-49083 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access after version 12.00 and prior to version 13.56.
Attackers with administrative access to the console can cause unsafe content to
be deserialized and executed in the security context of the console. The attack
complexity is low and there are no attack requirements. Privileges required are
high and there is no user interaction required. The impact to confidentiality
is low, impact to integrity is high and there is no impact to availability. The
impact to the confidentiality and integrity of subsequent systems is low and
there is no subsequent system impact to availability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49084 | Elevation of privilege vulnerability in the Secure Access administrative console of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49084</link><description>CVE-2025-49084 is a vulnerability in the management console
of Absolute Secure Access prior to version 13.56. Attackers with administrative
access can overwrite policy rules without the requisite permissions. The attack
complexity is low, attack requirements are present, privileges required are
high and no user interaction is required. There is no impact to
confidentiality, the impact to integrity is low, and there is no impact to
availability. The impact to confidentiality and availability of subsequent systems
is high and the impact to the integrity of subsequent systems is low.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8338 | projectworlds Online Admission System adminac.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8338</link><description>A vulnerability was found in projectworlds Online Admission System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /adminac.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8337 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System add_vehicles.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8337</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/add_vehicles.php. The manipulation of the argument car_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:21:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8336 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8336</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_user. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:48:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8335 | code-projects Simple Car Rental System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8335</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Simple Car Rental System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:29:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8334 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8334</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=delete_recruitment_status. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:41:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54586 | GitProxy is susceptible to a hidden commits injection attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54586</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint. In versions 1.19.1 and below,   attackers can inject extra commits into the pack sent to GitHub, commits that aren’t pointed to by any branch. Although these “hidden” commits never show up in the repository’s visible history, GitHub still serves them at their direct commit URLs. This lets an attacker exfiltrate sensitive data without ever leaving a trace in the branch view. We rate this a High‑impact vulnerability because it completely compromises repository confidentiality. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8333 | code-projects Online Farm System categoryvalue.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8333</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /categoryvalue.php. The manipulation of the argument Value leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 21:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8332 | code-projects Online Farm System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8332</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:48:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54585 | GitProxy is vulnerable to a new branch approval exploit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54585</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint. In versions 1.19.1 and below, attackers can exploit the way GitProxy handles new branch creation to bypass the approval of prior commits on the parent branch. The vulnerability impacts all users or organizations relying on GitProxy to enforce policy and prevent unapproved changes. It requires no elevated privileges beyond regular push access, and no extra user interaction. It does however, require a GitProxy administrator or designated user (canUserApproveRejectPush) to approve pushes to the child branch. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54581 | vproxy is vulnerable to a divide by zero DoS attack</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54581</link><description>vproxy is an HTTP/HTTPS/SOCKS5 proxy server. In versions 2.3.3 and below, untrusted data is extracted from the user-controlled HTTP Proxy-Authorization header and passed to Extension::try_from and flows into parse_ttl_extension where it is parsed as a TTL value. If an attacker supplies a TTL of zero (e.g. by using a username such as 'configuredUser-ttl-0'), the modulo operation 'timestamp % ttl' will cause a division by zero panic, causing the server to crash causing a denial-of-service. This is fixed in version 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54583 | GitProxy bypasses approvals when pushing multiple branches</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54583</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint (e.g., github.com). Versions 1.19.1 and below allow users to push to remote repositories while bypassing policies and explicit approvals. Since checks and plugins are skipped, code containing secrets or unwanted changes could be pushed into a repository. This is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54584 | GitProxy is vulnerable to a packfile parsing exploit</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54584</link><description>GitProxy is an application that stands between developers and a Git remote endpoint (e.g., github.com). In versions 1.19.1 and below, an attacker can craft a malicious Git packfile to exploit the PACK signature detection in the parsePush.ts file. By embedding a misleading PACK signature within commit content and carefully constructing the packet structure, the attacker can trick the parser into treating invalid or unintended data as the packfile. Potentially, this would allow bypassing approval or hiding commits. This issue is fixed in version 1.19.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8331 | code-projects Online Farm System forgot_pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8331</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Online Farm System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /forgot_pass.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:31:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54575 | ImageSharp Triggers an Infinite Loop in its GIF Decoder When Skipping Malformed Comment Extension Blocks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54575</link><description>ImageSharp is a 2D graphics library. In versions below 2.1.11 and 3.0.0 through 3.1.10, a specially crafted GIF file containing a malformed comment extension block (with a missing block terminator) can cause the ImageSharp GIF decoder to enter an infinite loop while attempting to skip the block. This leads to a denial of service. Applications processing untrusted GIF input should upgrade to a patched version. This issue is fixed in versions 2.1.11 and 3.1.11.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-48916 | Ceph is vulnerable to authentication bypass through RadosGW</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-48916</link><description>Ceph is a distributed object, block, and file storage platform. In versions 19.2.3 and below, it is possible to send an JWT that has "none" as JWT alg. And by doing so the JWT signature is not checked. The vulnerability is most likely in the RadosGW OIDC provider. As of time of publication, a known patched version has yet to be published.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54576 | OAuth2-Proxy has authentication bypass in oauth2-proxy skip_auth_routes due to Query Parameter inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54576</link><description>OAuth2-Proxy is an open-source tool that can act as either a standalone reverse proxy or a middleware component integrated into existing reverse proxy or load balancer setups. In versions 7.10.0 and below, oauth2-proxy deployments are vulnerable when using the skip_auth_routes configuration option with regex patterns. Attackers can bypass authentication by crafting URLs with query parameters that satisfy configured regex patterns, allowing unauthorized access to protected resources. The issue stems from skip_auth_routes matching against the full request URI. Deployments using skip_auth_routes with regex patterns containing wildcards or broad matching patterns are most at risk. This issue is fixed in version 7.11.0. Workarounds include: auditing all skip_auth_routes configurations for overly permissive patterns, replacing wildcard patterns with exact path matches where possible, ensuring regex patterns are properly anchored (starting with ^ and ending with $), or implementing custom validation that strips query parameters before regex matching.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:52:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8330 | code-projects Vehicle Management edit1.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8330</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /edit1.php. The manipulation of the argument sno leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:43:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53022 | TrustedFirmware-M (aka Trusted Firmware for M profile Arm CPUs) before 2.1.3 and 2.2.x before 2.2.1 lacks length validation during a firmwar...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53022</link><description>TrustedFirmware-M (aka Trusted Firmware for M profile Arm CPUs) before 2.1.3 and 2.2.x before 2.2.1 lacks length validation during a firmware upgrade. While processing a new image, the Firmware Upgrade (FWU) module does not validate the length field of the Type-Length-Value (TLV) structure for dependent components against the maximum allowed size. If the length specified in the TLV exceeds the size of the buffer allocated on the stack, the FWU module will overwrite the buffer (and potentially other stack data) with the TLV's value content. An attacker could exploit this by crafting a malicious TLV entry in the unprotected section of the MCUBoot upgrade image. By setting the length field to exceed the expected structure size, the attacker can manipulate the stack memory of the system during the upgrade process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:43:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51954 | playground.electronhub.ai v1.1.9 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51954</link><description>playground.electronhub.ai v1.1.9 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52187 | GetProjectsIdea Create School Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in my_profile_update_form1.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52187</link><description>GetProjectsIdea Create School Management System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in my_profile_update_form1.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50464 | A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the upload.cgi module of the iptime NAS firmware v1.5.04. The vulnerability arises due to the unsa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50464</link><description>A buffer overflow vulnerability exists in the upload.cgi module of the iptime NAS firmware v1.5.04. The vulnerability arises due to the unsafe use of the strcpy function to copy attacker-controlled data from the CONTENT_TYPE HTTP header into a fixed-size stack buffer (v8, allocated 8 bytes) without bounds checking. Since this operation occurs before authentication logic is executed, the vulnerability is exploitable pre-authentication.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51951 | andisearch v0.5.249 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51951</link><description>andisearch v0.5.249 was discovered to contain a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8329 | code-projects Vehicle Management filter3.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8329</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Vehicle Management 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /filter3.php. The manipulation of the argument company leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50777 | The firmware of the AZIOT 2MP Full HD Smart Wi-Fi CCTV Home Security Camera (version V1.00.02) contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50777</link><description>The firmware of the AZIOT 2MP Full HD Smart Wi-Fi CCTV Home Security Camera (version V1.00.02) contains an Incorrect Access Control vulnerability that allows local attackers to gain root shell access. Once accessed, the device exposes critical data including Wi-Fi credentials and ONVIF service credentials stored in plaintext, enabling further compromise of the network and connected systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:51:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30103 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5 contains a Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. A l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30103</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5 contains a Files or Directories Accessible to External Parties vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Filesystem access for attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36608 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36608</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains an Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36609 | Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36609</link><description>Dell SmartFabric OS10 Software, versions prior to 10.6.0.5, contains a Use of Hard-coded Password vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Elevation of privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30480 | Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, versions prior to 19.19, contain(s) an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in PowerProtect Data Manager....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30480</link><description>Dell PowerProtect Data Manager, versions prior to 19.19, contain(s) an Improper Input Validation vulnerability in PowerProtect Data Manager. A low privileged attacker with remote access could potentially exploit this vulnerability to read arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8328 | code-projects Exam Form Submission register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8328</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument USN leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26332 | TechAdvisor versions 2.6 through 3.37-30 for Dell XtremIO X2, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26332</link><description>TechAdvisor versions 2.6 through 3.37-30 for Dell XtremIO X2, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:22:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30105 | Dell XtremIO, version(s) 6.4.0-22, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30105</link><description>Dell XtremIO, version(s) 6.4.0-22, contain(s) an Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File vulnerability. A low privileged attacker with local access could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to Information exposure. The attacker may be able to use the exposed credentials to access the vulnerable application with privileges of the compromised account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8327 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s8.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8327</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/delete_s8.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45955 | Rocket Software Rocket Zena 4.4.1.26 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the filter parameter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45955</link><description>Rocket Software Rocket Zena 4.4.1.26 is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the filter parameter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45619 | An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 firmware v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SendAction function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45619</link><description>An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 firmware v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the SendAction function</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25691 | A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the component /themes/import of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25691</link><description>A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the component /themes/import of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-45620 | An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-45620</link><description>An issue in Aver PTC310UV2 v.0.1.0000.59 allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information via a crafted request</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:19:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25692 | A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the _getHeaders function of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25692</link><description>A PHAR deserialization vulnerability in the _getHeaders function of PrestaShop v8.2.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36611 | Dell Encryption and Dell Security Management Server, versions prior to 11.11.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Lin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36611</link><description>Dell Encryption and Dell Security Management Server, versions prior to 11.11.0, contain an Improper Link Resolution Before File Access ('Link Following') Vulnerability. A local malicious user could potentially exploit this vulnerability, leading to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8312 | Deadlock in PAM automatic check-in feature in Devolutions Server allows a password to remain valid beyond the end of its intended check-out ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8312</link><description>Deadlock in PAM automatic check-in feature in Devolutions Server allows a password to remain valid beyond the end of its intended check-out period due to a deadlock occurring in the scheduling service.This issue affects the following version(s) :

  *  
Devolutions Server 2025.2.5.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8353 | UI synchronization issue in the Just-in-Time (JIT) access request approval interface in Devolutions Server 2025.2.4.0 and earlier allows a r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8353</link><description>UI synchronization issue in the Just-in-Time (JIT) access request approval interface in Devolutions Server 2025.2.4.0 and earlier allows a remote authenticated attacker to gain unauthorized access to deleted JIT Groups via stale UI state during standard checkout request processing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54656 | Apache Struts Extras: Improper Output Neutralization for Logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54656</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** Improper Output Neutralization for Logs vulnerability in Apache Struts.

This issue affects Apache Struts Extras: before 2.

When using LookupDispatchAction, in some cases, Struts may print untrusted input to the logs without any filtering. Specially-crafted input may lead to log output where part of the message masquerades as a separate log line, confusing consumers of the logs (either human or automated). 

As this project is retired, we do not plan to release a version that fixes this issue. Users are recommended to find an alternative or restrict access to the instance to trusted users.

NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:34:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2593 | Kernel: ksmbd memory exhaustion denial-of-service vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2593</link><description>A flaw exists within the Linux kernel's handling of new TCP connections. The issue results from the lack of memory release after its effective lifetime. This vulnerability allows an unauthenticated attacker to create a denial of service condition on the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50578 | LinuxServer.io heimdall 2.6.3-ls307 contains a vulnerability in how it handles user-supplied HTTP headers, specifically `X-Forwarded-Host` a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50578</link><description>LinuxServer.io heimdall 2.6.3-ls307 contains a vulnerability in how it handles user-supplied HTTP headers, specifically `X-Forwarded-Host` and `Referer`. An unauthenticated remote attacker can manipulate these headers to perform Host Header Injection and Open Redirect attacks. This allows the loading of external resources from attacker-controlled domains and unintended redirection of users, potentially enabling phishing, UI redress, and session theft. The vulnerability exists due to insufficient validation and trust of untrusted input, affecting the integrity and trustworthiness of the application.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43018 | Certain HP LaserJet Pro Printers – Potential Information Disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43018</link><description>Certain HP LaserJet Pro printers may be vulnerable to information disclosure when a non-authenticated user queries a device’s local address book.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53944 | AutoGPT Platform Exposes Graph Execution Results via Authorization Gap</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53944</link><description>AutoGPT is a platform that allows users to create, deploy, and manage continuous artificial intelligence agents. In v0.6.15 and below, the external API's get_graph_execution_results endpoint has an authorization bypass vulnerability. While it correctly validates user access to the graph_id, it fails to verify ownership of the graph_exec_id parameter, allowing authenticated users to access any execution results by providing arbitrary execution IDs. The internal API implements proper validation for both parameters. This is fixed in v0.6.16.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54433 | Bugsink is vulnerable to Path Traversal attacks via event_id in ingestion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54433</link><description>Bugsink is a self-hosted error tracking service. In versions 1.4.2 and below, 1.5.0 through 1.5.4, 1.6.0 through 1.6.3, and 1.7.0 through 1.7.3,  ingestion paths construct file locations directly from untrusted event_id input without validation. A specially crafted event_id can result in paths outside the intended directory, potentially allowing file overwrite or creation in arbitrary locations. Submitting such input requires access to a valid DSN, potentially exposing them. If Bugsink runs in a container, the effect is confined to the container’s filesystem. In non-containerized setups, the overwrite may affect other parts of the system accessible to that user. This is fixed in versions 1.4.3, 1.5.5, 1.6.4 and 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54573 | CVAT vulnerable to email verification bypass by use of basic authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54573</link><description>CVAT is an open source interactive video and image annotation tool for computer vision. In versions 1.1.0 through 2.41.0, email verification was not enforced when using Basic HTTP Authentication. As a result, users could create accounts using fake email addresses and use the product as verified users. Additionally, the missing email verification check leaves the system open to bot signups and further usage. CVAT 2.42.0 and later versions contain a fix for the issue. CVAT Enterprise customers have a workaround available; those customers may disable registration to prevent this issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:49:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45515 | An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) through 10.1. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Zimbra webmail due ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45515</link><description>An issue was discovered in Zimbra Collaboration (ZCS) through 10.1. A Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in Zimbra webmail due to insufficient validation of the content type metadata when importing files into the briefcase. Attackers can exploit this issue by crafting a file with manipulated metadata, allowing them to bypass content type checks and execute arbitrary JavaScript within the victim's session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46811 | SUSE Multi Linux Manager has unprotected websocket endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46811</link><description>A Missing Authentication for Critical Function vulnerability in SUSE Manager allows anyone with access to the websocket at /rhn/websocket/minion/remote-commands to execute arbitrary commands as root.




This issue affects Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 0.3.7-150600.3.6.2; Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 5.0.14-150600.4.17.1; Container suse/manager/5.0/x86_64/server:5.0.5.7.30.1: from ? before 5.0.14-150600.4.17.1; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-Azure: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-Azure: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-EC2: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-EC2: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-GCE: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; Image SLES15-SP4-Manager-Server-4-3-BYOS-GCE: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 0.3.7-150400.3.39.4; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2; SUSE Manager Server Module 4.3: from ? before 4.3.33-150400.3.55.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53111 | GLPI exposes data to non-allowed users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53111</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. In versions 0.80 through 10.0.18, a lack of permission checks can result in unauthorized access to some resources. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53112 | GLPI&amp;#x27;s incomprehensive permission checks can lead to data removal from allowed users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53112</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 9.1.0 through 10.0.18, a lack of permission checks can result in unauthorized removal of some specific resources. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53113 | GLPI technicians can access unauthorized information through external links</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53113</link><description>GLPI, which stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique, is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.65 through 10.0.18, a technician can use the external links feature to fetch information on items they do not have the right to see. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53357 | GLPI permits reservation modification by unauthorized users</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53357</link><description>GLPI, which stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique, is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.78 through 10.0.18, a connected user can alter the reservations of another user. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52567 | GLPI has overly permissive URL verification</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52567</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, Data center management, ITIL Service Desk, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 0.84 through 10.0.18, usage of RSS feeds or external calendars when planning is subject to SSRF exploit. The previous security patches provided since GLPI 10.0.4 were not robust enough for certain specific cases. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52897 | GLPI is vulnerable to XSS and open redirection attacks through planning feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52897</link><description>GLPI is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package. In versions 9.1.0 through 10.0.18, an unauthenticated user can send a malicious link to attempt a phishing attack from the planning feature. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53008 | GLPI&amp;#x27;s MailCollector Receiver is vulnerable to credential exfiltration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53008</link><description>GLPI stands for Gestionnaire Libre de Parc Informatique is a Free Asset and IT Management Software package, that provides ITIL Service Desk features, licenses tracking and software auditing. In versions 9.3.1 through 10.0.19, a connected user can use a malicious payload to steal mail receiver credentials. This is fixed in version 10.0.19.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54572 | Ruby SAML DOS vulnerability with large SAML response</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54572</link><description>The Ruby SAML library is for implementing the client side of a SAML authorization. In versions 1.18.0 and below, a denial-of-service vulnerability exists in ruby-saml even with the message_max_bytesize setting configured. The vulnerability occurs because the SAML response is validated for Base64 format prior to checking the message size, leading to potential resource exhaustion. This is fixed in version 1.18.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54425 | Umbraco&amp;#x27;s Delivery API allows for cached requests to be returned with an invalid API key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54425</link><description>Umbraco is an ASP.NET CMS. In versions 13.0.0 through 13.9.2, 15.0.0 through 15.4.1 and 16.0.0 through 16.1.0, the content delivery API can be restricted from public access where an API key must be provided in a header to authorize the request. It's also possible to configure output caching, such that the delivery API outputs will be cached for a period of time, improving performance. There's an issue when these two things are used together, where caching doesn't vary by the header that contains the API key. As such, it's possible for a user without a valid API key to retrieve a response for a given path and query if it has recently been requested and cached by request with a valid key. This is fixed in versions 13.9.3, 15.4.4 and 16.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54430 | dedupe is vulnerable to secret exfiltration via `issue_comment`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54430</link><description>dedupe is a python library that uses machine learning to perform fuzzy matching, deduplication and entity resolution quickly on structured data. Before commit 3f61e79, a critical severity vulnerability has been identified within the .github/workflows/benchmark-bot.yml workflow, where a issue_comment can be triggered using the @benchmark body. This workflow is susceptible to exploitation as it checkout the ${{ github.event.issue.number }}, which correspond to the branch of the PR manipulated by potentially malicious actors, and where untrusted code may be executed. Running untrusted code may lead to the exfiltration of GITHUB_TOKEN, which in this workflow has write permissions on most of the scopes - in particular the contents one - and could lead to potential repository takeover. This is fixed by commit 3f61e79.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:59:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54388 | Moby&amp;#x27;s Firewalld reload makes published container ports accessible from remote hosts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54388</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework developed by Docker Inc. that is distributed as Docker Engine, Mirantis Container Runtime, and various other downstream projects/products. In versions 28.2.0 through 28.3.2, when the firewalld service is reloaded it removes all iptables rules including those created by Docker. While Docker should automatically recreate these rules, versions before 28.3.3 fail to recreate the specific rules that block external access to containers. This means that after a firewalld reload, containers with ports published to localhost (like 127.0.0.1:8080) become accessible from remote machines that have network routing to the Docker bridge, even though they should only be accessible from the host itself. The vulnerability only affects explicitly published ports - unpublished ports remain protected. This issue is fixed in version 28.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54410 | Moby&amp;#x27;s Firewalld reload removes bridge network isolation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54410</link><description>Moby is an open source container framework developed by Docker Inc. that is distributed as Docker Engine, Mirantis Container Runtime, and various other downstream projects/products. A firewalld vulnerability affects Moby releases before 28.0.0. When firewalld reloads, Docker fails to re-create iptables rules that isolate bridge networks, allowing any container to access all ports on any other container across different bridge networks on the same host. This breaks network segmentation between containers that should be isolated, creating significant risk in multi-tenant environments. Only containers in --internal networks remain protected.
Workarounds include reloading firewalld and either restarting the docker daemon, re-creating bridge networks, or using rootless mode. Maintainers anticipate a fix for this issue in version 25.0.13.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47001 | Adobe Experience Manager | Cross-site Scripting (Stored XSS) (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47001</link><description>Adobe Experience Manager versions 6.5.22 and earlier are affected by a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability that could be abused by a low privileged attacker to inject malicious scripts into vulnerable form fields. Malicious JavaScript may be executed in a victim’s browser when they browse to the page containing the vulnerable field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8326 | code-projects Exam Form Submission delete_s7.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8326</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Exam Form Submission 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/delete_s7.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6348 | Smart Slider 3 &amp;lt;= 3.5.1.28 - Authenticated (Administrator+) SQL Injection via `sliderid` Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6348</link><description>The Smart Slider 3 plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘sliderid’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.1.28 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1221 | DoS in Zigbee device due to heavy traffic</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1221</link><description>A Zigbee Radio Co-Processor (RCP), which is using SiLabs EmberZNet Zigbee stack, was unable to send messages to the host system (CPCd) due to heavy Zigbee traffic, resulting in a Denial of Service (DoS) attack, Only hard reset will bring the device to normal operation</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1394 | Denial of Service (DoS) and memory leak vulnerabilities in Zigbee library</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1394</link><description>Failure to handle the error status returned by the buffer management APIs in SiLabs EmberZNet Zigbee stack may result in data leaks or potential Denial of Service (DoS).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38498 | do_change_type(): refuse to operate on unmounted/not ours mounts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38498</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

do_change_type(): refuse to operate on unmounted/not ours mounts

Ensure that propagation settings can only be changed for mounts located
in the caller's mount namespace. This change aligns permission checking
with the rest of mount(2).</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 06:39:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8322 | Ventem｜e-School - Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8322</link><description>The e-School from Ventem has a Missing Authorization vulnerability, allowing remote attackers with regular privilege to access administrator functions, including creating, modifying, and deleting accounts. They can even escalate any account to system administrator privilege.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8323 | Ventem｜e-School - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8323</link><description>The e-School from Ventem has a Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to upload and execute web shell backdoors, thereby enabling arbitrary code execution on the server.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:53:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4422 | EfiSmiServices : EfiPcdProtocol, SMM memory corruption vulnerabilities in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4422</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4423 | SetupAutomationSmm:Vulnerability in the SMM module allow attacker to write arbitrary code and lead to memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4423</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4424 | SetupAutomationSmm : Arbitrary calls to SmmSetVariable with unsanitised arguments in SMI handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4424</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4425 | SetupAutomationSmm: Stack overflow vulnerability in SMI handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4425</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4426 | SetupAutomationSmm : SMRAM memory contents leak / information disclosure vulnerability in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4426</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8320 | Tesla Wall Connector Content-Length Header Improper Input Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8320</link><description>Tesla Wall Connector Content-Length Header Improper Input Validation Remote Code Execution Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows network-adjacent attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the parsing of the HTTP Content-Length header. The issue results from the lack of proper validation of user-supplied data, which can result in memory access past the end of an allocated buffer. An attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26300.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8321 | Tesla Wall Connector Firmware Downgrade Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8321</link><description>Tesla Wall Connector Firmware Downgrade Vulnerability. This vulnerability allows physically present attackers to execute arbitrary code on affected installations of Tesla Wall Connector devices. Authentication is not required to exploit this vulnerability.

The specific flaw exists within the firmware upgrade feature. The issue results from the lack of an anti-downgrade mechanism. An attacker can leverage this in conjunction with other vulnerabilities to execute code in the context of the device. Was ZDI-CAN-26299.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:28:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0712 | APM Server Uncontrolled Search Path Element can lead to Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) when using the Windows Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0712</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability can lead to local privilege Escalation (LPE) via Insecure Directory Permissions. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of directory permissions. An attacker with local access may exploit this flaw to move and delete arbitrary files, potentially gaining SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25011 | Beats Uncontrolled Search Path Element can lead to Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) when using the Windows Installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25011</link><description>An uncontrolled search path element vulnerability can lead to local privilege Escalation (LPE) via Insecure Directory Permissions. The vulnerability arises from improper handling of directory permissions. An attacker with local access may exploit this flaw to move and delete arbitrary files, potentially gaining SYSTEM privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4421 | EfiSmiServices: gEfiSmmCpuProtocol, SMM memory corruption vulnerabilities in SMM module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4421</link><description>The vulnerability was identified in the code developed specifically for Lenovo. Please visit "Lenovo Product Security Advisories and Announcements" webpage for more information about the vulnerability.  https://support.lenovo.com/us/en/product_security/home</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8217 | Inert Malicious script injected into Amazon Q Developer Visual Studio Code (VS Code) Extension</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8217</link><description>The Amazon Q Developer Visual Studio Code (VS Code) extension v1.84.0 contains inert, injected code designed to call the Q Developer CLI. The code executes when the extension is launched within the VS Code environment; however the injected code contains a syntax error which prevents it from making a successful API call to the Q Developer CLI.



To mitigate this issue, users should upgrade to version v1.85.0. All installations of v1.84.0 should be removed from use.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 02:29:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43191 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43191</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to cause a denial-of-service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43196 | A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43196</link><description>A path handling issue was addressed with improved validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to gain root privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43197 | This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43197</link><description>This issue was addressed with additional entitlement checks. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. An app may be able to access sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43206 | A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, m...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43206</link><description>A parsing issue in the handling of directory paths was addressed with improved path validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Ventura 13.7.7, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7. An app may be able to access protected user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43218 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43218</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. Processing a maliciously crafted USD file may disclose memory contents.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43233 | This issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43233</link><description>This issue was addressed with improved access restrictions. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6, macOS Sonoma 14.7.7, macOS Ventura 13.7.7. A malicious app acting as a HTTPS proxy could get access to sensitive user data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43237 | An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43237</link><description>An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved bounds checking. This issue is fixed in macOS Sequoia 15.6. An app may be able to cause unexpected system termination.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43265 | An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, visionOS 2.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 1...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43265</link><description>An out-of-bounds read was addressed with improved input validation. This issue is fixed in watchOS 11.6, visionOS 2.6, iOS 18.6 and iPadOS 18.6, macOS Sequoia 15.6, tvOS 18.6. Processing maliciously crafted web content may disclose internal states of the app.</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>