<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:11:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-38330 | IBM i privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38330</link><description>IBM System Management for i 7.2, 7.3, and 7.4 could allow a local user to gain elevated privileges due to an unqualified library program call.  A malicious actor could cause user-controlled code to run with administrator privilege.  IBM X-Force ID:  295227.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39723 | IBM FlashSystem denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39723</link><description>IBM FlashSystem 5300 USB ports may be usable even if the port has been disabled by the administrator. A user with physical access to the system could use the USB port to cause loss of access to data.  IBM X-Force ID:  295935.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5711 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in stitionai/devika</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5711</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) - Stored in GitHub repository stitionai/devika prior to -.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6539 | heyewei SpringBootCMS Guestbook guestbook cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6539</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in heyewei SpringBootCMS up to 2024-05-28. Affected is an unknown function of the file /guestbook of the component Guestbook Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. VDB-270450 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:33:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-3651 | Denial of Service via Quadratic Complexity in kjd/idna</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-3651</link><description>A vulnerability was identified in the kjd/idna library, specifically within the `idna.encode()` function, affecting version 3.6. The issue arises from the function's handling of crafted input strings, which can lead to quadratic complexity and consequently, a denial of service condition. This vulnerability is triggered by a crafted input that causes the `idna.encode()` function to process the input with considerable computational load, significantly increasing the processing time in a quadratic manner relative to the input size.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6229 | Stored XSS in stangirard/quivr</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6229</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the 'Upload Knowledge' feature of stangirard/quivr, affecting the latest version. Users can upload files via URL, which allows the insertion of malicious JavaScript payloads. These payloads are stored on the server and executed whenever any user clicks on a link containing the payload, leading to potential data theft, session hijacking, and reputation damage.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:27:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40614 | EGroupware before 23.1.20240624 mishandles an ORDER BY clause.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40614</link><description>EGroupware before 23.1.20240624 mishandles an ORDER BY clause.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40596 | An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. The Special:Investigate feature can expose suppressed infor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40596</link><description>An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. The Special:Investigate feature can expose suppressed information for log events. (TimelineService does not support properly suppressing.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40597 | An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. It can expose suppressed information for log events. (The l...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40597</link><description>An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. It can expose suppressed information for log events. (The log_deleted attribute is not respected.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40598 | An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. The API can expose suppressed information for log events. (...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40598</link><description>An issue was discovered in the CheckUser extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. The API can expose suppressed information for log events. (The log_deleted attribute is not applied to entries.)</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40599 | An issue was discovered in the GuMaxDD skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40599</link><description>An issue was discovered in the GuMaxDD skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40600 | An issue was discovered in the Metrolook skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40600</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Metrolook skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40601 | An issue was discovered in the MediaWikiChat extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. CSRF can occur in API modules.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40601</link><description>An issue was discovered in the MediaWikiChat extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. CSRF can occur in API modules.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40602 | An issue was discovered in the Tempo skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40602</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Tempo skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40603 | An issue was discovered in the ArticleRatings extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. Special:ChangeRating allows CSRF to alter data via a G...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40603</link><description>An issue was discovered in the ArticleRatings extension for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. Special:ChangeRating allows CSRF to alter data via a GET request.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40604 | An issue was discovered in the Nimbus skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is Stored XSS via MediaWiki:Nimbus-sidebar menu and submenu e...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40604</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Nimbus skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is Stored XSS via MediaWiki:Nimbus-sidebar menu and submenu entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40605 | An issue was discovered in the Foreground skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entrie...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40605</link><description>An issue was discovered in the Foreground skin for MediaWiki through 1.42.1. There is stored XSS via MediaWiki:Sidebar top-level menu entries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:29:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-6095 | SSRF and Partial LFI in /models/apply Endpoint in mudler/localai</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-6095</link><description>A vulnerability in the /models/apply endpoint of mudler/localai versions 2.15.0 allows for Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) and partial Local File Inclusion (LFI). The endpoint supports both http(s):// and file:// schemes, where the latter can lead to LFI. However, the output is limited due to the length of the error message. This vulnerability can be exploited by an attacker with network access to the LocalAI instance, potentially allowing unauthorized access to internal HTTP(s) servers and partial reading of local files. The issue is fixed in version 2.17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 17:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37554 | WordPress UltraAddons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37554</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in CodeAstrology Team UltraAddons Elementor Lite (Header &amp; Footer Builder, Menu Builder, Cart Icon, Shortcode).This issue affects UltraAddons Elementor Lite (Header &amp; Footer Builder, Menu Builder, Cart Icon, Shortcode): from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37553 | WordPress Testimonials Widget plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37553</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Axelerant Testimonials Widget allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Testimonials Widget: from n/a through 4.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:25:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37547 | WordPress Elementor Addons by Livemesh plugin &amp;lt;= 8.3.7 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37547</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Livemesh Livemesh Addons for Elementor.This issue affects Livemesh Addons for Elementor: from n/a through 8.3.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37546 | WordPress Image Hover Effects for Elementor with Lightbox and Flipbox plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37546</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in biplob018 Image Hover Effects - Caption Hover with Carousel allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Image Hover Effects - Caption Hover with Carousel: from n/a through 3.0.2.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:37:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37542 | WordPress Gallery – Image and Video Gallery with Thumbnails plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37542</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in WpDevArt Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album.This issue affects Responsive Image Gallery, Gallery Album: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37541 | WordPress Elementor Addons, Widgets and Enhancements – Stax plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.4.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in StaxWP Elementor Addons, Widgets and Enhancements – Stax allows Stored XSS.This issue affects Elementor Addons, Widgets and Enhancements – Stax: from n/a through 1.4.4.1.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 12:55:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37539 | WordPress WP To Do plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Delower WP To Do allows Stored XSS.This issue affects WP To Do: from n/a through 1.3.0.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 12:36:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37234 | WordPress Academy LMS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.4 - Open Redirection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37234</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in Kodezen Limited Academy LMS.This issue affects Academy LMS: from n/a through 2.0.4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 09:59:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37208 | WordPress WP Scraper plugin &amp;lt;= 5.7 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37208</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Robert Macchi WP Scraper.This issue affects WP Scraper: from n/a through 5.7.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 09:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-37260 | WordPress Foxiz Theme theme &amp;lt;= 2.3.5 - Server Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-37260</link><description>Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability in Theme-Ruby Foxiz.This issue affects Foxiz: from n/a through 2.3.5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 09:59:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-39486 | drm/drm_file: Fix pid refcounting race</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-39486</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

drm/drm_file: Fix pid refcounting race


filp-&gt;pid is supposed to be a refcounted pointer; however, before this
patch, drm_file_update_pid() only increments the refcount of a struct
pid after storing a pointer to it in filp-&gt;pid and dropping the
dev-&gt;filelist_mutex, making the following race possible:

process A               process B
=========               =========
                        begin drm_file_update_pid
                        mutex_lock(&amp;amp;dev-&gt;filelist_mutex)
                        rcu_replace_pointer(filp-&gt;pid, , 1)
                        mutex_unlock(&amp;amp;dev-&gt;filelist_mutex)
begin drm_file_update_pid
mutex_lock(&amp;amp;dev-&gt;filelist_mutex)
rcu_replace_pointer(filp-&gt;pid, , 1)
mutex_unlock(&amp;amp;dev-&gt;filelist_mutex)
get_pid()
synchronize_rcu()
put_pid()   *** pid B reaches refcount 0 and is freed here ***
                        get_pid()   *** UAF ***
                        synchronize_rcu()
                        put_pid()

As far as I know, this race can only occur with CONFIG_PREEMPT_RCU=y
because it requires RCU to detect a quiescent state in code that is not
explicitly calling into the scheduler.

This race leads to use-after-free of a "struct pid".
It is probably somewhat hard to hit because process A has to pass
through a synchronize_rcu() operation while process B is between
mutex_unlock() and get_pid().

Fix it by ensuring that by the time a pointer to the current task's pid
is stored in the file, an extra reference to the pid has been taken.

This fix also removes the condition for synchronize_rcu(); I think
that optimization is unnecessary complexity, since in that case we
would usually have bailed out on the lockless check above.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 09:29:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-5616 | CSRF Vulnerability in mudler/LocalAI</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-5616</link><description>A Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability exists in mudler/LocalAI versions up to and including 2.15.0, which allows attackers to trick victims into deleting installed models. By crafting a malicious HTML page, an attacker can cause the deletion of a model, such as 'gpt-4-vision-preview', without the victim's consent. The vulnerability is due to insufficient CSRF protection mechanisms on the model deletion functionality.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 08:46:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40594 | The OpenAI ChatGPT app before 2024-07-05 for macOS opts out of the sandbox, and stores conversations in cleartext in a location accessible t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40594</link><description>The OpenAI ChatGPT app before 2024-07-05 for macOS opts out of the sandbox, and stores conversations in cleartext in a location accessible to other apps.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>