<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:08:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-29339 | An issue in UPF in Open5GS UPF versions up to v2.7.2 results an assertion failure vulnerability in PFCP session parameter validation. When p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29339</link><description>An issue in UPF in Open5GS UPF versions up to v2.7.2 results an assertion failure vulnerability in PFCP session parameter validation. When processing a PFCP Session Establishment Request with PDN Type=0, the UPF fails to handle the invalid value propagated from SMF (or via direct attack), triggering a fatal assertion check and causing a daemon crash.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34028 | Commvault Command Center Innovation Release Unathenticated Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34028</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in Commvault Command Center Innovation Release allows an unauthenticated actor to upload ZIP files, which, when expanded by the target server, result in Remote Code Execution.





This issue affects Command Center Innovation Release: 11.38.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27907 | IBM WebSphere Application Server server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27907</link><description>IBM WebSphere Application Server 8.5 and 9.0 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:43:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28024 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the cstecgi.cgi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28024</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was found to contain a buffer overflow vulnerability in the cstecgi.cgi</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28030 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the startTime and endTime parameters in setParentalRul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28030</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the startTime and endTime parameters in setParentalRules function.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:21:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28031 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password for the telnet service in product.ini.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28031</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 was discovered to contain a hardcoded password for the telnet service in product.ini.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28037 | TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 and A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903 were found to contain a pre-auth remote command execution vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28037</link><description>TOTOLINK A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026 and A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903 were found to contain a pre-auth remote command execution vulnerability in the setDiagnosisCfg function through the ipDomain parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-33452 | An issue in OpenResty lua-nginx-module v.0.10.26 and before allows a remote attacker to conduct HTTP request smuggling via a crafted HEAD re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-33452</link><description>An issue in OpenResty lua-nginx-module v.0.10.26 and before allows a remote attacker to conduct HTTP request smuggling via a crafted HEAD request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23250 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23250</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where an attacker could cause an improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory by an arbitrary file write. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23251 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper control of generation of code by remote code execution. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23251</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause an improper control of generation of code by remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23249 | NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data by remote code execution. A succ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23249</link><description>NVIDIA NeMo Framework contains a vulnerability where a user could cause a deserialization of untrusted data by remote code execution. A successful exploit of this vulnerability might lead to code execution and data tampering.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:44:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3767 | SQL Injection in Centreon BAM boolean KPI listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3767</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Centreon BAM (Boolean KPi Listing modules) allows SQL Injection.


This page is only accessible to authenticated users with high privileges.

This issue affects Centreon BAM: from 24.10 before 24.10.1, from 24.04 before 24.04.5, from 23.10 before 23.10.10, from 23.04 before 23.04.10.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1950 | IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1950</link><description>IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems V10.2.1030.0 and V10.3.1050.0 could allow a local user to execute commands locally due to improper validation of libraries of an untrusted source.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1951 | IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems command execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1951</link><description>IBM Hardware Management Console - Power Systems V10.2.1030.0 and V10.3.1050.0 could allow a local user to execute commands as a privileged user due to execution of commands with unnecessary privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23176 | Tecnick –  CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command (&amp;#x27;SQL Injection&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23176</link><description>CWE-89: Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection')</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29547 | In Rollback Rx Professional 12.8.0.0, the driver file shieldm.sys allows local users to cause a denial of service because of a null pointer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29547</link><description>In Rollback Rx Professional 12.8.0.0, the driver file shieldm.sys allows local users to cause a denial of service because of a null pointer dereference from IOCtl 0x96202000.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40445 | Directory Traversal vulnerability in forkosh Mime Tex before v.1.77 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40445</link><description>Directory Traversal vulnerability in forkosh Mime Tex before v.1.77 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted file upload</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40446 | An issue in forkosh Mime Tex before v.1.77 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40446</link><description>An issue in forkosh Mime Tex before v.1.77 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28033 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28033</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 were found to contain a pre-auth buffer overflow vulnerability in the setNoticeCfg function through the IpTo parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28034 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28034</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 were found to contain a pre-auth remote command execution vulnerability in the NTPSyncWithHost function through the hostTime parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28032 | TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28032</link><description>TOTOLINK A800R V4.1.2cu.5137_B20200730, A810R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201026, A830R V4.1.2cu.5182_B20201102, A950RG V4.1.2cu.5161_B20200903, A3000RU V5.9c.5185_B20201128, and A3100R V4.1.2cu.5247_B20211129 contain a pre-auth buffer overflow vulnerability in the setNoticeCfg function through the IpForm parameter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:53:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46546 | NEXTU FLETA AX1500 WIFI6 Router v1.0.3 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the url parameter at /boafrm/formFilter. This vulnerab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46546</link><description>NEXTU FLETA AX1500 WIFI6 Router v1.0.3 was discovered to contain a stack overflow via the url parameter at /boafrm/formFilter. This vulnerability allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:46:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23175 | Tecnick -  Multiple XSS (CWE-79)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23175</link><description>Multiple XSS (CWE-79)</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2092 | Remote site authentication secrets written to web log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2092</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information into Log File in Checkmk GmbH's Checkmk versions &lt;2.3.0p29, &lt;2.2.0p41 and &lt;=2.1.0p49 (EOL) causes remote site authentication secrets to be written to log files accessible to administrators.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:42:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11299 | Memberpress &amp;lt;= 1.11.37 - Unauthenticated Content Restriction Bypass to Sensitive Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11299</link><description>The Memberpress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.11.37 via the WordPress core search feature. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to extract sensitive data from posts that have been restricted to higher-level roles such as administrator.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3457 | Ocean Extra &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3457</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'oceanwp_icon' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3458 | Ocean Extra &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via &amp;#x27;ocean_gallery_id&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3458</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ocean_gallery_id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. The Classic Editor plugin must be installed and activated to exploit the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:26:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3472 | Ocean Extra &amp;lt;= 2.4.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3472</link><description>The Ocean Extra plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.4.6. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes when WooCommerce is also installed and activated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46225 | WordPress Post in page for Elementor plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46225</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Michael Post in page for Elementor allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Post in page for Elementor: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46226 | WordPress MPL-Publisher &amp;lt;= 2.18.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46226</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in ferranfg MPL-Publisher allows Stored XSS. This issue affects MPL-Publisher: from n/a through 2.18.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46227 | WordPress Custom Related Posts &amp;lt;= 1.7.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46227</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Brecht Custom Related Posts allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Custom Related Posts: from n/a through 1.7.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46228 | WordPress Event post &amp;lt;= 5.9.11 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46228</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bastien Ho Event post allows DOM-Based XSS. This issue affects Event post: from n/a through 5.9.11.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46229 | WordPress Textmetrics &amp;lt;= 3.6.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46229</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Israpil Textmetrics allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Textmetrics: from n/a through 3.6.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46231 | WordPress affiliate-toolkit &amp;lt;= 3.7.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46231</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in SERVIT Software Solutions affiliate-toolkit allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects affiliate-toolkit: from n/a through 3.7.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46232 | WordPress Download Alt Text AI &amp;lt;= 1.9.93 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46232</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in alttextai Download Alt Text AI allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Download Alt Text AI: from n/a through 1.9.93.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46233 | WordPress Sirv &amp;lt;= 7.5.3 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46233</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Sirv CDN and Image Hosting Sirv allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sirv: from n/a through 7.5.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46235 | WordPress SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46235</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sonalsinha21 SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects SKT Blocks – Gutenberg based Page Builder: from n/a through 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46236 | WordPress HTML Forms &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46236</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Link Software LLC HTML Forms allows Stored XSS. This issue affects HTML Forms: from n/a through 1.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46237 | WordPress Link Library &amp;lt;= 7.8 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46237</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yannick Lefebvre Link Library allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Link Library: from n/a through 7.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46238 | WordPress List Last Changes &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46238</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in rbaer List Last Changes allows Stored XSS. This issue affects List Last Changes: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46239 | WordPress Theme Switcha &amp;lt;= 3.4 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46239</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeff Starr Theme Switcha allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Theme Switcha: from n/a through 3.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46240 | WordPress Simple Download Counter &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46240</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Jeff Starr Simple Download Counter allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Simple Download Counter: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46241 | WordPress Appointment Booking Calendar plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.92 - CSRF to SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46241</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in codepeople Appointment Booking Calendar allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Appointment Booking Calendar: from n/a through 1.3.92.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46242 | WordPress Watu Quiz &amp;lt;= 3.4.3 - SQL Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46242</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Bob Watu Quiz allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Watu Quiz: from n/a through 3.4.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46243 | WordPress Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46243</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in sonalsinha21 Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Recover abandoned cart for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46244 | WordPress Advanced Linked Variations for Woocommerce &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46244</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Dotstore Advanced Linked Variations for Woocommerce allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Advanced Linked Variations for Woocommerce: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46245 | WordPress CM Ad Changer &amp;lt;= 2.0.5 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46245</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Ad Changer allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects CM Ad Changer: from n/a through 2.0.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46246 | WordPress CM Answers &amp;lt;= 3.3.3 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46246</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in CreativeMindsSolutions CM Answers allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects CM Answers: from n/a through 3.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46247 | WordPress Appointment Booking Calendar &amp;lt;= 1.3.92 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46247</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in codepeople Appointment Booking Calendar allows Accessing Functionality Not Properly Constrained by ACLs. This issue affects Appointment Booking Calendar: from n/a through 1.3.92.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46249 | WordPress Simple calendar for Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46249</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Michael Simple calendar for Elementor allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects Simple calendar for Elementor: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46250 | WordPress VForm &amp;lt;= 3.1.14 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46250</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Vikas Ratudi VForm allows Stored XSS. This issue affects VForm: from n/a through 3.1.14.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46251 | WordPress VikRestaurants Table Reservations and Take-Away plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - CSRF to Stored XSS vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46251</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in e4jvikwp VikRestaurants Table Reservations and Take-Away allows Cross Site Request Forgery. This issue affects VikRestaurants Table Reservations and Take-Away: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46252 | WordPress Message Filter for Contact Form 7 plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.3.2 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46252</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in kofimokome Message Filter for Contact Form 7 allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Message Filter for Contact Form 7: from n/a through 1.6.3.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46253 | WordPress GutenKit plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46253</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Ataur R GutenKit allows Stored XSS. This issue affects GutenKit: from n/a through 2.2.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46254 | WordPress Visual Composer Website Builder plugin &amp;lt;= 45.10.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46254</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Visual Composer Visual Composer Website Builder allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Visual Composer Website Builder: from n/a through 45.10.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:16:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3518 | File upload functionality possible even when disabled</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3518</link><description>It technically possible for a user to upload a file to a conversation despite the file upload functionality being disabled.

The file upload functionality can be enabled or disabled for specific use cases through configuration. In case the functionality is disabled for at least one use case, the system nevertheless allows files to be uploaded through direct API requests. During the upload file, interception and allowed file type rules are still applied correctly.

If file sharing is generally enabled, this issue is not of concern.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3519 | Replace uploaded files knowing the file upload ID</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3519</link><description>An authorization bypass in Unblu Spark allows a participant of a conversation to replace an existing, uploaded file.

Every uploaded file in Unblu gets assigned with a randomly generated Universally Unique ID (UUID). In case a participant of this or another conversation gets access to such a file ID, it can be used to replace the file without changing the file name and details or the name of the user who uploaded the file. During the upload, file interception and allowed file type rules are still applied correctly.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-26413 | Apache Kvrocks: The server was crashed by the negative offset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-26413</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in Apache Kvrocks.

The SETRANGE command didn't check if the `offset` input is a positive integer and use it as an index
of a string. So it will cause the server to crash due to its index is  out of range.
This issue affects Apache Kvrocks: through 2.11.1.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.12.0, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 07:29:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13569 | Front End Users &amp;lt;= 3.2.32 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13569</link><description>The Front End Users WordPress plugin through 3.2.32 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2594 | User Registration &amp;amp; Membership &amp;lt; 4.1.3 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2594</link><description>The User Registration &amp; Membership  WordPress plugin before 4.1.3 does not properly validate data in an AJAX action when the Membership Addon is enabled, allowing attackers to authenticate as any user, including administrators, by simply using the target account's user ID.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 06:27:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2839 | WP Import Export Lite &amp;lt;= 3.9.27 - Authenticated (Contributor+) DOM-Based Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2839</link><description>The WP Import Export Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘wpiePreviewData’ function in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.27 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3814 | Tax Switch for WooCommerce &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via class-name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3814</link><description>The Tax Switch for WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘class-name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 05:35:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46899 | Authentication credentials leakage vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services within Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint OVF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46899</link><description>Hitachi Ops Center Common Services within Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint OVF contains an authentication credentials leakage vulnerability.This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Common Services: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.0-04; Hitachi Ops Center Analyzer viewpoint OVF: from 10.0.0-00 before 11.0.0-04.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2300 | Information exposure vulnerability in Hitachi Ops Center Common Services within Hitachi Ops Center OVA</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2300</link><description>Hitachi Ops Center Common Services within Hitachi Ops Center OVA contains an information exposure vulnerability.
This issue affects Hitachi Ops Center Common Services: from 11.0.3-00 before 11.0.4-00.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3616 | Greenshift  11.4 - 11.4.5 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3616</link><description>The Greenshift – animation and page builder blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the gspb_make_proxy_api_request() function in versions 11.4 to 11.4.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. The arbitrary file upload was sufficiently patched in 11.4.5, but a capability check was added in 11.4.6 to properly prevent unauthorized limited file uploads.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 04:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1731 | An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in the PostgreSQL commands of the USG FLEX H series uOS firmware versions from V1.20 throug...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1731</link><description>An incorrect permission assignment vulnerability in the PostgreSQL commands of the USG FLEX H series uOS firmware versions from V1.20 through V1.31 could allow an authenticated local attacker with low privileges to gain access to the Linux shell and escalate their privileges by crafting malicious scripts or modifying system configurations with administrator-level access through a stolen token. Modifying the system configuration is only possible if the administrator has not logged out and the token remains valid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 02:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1732 | An improper privilege management vulnerability in the recovery function of the USG FLEX H series uOS firmware version V1.31 and earlier coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1732</link><description>An improper privilege management vulnerability in the recovery function of the USG FLEX H series uOS firmware version V1.31 and earlier could allow an authenticated local attacker with administrator privileges to upload a crafted configuration file and escalate privileges on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 02:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3577 | **UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED** A path traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of the Zyxel AMG1302-T10B firmware version 2.00...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3577</link><description>**UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED** A path traversal vulnerability in the web management interface of the Zyxel AMG1302-T10B firmware version 2.00(AAJC.16)C0 could allow an authenticated attacker with administrator privileges to access restricted directories by sending a crafted HTTP request to an affected device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3856 | xxyopen Novel-Plus searchByPage sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3856</link><description>A vulnerability was found in xxyopen Novel-Plus 5.1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function searchByPage of the file /book/searchByPage. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 02:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3854 | H3C GR-3000AX HTTP POST Request aspForm Edit_List_SSID buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3854</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in H3C GR-3000AX up to V100R006. Affected is the function EnableIpv6/UpdateWanModeMulti/UpdateIpv6Params/EditWlanMacList/Edit_List_SSID of the file /goform/aspForm of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument param leads to buffer overflow. The attack needs to be initiated within the local network. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. Other functions might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3855 | CodeCanyon RISE Ultimate Project Manager Profile Picture save_profile_image resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3855</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeCanyon RISE Ultimate Project Manager 3.8.2 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php/team_members/save_profile_image/ of the component Profile Picture Handler. The manipulation of the argument profile_image_file leads to improper control of resource identifiers. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:50:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58250 | The passprompt plugin in pppd in ppp before 2.5.2 mishandles privileges.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58250</link><description>The passprompt plugin in pppd in ppp before 2.5.2 mishandles privileges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3850 | YXJ2018 SpringBoot-Vue-OnlineExam API improper authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3850</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in YXJ2018 SpringBoot-Vue-OnlineExam 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component API. The manipulation leads to improper authentication. The attack may be initiated remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:50:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2987 | IBM Maximo Asset Management server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2987</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 is vulnerable to server-side request forgery (SSRF). This may allow an authenticated attacker to send unauthorized requests from the system, potentially leading to network enumeration or facilitating other attacks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 23:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3849 | YXJ2018 SpringBoot-Vue-OnlineExam studentPWD unverified password change</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3849</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in YXJ2018 SpringBoot-Vue-OnlineExam 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /api/studentPWD. The manipulation of the argument studentId leads to unverified password change. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 23:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3847 | markparticle WebServer Login httprequest.cpp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3847</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in markparticle WebServer up to 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file code/http/httprequest.cpp of the component Login. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 23:18:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3846 | markparticle WebServer Registration httprequest.cpp sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3846</link><description>A vulnerability was found in markparticle WebServer up to 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file code/http/httprequest.cpp of the component Registration. The manipulation of the argument username/password leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 22:45:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3843 | panhainan DS-Java cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3843</link><description>A vulnerability was found in panhainan DS-Java 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 22:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3845 | markparticle WebServer buffer.cpp HasWritten buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3845</link><description>A vulnerability was found in markparticle WebServer up to 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function Buffer::HasWritten of the file code/buffer/buffer.cpp. The manipulation of the argument writePos_ leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 22:19:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32955 | Harden-Runner Evasion of &amp;#x27;disable-sudo&amp;#x27; policy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32955</link><description>Harden-Runner is a CI/CD security agent that works like an EDR for GitHub Actions runners. Versions from 0.12.0 to before 2.12.0 are vulnerable to `disable-sudo` bypass. Harden-Runner includes a policy option `disable-sudo` to prevent the GitHub Actions runner user from using sudo. This is implemented by removing the runner user from the sudoers file. However, this control can be bypassed as the runner user, being part of the docker group, can interact with the Docker daemon to launch privileged containers or access the host filesystem. This allows the attacker to regain root access or restore the sudoers file, effectively bypassing the restriction. This issue has been patched in version 2.12.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32956 | ManageWiki has SQL injection vulnerability in NamespaceMigrationJob</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32956</link><description>ManageWiki is a MediaWiki extension allowing users to manage wikis. Versions before commit f504ed8, are vulnerable to SQL injection when renaming a namespace in Special:ManageWiki/namespaces when using a page prefix (namespace name, which is the current namespace you are renaming) with an injection payload. This issue has been patched in commit f504ed8. A workaround for this vulnerability involves setting `$wgManageWiki['namespaces'] = false;`.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:50:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32958 | Adept exposed the GITHUB_TOKEN in workflow run artifact</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32958</link><description>Adept is a language for general purpose programming. Prior to commit a1a41b7, the remoteBuild.yml workflow file uses actions/upload-artifact@v4 to upload the mac-standalone artifact. This artifact is a zip of the current directory, which includes the automatically generated .git/config file containing the run's GITHUB_TOKEN. Seeing as the artifact can be downloaded prior to the end of the workflow, there is a few seconds where an attacker can extract the token from the artifact and use it with the Github API to push malicious code or rewrite release commits in the AdeptLanguage/Adept repository. This issue has been patched in commit a1a41b7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:50:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3842 | panhainan DS-Java FileUpload.java uploadUserPic.action code injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3842</link><description>A vulnerability was found in panhainan DS-Java 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function uploadUserPic.action of the file src/com/phn/action/FileUpload.java. The manipulation of the argument fileUpload leads to code injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3841 | wix-incubator jam Jinja2 Template jam.py special elements used in a template engine</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3841</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in wix-incubator jam up to e87a6fd85cf8fb5ff37b62b2d68f917219d07ae9. This affects an unknown part of the file jam.py of the component Jinja2 Template Handler. The manipulation of the argument config['template'] leads to improper neutralization of special elements used in a template engine. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product takes the approach of rolling releases to provide continious delivery. Therefore, version details for affected and updated releases are not available.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 19:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27086 | Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Performance Cluster Manager (HPCM).This issue affects HPE Performance Cluster Manager (HPCM)...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27086</link><description>Vulnerability in Hewlett Packard Enterprise HPE Performance Cluster Manager (HPCM).This issue affects HPE Performance Cluster Manager (HPCM): through 1.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:22:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57394 | The quarantine - restore function in Qi-ANXIN Tianqing Endpoint Security Management System v10.0 allows user to restore a malicious file to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57394</link><description>The quarantine - restore function in Qi-ANXIN Tianqing Endpoint Security Management System v10.0 allows user to restore a malicious file to an arbitrary file path. Attackers can write malicious DLL to system path and perform privilege escalation by leveraging Windows DLL hijacking vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28104 | Incorrect access control in laskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to access all usernames via a crafted input.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28104</link><description>Incorrect access control in laskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to access all usernames via a crafted input.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28103 | Incorrect access control in laskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete user accounts via a crafted request.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28103</link><description>Incorrect access control in laskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to arbitrarily delete user accounts via a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28102 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in flaskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted paylo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28102</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in flaskBlog v2.6.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the postContent parameter at /createpost.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29446 | open-webui v0.5.16 is vulnerable to SSRF in routers/ollama.py in function verify_connection.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29446</link><description>open-webui v0.5.16 is vulnerable to SSRF in routers/ollama.py in function verify_connection.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:20:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28099 | opencms V2.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary file read in src/main/webapp/view/admin/document/dataPage.jsp,</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28099</link><description>opencms V2.3 is vulnerable to Arbitrary file read in src/main/webapp/view/admin/document/dataPage.jsp,</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23174 | Yoel Geva - CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23174</link><description>CWE-200: Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43922 | The FileWave Windows client before 16.0.0, in some non-default configurations, allows an unprivileged local user to escalate privileges to S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43922</link><description>The FileWave Windows client before 16.0.0, in some non-default configurations, allows an unprivileged local user to escalate privileges to SYSTEM.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32431 | Traefik has a possible vulnerability with the path matchers</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32431</link><description>Traefik (pronounced traffic) is an HTTP reverse proxy and load balancer. In versions prior to 2.11.24, 3.3.6, and 3.4.0-rc2. There is a potential vulnerability in Traefik managing the requests using a PathPrefix, Path or PathRegex matcher. When Traefik is configured to route the requests to a backend using a matcher based on the path, if the URL contains a /../ in its path, it’s possible to target a backend, exposed using another router, by-passing the middlewares chain. This issue has been patched in versions 2.11.24, 3.3.6, and 3.4.0-rc2. A workaround involves adding a `PathRegexp` rule to the matcher to prevent matching a route with a `/../` in the path.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32793 | Cilium packets from terminating endpoints may not be encrypted in Wireguard-enabled clusters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32793</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. Versions 1.15.0 to 1.15.15, 1.16.0 to 1.16.8, and 1.17.0 to 1.17.2, are vulnerable when using Wireguard transparent encryption in a Cilium cluster, packets that originate from a terminating endpoint can leave the source node without encryption due to a race condition in how traffic is processed by Cilium. This issue has been patched in versions 1.15.16, 1.16.9, and 1.17.3. There are no workarounds available for this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:44:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12543 | A user enumeration and subsequent data integrity vulnerability affecting barcode functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12543</link><description>User Enumeration and Data Integrity in Barcode functionality in OpenText Content Management versions 24.3-25.1on Windows and Linux allows a malicous authenticated attacker to potentially alter barcode attributes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:33:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28367 | mojoPortal &lt;=2.9.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via BetterImageGallery API Controller - ImageHandler Action. An attacker can explo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28367</link><description>mojoPortal &lt;=2.9.0.1 is vulnerable to Directory Traversal via BetterImageGallery API Controller - ImageHandler Action. An attacker can exploit this vulnerability to access the Web.Config file and obtain the MachineKey.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3857 | Infinite loop condition in Amazon.IonDotnet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3857</link><description>When reading binary Ion data through Amazon.IonDotnet using the RawBinaryReader class, Amazon.IonDotnet does not check the number of bytes read from the underlying stream while deserializing the binary format. If the Ion data is malformed or truncated, this triggers an infinite loop condition that could potentially result in a denial of service. Users should upgrade to Amazon.IonDotnet version 1.3.1 and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12863 | Stored XSS in Discussions functionality</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12863</link><description>Stored XSS in Discussions in OpenText Content Management CE 20.2 to 25.1 on Windows and Linux allows authenticated malicious users to inject code into the system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2298 | Authenticated API Endpoint Allows Arbitrary File Deletion in Dremio Software</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2298</link><description>An improper authorization vulnerability in Dremio Software allows authenticated users to delete arbitrary files that the system has access to, including system files and files stored in remote locations such as S3, Azure Blob Storage, and local filesystems. This vulnerability exists due to insufficient access controls on an API endpoint, enabling any authenticated user to specify and delete files outside their intended scope. Exploiting this flaw could lead to data loss, denial of service (DoS), and potential escalation of impact depending on the deleted files.

Affected versions:
  *  Any version of Dremio below 24.0.0


  *  Dremio 24.3.0 - 24.3.16


  *  Dremio 25.0.0 - 25.0.14


  *  Dremio 25.1.0 - 25.1.7


  *  Dremio 25.2.0 - 25.2.4





Fixed in version: 
  *  Dremio 24.3.17 and above


  *  Dremio 25.0.15 and above


  *  Dremio 25.1.8 and above


  *  Dremio 25.2.5 and above


  *  Dremio 26.0.0 and above</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:16:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42699 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Create/Modify article function in Alkacon OpenCMS 17.0 allows remote attacker to inject javascript pay...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42699</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Create/Modify article function in Alkacon OpenCMS 17.0 allows remote attacker to inject javascript payload via image title sub-field in the image field</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 15:16:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29660 | A vulnerability exists in the daemon process of the Yi IOT XY-3820 v6.0.24.10, which exposes a TCP service on port 6789. This service lacks ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29660</link><description>A vulnerability exists in the daemon process of the Yi IOT XY-3820 v6.0.24.10, which exposes a TCP service on port 6789. This service lacks proper input validation, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary scripts present on the device by sending specially crafted TCP requests using directory traversal techniques.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:57:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29287 | An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the ueditor component of MCMS v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29287</link><description>An arbitrary file upload vulnerability in the ueditor component of MCMS v5.4.3 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via uploading a crafted file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:43:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12862 | REST API allows users without permissions to remove external collaborators</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12862</link><description>Incorrect Authorization vulnerability in the OpenText Content Server REST API on Windows, Linux allows users without the appropriate permissions to remove external collaborators.This issue affects Content Server: 20.2-24.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-28121 | code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in feedback.php via the "q" parameter allowing re...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-28121</link><description>code-projects Online Exam Mastering System 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) in feedback.php via the "q" parameter allowing remote attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29659 | Yi IOT XY-3820 6.0.24.10 is vulnerable to Remote Command Execution via the "cmd_listen" function located in the "cmd" binary.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29659</link><description>Yi IOT XY-3820 6.0.24.10 is vulnerable to Remote Command Execution via the "cmd_listen" function located in the "cmd" binary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2517 | Reference to Expired Domain Vulnerability in OpenText™ ArcSight Enterprise Security Manager</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2517</link><description>Reference to Expired Domain Vulnerability in OpenText™ ArcSight Enterprise Security Manager.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41446 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Alkacon OpenCMS v17.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41446</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Alkacon OpenCMS v17.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload injected into the image parameter under the Create/Modify article function.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43916 | Sonos api.sonos.com through 2025-04-21, when the /login/v3/oauth endpoint is used, accepts a redirect_uri containing userinfo in the authori...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43916</link><description>Sonos api.sonos.com through 2025-04-21, when the /login/v3/oauth endpoint is used, accepts a redirect_uri containing userinfo in the authority component, which is not consistent with RFC 6819 section 5.2.3.5. An authorization code may be sent to an attacker-controlled destination. This might have further implications in conjunction with "Decompiling the app revealed a hardcoded secret."</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32408 | In Soffid Console 3.5.38 before 3.5.39, necessary checks were not applied to some Java objects. A malicious agent could possibly execute arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32408</link><description>In Soffid Console 3.5.38 before 3.5.39, necessary checks were not applied to some Java objects. A malicious agent could possibly execute arbitrary code in the Sync Server and compromise security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:56:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3840 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3840</link><description>An improper neutralization of input vulnerability was identified in the End of Life (EOL) OVA based connect installer component which is deployed for installation purposes in a customer network. This EOL component was deprecated in September 2023 with end of support extended till January 2024. An actor can manipulate the action parameter of the login form to inject malicious scripts which would lead to a XSS attack under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3838 | Improper Authorization in the installer for the EOL OVA based connect component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3838</link><description>An Improper Authorization vulnerability was identified in the EOL OVA based connect component which is deployed for installation purposes in the customer internal network. Under certain conditions, this could allow a bad actor to gain unauthorized access to the local db containing weakly hashed credentials of the installer. This EOL component was deprecated in September 2023 with end of support extended till January 2024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3837 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in the End of Life (EOL) OVA based connect component</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3837</link><description>An improper input validation vulnerability is identified in the End of Life (EOL) OVA based connect component which is deployed for installation purposes in the customer internal network. This EOL component was deprecated in September 2023 with end of support extended till January 2024. Under certain circumstances, an actor can manipulate a specific request parameter and inject code execution payload which could lead to a remote code execution on the infrastructure hosting this component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 09:32:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-25228 | Extension - virtuemart.net - SQL injection in VirtueMart component 1.0.0 - 4.4.7 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-25228</link><description>A SQL injection in VirtueMart component 1.0.0 - 4.4.7 for Joomla allows authenticated attackers (administrator) to execute arbitrary SQL commands in the product management area in backend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 07:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0632 | Local File Inclusion (LFI) leading to sensitive data exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0632</link><description>Local File Inclusion (LFI) vulnerability in a Render function of Formulatrix Rock Maker Web (RMW) allows a remote attacker to obtain sensitive data via arbitrary code execution. A malicious actor could execute malicious scripts to automatically download configuration files in known locations to exfiltrate data including credentials, and with no rate limiting a malicious actor could enumerate the filesystem of the host machine and potentially lead to full host compromise.

This issue affects Rock Maker Web: from 3.2.1.1 and later</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 05:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43970 | An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/mrt/mrt.go does not properly check the input length, e.g.. by ensuring that there...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43970</link><description>An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/mrt/mrt.go does not properly check the input length, e.g.. by ensuring that there are 12 bytes or 36 bytes (depending on the address family).</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 01:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43971 | An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/bgp/bgp.go allows attackers to cause a panic via a zero value for softwareVersion...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43971</link><description>An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/bgp/bgp.go allows attackers to cause a panic via a zero value for softwareVersionLen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43972 | An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. An attacker can cause a crash in the pkg/packet/bgp/bgp.go flowspec parser by sending fewer ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43972</link><description>An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. An attacker can cause a crash in the pkg/packet/bgp/bgp.go flowspec parser by sending fewer than 20 bytes in a certain context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 01:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43973 | An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/rtr/rtr.go does not verify that the input length corresponds to a situation in wh...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43973</link><description>An issue was discovered in GoBGP before 3.35.0. pkg/packet/rtr/rtr.go does not verify that the input length corresponds to a situation in which all bytes are available for an RTR message.</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43961 | In LibRaw before 0.21.4, metadata/tiff.cpp has an out-of-bounds read in the Fujifilm 0xf00c tag parser.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43961</link><description>In LibRaw before 0.21.4, metadata/tiff.cpp has an out-of-bounds read in the Fujifilm 0xf00c tag parser.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43962 | In LibRaw before 0.21.4, phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp has out-of-bounds reads for tag 0x412 processing, related to large w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43962</link><description>In LibRaw before 0.21.4, phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp has out-of-bounds reads for tag 0x412 processing, related to large w0 or w1 values or the frac and mult calculations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43963 | In LibRaw before 0.21.4, phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp allows out-of-buffer access because split_col and split_row values a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43963</link><description>In LibRaw before 0.21.4, phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp allows out-of-buffer access because split_col and split_row values are not checked in 0x041f tag processing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43964 | In LibRaw before 0.21.4, tag 0x412 processing in phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp does not enforce minimum w0 and w1 values.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43964</link><description>In LibRaw before 0.21.4, tag 0x412 processing in phase_one_correct in decoders/load_mfbacks.cpp does not enforce minimum w0 and w1 values.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43966 | libheif before 1.19.6 has a NULL pointer dereference in ImageItem_iden in image-items/iden.cc.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43966</link><description>libheif before 1.19.6 has a NULL pointer dereference in ImageItem_iden in image-items/iden.cc.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43967 | libheif before 1.19.6 has a NULL pointer dereference in ImageItem_Grid::get_decoder in image-items/grid.cc because a grid image can referenc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43967</link><description>libheif before 1.19.6 has a NULL pointer dereference in ImageItem_Grid::get_decoder in image-items/grid.cc because a grid image can reference a nonexistent image item.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 23:44:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36844 | The KnowBe4 Security Awareness Training application before 2020-01-10 allows reflected XSS. The response has a SCRIPT element that sets wind...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36844</link><description>The KnowBe4 Security Awareness Training application before 2020-01-10 allows reflected XSS. The response has a SCRIPT element that sets window.location.href to a JavaScript URL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2020-36845 | The KnowBe4 Security Awareness Training application before 2020-01-10 contains a redirect function that does not validate the destination UR...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2020-36845</link><description>The KnowBe4 Security Awareness Training application before 2020-01-10 contains a redirect function that does not validate the destination URL before redirecting. The response has a SCRIPT element that sets window.location.href to an arbitrary https URL.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 21:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43955 | TwsCachedXPathAPI in Convertigo through 8.3.4 does not restrict the use of commons-jxpath APIs.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43955</link><description>TwsCachedXPathAPI in Convertigo through 8.3.4 does not restrict the use of commons-jxpath APIs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 19:33:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43954 | QMarkdown (aka quasar-ui-qmarkdown) before 2.0.5 allows XSS via headers even when when no-html is set.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43954</link><description>QMarkdown (aka quasar-ui-qmarkdown) before 2.0.5 allows XSS via headers even when when no-html is set.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 18:44:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3830 | kuangstudy KuangSimpleBBS QuestionController.java fileUpload unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3830</link><description>A vulnerability was found in kuangstudy KuangSimpleBBS 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fileUpload of the file src/main/java/com/kuang/controller/QuestionController.java. The manipulation of the argument editormd-image-file leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3829 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System sales-reports-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3829</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/sales-reports-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 16:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3828 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System view-appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3828</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/view-appointment.php?viewid=11. The manipulation of the argument remark leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 15:39:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3827 | PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3827</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Men Salon Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 15:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3826 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System add-supplier.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3826</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file add-supplier.php. The manipulation of the argument txtsupplier_name/txtaddress leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 13:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3825 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System add-category.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3825</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file add-category.php. The manipulation of the argument txtcategory_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 11:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3824 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System add-product.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3824</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file add-product.php. The manipulation of the argument txtprice/txtproduct_name leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 11:05:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3823 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System add-stock.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3823</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file add-stock.php. The manipulation of the argument txttotalcost/txtproductID/txtprice/txtexpirydate leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 10:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3822 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System changepassword.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3822</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file changepassword.php. The manipulation of the argument txtconfirm_password/txtnew_password/txtold_password leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 06:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3821 | SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System add-admin.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3821</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Web-based Pharmacy Product Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file add-admin.php. The manipulation of the argument txtpassword/txtfullname/txtemail leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 04:20:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43928 | In Infodraw Media Relay Service (MRS) 7.1.0.0, the MRS web server (on port 12654) allows reading arbitrary files via ../ directory traversal...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43928</link><description>In Infodraw Media Relay Service (MRS) 7.1.0.0, the MRS web server (on port 12654) allows reading arbitrary files via ../ directory traversal in the username field. Reading ServerParameters.xml may reveal administrator credentials in cleartext or with MD5 hashing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43929 | open_actions.py in kitty before 0.41.0 does not ask for user confirmation before running a local executable file that may have been linked f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43929</link><description>open_actions.py in kitty before 0.41.0 does not ask for user confirmation before running a local executable file that may have been linked from an untrusted document (e.g., a document opened in KDE ghostwriter).</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43919 | GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files via ../ directory traversal at ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43919</link><description>GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files via ../ directory traversal at /mailman/private/mailman (aka the private archive authentication endpoint) via the username parameter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 01:14:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43920 | GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via shell metacharacte...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43920</link><description>GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary OS commands via shell metacharacters in an email Subject line.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 01:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43921 | GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to create lists via the /mailman/create endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43921</link><description>GNU Mailman 2.1.39, as bundled in cPanel (and WHM), allows unauthenticated attackers to create lists via the /mailman/create endpoint.</description><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 01:14:38 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>