<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2024-45077 | IBM Maximo Asset Management file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45077</link><description>IBM Maximo Asset Management 7.6.1.3 MXAPIASSET API is vulnerable to unrestricted file upload which allows authenticated low privileged user to upload restricted file types with a simple method of adding a dot to the end of the file name if Maximo is installed on Windows operating system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22606 | Coolify Command Injection Vulnerability in Project Name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22606</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. In version 4.0.0-beta.358 and possibly earlier versions, when creating or updating a "project," it is possible to inject arbitrary shell commands by altering the project name. If a name includes unescaped characters, such as single quotes (`'`), it breaks out of the intended command structure, allowing attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host system. This vulnerability allows attackers to execute arbitrary commands on the host server, which could result in full system compromise; create, modify, or delete sensitive system files; and escalate privileges depending on the permissions of the executed process. Attackers with access to project management features could exploit this flaw to gain unauthorized control over the host environment. Version 4.0.0-beta.359 fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0698 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0698</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/sys/menu/list. The manipulation of the argument sort/order leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Continious delivery with rolling releases is used by this product. Therefore, no version details of affected nor updated releases are available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0699 | JoeyBling bootplus list sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0699</link><description>A vulnerability was found in JoeyBling bootplus up to 247d5f6c209be1a5cf10cd0fa18e1d8cc63cf55d. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/sys/role/list. The manipulation of the argument sort leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This product does not use versioning. This is why information about affected and unaffected releases are unavailable.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23991 | WordPress Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.5 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23991</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in theDotstore Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce.This issue affects Product Size Charts Plugin for WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.4.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13698 | Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme &amp;lt;= 4.2.7 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Server-Side Request Forgery, Arbitrary Image Upload, and Image Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13698</link><description>The Jobify - Job Board WordPress Theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'download_image_via_ai' and 'generate_image_via_ai' functions in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.7. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application to upload files in an image format, and to generate AI images using the site's OpenAI key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-25034 | IBM Planning Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-25034</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 and 2.1 could be vulnerable to malicious file upload by not validating the type of file in the File Manager T1 process. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system that can be sent to victims for performing further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40693 | IBM Planning Analytics file upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40693</link><description>IBM Planning Analytics 2.0 and 2.1 could be vulnerable to malicious file upload by not validating the content of the file uploaded to the web interface. Attackers can make use of this weakness and upload malicious executable files into the system, and it can be sent to victim for performing further attacks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40706 | IBM InfoSphere Information Server information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40706</link><description>IBM InfoSphere Information Server 11.7 could allow a remote user to obtain sensitive version information that could aid in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41757 | IBM Concert Software information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41757</link><description>IBM Concert Software 1.0.0 and 1.0.1 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information, caused by the failure to properly enable HTTP Strict Transport Security. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability to obtain sensitive information using man in the middle techniques.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:30:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0697 | Telstra Smart Modem Gen 2 HTTP Header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0697</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Telstra Smart Modem Gen 2 up to 20250115. This affects an unknown part of the component HTTP Header Handler. The manipulation of the argument Content-Disposition leads to injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22605 | Coolify OS Command Injection Vulnerability in SSH Command Generation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22605</link><description>Coolify is an open-source and self-hostable tool for managing servers, applications, and databases. Starting in version 4.0.0-beta.18 and prior to 4.0.0-beta.253, a vulnerability in the execution of commands on remote servers allows an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code on the local Coolify container, gaining access to data and private keys or tokens of other users/teams. The ability to inject malicious commands into the Coolify container gives authenticated attackers the ability to fully retrieve and control the data and availability of the software. Centrally hosted Coolify instances (open registration and/or multiple teams with potentially untrustworthy users) are especially at risk, as sensitive data of all users and connected servers can be leaked by any user. Additionally, attackers are able to modify the running software, potentially deploying malicious images to remote nodes or generally changing its behavior. Version 4.0.0-beta.253 patches this issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9494 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in CP210 VCP Win 2k installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9494</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the 



CP210 VCP Win 2k



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9495 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in CP210x VCP Windows installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9495</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the CP210x VCP Windows 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9496 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress Dev Kit installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9496</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress Dev Kit

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9497 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress 4 SDK installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9497</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress 4 SDK

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9498 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress SDK installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9498</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress SDK

 



 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9499 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in USBXpress Win 98SE Dev Kit installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9499</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the USBXpress Win 98SE Dev Kit installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9492 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Flash Programming Utility installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9492</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Flash Programming Utility installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9493 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in ToolStick installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9493</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in the 

ToolStick

 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9490 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Silicon Labs IDE installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9490</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Silicon Labs (8-bit) IDE installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9491 | Uncontrolled search path can lead to DLL hijacking in Configuration Wizard 2 installer</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9491</link><description>DLL hijacking vulnerabilities, caused by an uncontrolled search path in Configuration Wizard 2 installer can lead to privilege escalation and arbitrary code execution when running the impacted installer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57184 | An issue was discovered in GPAC v0.8.0, as demonstrated by MP4Box. It contains a heap-based buffer overflow in gf_m2ts_process_pmt in media_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57184</link><description>An issue was discovered in GPAC v0.8.0, as demonstrated by MP4Box. It contains a heap-based buffer overflow in gf_m2ts_process_pmt in media_tools/mpegts.c:2163 that can cause a denial of service (DOS) via a crafted MP4 file.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:08:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47090 | GPAC MP4box 2.1-DEV-rev574-g9d5bb184b contains a buffer overflow in gf_vvc_read_pps_bs_internal function of media_tools/av_parsers.c, check ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47090</link><description>GPAC MP4box 2.1-DEV-rev574-g9d5bb184b contains a buffer overflow in gf_vvc_read_pps_bs_internal function of media_tools/av_parsers.c, check needed for num_exp_tile_columns</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10324 | RomethemeKit For Elementor &amp;lt;= 1.5.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Sensitive Information Exposure via Elementor Templates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10324</link><description>The RomethemeKit For Elementor plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Sensitive Information Exposure in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.2 via the register_controls function in widgets/offcanvas-rometheme.php. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to extract sensitive private, pending, and draft template data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11913 | Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Blind Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11913</link><description>The Activity Plus Reloaded for BuddyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Blind Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.1 via the 'ajax_preview_link' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41739 | IBM Cognos Dashboards on Cloud Pak for Data privilege escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41739</link><description>IBM Cognos Dashboards 4.0.7 and 5.0.0 on Cloud Pak for Data could allow a remote attacker to perform unauthorized actions due to dependency confusion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:47:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13335 | Sastra Essential Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons, Widgets and Templates &amp;lt;= 1.0.14 - Missing Authorization to Spexo Theme Install</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13335</link><description>The Spexo Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons, Widgets and Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the tmpcoder_theme_install_func() function in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.14. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to install a theme.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13354 | Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13354</link><description>The Responsive Addons for Elementor – Free Elementor Addons Plugin and Elementor Templates plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via HTML tags in several widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13408 | Post Grid, Slider &amp;amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor Widget &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13408</link><description>The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.10 via the 'theme' attribute of the `pgcu` shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where php files can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13409 | Post Grid, Slider &amp;amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp;amp; Elementor Widget &amp;lt;= 1.6.10 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion via post_type_ajax_handler()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13409</link><description>The Post Grid, Slider &amp; Carousel Ultimate – with Shortcode, Gutenberg Block &amp; Elementor Widget plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.10 via the 'theme' parameter of the post_type_ajax_handler() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13542 | WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp;amp; Google maps + Local SEO &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13542</link><description>The WP Google Street View (with 360° virtual tour) &amp; Google maps + Local SEO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpgsv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.1.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13572 | Precious Metals Charts and Widgets for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13572</link><description>The Precious Metals Charts and Widgets for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'nfusion-widget' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13594 | Simple Downloads List &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13594</link><description>The Simple Downloads List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'category' attribute of the 'neofix_sdl' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:13:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22714 | WordPress MDJM Event Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.5.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22714</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in MDJM MDJM Event Management allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MDJM Event Management: from n/a through 1.7.5.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23422 | WordPress Store Locator plugin &amp;lt;= 3.98.10 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23422</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound Store Locator allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Store Locator: from n/a through 3.98.10.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23427 | WordPress Redux Converter plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23427</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dovy Paukstys Redux Converter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Redux Converter: from n/a through 1.1.3.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23522 | WordPress HM Portfolio plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23522</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in humanmade limited, Joe Hoyle, Tom Wilmott, Matthew Haines-Young HM Portfolio allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects HM Portfolio: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23621 | WordPress Causes – Donation plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.01 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23621</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Causes – Donation Plugin allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Causes – Donation Plugin: from n/a through 1.0.01.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23622 | WordPress CBX Accounting &amp;amp; Bookkeeping plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.14 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23622</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound CBX Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CBX Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping: from n/a through 1.3.14.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23711 | WordPress Quote me plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23711</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Quote me allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Quote me: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23734 | WordPress Gigaom Sphinx plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23734</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Gigaom Sphinx allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Gigaom Sphinx: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23737 | WordPress Network-Favorites plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23737</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Network-Favorites allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Network-Favorites: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23837 | WordPress One Backend Language Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23837</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound One Backend Language allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects One Backend Language: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23838 | WordPress Bauernregeln Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23838</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Bauernregeln allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bauernregeln: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23839 | WordPress Sticky Button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23839</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Sticky Button allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Sticky Button: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23885 | WordPress MJ Contact us Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23885</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MJ Contact us allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MJ Contact us: from n/a through 5.2.3.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23888 | WordPress Custom Page Extensions Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.6 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23888</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Custom Page Extensions allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Page Extensions: from n/a through 0.6.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23889 | WordPress FooGallery Captions Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23889</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FooGallery Captions allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FooGallery Captions: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 10:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12494 | BMLT Meeting Map &amp;lt;= 2.6.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12494</link><description>The BMLT Meeting Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bmlt_meeting_map' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13583 | Simple Gallery with Filter &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13583</link><description>The Simple Gallery with Filter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'c2tw_sgwf' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 09:31:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13545 | Bootstrap Ultimate &amp;lt;= 1.4.9 - Unauthenticated Limited Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13545</link><description>The Bootstrap Ultimate theme for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 1.4.9 via the path parameter. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to include PHP files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where PHP files can be uploaded and included. If php://filter is enabled on the server, this issue may directly lead to Remote Code Execution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 08:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13680 | Form Builder CP &amp;lt;= 1.2.41 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13680</link><description>The Form Builder CP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'id' parameter of the 'CP_EASY_FORM_WILL_APPEAR_HERE' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.41 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13683 | Automate Hub Free by Sperse.IO &amp;lt;= 1.7.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Activation Status Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13683</link><description>The Automate Hub Free by Sperse.IO plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.7.0. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'automate_hub' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update an activation status via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 07:12:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13659 | Listamester &amp;lt;= 2.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13659</link><description>The Listamester plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'listamester' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11931 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11931</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 17.0 prior to 17.6.4, from 17.7 prior to 17.7.3, and from 17.8 prior to 17.8.1. Under certain conditions, it may have been possible for users with developer role to exfiltrate protected CI variables via CI lint.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0314 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0314</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.2 before 17.6.4, 17.7 before 17.7.3, and 17.8 before 17.8.1. Improper rendering of certain file types lead to cross-site scripting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 02:51:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-42718 | Sensitive data unnecessarily returned from authenticated API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-42718</link><description>Information Disclosure in API in Replicated Replicated Classic versions prior to 2.53.1 on all platforms allows authenticated users with Admin Console access to retrieve sensitive data, including application secrets, via accessing container definitions with environment variables through the Admin Console API on port 8800.

This CVE was originally reserved in 2021 and later publicly disclosed by Replicated on their website on 21 October 2021. However, it mistakenly remained in the Reserved But Public (RBP) status with the CVE Numbering Authority (CNA). Please note that this product reached its end of life on 31 December 2024. Publishing this CVE with the CNA was required to comply with CNA rules, despite the fact that the issue was disclosed and fixed four years ago, and the affected product is no longer supported as of 2024.

Summary of VulnerabilityThis advisory discloses a low severity security vulnerability in the versions of Replicated Classic listed above (“Affected Replicated Classic Versions”)

DescriptionReplicated Classic versions prior to 2.53.1 have an authenticated API from the Replicated Admin Console that may expose sensitive data including application secrets, depending on how the application manifests are written. A user with valid credentials and access to the Admin Console port (8800) on the Replicated Classic server can retrieve container definitions including environment variables which may contain passwords and other secrets depending on how the application is configured.

This data is shared over authenticated sessions to the Admin Console only, and was never displayed or used in the application processing. To remediate this issue, we removed the sensitive data from the API, sending only the data to the Admin Console that was needed.

TimelineThis issue was discovered during a security review on 16 September 2021.
Patched versions were released on 23 September 2021.
This advisory was published on 21 October 2021.


The CVE Numbering Authority (CNA) notified Replicated on 23 January 2025 that the CVE was still in Reserved But Public (RBP) status. Upon discovering the oversight in updating the status to published with the CNA, Replicated submitted the updated report on the same day, 23 January 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:51:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53379 | Heap buffer overflow in the server site handshake implementation in Real Time Logic LLC's SharkSSL version (from 05/05/24) commit 64808a5e12...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53379</link><description>Heap buffer overflow in the server site handshake implementation in Real Time Logic LLC's SharkSSL version (from 05/05/24) commit 64808a5e12c83b38f85c943dee0112e428dc2a43 allows a remote attacker to trigger a Denial-of-Service via a malformed Client-Hello message.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55573 | An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-web 24.10.x before 24.10.3, 24.04.x before 24.04.9, 23.10.x before 23.10.19, 23.04.x before 23....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55573</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon centreon-web 24.10.x before 24.10.3, 24.04.x before 24.04.9, 23.10.x before 23.10.19, 23.04.x before 23.04.24. A user with high privileges is able to inject SQL into the form used to create virtual metrics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46400 | KWHotel 0.47 is vulnerable to CSV Formula Injection in the add guest function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46400</link><description>KWHotel 0.47 is vulnerable to CSV Formula Injection in the add guest function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46401 | KWHotel 0.47 is vulnerable to CSV Formula Injection in the invoice adding function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46401</link><description>KWHotel 0.47 is vulnerable to CSV Formula Injection in the invoice adding function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50664 | gpac 2.4 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at isomedia/sample_descs.c:1799 in gf_isom_new_mpha_description in gpac/MP4Box.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50664</link><description>gpac 2.4 contains a heap-buffer-overflow at isomedia/sample_descs.c:1799 in gf_isom_new_mpha_description in gpac/MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-50665 | gpac 2.4 contains a SEGV at src/isomedia/drm_sample.c:1562:96 in isom_cenc_get_sai_by_saiz_saio in MP4Box.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-50665</link><description>gpac 2.4 contains a SEGV at src/isomedia/drm_sample.c:1562:96 in isom_cenc_get_sai_by_saiz_saio in MP4Box.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53923 | An issue was discovered in Centreon Web 24.10.x before 24.10.3, 24.04.x before 24.04.9, 23.10.x before 23.10.19, 23.04.x before 23.04.24. A ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53923</link><description>An issue was discovered in Centreon Web 24.10.x before 24.10.3, 24.04.x before 24.04.9, 23.10.x before 23.10.19, 23.04.x before 23.04.24. A user with high privileges is able to achieve SQL injection in the form to upload media.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55194 | OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component /OpenImageIO/fmath.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55194</link><description>OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component /OpenImageIO/fmath.h.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55195 | An allocation-size-too-big bug in the component /imagebuf.cpp of OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev may cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when the progra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55195</link><description>An allocation-size-too-big bug in the component /imagebuf.cpp of OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev may cause a Denial of Service (DoS) when the program to requests to allocate too much space.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:28:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55192 | OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component OpenImageIO_v3_1_0::farmhash::inlined::Fetch64(char cons...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55192</link><description>OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a heap overflow via the component OpenImageIO_v3_1_0::farmhash::inlined::Fetch64(char const*).</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55193 | OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component /OpenImageIO/string_view.h.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55193</link><description>OpenImageIO v3.1.0.0dev was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component /OpenImageIO/string_view.h.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57556 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in nbubna store v.2.14.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the store.deep...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57556</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in nbubna store v.2.14.2 and before allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the store.deep.js component</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:09:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57328 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login form of Online Food Ordering System v1.0. The vulnerability arises because the input field...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57328</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in the login form of Online Food Ordering System v1.0. The vulnerability arises because the input fields username and password are not properly sanitized, allowing attackers to inject malicious SQL queries to bypass authentication and gain unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57329 | HortusFox v3.9 contains a stored XSS vulnerability in the "Add Plant" function. The name input field does not sanitize or escape user inputs...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57329</link><description>HortusFox v3.9 contains a stored XSS vulnerability in the "Add Plant" function. The name input field does not sanitize or escape user inputs, allowing attackers to inject and execute arbitrary JavaScript payloads.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53588 | A DLL hijacking vulnerability in iTop VPN v16.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via placing a crafted DLL file into the path \Pro...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53588</link><description>A DLL hijacking vulnerability in iTop VPN v16.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via placing a crafted DLL file into the path \ProgramData\iTop VPN\Downloader\vpn6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57326 | A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the search.php file of the Online Pizza Delivery System 1.0. The vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57326</link><description>A Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the search.php file of the Online Pizza Delivery System 1.0. The vulnerability allows an attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code in the browser via unsanitized input passed through the search parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:41:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57386 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Wallos v.2.41.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the profile picture function.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57386</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Wallos v.2.41.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the profile picture function.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0693 | Issue with AWS Sign-in IAM User Login Flow - Possible Username Enumeration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0693</link><description>Variable response times in the AWS Sign-in IAM user login flow allowed for the use of brute force enumeration techniques to identify valid IAM usernames in an arbitrary AWS account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 21:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23011 | Fedora Repository archive extraction path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23011</link><description>Fedora Repository 3.8.1 allows path traversal when extracting uploaded archives ("Zip Slip"). A remote, authenticated attacker can upload a specially crafted archive that will extract an arbitrary JSP file to a location that can be executed by an unauthenticated GET request. Fedora Repository 3.8.1 was released on 2015-06-11 and is no longer maintained. Migrate to a currently supported version (6.5.1 as of 2025-01-23).</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23012 | Fedora Repository fedoraIntCallUser default credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23012</link><description>Fedora Repository 3.8.x includes a service account (fedoraIntCallUser) with default credentials and privileges to read read local files by manipulating datastreams. Fedora Repository 3.8.1 was released on 2015-06-11 and is no longer maintained. Migrate to a currently supported version (6.5.1 as of 2025-01-23).</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24353 | Directus privilege escalation vulnerability using Share feature</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24353</link><description>Directus is a real-time API and App dashboard for managing SQL database content. Prior to version 11.2.0, when sharing an item, a typical user can specify an arbitrary role. It allows the user to use a higher-privileged role to see fields that otherwise the user should not be able to see. Instances that are impacted are those that use the share feature and have specific roles hierarchy and fields that are not visible for certain roles. Version 11.2.0 contains a patch the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55930 | Weak default folder permissions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55930</link><description>Weak default folder permissions</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24033 | @fastify/multipart vulnerable to unlimited consumption of resources</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24033</link><description>@fastify/multipart is a Fastify plugin for parsing the multipart content-type. Prior to versions 8.3.1 and 9.0.3, the `saveRequestFiles` function does not delete the uploaded temporary files when user cancels the request. The issue is fixed in versions 8.3.1 and 9.0.3. As a workaround, do not use `saveRequestFiles`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24034 | Himmelblau leaks credentials in the debug log</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24034</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. Starting in version 0.7.0 and prior to versions 0.7.15 and 0.8.3, Himmelblau is vulnerable to leaking credentials in debug logs. When debug logging is enabled, user access tokens are inadvertently logged, potentially exposing sensitive authentication data. Similarly, Kerberos Ticket-Granting Tickets (TGTs) are logged when debug logging is enabled. Both issues pose a risk of exposing sensitive credentials, particularly in environments where debug logging is enabled. Himmelblau versions 0.7.15 and 0.8.3 contain a patch that fixes both issues. Some workarounds are available for users who are unable to upgrade. For the **logon compliance script issue**, disable the `logon_script` option in `/etc/himmelblau/himmelblau.conf`, and avoid using the `-d` flag when starting the `himmelblaud` daemon. For the Kerberos CCache issue, one may disable debug logging globally by setting the `debug` option in `/etc/himmelblau/himmelblau.conf` to `false` and avoiding the `-d` parameter when starting `himmelblaud`.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-45672 | IBM Security Verify Bridge data manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-45672</link><description>IBM Security Verify Bridge 1.0.0 through 1.0.15 could allow a local privileged user to overwrite files due to excessive privileges granted to the agent. which could also cause a denial of service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:38:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55929 | Mail spoofing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55929</link><description>Mail spoofing</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22153 | try/except* clauses could allow bypass RestrictedPython via type confusion bug in the CPython interpreter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22153</link><description>RestrictedPython is a tool that helps to define a subset of the Python language which allows to provide a program input into a trusted environment. Via a type confusion bug in versions of the CPython interpreter starting in 3.11 and prior to 3.13.2 when using `try/except*`, RestrictedPython starting in version 6.0 and prior to version 8.0 could be bypassed. The issue is patched in version 8.0 of RestrictedPython by removing support for `try/except*` clauses. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55927 | Flawed token generation implementation &amp;amp; Hard-coded key implementation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55927</link><description>Flawed token generation implementation &amp; Hard-coded key implementation</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55928 | Clear text secrets returned &amp;amp; Remote system secrets in clear text</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55928</link><description>Clear text secrets returned &amp; Remote system secrets in clear text</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:29:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23227 | IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23227</link><description>IBM Tivoli Application Dependency Discovery Manager 7.3.0.0 through 7.3.0.11 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55926 | Arbitrary file upload, deletion and read through header manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55926</link><description>Arbitrary file upload, deletion and read through header manipulation</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:29:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55925 | API Security bypass through header manipulation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55925</link><description>API Security bypass through header manipulation</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11147 | ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums deterministic root password</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11147</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums use a deterministic root password generated based on model and serial number. An attacker with shell access can login as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12078 | ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums static BLE GATT encryption key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12078</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawn mowers and vacuums use a shared, static secret key to encrypt BLE GATT messages. An unauthenticated attacker within BLE range can control any robot using the same key.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12079 | ECOVACS lawnmowers cleartext storage of anti-theft PIN</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12079</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawnmowers store the anti-theft PIN in cleartext on the device filesystem. An attacker can steal a lawnmower, read the PIN, and reset the anti-theft mechanism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52327 | ECOVACS lawnmower and vacuum cloud service live video PIN bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52327</link><description>The cloud service used by ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums allows authenticated attackers to bypass the PIN entry required to access the live video feed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52328 | ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums insecurely store audio warning files</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52328</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums insecurely store audio files used to indicate that the camera is on. An attacker with access to the /data filesystem can delete or modify warning files such that users may not be aware that the camera is on.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52329 | ECOVACS HOME mobile app plugins do not properly validate TLS certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52329</link><description>ECOVACS HOME mobile app plugins for specific robots do not properly validate TLS certificates. An unauthenticated attacker can read or modify TLS traffic and obtain authentication tokens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52330 | ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums do not properly validate TLS certificates</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52330</link><description>ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums do not properly validate TLS certificates. An unauthenticated attacker can read or modify TLS traffic, possibly modifying firmware updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52331 | ECOVACS lawnmowers and vacuums deterministic firmware encryption key</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52331</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums use a deterministic symmetric key to decrypt firmware updates. An attacker can create and encrypt malicious firmware that will be successfully decrypted and installed by the robot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0650 | Ovn: egress acls may be bypassed via specially crafted udp packet</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0650</link><description>A flaw was found in the Open Virtual Network (OVN). Specially crafted UDP packets may bypass egress access control lists (ACLs) in OVN installations configured with a logical switch with DNS records set on it and if the same switch has any egress ACLs configured. This issue can lead to unauthorized access to virtual machines and containers running on the OVN network.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52325 | ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52325</link><description>ECOVACS robot lawnmowers and vacuums are vulnerable to command injection via SetNetPin() over an unauthenticated BLE connection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:22:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22264 | WordPress WP Query Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22264</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tarak Patel WP Query Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Query Creator: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22768 | WordPress Rocket Media Library Mime Type plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - CSRF to Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22768</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Qwerty23 Rocket Media Library Mime Type allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Rocket Media Library Mime Type: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23541 | WordPress Download, Downloads plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23541</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in edmon Download, Downloads  allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Download, Downloads : from n/a through 1.4.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23544 | WordPress StatPressCN plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23544</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in heart5 StatPressCN allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects StatPressCN: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23545 | WordPress WP Social Broadcast plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23545</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Navnish Bhardwaj WP Social Broadcast allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Social Broadcast: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23624 | WordPress WpDevTool plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23624</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Alessandro Benoit WpDevTool allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WpDevTool: from n/a through 0.1.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23626 | WordPress Kumihimo plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23626</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Hidetoshi Fukushima Kumihimo allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Kumihimo: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23628 | WordPress GeoDigs plugin &amp;lt;= 3.4.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23628</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in New Media One GeoDigs allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects GeoDigs: from n/a through 3.4.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23629 | WordPress Gallerio plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23629</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Subhasis Laha Gallerio allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Gallerio: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23634 | WordPress Youtube Video Grid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23634</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Youtube Video Grid allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Youtube Video Grid: from n/a through 1.9.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23636 | WordPress My Favorite Car plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23636</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dimitar Atanasov My Favorite Car allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects My Favorite Car: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23722 | WordPress Mind3doM RyeBread Widgets plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23722</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Mind3doM RyeBread Widgets allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Mind3doM RyeBread Widgets: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23723 | WordPress Plestar Directory Listing plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23723</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Plestar Inc Plestar Directory Listing allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Plestar Directory Listing: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23724 | WordPress University Quizzes Online plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23724</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Oleksandr Ustymenko University Quizzes Online allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects University Quizzes Online: from n/a through 1.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23725 | WordPress Accessibility Task Manager plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23725</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in TaskMeister Accessibility Task Manager allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Accessibility Task Manager: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23727 | WordPress AZ Content Finder plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23727</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound AZ Content Finder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects AZ Content Finder: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23729 | WordPress XTRA Settings plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.8 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23729</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in fures XTRA Settings allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects XTRA Settings: from n/a through 2.1.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23730 | WordPress FLX Dashboard Groups plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23730</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FLX Dashboard Groups allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FLX Dashboard Groups: from n/a through 0.0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23733 | WordPress SC Simple Zazzle plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23733</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in sayocode SC Simple Zazzle allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects SC Simple Zazzle: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23834 | WordPress Links/Problem Reporter plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23834</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Links/Problem Reporter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Links/Problem Reporter: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23835 | WordPress Legal + Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23835</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Legal + allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Legal +: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23836 | WordPress Custom Coming Soon Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23836</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in SuryaBhan Custom Coming Soon allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom Coming Soon: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23894 | WordPress wp-flickr-press Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23894</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Tatsuya Fukata, Alexander Ovsov wp-flickr-press allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects wp-flickr-press: from n/a through 2.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23960 | WordPress Save &amp;amp; Import Image from URL Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23960</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in basteln3rk Save &amp; Import Image from URL allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Save &amp; Import Image from URL: from n/a through 0.7.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10846 | Excessive Platform Resource Consumption within a Loop when unmarshalling Compose file having recursive loop</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10846</link><description>The compose-go library component in versions v2.10-v2.4.0 allows an authorized user who sends malicious YAML payloads to cause the compose-go to consume excessive amount of Memory and CPU cycles while parsing YAML, such as used by Docker Compose from versions  v2.27.0 to v2.29.7 included</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55971 | SQL Injection vulnerability in the default configuration of the Logitime WebClock application &lt;= 5.43.0 allows an unauthenticated user to ru...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55971</link><description>SQL Injection vulnerability in the default configuration of the Logitime WebClock application &lt;= 5.43.0 allows an unauthenticated user to run arbitrary code on the backend database server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0637 | Inadequate access control in Beta10</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0637</link><description>It has been found that the Beta10 software does not provide for proper authorisation control in multiple areas of the application. This deficiency could allow a malicious actor, without authentication, to access private areas and/or areas intended for other roles. The vulnerability has been identified at least in the file or path ‘/app/tools.html’.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23540 | WordPress WP Front-end login and register plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23540</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Mohsin khan WP Front-end login and register allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Front-end login and register: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:38:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57947 | netfilter: nf_set_pipapo: fix initial map fill</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57947</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

netfilter: nf_set_pipapo: fix initial map fill

The initial buffer has to be inited to all-ones, but it must restrict
it to the size of the first field, not the total field size.

After each round in the map search step, the result and the fill map
are swapped, so if we have a set where f-&gt;bsize of the first element
is smaller than m-&gt;bsize_max, those one-bits are leaked into future
rounds result map.

This makes pipapo find an incorrect matching results for sets where
first field size is not the largest.

Followup patch adds a test case to nft_concat_range.sh selftest script.

Thanks to Stefano Brivio for pointing out that we need to zero out
the remainder explicitly, only correcting memset() argument isn't enough.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:13:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10539 | Reflected XSS in Uyumsoft&amp;#x27;s ERP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10539</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Uyumsoft Informatin Systems Uyumsoft ERP allows XSS Using Invalid Characters, Reflected XSS.This issue affects Uyumsoft ERP: before Erp4.2109.166p45.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 13:36:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23006 | Pre-authentication deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Management Console (AMC) and...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23006</link><description>Pre-authentication deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability has been identified in the SMA1000 Appliance Management Console (AMC) and Central Management Console (CMC), which in specific conditions could potentially enable a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary OS commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:45:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12118 | The Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 6.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12118</link><description>The The Events Calendar plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Event Calendar Link Widget through the html_tag attribute in all versions up to, and including, 6.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12504 | Broadcast Live Video – Live Streaming : HTML5, WebRTC, HLS, RTSP, RTMP &amp;lt;= 6.1.9 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12504</link><description>The Broadcast Live Video – Live Streaming : HTML5, WebRTC, HLS, RTSP, RTMP plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_hls' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 6.1.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13236 | Tainacan &amp;lt;= 0.21.12 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13236</link><description>The Tainacan plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'collection_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.21.12 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13340 | MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter &amp;lt;= 1.3.3.6 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13340</link><description>The MDTF – Meta Data and Taxonomies Filter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'mdf_results_by_ajax' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.3.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13389 | Cliptakes &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13389</link><description>The Cliptakes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'cliptakes_input_email' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13422 | SEO Blogger to WordPress Migration using 301 Redirection &amp;lt;= 0.4.8 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13422</link><description>The SEO Blogger to WordPress Migration using 301 Redirection plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'url' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 0.4.8 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12043 | Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Ecommerce Slider) &amp;lt;= 3.16.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12043</link><description>The Prime Slider – Addons For Elementor (Revolution of a slider, Hero Slider, Post Slider and Ecommerce Slider) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'social_link_title' parameter of the 'blog' widget in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13234 | Product Table by WBW &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Unuthenticated SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13234</link><description>The Product Table by WBW plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'additionalCondition' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0619 | Unsafe stored password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0619</link><description>Unsafe password recovery from configuration in M-Files Server before 25.1 allows a highly privileged user to recover external connector passwords</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0635 | Denial of Service condition in M-Files Server</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0635</link><description>Denial of service condition in M-Files Server in versions before 

25.1.14445.5 allows an unauthenticated user to consume computing resources in certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0648 | M-Files Server crash via EOT database driver configuration</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0648</link><description>Unexpected server crash in database driver in M-Files Server before 25.1.14445.5 allows a highly privileged attacker to cause denial of service via configuration change.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:24:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43708 | An allocation of resources without limits or throttling in Kibana can lead to a crash caused by a specially crafted payload to a number of i...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43708</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling in Kibana can lead to a crash caused by a specially crafted payload to a number of inputs in Kibana UI. This can be carried out by users with read access to any feature in Kibana.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 10:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12957 | A file handling command vulnerability in certain versions of Armoury Crate may result in arbitrary file deletion.
Refer to the '01/23/2025 S...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12957</link><description>A file handling command vulnerability in certain versions of Armoury Crate may result in arbitrary file deletion.
Refer to the '01/23/2025 Security Update for Armoury Crate App' section on the ASUS Security Advisory for more information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:47:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13511 | Variation Swatches for WooCommerce 1.0.8 - 1.3.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Plugin Settings Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13511</link><description>The Variation Swatches for WooCommerce plugin, in all versions starting at 1.0.8 up until 1.3.2, contains a vulnerability due to improper nonce verification in its settings reset functionality. The issue exists in the settings_init() function, which processes a reset action based on specific query parameters in the URL. The related delete_settings() function performs a faulty nonce validation check, making the reset operation insecure and susceptible to unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:31:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13593 | BMLT Meeting Map &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Local File Inclusion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13593</link><description>The BMLT Meeting Map plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Local File Inclusion in all versions up to, and including, 2.6.0 via the 'bmlt_meeting_map' shortcode. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to include and execute arbitrary files on the server, allowing the execution of any PHP code in those files. This can be used to bypass access controls, obtain sensitive data, or achieve code execution in cases where images and other “safe” file types can be uploaded and included.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 09:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53299 | Apache Wicket: An attacker can intentionally trigger a memory leak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53299</link><description>The request handling in the core in Apache Wicket 7.0.0 on any platform allows an attacker to create a DOS via multiple requests to server resources.
Users are recommended to upgrade to versions 9.19.0 or 10.3.0, which fixes this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 08:44:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52975 | Fleet Server sensitive information exposure via logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52975</link><description>An issue was identified in Fleet Server where Fleet policies that could contain sensitive information were logged on INFO and ERROR log levels. The nature of the sensitive information largely depends on the integrations enabled.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 07:34:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-52972 | Kibana allocation of resources without limits or throttling leads to crash</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-52972</link><description>An allocation of resources without limits or throttling in Kibana can lead to a crash caused by a specially crafted request to /api/metrics/snapshot. This can be carried out by users with read access to the Observability Metrics or Logs features in Kibana.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43707 | Kibana exposure of sensitive information to an unauthorized actor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43707</link><description>An issue was identified in Kibana where a user without access to Fleet can view Elastic Agent policies that could contain sensitive information. The nature of the sensitive information depends on the integrations enabled for the Elastic Agent and their respective versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:24:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-43710 | Kibana server-side request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-43710</link><description>A server side request forgery vulnerability was identified in Kibana where the /api/fleet/health_check API could be used to send requests to internal endpoints. Due to the nature of the underlying request, only endpoints available over https that return JSON could be accessed. This can be carried out by users with read access to Fleet.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 06:24:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24529 | An issue was discovered in phpMyAdmin 5.x before 5.2.2. An XSS vulnerability has been discovered for the Insert tab.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24529</link><description>An issue was discovered in phpMyAdmin 5.x before 5.2.2. An XSS vulnerability has been discovered for the Insert tab.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24530 | An issue was discovered in phpMyAdmin 5.x before 5.2.2. An XSS vulnerability has been discovered for the check tables feature. A crafted tab...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24530</link><description>An issue was discovered in phpMyAdmin 5.x before 5.2.2. An XSS vulnerability has been discovered for the check tables feature. A crafted table or database name could be used for XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 05:38:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24030 | Envoy Admin Interface Exposed through prometheus metrics endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24030</link><description>Envoy Gateway is an open source project for managing Envoy Proxy as a standalone or Kubernetes-based application gateway. A user with access to the Kubernetes cluster can use a path traversal attack to execute Envoy Admin interface commands on proxies managed by any version of Envoy Gateway prior to 1.2.6. The admin interface can be used to terminate the Envoy process and extract the Envoy configuration (possibly containing confidential data). Version 1.2.6 fixes the issue. As a workaround, the `EnvoyProxy` API can be used to apply a bootstrap config patch that restricts access strictly to the prometheus stats endpoint. Find below an example of such a bootstrap patch.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 03:29:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42186 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an insecure protocol support</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42186</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an insecure protocol support.  The application can allow improper handling of SSL certificates validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 03:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42187 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by path traversal vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42187</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by path traversal vulnerability.  The application could allow operators to download files from a local repository which is vulnerable to path traversal attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 03:09:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32340 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32340</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-50309 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-50309</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 is vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows users to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42184 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by insecure support for file URI scheme</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42184</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by insecure support for file URI scheme.  It could allow a malicious operator to attempt to download files using the file:// URI scheme.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42185 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an insecure package which is susceptible to XML injection attacks</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42185</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an insecure package which is susceptible to XML injection attacks.  This allows an attacker to exploit this vulnerability by injecting malicious XML content, which can lead to various issues including denial of service and unauthorized access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42183 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an arbitrary file download vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42183</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by an arbitrary file download vulnerability.  It could allow a malicious operator to download files from arbitrary URLs without any proper validation or allowlist controls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:14:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42182 | HCL BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42182</link><description>BigFix Patch Download Plug-ins are affected by Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerability.  It may allow the application to download files from an internally hosted server on localhost.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 02:14:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57719 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component blend_transformed_tiled_argb.isra.0.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57719</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component blend_transformed_tiled_argb.isra.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57720 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component plutovg_blend.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57720</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component plutovg_blend.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57721 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component plutovg_path_add_path.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57721</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component plutovg_path_add_path.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57722 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a allocation-size-too-big bug via the component plutovg_surface_create.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57722</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a allocation-size-too-big bug via the component plutovg_surface_create.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57723 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component composition_source_over.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57723</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component composition_source_over.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-57724 | lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_record_cell.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-57724</link><description>lunasvg v3.0.0 was discovered to contain a segmentation violation via the component gray_record_cell.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 01:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12477 | Avada Builder &amp;lt;= 3.11.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting in Multiple Widgets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12477</link><description>The Avada Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcodes in all versions up to, and including, 3.11.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56923 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the Categorization Option of My Subscriptions Functionality in Silverpeas Core 6.4.1 allows a remote at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56923</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in the Categorization Option of My Subscriptions Functionality in Silverpeas Core 6.4.1 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary JavaScript code. This is achieved by injecting a malicious payload into the Name field of a subscription. The attack can lead to session hijacking, data theft, or unauthorized actions when an admin user views the affected subscription.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 20:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56924 | A Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Code Astro Internet banking system 2.0.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary J...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56924</link><description>A Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Code Astro Internet banking system 2.0.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript on the admin page (pages_account), potentially leading to unauthorized actions such as changing account settings or stealing sensitive user information. This vulnerability occurs due to improper validation of user requests, which enables attackers to exploit the system by tricking the admin user into executing malicious scripts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 20:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56914 | D-Link DSL-3782 v1.01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in /New_GUI/ParentalControl.asp.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56914</link><description>D-Link DSL-3782 v1.01 is vulnerable to Buffer Overflow in /New_GUI/ParentalControl.asp.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:58:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0611 | Object corruption in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0611</link><description>Object corruption in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0612 | Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0612</link><description>Out of bounds memory access in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 132.0.6834.110 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:29:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11166 | Traffic Alert and Collision Avoidance System (TCAS) II has an External Control of System or Configuration Setting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11166</link><description>For TCAS II systems using transponders compliant with MOPS earlier than RTCA DO-181F, an attacker can impersonate a ground station and issue a Comm-A Identity Request. This action can set the Sensitivity Level Control (SLC) to the lowest setting and disable the Resolution Advisory (RA), leading to a denial-of-service condition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 18:44:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-9310 | Traffic Alert and Collision Avoidance System (TCAS) II has a Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-9310</link><description>By utilizing software-defined radios and a custom low-latency processing pipeline, RF signals with spoofed location data can be transmitted to aircraft targets. This can lead to the appearance of fake aircraft on displays and potentially trigger undesired Resolution Advisories (RAs).</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 18:44:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0651 | File symlink abuse might lead to deleting files belonging to SYSTEM user</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0651</link><description>Improper Privilege Management vulnerability in Cloudflare WARP on Windows allows File Manipulation.

User with a low system privileges  can create a set of symlinks inside the C:\ProgramData\Cloudflare\warp-diag-partials folder. After triggering the 'Reset all settings" option the WARP service will delete the files that the symlink was pointing to. Given the WARP service operates with System privileges this might lead to deleting files owned by the System user.
This issue affects WARP: before 2024.12.492.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23047 | Cilium vulnerable to information leakage via insecure default Hubble UI CORS header</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23047</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. An insecure default `Access-Control-Allow-Origin` header value could lead to sensitive data exposure for users of Cilium versions 1.14.0 through 1.14.7, 1.15.0 through 1.15.11, and 1.16.0 through 1.16.4 who deploy Hubble UI using either Cilium CLI or via the Cilium Helm chart. A user with access to a Hubble UI instance affected by this issue could leak configuration details about the Kubernetes cluster which Hubble UI is monitoring, including node names, IP addresses, and other metadata about workloads and the cluster networking configuration. In order for this vulnerability to be exploited, a victim would have to first visit a malicious page. This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.14.18, v1.15.12, and v1.16.5. As a workaround, users who deploy Hubble UI using the Cilium Helm chart directly can remove the CORS headers from the Helm template as shown in the patch from commit a3489f190ba6e87b5336ee685fb6c80b1270d06d.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:31:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55957 | In Thermo Fisher Scientific Xcalibur before 4.7 SP1 and Thermo Foundation Instrument Control Software (ICSW) before 3.1 SP10, the driver pac...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55957</link><description>In Thermo Fisher Scientific Xcalibur before 4.7 SP1 and Thermo Foundation Instrument Control Software (ICSW) before 3.1 SP10, the driver packages have a local privilege escalation vulnerability due to improper access control permissions on Windows systems.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:31:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24397 | An incorrect permission check in Jenkins GitLab Plugin 1.9.6 and earlier allows attackers with global Item/Configure permission (while lacki...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24397</link><description>An incorrect permission check in Jenkins GitLab Plugin 1.9.6 and earlier allows attackers with global Item/Configure permission (while lacking Item/Configure permission on any particular job) to enumerate credential IDs of GitLab API token and Secret text credentials stored in Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24398 | Jenkins Bitbucket Server Integration Plugin 2.1.0 through 4.1.3 (both inclusive) allows attackers to craft URLs that would bypass the CSRF p...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24398</link><description>Jenkins Bitbucket Server Integration Plugin 2.1.0 through 4.1.3 (both inclusive) allows attackers to craft URLs that would bypass the CSRF protection of any target URL in Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24399 | Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.452.v2849b_d3945fa_ and earlier, except 4.438.440.v3f5f201de5dc, treats usernames as case-ins...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24399</link><description>Jenkins OpenId Connect Authentication Plugin 4.452.v2849b_d3945fa_ and earlier, except 4.438.440.v3f5f201de5dc, treats usernames as case-insensitive, allowing attackers on Jenkins instances configured with a case-sensitive OpenID Connect provider to log in as any user by providing a username that differs only in letter case, potentially gaining administrator access to Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24400 | Jenkins Eiffel Broadcaster Plugin 2.8.0 through 2.10.2 (both inclusive) uses the credential ID as the cache key during signing operations, a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24400</link><description>Jenkins Eiffel Broadcaster Plugin 2.8.0 through 2.10.2 (both inclusive) uses the credential ID as the cache key during signing operations, allowing attackers able to create a credential with the same ID as a legitimate one in a different credentials store to sign an event published to RabbitMQ with the legitimate credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24401 | Jenkins Folder-based Authorization Strategy Plugin 217.vd5b_18537403e and earlier does not verify that permissions configured to be granted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24401</link><description>Jenkins Folder-based Authorization Strategy Plugin 217.vd5b_18537403e and earlier does not verify that permissions configured to be granted are enabled, potentially allowing users formerly granted (typically optional permissions, like Overall/Manage) to access functionality they're no longer entitled to.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24402 | A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins Azure Service Fabric Plugin 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to connect to a Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24402</link><description>A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Jenkins Azure Service Fabric Plugin 1.6 and earlier allows attackers to connect to a Service Fabric URL using attacker-specified credentials IDs obtained through another method.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24403 | A missing permission check in Jenkins Azure Service Fabric Plugin 1.6 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to enumerate...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24403</link><description>A missing permission check in Jenkins Azure Service Fabric Plugin 1.6 and earlier allows attackers with Overall/Read permission to enumerate credentials IDs of Azure credentials stored in Jenkins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23028 | DoS in Cilium agent DNS proxy from crafted DNS responses</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23028</link><description>Cilium is a networking, observability, and security solution with an eBPF-based dataplane. A denial of service vulnerability affects versions 1.14.0 through 1.14.7, 1.15.0 through 1.15.11, and 1.16.0 through 1.16.4. In a Kubernetes cluster where Cilium is configured to proxy DNS traffic, an attacker can crash Cilium agents by sending a crafted DNS response to workloads from outside the cluster. For traffic that is allowed but without using DNS-based policy, the dataplane will continue to pass traffic as configured at the time of the DoS. For workloads that have DNS-based policy configured, existing connections may continue to operate, and new connections made without relying on DNS resolution may continue to be established, but new connections which rely on DNS resolution may be disrupted. Any configuration changes that affect the impacted agent may not be applied until the agent is able to restart. This issue is fixed in Cilium v1.14.18, v1.15.12, and v1.16.5. No known workarounds are available.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-51457 | IBM Robotic Process Automation for Cloud Pak cross-site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-51457</link><description>IBM Robotic Process Automation for Cloud Pak 21.0.0 through 21.0.7.19 and 23.0.0 through 23.0.19 is vulnerable to cross-site scripting. This vulnerability allows an authenticated user to embed arbitrary JavaScript code in the Web UI thus altering the intended functionality potentially leading to credentials disclosure within a trusted session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:45:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20128 | ClamAV OLE2 File Format Decryption Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20128</link><description>A vulnerability in the Object Linking and Embedding 2 (OLE2) decryption routine of ClamAV could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to cause a denial of service (DoS) condition on an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to an integer underflow in a bounds check that allows for a heap buffer overflow read. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a crafted file containing OLE2 content to be scanned by ClamAV on an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to terminate the ClamAV scanning process, resulting in a DoS condition on the affected software.
For a description of this vulnerability, see the .
Cisco has released software updates that address this vulnerability. There are no workarounds that address this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20156 | Cisco Meeting Management Client-Server Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20156</link><description>A vulnerability in the REST API of Cisco Meeting Management could allow a remote, authenticated attacker with low privileges to elevate privileges to administrator on an affected device.

This vulnerability exists because proper authorization is not enforced upon&amp;nbsp;REST API users. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending API requests to a specific endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to gain administrator-level control over edge nodes that are managed by Cisco Meeting Management.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:34:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20165 | Cisco BroadWorks SIP Denial of Service Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20165</link><description>A vulnerability in the SIP processing subsystem of Cisco BroadWorks could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to halt the processing of incoming SIP requests, resulting in a denial of service (DoS) condition.

This vulnerability is due to improper memory handling for certain SIP requests. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a high number of SIP requests to an affected system. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to exhaust the memory that was allocated to the Cisco BroadWorks Network Servers that handle SIP traffic. If no memory is available, the Network Servers can no longer process incoming requests, resulting in a DoS condition that requires manual intervention to recover.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-10929 | Spectre-BSE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-10929</link><description>In certain circumstances, an issue in Arm Cortex-A72 (revisions before r1p0), Cortex-A73 and Cortex-A75 may allow an adversary to gain a weak form of control over the victim's branch history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31903 | IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31903</link><description>IBM Sterling B2B Integrator Standard Edition 6.0.0.0 through 6.1.2.5 and 6.2.0.0 through 6.2.0.2 allow an attacker on the local network to execute arbitrary code on the system, caused by the deserialization of untrusted data.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-55488 | A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Umbraco CMS v14.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a cra...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-55488</link><description>A stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Umbraco CMS v14.3.1 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via a crafted payload.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:14:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42012 | GRAU DATA Blocky before 3.1 stores passwords encrypted rather than hashed. At the login screen, the user's password is compared to the user'...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42012</link><description>GRAU DATA Blocky before 3.1 stores passwords encrypted rather than hashed. At the login screen, the user's password is compared to the user's decrypted cleartext password. An attacker with Windows admin or debugging rights can therefore steal the user's Blocky password and from there impersonate that local user.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-42013 | In GRAU DATA Blocky before 3.1, Blocky-Gui has a Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security vulnerability. An attacker with Windows adm...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-42013</link><description>In GRAU DATA Blocky before 3.1, Blocky-Gui has a Client-Side Enforcement of Server-Side Security vulnerability. An attacker with Windows administrative or debugging privileges can patch a binary in memory or on disk to bypass the password login requirement and gain full access to all functions of the program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:56:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0638 | Routinator crashes when illegal characters are present in manifest file names</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0638</link><description>The initial code parsing the manifest did not check the content of the file names yet later code assumed that it was checked and panicked when encountering illegal characters, resulting in a crash of Routinator.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23809 | WordPress Blue Wrench Video Widget Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23809</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Blue Wrench Video Widget allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Blue Wrench Video Widget: from n/a through 2.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23914 | WordPress Muzaara Google Ads Report Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.1 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23914</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound Muzaara Google Ads Report allows Object Injection. This issue affects Muzaara Google Ads Report: from n/a through 3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23992 | WordPress Toocheke Companion plugin &amp;lt;= 1.166 - Stored Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23992</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Leetoo Toocheke Companion allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Toocheke Companion: from n/a through 1.166.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37777 | Synnefo Internet Management Software 2023 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37777</link><description>Synnefo Internet Management Software 2023 was discovered to contain a SQL injection vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24429 | A reachable assertion in the nas_eps_send_emm_to_esm function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24429</link><description>A reachable assertion in the nas_eps_send_emm_to_esm function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NGAP packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:21:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36998 | The NextEPC MME &lt;= 1.0.1 (fixed in commit a8492c9c5bc0a66c6999cb5a263545b32a4109df) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36998</link><description>The NextEPC MME &lt;= 1.0.1 (fixed in commit a8492c9c5bc0a66c6999cb5a263545b32a4109df) contains a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the Emergency Number List decoding method. An attacker may send a NAS message containing an oversized Emergency Number List value to the MME to overwrite the stack with arbitrary bytes. An attacker with a cellphone connection to any base station managed by the MME may exploit this vulnerability without having to authenticate with the LTE core.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37023 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a reachable assertion in the `Uplink NAS Transport` packet handler. A packet missing its `MME_UE_S1AP_...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37023</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a reachable assertion in the `Uplink NAS Transport` packet handler. A packet missing its `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field causes Open5gs to crash; an attacker may repeatedly send such packets to cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-34235 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-34235</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `Initial UE Message` missing a required `NAS_PDU` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37019 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37019</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `S1Setup Request` message missing a required `Supported TAs` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37020 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37020</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `UE Context Release Complete` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37021 | Open5GS MME version &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37021</link><description>Open5GS MME version &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `UE Context Modification Failure` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37022 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a reachable assertion in the `UE Context Release Request` packet handler. A packet containing an inval...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37022</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a reachable assertion in the `UE Context Release Request` packet handler. A packet containing an invalid `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field causes Open5gs to crash; an attacker may repeatedly send such packets to cause denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37014 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37014</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `UE Context Release Request` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:53:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37015 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37015</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `Path Switch Request` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37016 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37016</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `UE Context Modification Response` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:53:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37017 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37017</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `S1Setup Request` message missing a required `Global eNB ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37018 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37018</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `UE Capability Info Indication` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:53:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37013 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a sufficiently large ASN.1 packet over the S1AP inter...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37013</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contains an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a sufficiently large ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may repeatedly send such an oversized packet to cause the `ogs_sctp_recvmsg` routine to reach an unexpected network state and crash, leading to denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37008 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a buffer overflow in the ASN.1 deserialization function of the S1AP handler. This buffer overflow caus...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37008</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain a buffer overflow in the ASN.1 deserialization function of the S1AP handler. This buffer overflow causes type confusion in decoded fields, leading to invalid parsing and freeing of memory. An attacker may use this to crash an MME or potentially execute code in certain circumstances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37009 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37009</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `Handover Notification` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37010 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37010</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `eNB Status Transfer` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37011 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37011</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `Handover Required` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37012 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37012</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `Initial UE Message` message missing a required `PLMN Identity` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0604 | Keycloak-ldap-federation: authentication bypass due to missing ldap bind after password reset in keycloak</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0604</link><description>A flaw was found in Keycloak. When an Active Directory user resets their password, the system updates it without performing an LDAP bind to validate the new credentials against AD. This vulnerability allows users whose AD accounts are expired or disabled to regain access in Keycloak, bypassing AD restrictions. The issue enables authentication bypass and could allow unauthorized access under certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37002 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37002</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `E-RAB Modification Indication` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37003 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37003</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `E-RAB Setup Response` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37004 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37004</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `Initial Context Setup Response` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37005 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37005</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send an `Initial Context Setup Failure` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37006 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37006</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `Handover Request Ack` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-37007 | Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-37007</link><description>Open5GS MME versions &lt;= 2.6.4 contain an assertion that can be remotely triggered via a malformed ASN.1 packet over the S1AP interface. An attacker may send a `Handover Cancel` message missing a required `MME_UE_S1AP_ID` field to repeatedly crash the MME, resulting in denial of service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24432 | A reachable assertion in the ogs_kdf_hash_mme function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24432</link><description>A reachable assertion in the ogs_kdf_hash_mme function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22772 | WordPress Mapbox for WP Advanced Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22772</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Mapbox for WP Advanced allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Mapbox for WP Advanced: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22980 | A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Senayan Library Management System SLiMS 9 Bulian 9.6.1 via the tempLoanID parameter in the loan form...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22980</link><description>A SQL Injection vulnerability exists in Senayan Library Management System SLiMS 9 Bulian 9.6.1 via the tempLoanID parameter in the loan form on /admin/modules/circulation/loan.php.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23449 | WordPress Simple shortcode buttons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23449</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Simple shortcode buttons allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple shortcode buttons: from n/a through 1.3.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23462 | WordPress FWD Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23462</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound FWD Slider allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FWD Slider: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23475 | WordPress History timeline plugin &amp;lt;= 0.7.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23475</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound History timeline allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects History timeline: from n/a through 0.7.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23486 | WordPress Database Sync plugin &amp;lt;= 0.5.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23486</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in NotFound Database Sync allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Database Sync: from n/a through 0.5.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23495 | WordPress WooCommerce Order Search plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23495</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WooCommerce Order Search allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WooCommerce Order Search: from n/a through 1.1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23498 | WordPress Translation.Pro plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23498</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Translation.Pro allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Translation.Pro: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23500 | WordPress Simple Custom post type custom field plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23500</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Faaiq Ahmed, Technial Architect,faaiqsj@gmail.com Simple Custom post type custom field allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Simple Custom post type custom field: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23503 | WordPress Customizable Captcha and Contact us plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23503</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Customizable Captcha and Contact Us allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Customizable Captcha and Contact Us: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23506 | WordPress WP IMAP Auth plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23506</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP IMAP Auth allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP IMAP Auth: from n/a through 4.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23507 | WordPress Blrt WP Embed plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.9 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23507</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Blrt Blrt WP Embed allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Blrt WP Embed: from n/a through 1.6.9.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23509 | WordPress HyperComments plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23509</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound HyperComments allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects HyperComments: from n/a through 0.9.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23512 | WordPress Team 118GROUP Agent plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Arbitrary Content Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23512</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Team118GROUP Team 118GROUP Agent allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Team 118GROUP Agent: from n/a through 1.6.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23535 | WordPress REAL WordPress Sidebar plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23535</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in clickandsell REAL WordPress Sidebar allows Stored XSS. This issue affects REAL WordPress Sidebar: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23548 | WordPress Responsivity plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23548</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Bilal TAS Responsivity allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Responsivity: from n/a through 0.0.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23562 | WordPress XLSXviewer plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Arbitrary File Deletion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23562</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in NotFound XLSXviewer allows Path Traversal. This issue affects XLSXviewer: from n/a through 2.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23578 | WordPress Custom CSS Addons plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23578</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Custom CSS Addons allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Custom CSS Addons: from n/a through 1.9.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23583 | WordPress Explara Membership plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.7 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23583</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Explara Explara Membership allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Explara Membership: from n/a through 0.0.7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23589 | WordPress ContentOptin Lite plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23589</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound ContentOptin Lite allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ContentOptin Lite: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23592 | WordPress dForms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23592</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound dForms allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects dForms: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23597 | WordPress Rio Photo Gallery plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23597</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Riosis Private Limited Rio Photo Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Rio Photo Gallery: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23601 | WordPress Tab My Content plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23601</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Tab My Content allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tab My Content: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23602 | WordPress EELV Newsletter  plugin &amp;lt;= 4.8.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23602</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound EELV Newsletter allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EELV Newsletter: from n/a through 4.8.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23603 | WordPress Group category creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23603</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Group category creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Group category creator: from n/a through 1.3.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23604 | WordPress Rezdy Reloaded plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23604</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Rezdy Reloaded allows Stored XSS. This issue affects Rezdy Reloaded: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23605 | WordPress Call To Action Popup plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23605</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in LamPD Call To Action Popup allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Call To Action Popup: from n/a through 1.0.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23606 | WordPress Calendi plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23606</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Calendi allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Calendi: from n/a through 1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23607 | WordPress CAMOO SMS plugin &amp;lt;= 3.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23607</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Camoo Sarl CAMOO SMS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CAMOO SMS: from n/a through 3.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23609 | WordPress Tagesteller plugin &amp;lt;= v.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23609</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Helmuth Lammer Tagesteller allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Tagesteller: from n/a through v.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23610 | WordPress Ultimate Events plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23610</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Ultimate Events allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Events: from n/a through 1.3.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23611 | WordPress WH Cache &amp;amp; Security plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23611</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WH Cache &amp; Security allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WH Cache &amp; Security: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23625 | WordPress Unique UX plugin &amp;lt;= 0.9.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23625</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AWcode, PDSonline Unique UX allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Unique UX: from n/a through 0.9.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23630 | WordPress Cyber Slider plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23630</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Cyber Slider allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Cyber Slider: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23631 | WordPress Content Planner plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23631</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Content Planner allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Content Planner: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23643 | WordPress ReadMe Creator plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23643</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound ReadMe Creator allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects ReadMe Creator: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23672 | WordPress Instant Appointment plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23672</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Instant Appointment allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Instant Appointment: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23674 | WordPress Bit.ly linker plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23674</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Bit.ly linker allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Bit.ly linker: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23676 | WordPress LH Email plugin &amp;lt;= 1.12 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23676</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound LH Email allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects LH Email: from n/a through 1.12.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23678 | WordPress LocalGrid plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound LocalGrid allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects LocalGrid: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23679 | WordPress FP RSS Category Excluder plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23679</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Moshiur Rahman Mehedi FP RSS Category Excluder allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects FP RSS Category Excluder: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23681 | WordPress REDIRECTION PLUS plugin &amp;lt;= 2.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23681</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in jannatqualitybacklinks.com REDIRECTION PLUS allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects REDIRECTION PLUS: from n/a through 2.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23682 | WordPress Preloader Quotes plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23682</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Preloader Quotes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Preloader Quotes: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23683 | WordPress MACME plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23683</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound MACME allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects MACME: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23684 | WordPress Debug Tool plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23684</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Eugen Bobrowski Debug Tool allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels. This issue affects Debug Tool: from n/a through 2.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23686 | WordPress Admin Menu Organizer plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23686</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Callum Richards Admin Menu Organizer allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Admin Menu Organizer: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23695 | WordPress CtyGrid Hyp3rL0cal Search plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1.1.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23695</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound CtyGrid Hyp3rL0cal Search allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CtyGrid Hyp3rL0cal Search: from n/a through 0.1.1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23696 | WordPress Staging CDN plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23696</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Staging CDN allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Staging CDN: from n/a through 1.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23697 | WordPress Podčlánková inzerce plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23697</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in WebDeal s.r.o. Podčlánková inzerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Podčlánková inzerce: from n/a through 2.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23700 | WordPress yCyclista plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23700</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Yonatan Reinberg yCyclista allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects yCyclista: from n/a through 1.2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23701 | WordPress Lime Developer Login plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23701</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Matthew Blackford, LimeSquare Pty Ltd Lime Developer Login allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Lime Developer Login: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23706 | WordPress Jet Skinner for BuddyPress plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.5 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23706</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Jet Skinner for BuddyPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Jet Skinner for BuddyPress: from n/a through 1.2.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23709 | WordPress Formatted post plugin &amp;lt;= 1.01 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23709</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kiro G. Formatted post allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Formatted post: from n/a through 1.01.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23732 | WordPress Easy Filtering plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23732</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Easy Filtering allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Easy Filtering: from n/a through 2.5.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23746 | WordPress CMC MIGRATE plugin &amp;lt;= 0.0.3 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23746</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound CMC MIGRATE allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects CMC MIGRATE: from n/a through 0.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23758 | WordPress pootle button plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.0 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23758</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Pootle button allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Pootle button: from n/a through 1.2.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23768 | WordPress InFunding plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23768</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound InFunding allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects InFunding: from n/a through 1.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23769 | WordPress Content Mirror plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 -  Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23769</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Content Mirror allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Content Mirror: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23770 | WordPress Fast Tube plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23770</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Fast Tube allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Fast Tube: from n/a through 2.3.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23774 | WordPress WPDB to Sql plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23774</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in NotFound WPDB to Sql allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects WPDB to Sql: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23781 | WordPress WM Options Import Export plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Sensitive Data Exposure vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23781</link><description>Insertion of Sensitive Information Into Sent Data vulnerability in NotFound WM Options Import Export allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data. This issue affects WM Options Import Export: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23784 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23784</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23798 | WordPress Mass Messaging in BuddyPress Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23798</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Eliott Robson Mass Messaging in BuddyPress allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Mass Messaging in BuddyPress: from n/a through 2.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23803 | WordPress Snippy Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.1 - CSRF to Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23803</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in PQINA Snippy allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Snippy: from n/a through 1.4.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23806 | WordPress Ultimate Subscribe Plugin &amp;lt;=1.3 - CSRF to Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23806</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeFarmer Ultimate Subscribe allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Ultimate Subscribe: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23811 | WordPress WP2APP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23811</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP2APP allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP2APP: from n/a through 2.6.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23812 | WordPress Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23812</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Contact Form 7 Round Robin Lead Distribution: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23846 | WordPress Flexible Blogtitle Plugin &amp;lt;= 0.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23846</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Kolja Nolte Flexible Blogtitle allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Flexible Blogtitle: from n/a through 0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23866 | WordPress EU DSGVO Helper Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.6.1 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23866</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound EU DSGVO Helper allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects EU DSGVO Helper: from n/a through 1.0.6.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23867 | WordPress WordPress File Search Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23867</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WordPress File Search allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WordPress File Search: from n/a through 1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23874 | WordPress WP Block Pack plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.6 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23874</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Block Pack allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Block Pack: from n/a through 1.1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23882 | WordPress WP Download Codes Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.4 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23882</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NotFound WP Download Codes allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects WP Download Codes: from n/a through 2.5.4.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23910 | WordPress Menus Plus+ Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.6 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23910</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound Menus Plus+ allows SQL Injection. This issue affects Menus Plus+: from n/a through 1.9.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23918 | WordPress Smallerik File Browser plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23918</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Smallerik File Browser allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Smallerik File Browser: from n/a through 1.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23921 | WordPress Multi Uploader for Gravity Forms plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23921</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NotFound Multi Uploader for Gravity Forms allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects Multi Uploader for Gravity Forms: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23931 | WordPress WordPress Local SEO plugin &amp;lt;= 2.3 - SQL Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23931</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in NotFound WordPress Local SEO allows Blind SQL Injection. This issue affects WordPress Local SEO: from n/a through 2.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23932 | WordPress Quick Count Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.00 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23932</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in NotFound Quick Count allows Object Injection. This issue affects Quick Count: from n/a through 3.00.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23938 | WordPress Image Gallery Box by CRUDLab Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23938</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in NotFound Image Gallery Box by CRUDLab allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Image Gallery Box by CRUDLab: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23942 | WordPress WP Load Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23942</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in NgocCode WP Load Gallery allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects WP Load Gallery: from n/a through 2.1.6.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23944 | WordPress WOOEXIM Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.0 - PHP Object Injection vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23944</link><description>Deserialization of Untrusted Data vulnerability in WOOEXIM.COM WOOEXIM allows Object Injection. This issue affects WOOEXIM: from n/a through 5.0.0.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23948 | WordPress Background animation blocks Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.5 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23948</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in WebArea Background animation blocks allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Background animation blocks: from n/a through 2.1.5.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23949 | WordPress Improved Sale Badges – Free Version Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Local File Inclusion vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23949</link><description>Improper Control of Filename for Include/Require Statement in PHP Program ('PHP Remote File Inclusion') vulnerability in Mihajlovic Nenad Improved Sale Badges – Free Version allows PHP Local File Inclusion. This issue affects Improved Sale Badges – Free Version: from n/a through 1.0.1.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23953 | WordPress user files plugin &amp;lt;= 2.4.2 - Arbitrary File Upload vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23953</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Innovative Solutions user files allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server. This issue affects user files: from n/a through 2.4.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23959 | WordPress Good Old Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.2 - Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23959</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Linus Lundahl Good Old Gallery allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects Good Old Gallery: from n/a through 2.1.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23966 | WordPress a Gateway for Pasargad Bank on WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5.2 - Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23966</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in AlaFalaki a Gateway for Pasargad Bank on WooCommerce allows Reflected XSS. This issue affects a Gateway for Pasargad Bank on WooCommerce: from n/a through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-24027 | ps_contactinfo has potential XSS due to usage of the nofilter tag in template</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-24027</link><description>ps_contactinfo, a PrestaShop module for displaying store contact information, has a cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in versions up to and including 3.3.2. This can not be exploited in a fresh install of PrestaShop, only shops made vulnerable by third party modules are concerned. For example, if the shop has a third party module vulnerable to SQL injections, then ps_contactinfo might execute a stored cross-site scripting in formatting objects. Commit d60f9a5634b4fc2d3a8831fb08fe2e1f23cbfa39 keeps formatted addresses from displaying a XSS stored in the database, and the fix is expected to be available in version 3.3.3. No workarounds are available aside from applying the fix and keeping all modules maintained and update.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-24430 | A reachable assertion in the mme_ue_find_by_imsi function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-24430</link><description>A reachable assertion in the mme_ue_find_by_imsi function of Open5GS &lt;= 2.6.4 allows attackers to cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via a crafted NAS packet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:29:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0395 | When the assert() function in the GNU C Library versions 2.13 to 2.40 fails, it does not allocate enough space for the assertion failure mes...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0395</link><description>When the assert() function in the GNU C Library versions 2.13 to 2.40 fails, it does not allocate enough space for the assertion failure message string and size information, which may lead to a buffer overflow if the message string size aligns to page size.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13447 | WP Hotel Booking &amp;lt;= 2.1.6 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) User Email Retrieval</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13447</link><description>The WP Hotel Booking plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access of data due to a missing capability check on the hotel_booking_load_order_user AJAX action in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to retrieve a list of registered user emails.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13495 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via gamipress_ajax_get_logs Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13495</link><description>The The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via the gamipress_ajax_get_logs() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13496 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection via orderby Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13496</link><description>The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘orderby’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13499 | GamiPress &amp;lt;= 7.2.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary Shortcode Execution via gamipress_do_shortcode() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13499</link><description>The The GamiPress – Gamification plugin to reward points, achievements, badges &amp; ranks in WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary shortcode execution via gamipress_do_shortcode() function in all versions up to, and including, 7.2.1. This is due to the software allowing users to execute an action that does not properly validate a value before running do_shortcode. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary shortcodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:10:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-23439 | A externally controlled reference to a resource in another sphere in Fortinet FortiManager before version 7.4.3, FortiMail before version 7....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-23439</link><description>A externally controlled reference to a resource in another sphere in Fortinet FortiManager before version 7.4.3, FortiMail before version 7.0.3, FortiAnalyzer before version 7.4.3, FortiVoice version 7.0.0, 7.0.1 and before 6.4.8, FortiProxy before version 7.0.4, FortiRecorder version 6.4.0 through 6.4.2 and before 6.0.10, FortiAuthenticator version 6.4.0 through 6.4.1 and before 6.3.3, FortiNDR version 7.2.0 before 7.1.0, FortiWLC before version 8.6.4, FortiPortal before version 6.0.9, FortiOS version 7.2.0 and before 7.0.5, FortiADC version 7.0.0 through 7.0.1 and before 6.2.3 , FortiDDoS before version 5.5.1, FortiDDoS-F before version 6.3.3, FortiTester before version 7.2.1, FortiSOAR before version 7.2.2 and FortiSwitch before version 6.3.3 allows attacker to poison web caches via crafted HTTP requests, where the `Host` header points to an arbitrary webserver</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 09:28:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13319 | Themify Builder &amp;lt;= 7.6.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13319</link><description>The Themify Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting due to the use of add_query_arg without appropriate escaping on the URL in all versions up to, and including, 7.6.5. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13360 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13360</link><description>The AI Power: Complete AI Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via the wpaicg_troubleshoot_add_vector(). This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13361 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Shortcode Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13361</link><description>The AI Power: Complete AI Pack plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the wpaicg_save_image_media function in all versions up to, and including, 1.8.96. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload image files and embed shortcode attributes in the image_alt value that will execute when sending a POST request to the attachment page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0428 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via wpaicg_export_prompts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0428</link><description>The "AI Power: Complete AI Pack" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via deserialization of untrusted input from the $form['post_content'] variable through the wpaicg_export_prompts function. This allows authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0429 | AI Power: Complete AI Pack &amp;lt;= 1.8.96 - Authenticated (Admin+) PHP Object Injection via wpaicg_export_ai_forms</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0429</link><description>The "AI Power: Complete AI Pack" plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to PHP Object Injection in versions up to, and including, 1.8.96 via deserialization of untrusted input from the $form['post_content'] variable through the wpaicg_export_ai_forms() function. This allows authenticated attackers, with administrative privileges, to inject a PHP Object. No POP chain is present in the vulnerable plugin. If a POP chain is present via an additional plugin or theme installed on the target system, it could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files, retrieve sensitive data, or execute code.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:38:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12117 | Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks &amp;lt;= 3.13.11 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12117</link><description>The Stackable – Page Builder Gutenberg Blocks plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'title' parameter of the Button block in all versions up to, and including, 3.13.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12857 | AdForest &amp;lt;= 5.1.8 - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12857</link><description>The AdForest theme for WordPress is vulnerable to authentication bypass in all versions up to, and including, 5.1.8. This is due to the plugin not properly verifying a user's identity prior to logging them in as that user. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to authenticate as any user as long as they have configured OTP login by phone number.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13406 | XML for Google Merchant Center &amp;lt;= 3.0.11 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13406</link><description>The XML for Google Merchant Center plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Reflected Cross-Site Scripting via the 'feed_id' parameter in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.11 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that execute if they can successfully trick a user into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 07:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23237 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23237</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If a user logs in to CLI of the affected product, an arbitrary OS command may be executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 06:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20617 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20617</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. If this vulnerability is exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by an attacker who can access the affected product with an administrative account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:55:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22450 | Inclusion of undocumented features issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. A remote attacker may disable the LAN-side f...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22450</link><description>Inclusion of undocumented features issue exists in UD-LT2 firmware Ver.1.00.008_SE and earlier. A remote attacker may disable the LAN-side firewall function of the affected products, and open specific ports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:55:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12879 | WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot &amp;lt;= 13.5.5 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Simple Text Response Creation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12879</link><description>The WPBot Pro Wordpress Chatbot plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data due to a missing capability check on the 'qc_wp_latest_update_check_pro' function in all versions up to, and including, 13.5.5. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to create Simple Text Responses to chat queries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:31:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-11218 | Podman: buildah: container breakout by using --jobs=2 and a race condition when building a malicious containerfile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-11218</link><description>A vulnerability was found in `podman build` and `buildah.` This issue occurs in a container breakout by using --jobs=2 and a race condition when building a malicious Containerfile. SELinux might mitigate it, but even with SELinux on, it still allows the enumeration of files and directories on the host.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:13:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13584 | Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List &amp;lt;= 1.5.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13584</link><description>The Picture Gallery – Frontend Image Uploads, AJAX Photo List plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'videowhisper_pictures' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13590 | Ketchup Shortcodes &amp;lt;= 0.1.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13590</link><description>The Ketchup Shortcodes plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'spacer' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13426 | WP-Polls &amp;lt;= 2.77.2 - Unauthenticated SQL Injection to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13426</link><description>The WP-Polls plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via COOKIE in all versions up to, and including, 2.77.2 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries. Those queries are stored and results are not displayed to the attacker, which means they cannot be exploited to obtain any additional information about the database. However, a properly configured payload allows for the injection of malicious JavaScript resulting in Stored Cross-Site Scripting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23083 | With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23083</link><description>With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only to workers but also exposes internal workers, where an instance of them can be fetched, and its constructor can be grabbed and reinstated for malicious usage. 

This vulnerability affects Permission Model users (--permission) on Node.js v20, v22, and v23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23087 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23087</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23088 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23088</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23089 | This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23089</link><description>This CVE has been issued to inform users that they are using End-of-Life (EOL) versions of Node.js. These versions are no longer supported and do not receive updates, including security patches. The continued use of EOL versions may expose systems to potential security risks due to unaddressed software vulnerabilities or dependencies (CWE-1104: Use of Unmaintained Third-Party Components).

Users are advised to upgrade to actively supported versions of Node.js to ensure continued security updates and support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23090 | With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23090</link><description>With the aid of the diagnostics_channel utility, an event can be hooked into whenever a worker thread is created. This is not limited only to workers
 but also exposes internal workers, where an instance of them can be fetched, and its constructor can be grabbed and reinstated for malicious usage.

This vulnerability affects Permission Model users (--permission) on Node.js v20, v22, and v23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:20:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0625 | CampCodes School Management Software Attachment resource injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0625</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in CampCodes School Management Software 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component Attachment Handler. The manipulation leads to improper control of resource identifiers. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:05:46 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>