<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-3321 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials in OnlineSuite</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3321</link><description>A predefined administrative account is not documented and cannot
be deactivated. This account cannot be misused from the network, only by local
users on the server.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5735 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formSetLg buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5735</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /boafrm/formSetLg of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:19:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5736 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formNtp buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5736</link><description>A vulnerability was found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formNtp of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument submit-url leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5732 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System cross-site request forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5732</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part. The manipulation leads to cross-site request forgery. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5734 | TOTOLINK X15 HTTP POST Request formWlanRedirect buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5734</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK X15 1.0.0-B20230714.1105 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /boafrm/formWlanRedirect of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument redirect-url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:43:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5728 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System manage_website.php unrestricted upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5728</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /manage_website.php. The manipulation of the argument website_image leads to unrestricted upload. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5729 | code-projects Health Center Patient Record Management System birthing_record.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5729</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Health Center Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /birthing_record.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-58114 | Resource allocation control failure vulnerability in the ArkUI framework
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect av...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-58114</link><description>Resource allocation control failure vulnerability in the ArkUI framework
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2935 | Anti-Spam: Spam Protection | Block Spam Users, Comments, Forms &amp;lt;= 2024.7 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Multiple Administrative Actions</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2935</link><description>The Anti-Spam: Spam Protection | Block Spam Users, Comments, Forms plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 2024.7. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation in the 'ss_option_maint.php' and 'ss_user_filter_list' files. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete pending comments, and re-enable a previously blocked user via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48908 | Ability Auto Startup service vulnerability in the foundation process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availa...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48908</link><description>Ability Auto Startup service vulnerability in the foundation process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48909 | Bypass vulnerability in the device management channel
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48909</link><description>Bypass vulnerability in the device management channel
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect service confidentiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48910 | Buffer overflow vulnerability in the DFile module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48910</link><description>Buffer overflow vulnerability in the DFile module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48911 | Vulnerability of improper permission assignment in the note sharing module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48911</link><description>Vulnerability of improper permission assignment in the note sharing module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4964 | WP Online Users Stats &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Authenticated (Editor+) SQL Injection via table_name Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4964</link><description>The WP Online Users Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to time-based SQL Injection via the ‘table_name’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Editor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4966 | WP Online Users Stats &amp;lt;= 1.0.0 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via hk_dataset_results Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4966</link><description>The WP Online Users Stats plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.0. This is due to missing nonce validation within the hk_dataset_results() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5018 | Hive Support &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Missing Authorization via hs_update_ai_chat_settings and hive_lite_support_get_all_binbox</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5018</link><description>The Hive Support plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access and modification of data due to a missing capability check on the hs_update_ai_chat_settings() and hive_lite_support_get_all_binbox() functions in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.4. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to read and overwrite the site’s OpenAI API key and inspection data or modify AI-chat prompts and behavior. This vulnerability is potentially a duplicate of CVE-2025-32208 or/and CVE-2025-32242.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5019 | Hive Support &amp;lt;= 1.2.4 - Cross-Site Request Forgery via hs_update_ai_chat_settings Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5019</link><description>The Hive Support | AI-Powered Help Desk, Live Chat &amp; AI Chat Bot Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the hs_update_ai_chat_settings() function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to reconfigure the plugin’s AI/chat settings (including API keys) and to potentially redirect notifications or leak data to attacker-controlled endpoints via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5486 | WP Email Debug 1.0 - 1.1.0 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via Password Reset</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5486</link><description>The WP Email Debug plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the WPMDBUG_handle_settings() function in versions 1.0 to 1.1.0. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to enable debugging and send all emails to an attacker controlled address and then trigger a password reset for an administrator to gain access to an administrator account.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5533 | Knowledge Base &amp;lt;= 2.3.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5533</link><description>The Knowledge Base plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'kbalert' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.3.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5534 | ESV Bible Shortcode for WordPress &amp;lt;= 1.0.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5534</link><description>The ESV Bible Shortcode for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'esv' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5536 | Freemind Viewer &amp;lt;= 1.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5536</link><description>The Freemind Viewer plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'freemind' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5538 | BNS Featured Category &amp;lt;= 2.8.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5538</link><description>The BNS Featured Category plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'bnsfc' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.8.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5541 | Runners Log &amp;lt;= 3.9.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5541</link><description>The Runners Log plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'runnerslog' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.9.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:59:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5563 | WP-Addpub &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 - Authenticated (Contributor+) SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5563</link><description>The WP-Addpub plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the 'wp-addpub' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.8 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query.  This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5565 | Hide It &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5565</link><description>The Hide It plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'hideit' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5586 | WordPress Ajax Load More and Infinite Scroll &amp;lt;= 1.6.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via id Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5586</link><description>The WordPress Ajax Load More and Infinite Scroll plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5686 | Paged Gallery &amp;lt;= 0.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5686</link><description>The Paged Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gallery' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5699 | Developer Formatter &amp;lt;= 2015.0.2.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Custom CSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5699</link><description>The Developer Formatter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the Custom CSS in all versions up to, and including, 2015.0.2.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page. This only affects multi-site installations and installations where unfiltered_html has been disabled.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5703 | StageShow &amp;lt;= 10.0.3 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via anchor Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5703</link><description>The StageShow plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘anchor’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 10.0.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48902 | Vulnerability of uncontrolled system resource applications in the setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48902</link><description>Vulnerability of uncontrolled system resource applications in the setting module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48903 | Permission bypass vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48903</link><description>Permission bypass vulnerability in the media library module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48904 | Vulnerability that cards can call unauthorized APIs in the FRS process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect avai...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48904</link><description>Vulnerability that cards can call unauthorized APIs in the FRS process
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48905 | Wasm exception capture vulnerability in the arkweb v8 module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the failure to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48905</link><description>Wasm exception capture vulnerability in the arkweb v8 module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may cause the failure to capture specific Wasm exception types.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48906 | Authentication bypass vulnerability in the DSoftBus module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48906</link><description>Authentication bypass vulnerability in the DSoftBus module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48907 | Deserialization vulnerability in the IPC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48907</link><description>Deserialization vulnerability in the IPC module
Impact: Successful exploitation of this vulnerability may affect availability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5727 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Announcement Page announcement cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5727</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /script/academic/announcement of the component Announcement Page. The manipulation of the argument Title leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:48:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-2921 | Short URL &amp;lt;= 1.6.8 - Subscriber+ SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-2921</link><description>The Short URL WordPress plugin through 1.6.8 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by users with relatively low privilege on the site, like subscribers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:20:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5726 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Division System Page division-system cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5726</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /script/academic/division-system of the component Division System Page. The manipulation of the argument Division leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 06:20:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5724 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Subjects Page subjects cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5724</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /script/academic/subjects of the component Subjects Page. The manipulation of the argument Subject leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5725 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Grading System Page grading-system cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5725</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /script/academic/grading-system of the component Grading System Page. The manipulation of the argument Remark leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:49:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1777 | BM Content Builder &amp;lt;= 3.16.2.1 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via ux_cb_page_options_save</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1777</link><description>The BM Content Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data to a missing capability check on the 'ux_cb_page_options_save' function in all versions up to, and including, 3.16.2.1. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:36:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1778 | Art Theme &amp;lt;= 3.12.2.3 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Theme Option Delete</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1778</link><description>The Art Theme for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized access due to a missing capability check on the 'arttheme_theme_option_restore' AJAX function in all versions up to, and including, 3.12.2.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level access and above, to delete the theme option.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:36:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5723 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Classes Page classes cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5723</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /script/academic/classes of the component Classes Page. The manipulation of the argument Class Name leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:11:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36513 | Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in surveillance cameras provided by i-PRO Co., Ltd.. If a user views a crafted page while lo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36513</link><description>Cross-site request forgery vulnerability exists in surveillance cameras provided by i-PRO Co., Ltd.. If a user views a crafted page while logged in to the affected product, unintended operations may be performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:43:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5722 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Add Academic Term terms cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5722</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /script/academic/terms of the component Add Academic Term. The manipulation of the argument Academic Term leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5721 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Profile Setting Page update_profile cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5721</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /script/academic/core/update_profile of the component Profile Setting Page. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 04:15:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5716 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5716</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5719 | The wallet has an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows access to specific pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5719</link><description>The wallet has an authentication bypass vulnerability that allows access to specific pages.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5733 | Modern Events Calendar &amp;lt;= 7.21.9 - Information Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5733</link><description>The Modern Events Calendar Lite plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 7.21.9. This is due improper or insufficient validation of the id property when exporting calendars. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-46941 | SystemUI component protection settings vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-46941</link><description>SystemUI has an incorrect component protection setting, which allows access to specific information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5714 | SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB Profile Information Update up.upload.php path traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5714</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB up to 20250516. It has been classified as problematic. This affects an unknown part of the file /sys/up.upload.php of the component Profile Information Update. The manipulation of the argument nomeArquivo leads to path traversal. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5715 | Signal App Biometric Authentication missing critical step in authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5715</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Signal App 7.41.4 on Android. It has been declared as problematic. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component Biometric Authentication Handler. The manipulation leads to missing critical step in authentication. It is possible to launch the attack on the physical device. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The vendor was contacted early about this disclosure but did not respond in any way.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:53:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5712 | SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System appointment.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5712</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in SourceCodester Open Source Clinic Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /appointment.php. The manipulation of the argument patient leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5713 | SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB Flow fluxos-dashboard cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5713</link><description>A vulnerability was found in SoluçõesCoop iSoluçõesWEB up to 20250519 and classified as problematic. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /fluxos-dashboard of the component Flow Handler. The manipulation of the argument Descrição da solicitação leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5711 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertCity.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5711</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Admin/InsertCity.php. The manipulation of the argument cmbState leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-22330 | IBM Security Verify Governance information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-22330</link><description>IBM Security Verify Governance 10.0.2 does not require that users should have strong passwords by default, which makes it easier for attackers to compromise user accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56342 | IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56342</link><description>IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials 24.06 could allow a remote attacker to obtain sensitive information when a detailed technical error message is returned in the browser.  This information could be used in further attacks against the system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-56343 | IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-56343</link><description>IBM Verify Identity Access Digital Credentials 24.06 could allow an authenticated user to crash the service with a specially crafted POST request.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5709 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertCategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5709</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /Admin/InsertCategory.php. The manipulation of the argument txtCategoryName leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5710 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System InsertState.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5710</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/InsertState.php. The manipulation of the argument txtStateName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5708 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System NewsReport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5708</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /Admin/NewsReport.php. The manipulation of the argument txtFrom leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5707 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System registered-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5707</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /registered-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument testtype leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5706 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System new-user-testing.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5706</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /new-user-testing.php. The manipulation of the argument state leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 01:50:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5705 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System Property.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5705</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /Admin/Property.php. The manipulation of the argument cmbCat leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 23:46:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5704 | code-projects Real Estate Property Management System User.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5704</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Real Estate Property Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /Admin/User.php. The manipulation of the argument txtUserName leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 23:20:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49012 | Himmelblau&amp;#x27;s Name-Based Group Matching in `pam_allow_groups` Leads to Potential Security Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49012</link><description>Himmelblau is an interoperability suite for Microsoft Azure Entra ID and Intune. Himmelblau versions 0.9.0 through 0.9.14 and 1.00-alpha are vulnerable to a privilege escalation issue when Entra ID group-based access restrictions are configured using group display names instead of object IDs. Starting in version 0.9.0, Himmelblau introduced support for specifying group names in the `pam_allow_groups` configuration option. However, Microsoft Entra ID permits the creation of multiple groups with the same `displayName` via the Microsoft Graph API—even by non-admin users, depending on tenant settings. As a result, a user could create a personal group with the same name as a legitimate access group (e.g., `"Allow-Linux-Login"`), add themselves to it, and be granted authentication or `sudo` rights by Himmelblau. Because affected Himmelblau versions compare group names by either `displayName` or by the immutable `objectId`, this allows bypassing access control mechanisms intended to restrict login to members of official, centrally-managed groups. This issue is fixed in Himmelblau version **0.9.15** and later. In these versions, group name matching in `pam_allow_groups` has been deprecated and removed, and only group `objectId`s (GUIDs) may be specified for secure group-based filtering. To mitigate the issue without upgrading, replace all entries in `pam_allow_groups` with the objectId of the target Entra ID group(s) and/or audit your tenant for groups with duplicate display names using the Microsoft Graph API.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:33:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5698 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System logSelect.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5698</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. Affected is an unknown function of the file /sysframework/logSelect.htm. The manipulation of the argument nodename leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5696 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System rentChangeCheckInfoPage.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5696</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /storagework/rentChangeCheckInfoPage.htm. The manipulation of the argument clientname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:42:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5697 | Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System tcCustDeferPosiQuery.htm sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5697</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Brilliance Golden Link Secondary System up to 20250424. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /reprotframework/tcCustDeferPosiQuery.htm. The manipulation of the argument custTradeId leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:42:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5695 | FLIR AX8 Backend subscriptions.php subscribe_to_alarm command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5695</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in FLIR AX8 up to 1.46.16. This affects the function subscribe_to_spot/subscribe_to_delta/subscribe_to_alarm of the file /usr/www/application/models/subscriptions.php of the component Backend. The manipulation leads to command injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Upgrading to version 1.55.16 is able to address this issue. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:18:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47966 | Power Automate Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47966</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48133 | WordPress Uncanny Automator &amp;lt;= 6.4.0.2 - Broken Access Control Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48133</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in Uncanny Owl Uncanny Automator allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Uncanny Automator: from n/a through 6.4.0.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 21:00:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5694 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5694</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument serachdata leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:38:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5685 | Tenda CH22 Natlimit formNatlimit stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5685</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This affects the function formNatlimit of the file /goform/Natlimit. The manipulation of the argument page leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:16:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5693 | PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System bwdates-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5693</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Human Metapneumovirus Testing Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /bwdates-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:16:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43026 | HP Support Assistant – Potential Escalation of Privilege</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43026</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the HP Support Assistant for versions prior to 9.44.18.0. The vulnerability could potentially allow a local attacker to escalate privileges via an arbitrary file write.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:44:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5680 | Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM Groovy Script SysScriptController.java executeScript deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5680</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM up to 2.5.0. Affected by this vulnerability is the function executeScript of the file /src/main/java/com/dstz/sys/rest/controller/SysScriptController.java of the component Groovy Script Handler. The manipulation of the argument script leads to deserialization. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5745 | The strncmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.40 and later writes to vector registers v20 to...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5745</link><description>The strncmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.40 and later writes to vector registers v20 to v31 without saving contents from the caller (those registers are defined as non-volatile registers by the powerpc64le ABI), resulting in overwriting of its contents and potentially altering control flow of the caller, or leaking the input strings to the function to other parts of the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:30:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5677 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5677</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=save_application. The manipulation of the argument position_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:13:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5679 | Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM SysToolsController.java parseStrByFreeMarker deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5679</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Shenzhen Dashi Tongzhou Information Technology AgileBPM up to 2.5.0. Affected is the function parseStrByFreeMarker of the file /src/main/java/com/dstz/sys/rest/controller/SysToolsController.java. The manipulation of the argument str leads to deserialization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:13:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5674 | code-projects Patient Record Management System urinalysis_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5674</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file urinalysis_form.php. The manipulation of the argument urinalysis_id leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5675 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5675</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /trms/admin/bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5676 | Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System ajax.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5676</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Recruitment Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/ajax.php?action=login. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5702 | The strcmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.39 and later writes to vector registers v20 to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5702</link><description>The strcmp implementation optimized for the Power10 processor in the GNU C Library version 2.39 and later writes to vector registers v20 to v31 without saving contents from the caller (those registers are defined as non-volatile registers by the powerpc64le ABI), resulting in overwriting of its contents and potentially altering control flow of the caller, or leaking the input strings to the function to other parts of the program.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:58:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46257 | WordPress Element Pack Pro Plugin &amp;lt; 8.0.0 - Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46257</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Pro allows Cross Site Request Forgery.This issue affects Element Pack Pro: from n/a before 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46258 | WordPress Element Pack Pro Plugin &amp;lt; 8.0.0 - Broken Access Control vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46258</link><description>Missing Authorization vulnerability in BdThemes Element Pack Pro allows Exploiting Incorrectly Configured Access Control Security Levels.This issue affects Element Pack Pro: from n/a before 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5671 | TOTOLINK N302R Plus HTTP POST Request formPortFw buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5671</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in TOTOLINK N302R Plus up to 3.4.0-B20201028. Affected is an unknown function of the file /boafrm/formPortFw of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument service_type leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5672 | TOTOLINK N302R Plus HTTP POST Request formFilter buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5672</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in TOTOLINK N302R Plus up to 3.4.0-B20201028 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /boafrm/formFilter of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument url leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5670 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System manage-card.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5670</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-card.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49009 | Para Inserts Sensitive Information into Log File for Facebook authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49009</link><description>Para is a multitenant backend server/framework for object persistence and retrieval. A vulnerability that exists in versions prior to 1.50.8 in `FacebookAuthFilter.java` results in a full request URL being logged during a failed request to a Facebook user profile. The log includes the user's access token in plain text. Since WARN-level logs are often retained in production and accessible to operators or log aggregation systems, this poses a risk of token exposure. Version 1.50.8 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48493 | Yii 2 Redis may expose AUTH paramters in logs in case of connection failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48493</link><description>The Yii 2 Redis extension provides the redis key-value store support for the Yii framework 2.0. On failing connection, the extension writes commands sequence to logs. Prior to version 2.0.20, AUTH parameters are written in plain text exposing username and password. That might be an issue if attacker has access to logs. Version 2.0.20 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5668 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System readenq.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5668</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/readenq.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5669 | PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System unreadenq.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5669</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Medical Card Generation System 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/unreadenq.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:49:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5667 | FreeFloat FTP Server REIN Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5667</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component REIN Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5666 | FreeFloat FTP Server XMKD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5666</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component XMKD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:45:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5665 | FreeFloat FTP Server XCWD Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5665</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component XCWD Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:11:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5664 | FreeFloat FTP Server RESTART Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5664</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component RESTART Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:48:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5663 | PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System search-autoortaxi.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5663</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Auto Taxi Stand Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/search-autoortaxi.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47827 | In IGEL OS before 11, Secure Boot can be bypassed because the igel-flash-driver module improperly verifies a cryptographic signature. Ultima...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47827</link><description>In IGEL OS before 11, Secure Boot can be bypassed because the igel-flash-driver module improperly verifies a cryptographic signature. Ultimately, a crafted root filesystem can be mounted from an unverified SquashFS image.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0691 | Improper access control in permissions component in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the "E...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0691</link><description>Improper access control in permissions component in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the "Edit permission" permission by bypassing the client side validation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:56:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3768 | Improper access control in Tor network blocking feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3768</link><description>Improper access control in Tor network blocking feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.10.0 and earlier allows an authenticated user to bypass the tor blocking feature when the Devolutions hosted endpoint is not reachable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5382 | Improper access control in users MFA feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a user with user management permission to r...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5382</link><description>Improper access control in users MFA feature in Devolutions Server 2025.1.7.0 and earlier allows a user with user management permission to remove or change administrators MFA.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5661 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System Setting save-settings.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5661</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /save-settings.php of the component Setting Handler. The manipulation of the argument site_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27445 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A path traversal vulnerability RSFirewall component 2.9.7 - 3.1.5 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27445</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability in RSFirewall component 2.9.7 - 3.1.5 for Joomla was discovered. This vulnerability allows authenticated users to read arbitrary files outside the Joomla root directory. The flaw is caused by insufficient sanitization of user-supplied input in file path parameters, allowing attackers to exploit directory traversal sequences (e.g., ../) to access sensitive files</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27753 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A SQLi vulnerability RSMediaGallery component 1.7.4 - 2.1.6 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27753</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in RSMediaGallery component 1.7.4 - 2.1.6 for Joomla was discovered. The vulnerability is due to the use of unescaped user-supplied parameters in SQL queries within the dashboard component. This allows an authenticated attacker to inject malicious SQL code through unsanitized input fields, which are used directly in SQL queries. Exploiting this flaw can lead to unauthorized database access, data leakage, or modification of records.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27754 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A stored XSS vulnerability RSBlog! component 1.11.6 - 1.14.4 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27754</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in RSBlog! component 1.11.6 - 1.14.4 for Joomla was discovered. The vulnerability allows authenticated users to inject malicious JavaScript into the plugin's resource. The injected payload is stored by the application and later executed when other users view the affected content.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30084 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A reflected XSS vulnerability RSMail! component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30084</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in RSMail! component 1.19.20 - 1.22.26 for Joomla was discovered. The issue occurs within the dashboard  component, where user-supplied input is not properly sanitized before being stored and rendered. An attacker can inject malicious JavaScript code into text fields or other input points, which is subsequently executed in the browser of any user who clicks on the crafted text in the dashboard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:46:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5659 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5659</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument pincode leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5660 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System register-complaint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5660</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user/register-complaint.php. The manipulation of the argument noc leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:18:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5658 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System updatecomplaint.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5658</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/updatecomplaint.php. The manipulation of the argument Status leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2011-10007 | File::Find::Rule through 0.34 for Perl is vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when `grep()` encounters a crafted file name</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2011-10007</link><description>File::Find::Rule through 0.34 for Perl is vulnerable to Arbitrary Code Execution when `grep()` encounters a crafted filename.

A file handle is opened with the 2 argument form of `open()` allowing an attacker controlled filename to provide the MODE parameter to `open()`, turning the filename into a command to be executed.

Example:

$ mkdir /tmp/poc; echo &gt; "/tmp/poc/|id"
$ perl -MFile::Find::Rule \
    -E 'File::Find::Rule-&gt;grep("foo")-&gt;in("/tmp/poc")'
uid=1000(user) gid=1000(user) groups=1000(user),100(users)</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5657 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System manage-users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5657</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/manage-users.php. The manipulation of the argument uid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5656 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-category.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5656</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-category.php. The manipulation of the argument description leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:37:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5341 | Forminator &amp;lt;= 1.44.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored DOM-Based Cross-Site Scripting via id and data-size Parameters</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5341</link><description>The Forminator Forms – Contact Form, Payment Form &amp; Custom Form Builder plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘id' and 'data-size’ parameters in all versions up to, and including, 1.44.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:26:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5701 | HyperComments &amp;lt;= 1.2.2 - Unauthenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary Options Update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5701</link><description>The HyperComments plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized modification of data that can lead to privilege escalation due to a missing capability check on the hc_request_handler function in all versions up to, and including, 1.2.2. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update arbitrary options on the WordPress site. This can be leveraged to update the default role for registration to administrator and enable user registration for attackers to gain administrative user access to a vulnerable site.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:26:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5654 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-state.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5654</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-state.php. The manipulation of the argument description leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5655 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System edit-subcategory.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5655</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-subcategory.php. The manipulation of the argument subcategory leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 11:08:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5653 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System between-date-userreport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5653</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/between-date-userreport.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4568 | SQL Injection in 2ClickPortal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4568</link><description>Improper neutralization of input provided by an unauthorized user into changes__reference_id parameter in URL allows for boolean-based Blind SQL Injection attacks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5651 | code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System saveuser.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5651</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in code-projects Traffic Offense Reporting System 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file saveuser.php. The manipulation of the argument user_id/username/email/name/position leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5652 | PHPGurukul Complaint Management System between-date-complaintreport.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5652</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Complaint Management System 2.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/between-date-complaintreport.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:24:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5650 | 1000projects Online Notice Board register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5650</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in 1000projects Online Notice Board 1.0. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /register.php. The manipulation of the argument fname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:46:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5648 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5648</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5649 | SourceCodester Student Result Management System Register Interface new_user access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5649</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in SourceCodester Student Result Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/core/new_user of the component Register Interface. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 09:15:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5647 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_context_break_pop memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5647</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9 and classified as problematic. This issue affects the function r_cons_context_break_pop in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is named 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:44:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5646 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_rainbow_free memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5646</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Radare2 5.9.9 and classified as problematic. This vulnerability affects the function r_cons_rainbow_free in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is identified as 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:20:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5645 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5645</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, was found in Radare2 5.9.9. This affects the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. Attacking locally is a requirement. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:43:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5643 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c cons_stack_load memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5643</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected by this vulnerability is the function cons_stack_load in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. An attack has to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation appears to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is named 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5644 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_flush use after free</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5644</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected by this issue is the function r_cons_flush in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to use after free. Local access is required to approach this attack. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The name of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 07:19:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5641 | Radare2 radiff2 cons.c r_cons_is_breaked memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5641</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Radare2 5.9.9. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects the function r_cons_is_breaked in the library /libr/cons/cons.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation of the argument -T leads to memory corruption. It is possible to launch the attack on the local host. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitation is known to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The identifier of the patch is 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". An additional warning regarding threading support has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:46:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5642 | Radare2 radiff2 pal.c r_cons_pal_init memory corruption</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5642</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Radare2 5.9.9. Affected is the function r_cons_pal_init in the library /libr/cons/pal.c of the component radiff2. The manipulation leads to memory corruption. The attack needs to be approached locally. The complexity of an attack is rather high. The exploitability is told to be difficult. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The real existence of this vulnerability is still doubted at the moment. The patch is identified as 5705d99cc1f23f36f9a84aab26d1724010b97798. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The documentation explains that the parameter -T is experimental and "crashy". Further analysis has shown "the race is not a real problem unless you use asan". A new warning has been added.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5640 | PX4-Autopilot TRAJECTORY_REPRESENTATION_WAYPOINTS Message mavlink_receiver.cpp stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5640</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PX4-Autopilot 1.12.3. It has been classified as problematic. This affects the function MavlinkReceiver::handle_message_trajectory_representation_waypoints of the file mavlink_receiver.cpp of the component TRAJECTORY_REPRESENTATION_WAYPOINTS Message Handler. The manipulation leads to stack-based buffer overflow. Local access is required to approach this attack. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 06:15:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3054 | WP User Frontend Pro &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3054</link><description>The WP User Frontend Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the upload_files() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible. Please note that this requires the 'Private Message' module to be enabled and the Business version of the PRO software to be in use.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-3055 | WP User Frontend Pro &amp;lt;= 4.1.3 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-3055</link><description>The WP User Frontend Pro plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the delete_avatar_ajax() function in all versions up to, and including, 4.1.3. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete arbitrary files on the server, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5639 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System forgot-password.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5639</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /forgot-password.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5683 | When loading a specifically crafted ICNS format image file in QImage then it will trigger a crash. This issue affects Qt from versions 6.3.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5683</link><description>When loading a specifically crafted ICNS format image file in QImage then it will trigger a crash. This issue affects Qt from versions 6.3.0 through 6.5.9, from 6.6.0 through 6.8.4, 6.9.0. This is fixed in 6.5.10, 6.8.5 and 6.9.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:35:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5638 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System admin-profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5638</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin-profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:14:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1793 | SQL Injection in run-llama/llama_index</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1793</link><description>Multiple vector store integrations in run-llama/llama_index version v0.12.21 have SQL injection vulnerabilities. These vulnerabilities allow an attacker to read and write data using SQL, potentially leading to unauthorized access to data of other users depending on the usage of the llama-index library in a web application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 05:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5636 | PCMan FTP Server SET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5636</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component SET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5637 | PCMan FTP Server SYSTEM Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5637</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. Affected is an unknown function of the component SYSTEM Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:44:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5634 | PCMan FTP Server NOOP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5634</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This affects an unknown part of the component NOOP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:17:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5635 | PCMan FTP Server PLS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5635</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PCMan FTP Server 2.0.7. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component PLS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 04:17:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5633 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5633</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument delete leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5632 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz users.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5632</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/users.php. The manipulation of the argument change_to_admin leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:54:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49466 | aerc before 93bec0d allows directory traversal in commands/msgview/open.go because of direct path concatenation of the name of an attachment...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49466</link><description>aerc before 93bec0d allows directory traversal in commands/msgview/open.go because of direct path concatenation of the name of an attachment part,</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5631 | code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System/News-Buzz publicposts.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5631</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects/anirbandutta9 Content Management System and News-Buzz 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /publicposts.php. The manipulation of the argument post leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48432 | An issue was discovered in Django 5.2 before 5.2.2, 5.1 before 5.1.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.22. Internal HTTP response logging does not escape...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48432</link><description>An issue was discovered in Django 5.2 before 5.2.2, 5.1 before 5.1.10, and 4.2 before 4.2.22. Internal HTTP response logging does not escape request.path, which allows remote attackers to potentially manipulate log output via crafted URLs. This may lead to log injection or forgery when logs are viewed in terminals or processed by external systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5629 | Tenda AC10 HTTP SetPptpServerCfg formSetPPTPServer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5629</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Tenda AC10 up to 15.03.06.47. This affects the function formSetPPTPServer of the file /goform/SetPptpServerCfg of the component HTTP Handler. The manipulation of the argument startIp/endIp leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:09:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5630 | D-Link DIR-816 form2lansetup.cgi stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5630</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /goform/form2lansetup.cgi. The manipulation of the argument ip leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5628 | SourceCodester Food Menu Manager Add Menu index.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5628</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in SourceCodester Food Menu Manager 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /index.php of the component Add Menu Handler. The manipulation of the argument name/description leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5626 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System edit-subjects-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5626</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/edit-subjects-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5627 | code-projects Patient Record Management System sputum_form.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5627</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in code-projects Patient Record Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sputum_form.php. The manipulation of the argument itr_no leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49008 | Atheos Improper Input Validation Vulnerability Enables RCE in Common.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49008</link><description>Atheos is a self-hosted browser-based cloud integrated development environment. Prior to version 6.0.4, improper use of `escapeshellcmd()` in `/components/codegit/traits/execute.php` allows argument injection, leading to arbitrary command execution. Atheos administrators and users of vulnerable versions are at risk of data breaches or server compromise. Version 6.0.4 introduces a `Common::safe_execute` function that sanitizes all arguments using `escapeshellarg()` prior to execution and migrated all components potentially vulnerable to similar exploits to use this new templated execution system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5624 | D-Link DIR-816 QoSPortSetup stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5624</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function QoSPortSetup of the file /goform/QoSPortSetup. The manipulation of the argument port0_group/port0_remarker/ssid0_group/ssid0_remarker leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5625 | Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System search-teacher.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5625</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Online Teacher Record Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search-teacher.php. The manipulation of the argument searchteacher leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5622 | D-Link DIR-816 wirelessApcli_5g stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5622</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is the function wirelessApcli_5g of the file /goform/wirelessApcli_5g. The manipulation of the argument apcli_mode_5g/apcli_enc_5g/apcli_default_key_5g leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5623 | D-Link DIR-816 qosClassifier stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5623</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05. It has been classified as critical. This affects the function qosClassifier of the file /goform/qosClassifier. The manipulation of the argument dip_address/sip_address leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 01:53:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5620 | D-Link DIR-816 setipsec_config os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5620</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05. Affected is the function setipsec_config of the file /goform/setipsec_config. The manipulation of the argument localIP/remoteIP leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 23:39:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5621 | D-Link DIR-816 qosClassifier os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5621</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in D-Link DIR-816 1.10CNB05 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function qosClassifier of the file /goform/qosClassifier. The manipulation of the argument dip_address/sip_address leads to os command injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 23:39:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5618 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System edit-team.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5618</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-team.php. The manipulation of the argument teamid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 23:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5619 | Tenda CH22 addUserName formaddUserName stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5619</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in Tenda CH22 1.0.0.1. This issue affects the function formaddUserName of the file /goform/addUserName. The manipulation of the argument Password leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 23:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49007 | ReDoS Vulnerability in Rack::Multipart handle_mime_head</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49007</link><description>Rack is a modular Ruby web server interface. Starting in version 3.1.0 and prior to version 3.1.16, there is a denial of service vulnerability in the Content-Disposition parsing component of Rack. This is very similar to the previous security issue CVE-2022-44571. Carefully crafted input can cause Content-Disposition header parsing in Rack to take an unexpected amount of time, possibly resulting in a denial of service attack vector. This header is used typically used in multipart parsing. Any applications that parse multipart posts using Rack (virtually all Rails applications) are impacted. Version 3.1.16 contains a patch for the vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5616 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5616</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5617 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System manage-teams.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5617</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/manage-teams.php. The manipulation of the argument teamid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:40:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5614 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System search-report-result.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5614</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /search-report-result.php. The manipulation of the argument serachdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:13:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5615 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5615</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /details.php. The manipulation of the argument requestid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:13:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5613 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System request-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5613</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /request-details.php. The manipulation of the argument requestid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 21:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5690 | Cursor allows PostgreSQL Anonymizer masked user to gain unauthorized access to authentic data</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5690</link><description>PostgreSQL Anonymizer v2.0 and v2.1 contain a vulnerability that allows a masked user to bypass the masking rules defined on a table and read the original data using a database cursor or the --insert option of pg_dump. This problem occurs only when dynamic masking is enabled, which is not the default setting. The problem is resolved in version 2.2.1</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 21:35:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5612 | PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System reporting.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5612</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Online Fire Reporting System 1.2 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /reporting.php. The manipulation of the argument fullname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 21:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5610 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System submitpropertydelete.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5610</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /submitpropertydelete.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5611 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System submitpropertyupdate.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5611</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /submitpropertyupdate.php. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:40:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46341 | Privilege escalation via SSRF when using HTTP auth</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46341</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. Prior to version 1.26.2, when the server is using HTTP auth via reverse proxy, it's possible to impersonate any user either via the `Remote-User` header or the `X-WebAuth-User` header by making specially crafted requests via the add feed functionality and obtaining the CSRF token via XPath scraping. The attacker has to know the IP address of the proxied FreshRSS instance and the admin's username, while also having an account on the instance. An attacker can send specially crafted requests in order to gain unauthorized access to internal services. This can also lead to privilege escalation like in the demonstrated scenario, although users that have setup OIDC are not affected by privilege escalation. Version 1.26.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48947 | NextJS-Auth0 SDK Vulnerable to CDN Caching of Session Cookies</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48947</link><description>The Auth0 Next.js SDK is a library for implementing user authentication in Next.js applications. In Auth0 Next.js SDK versions 4.0.1 through 4.6.0, `__session` cookies set by auth0.middleware may be cached by CDNs due to missing Cache-Control headers. Three preconditions must be met in order for someone to be affected by the vulnerability: Applications using the NextJS-Auth0 SDK, versions between 4.0.1 to 4.6.0, applications using CDN or edge caching that caches responses with the Set-Cookie header, and if the Cache-Control header is not properly set for sensitive responses. Users should upgrade auth0/nextjs-auth0 to v4.6.1 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32015 | FreshRSS vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting by embedding &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; tag inside &amp;lt;iframe srcdoc&amp;gt;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32015</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. Prior to version 1.26.2, HTML is sanitized improperly inside the `` attribute, which leads to cross-site scripting (XSS) by loading an attacker's UserJS inside `</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46339 | FreshRSS vulnerable to favicon cache poisoning via proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46339</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. Prior to version 1.26.2, it's possible to poison feed favicons by adding a given URL as a feed with the proxy set to an attacker-controlled one and disabled SSL verifying. The favicon hash is computed by hashing the feed URL and the salt, whilst not including the following variables: proxy address, proxy protocol, and whether SSL should be verified. Therefore it's possible to poison a favicon of a given feed by simply intercepting the response of the feed, and changing the website URL to one where a threat actor controls the feed favicon. Feed favicons can be replaced for all users by anyone. Version 1.26.2 fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5608 | Tenda AC18 SetSysAutoRebbotCfg formsetreboottimer buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5608</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected is the function formsetreboottimer of the file /goform/SetSysAutoRebbotCfg. The manipulation of the argument rebootTime leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5609 | Tenda AC18 AdvSetLanip fromadvsetlanip buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5609</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. Affected by this vulnerability is the function fromadvsetlanip of the file /goform/AdvSetLanip. The manipulation of the argument lanMask leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:21:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31482 | FreshRSS vulnerable to DoS by malicious feed entry loading logout URL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31482</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. A vulnerability in versions prior to 1.26.2 causes a user to be repeatedly logged out after fetching a malicious feed entry, effectively causing that user to suffer denial of service. Version 1.26.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46011 | Listmonk v2.4.0 through v4.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the QuerySubscribers function which allows attackers to escalate privileges...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46011</link><description>Listmonk v2.4.0 through v4.1.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection in the QuerySubscribers function which allows attackers to escalate privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:54:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31136 | FreshRSS vulnerable to Cross-site Scripting by &amp;lt;iframe&amp;gt;&amp;#x27;ing a vulnerable same-origin page in a feed entry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31136</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. Prior to version 1.26.2, it's possible to run arbitrary JavaScript on the feeds page.
This occurs by combining a cross-site scripting (XSS) issue that occurs in `f.php` when SVG favicons are downloaded from an attacker-controlled feed containing `</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:54:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31134 | FreshRSS vulnerable to directory enumeration via ext.php</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31134</link><description>FreshRSS is a self-hosted RSS feed aggregator. Prior to version 1.26.2, an attacker can gain additional information about the server by checking if certain directories exist. An attacker can, for example, check if older PHP versions are installed or if certain software is installed on the server and potentially use that information to further attack the server. Version 1.26.2 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:47:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46203 | An issue in Unifiedtransform v2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /students/edit/{id} endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46203</link><description>An issue in Unifiedtransform v2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /students/edit/{id} endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46204 | An issue in Unifiedtransform v2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /course/edit/{id} endpoint.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46204</link><description>An issue in Unifiedtransform v2.0 allows a remote attacker to escalate privileges via the /course/edit/{id} endpoint.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:47:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22243 | VMware NSX Manager UI is vulnerable to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack due to improper input validation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22243</link><description>VMware NSX Manager UI is vulnerable to a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) attack due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:40:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22244 | VMware NSX contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the gateway firewall due to improper input validation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22244</link><description>VMware NSX contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the gateway firewall due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-22245 | VMware NSX contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the router port due to improper input validation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-22245</link><description>VMware NSX contains a stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the router port due to improper input validation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:40:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48935 | Deno has --allow-read / --allow-write permission bypass in `node:sqlite`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48935</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Starting in version 2.2.0 and prior to versions 2.2.5, it is possible to bypass Deno's permission read/write db permission check by using `ATTACH DATABASE` statement. Version 2.2.5 contains a patch for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5607 | Tenda AC18 setPptpUserList formSetPPTPUserList buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5607</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects the function formSetPPTPUserList of the file /goform/setPptpUserList. The manipulation of the argument list leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:40:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48888 | Deno run with --allow-read and --deny-read flags results in allowed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48888</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Starting in version 1.41.3 and prior to versions 2.1.13, 2.2.13, and 2.3.2, `deno run --allow-read --deny-read main.ts` results in allowed, even though 'deny' should be stronger. The result is the same with all global unary permissions given as `--allow-* --deny-*`. This only affects a nonsensical combination of flags, so there shouldn't be a real impact on the userbase. Users may upgrade to version 2.1.13, 2.2.13, or 2.3.2 to receive a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48934 | Deno.env.toObject() ignores the variables listed in --deny-env and returns all environment variables</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48934</link><description>Deno is a JavaScript, TypeScript, and WebAssembly runtime. Prior to versions 2.1.13 and 2.2.13, the `Deno.env.toObject` method ignores any variables listed in the `--deny-env` option of the `deno run` command. When looking at the documentation of the `--deny-env` option this might lead to a false impression that variables listed in the option are impossible to read. Software relying on the combination of both flags to allow access to most environment variables except a few sensitive ones will be vulnerable to malicious code trying to steal secrets using the `Deno.env.toObject()` method. Versions 2.1.13 and 2.2.13 contains a patch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5606 | Tenda AC18 SetIPTVCfg formSetIptv command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5606</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC18 15.03.05.05. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects the function formSetIptv of the file /goform/SetIPTVCfg. The manipulation of the argument list leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5604 | Campcodes Hospital Management System user-login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5604</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Campcodes Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /user-login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 18:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5602 | Campcodes Hospital Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5602</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in Campcodes Hospital Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /admin/registration.php. The manipulation of the argument full_name leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5603 | Campcodes Hospital Management System registration.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5603</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Campcodes Hospital Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /registration.php. The manipulation of the argument full_name/username leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 18:24:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5599 | PHPGurukul Student Result Management System editmyexp.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5599</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Student Result Management System 1.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /editmyexp.php. The manipulation of the argument emp1ctc leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5600 | TOTOLINK EX1200T cstecgi.cgi setLanguageCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5600</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in TOTOLINK EX1200T 4.1.2cu.5232_B20210713. This issue affects the function setLanguageCfg of the file /cgi-bin/cstecgi.cgi. The manipulation of the argument LangType leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:44:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5688 | Out of Bounds Write in FreeRTOS-Plus-TCP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5688</link><description>We have identified a buffer overflow issue allowing out-of-bounds write when processing LLMNR or mDNS queries with very long DNS names. This issue only affects systems using Buffer Allocation Scheme 1 with LLMNR or mDNS enabled.


Users should upgrade to the latest version and ensure any forked or derivative code is patched to incorporate the new fixes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5596 | FreeFloat FTP Server REGET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5596</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the component REGET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:09:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2336 | AngularJS improper sanitization in SVG &amp;#x27;&amp;lt;image&amp;gt;&amp;#x27; element with &amp;#x27;ngSanitize&amp;#x27;</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2336</link><description>Improper sanitization of the value of the 'href' and 'xlink:href' attributes in '' SVG elements in AngularJS's 'ngSanitize' module allows attackers to bypass common image source restrictions. This can lead to a form of  Content Spoofing https://owasp.org/www-community/attacks/Content_Spoofing  and also negatively affect the application's performance and behavior by using too large or slow-to-load images.

This issue affects AngularJS versions greater than or equal to 1.3.1.

Note:
The AngularJS project is End-of-Life and will not receive any updates to address this issue. For more information see  here https://docs.angularjs.org/misc/version-support-status .</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5595 | FreeFloat FTP Server PROGRESS Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5595</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component PROGRESS Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20129 | Cisco Customer Collaboration Platform Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20129</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based chat interface of Cisco Customer Collaboration Platform (CCP), formerly Cisco SocialMiner, could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to persuade users to disclose sensitive data.

This vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of HTTP requests that are sent to the web-based chat interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending crafted HTTP requests to the chat interface of a targeted user on a vulnerable server. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to redirect chat traffic to a server that is under their control, resulting in sensitive information being redirected to the attacker.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20130 | Cisco Identity Services Engine Access Control Bypass Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20130</link><description>A vulnerability in the API of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) and Cisco ISE Passive Identity Connector (ISE-PIC) could allow an authenticated, remote attacker with administrative privileges to upload files to an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of the file copy function. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted file upload request to a specific API endpoint. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to upload arbitrary files to an affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20163 | Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller SSH Host Key Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20163</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH implementation of Cisco Nexus Dashboard Fabric Controller (NDFC) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to impersonate Cisco NDFC-managed devices.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient SSH host key validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by performing a machine-in-the-middle attack on SSH connections to Cisco NDFC-managed devices, which could allow an attacker to intercept this traffic. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to impersonate a managed device and capture user credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20259 | Cisco ThousandEyes Endpoint Agent for Windows Arbitrary File Write Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20259</link><description>Multiple vulnerabilities in the update process of Cisco ThousandEyes Endpoint Agent for Windows could allow an authenticated, local attacker to delete arbitrary files on an affected device.

These vulnerabilities are due to improper access controls on files that are in the local file system. An attacker could exploit these vulnerabilities by using a symbolic link to perform an agent upgrade that redirects the delete operation of any protected file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to delete arbitrary files from the file system of the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20261 | Cisco Integrated Management Controller Privilege Escalation Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20261</link><description>A vulnerability in the SSH connection handling of Cisco Integrated Management Controller (IMC) for Cisco UCS B-Series, UCS C-Series, UCS S-Series, and UCS X-Series Servers could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to access internal services with elevated privileges.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient restrictions on access to internal services. An attacker with a valid user account could exploit this vulnerability by using crafted syntax when connecting to the Cisco IMC of an affected device through SSH. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access internal services with elevated privileges, which may allow unauthorized modifications to the system, including the possibility of creating new administrator accounts on the affected device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20273 | Cisco Unified Intelligent Contact Management Enterprise Cross-Site Scripting vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20273</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified Intelligent Contact Management Enterprise could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a cross-site scripting (XSS) attack against a user of the web-based management interface of an affected device.

This vulnerability is due to insufficient user input validation. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading a user of the interface to click a crafted link. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary script code in the context of the affected interface or access sensitive, browser-based information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20275 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Editor Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20275</link><description>A vulnerability in the file opening process of Cisco Unified Contact Center Express (Unified CCX) Editor could allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insecure deserialization of Java objects by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by persuading an authenticated, local user to open a crafted .aef file. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the host that is running the editor application with the privileges of the user who launched it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20276 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Remote Code Execution Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20276</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.&amp;nbsp;

This vulnerability is due to insecure deserialization of Java objects by the affected software. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted Java object to an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of an affected device as a low-privilege user. A successful exploit could also allow the attacker to undertake further actions to elevate their privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20277 | Cisco Unified Contact Center Express Path Traversal Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20277</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary code on an affected device. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper limitation of a pathname to a restricted directory (path traversal). An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a crafted web request to an affected device, followed by a specific command through an SSH session. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary code on the underlying operating system of an affected device as a low-privilege user. A successful exploit could also allow the attacker to undertake further actions to elevate their privileges to root.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20278 | Cisco Unified Communications Products Command Injection Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20278</link><description>A vulnerability in the CLI of multiple Cisco Unified Communications products could allow an authenticated, local attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device as the root user.

This vulnerability is due to improper validation of user-supplied command arguments. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by executing crafted commands on the CLI of an affected device. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of an affected device as the root user. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20279 | Cisco Unifed Contact Center Express Stored Cross-Site Scripting Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20279</link><description>A vulnerability in the web-based management interface of Cisco Unified CCX could allow an authenticated, remote attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack on an affected system. To exploit this vulnerability, the attacker must have valid administrative credentials.

This vulnerability is due to improper sanitization of user input to the web-based management interface. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by submitting a malicious script through the interface. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to conduct a stored XSS attack on the affected system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20286 | ISE on AWS Static Credential</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20286</link><description>A vulnerability in Amazon Web Services (AWS), Microsoft Azure, and Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) cloud deployments of Cisco Identity Services Engine (ISE) could allow an unauthenticated, remote attacker to access sensitive data, execute limited administrative operations, modify system configurations, or disrupt services within the impacted systems.

This vulnerability exists  because credentials are improperly generated when Cisco ISE is being deployed on cloud platforms, resulting in different Cisco ISE deployments sharing the same credentials. These credentials are shared across multiple Cisco ISE deployments as long as the software release and cloud platform are the same. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by extracting the user credentials from Cisco ISE that is deployed in the cloud and then using them to access Cisco ISE that is deployed in other cloud environments through unsecured ports. A successful exploit could allow the attacker to access sensitive data, execute limited administrative operations, modify system configurations, or disrupt services within the impacted systems.
Note: If the Primary Administration node is deployed in the cloud, then Cisco ISE is affected by this vulnerability. If the Primary Administration node is on-premises, then it is not affected.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:43:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29094 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Motivian Content Mangment System v.41.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the M...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29094</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Motivian Content Mangment System v.41.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Marketing/Forms, Marketing/Offers and Content/Pages components.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5594 | FreeFloat FTP Server SET Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5594</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the component SET Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:23:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5593 | FreeFloat FTP Server HOST Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5593</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the component HOST Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23106 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23106</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 2200, 1480, and 2400. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-29093 | File Upload vulnerability in Motivian Content Mangment System v.41.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content/Ga...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-29093</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in Motivian Content Mangment System v.41.0.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via the Content/Gallery/Images component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23095 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Double Free in the mobile processor leads to priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23095</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Double Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:39:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23096 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Double Free in the mobile processor leads to priv...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23096</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1280, 2200, 1380, 1480, 2400. A Double Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-23101 | An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1380. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-23101</link><description>An issue was discovered in Samsung Mobile Processor Exynos 1380. A Use-After-Free in the mobile processor leads to privilege escalation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 14:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27811 | A local privilege escalation in the razer_elevation_service.exe in Razer Synapse 4 through 4.0.86.2502180127 allows a local attacker to esca...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27811</link><description>A local privilege escalation in the razer_elevation_service.exe in Razer Synapse 4 through 4.0.86.2502180127 allows a local attacker to escalate their privileges via a vulnerable COM interface in the target service.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5592 | FreeFloat FTP Server PASSIVE Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5592</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component PASSIVE Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48960 | Weak server key used for TLS encryption. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48960</link><description>Weak server key used for TLS encryption. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 39938.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48961 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) befor...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48961</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure folder permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows) before build 39938.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48962 | Sensitive information disclosure due to SSRF. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows, Linux) before build 39...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48962</link><description>Sensitive information disclosure due to SSRF. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect 16 (Windows, Linux) before build 39938.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 13:41:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1701 | Local Privilege Escalation in MIM Admin Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1701</link><description>CVE-2025-1701 is a high-severity vulnerability in the MIM Admin service. An attacker could exploit this vulnerability by sending a specially crafted request over the RMI interface to execute arbitrary code with the privileges of the MIM Admin service. The RMI interface is only accessible locally (listening on 127.0.0.1), limiting the attack vector to the local machine.  This means that in a properly configured hospital environment, an attacker must have already compromised the network and additionally compromised the system where the MIM Admin service is running.  From there, attackers with sufficient knowledge of MIM's implementation, library usage, and functionality with access to extend the MIM RMI library could force the MIM Admin service to run commands on the local machine with its privileges.

Users of MIM Software products exposed via RDP or multi-user application virtualization system should take note that the system being exposed is the environment hosting the virtualized MIM client.



This issue affects MIM Admin Service: before 7.2.13, 7.3.8, 7.4.3</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 13:41:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-30415 | Denial of service due to improper handling of malformed input. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-30415</link><description>Denial of service due to improper handling of malformed input. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Linux, macOS, Windows) before build 40077.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48959 | Local privilege escalation due to insecure file permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48959</link><description>Local privilege escalation due to insecure file permissions. The following products are affected: Acronis Cyber Protect Cloud Agent (Windows) before build 40077.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5597 | WF Steuerungstechnik GmbH - airleader MASTER - Authentication Bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5597</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in WF Steuerungstechnik GmbH airleader MASTER allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects airleader MASTER: 3.00571.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:40:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5598 | WF Steuerungstechnik GmbH - airleader MASTER - Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5598</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in WF Steuerungstechnik GmbH airleader MASTER allows Retrieve Embedded Sensitive Data.This issue affects airleader MASTER: 3.0046.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:30:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5601 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input (&amp;#x27;Classic Buffer Overflow&amp;#x27;) in Wireshark</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5601</link><description>Column handling crashes in Wireshark 4.4.0 to 4.4.6 and 4.2.0 to 4.2.12 allows denial of service via packet injection or crafted capture file</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 10:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5584 | PHPGurukul Hospital Management System POST Parameter edit-patient.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5584</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Hospital Management System 4.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is an unknown function of the file /doctor/edit-patient.php?editid=2 of the component POST Parameter Handler. The manipulation of the argument patname leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 10:13:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25112 | PHOENIX CONTACT: ILC 1x1 ETH Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25112</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use an uncontrolled resource consumption in the IEC 61131 program of the affected products by creating large amounts of network traffic that needs to be handled by the ILC. This results in a Denial-of-Service of the device.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:48:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5583 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System register.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5583</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the file /register.php. The manipulation leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:48:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5581 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5581</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/index.php. The manipulation of the argument User leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5582 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5582</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument content leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5580 | CodeAstro Real Estate Management System login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5580</link><description>A vulnerability was found in CodeAstro Real Estate Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument email leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:45:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-13967 | ession-Management Failure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-13967</link><description>This vulnerability allows the successful attacker to gain unauthorized access to a 
configuration web page delivered by the integrated web Server of EIBPORT.

This issue affects EIBPORT V3 KNX: through 3.9.8; EIBPORT V3 KNX GSM: through 3.9.8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47728 | File Parsing Memory Corruption in CNCSoft-G2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47728</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft-G2 lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5578 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System sales-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5578</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /sales-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5579 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System search-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5579</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /search-product.php. The manipulation of the argument productname leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5576 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System bwdate-report-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5576</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /bwdate-report-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5577 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System profile.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5577</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. Affected is an unknown function of the file /profile.php. The manipulation of the argument mobilenumber leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:44:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27444 | Extension - rsjoomla.com - A reflected XSS vulnerability RSform!Pro component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27444</link><description>A reflected XSS vulnerability in RSform!Pro component 3.0.0 - 3.3.13 for Joomla was discovered. The issue arises from the improper handling of the filter[dateFrom] GET parameter, which is reflected unescaped in the administrative backend interface. This allows an authenticated attacker with admin or editor privileges to inject arbitrary JavaScript code by crafting a malicious URL.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47724 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47724</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47725 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47725</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47726 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47726</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47727 | Out-of-bounds Write in CNCSoft</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47727</link><description>Delta Electronics CNCSoft lacks proper validation of the user-supplied file. If a user opens a malicious file, an attacker can leverage this vulnerability to execute code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5482 | Sunshine Photo Cart &amp;lt;= 3.4.11 - Authenticated (Subscriber) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5482</link><description>The Sunshine Photo Cart: Free Client Photo Galleries for Photographers plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation via account takeover in all versions up to, and including, 3.4.11. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user-supplied key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change arbitrary user's passwords through the password reset functionality, including administrators, and leverage that to reset the user's password and gain access to their account.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5575 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System add-product.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5575</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /add-product.php. The manipulation of the argument productname leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5574 | PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System add-company.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5574</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Dairy Farm Shop Management System 1.3. This affects an unknown part of the file /add-company.php. The manipulation of the argument companyname leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:47:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4578 | File Provider &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Unauthenticated SQLi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4578</link><description>The File Provider WordPress plugin through 1.2.3 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement via an AJAX action available to unauthenticated users, leading to a SQL injection</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4580 | File Provider &amp;lt;= 1.2.3 - Item Deletion via CSRF</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4580</link><description>The File Provider WordPress plugin through 1.2.3 does not have CSRF check in place when updating its settings, which could allow attackers to make a logged in admin change them via a CSRF attack</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5572 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemEmail stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5572</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function setSystemEmail of the file /setSystemEmail. The manipulation of the argument EmailSMTPPortNumber leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5573 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemWizard setSystemControl os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5573</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function setSystemWizard/setSystemControl of the file /setSystemWizard. The manipulation of the argument AdminID leads to os command injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 06:20:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48710 | kro (Kube Resource Orchestrator) 0.1.0 before 0.2.1 allows users (with permission to create or modify ResourceGraphDefinition resources) to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48710</link><description>kro (Kube Resource Orchestrator) 0.1.0 before 0.2.1 allows users (with permission to create or modify ResourceGraphDefinition resources) to supply arbitrary container images. This can lead to a confused-deputy scenario where kro's controllers deploy and run attacker-controlled images, resulting in unauthenticated remote code execution on cluster nodes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5569 | IdeaCMS getList.html Goods sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5569</link><description>A vulnerability was found in IdeaCMS up to 1.7 and classified as critical. This issue affects the function Article/Goods of the file /api/v1.index.article/getList.html. The manipulation of the argument Field leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. Upgrading to version 1.8 is able to address this issue. The patch is named 935aceb4c21338633de6d41e13332f7b9db4fa6a. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:39:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5571 | D-Link DCS-932L setSystemAdmin os command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5571</link><description>A vulnerability was found in D-Link DCS-932L 2.18.01. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function setSystemAdmin of the file /setSystemAdmin. The manipulation of the argument AdminID leads to os command injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5562 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System edit-category-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5562</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/edit-category-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5566 | PHPGurukul Notice Board System search-notice.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5566</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in PHPGurukul Notice Board System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /search-notice.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20981 | Improper access control in AudioService prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20981</link><description>Improper access control in AudioService prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20984 | Incorrect default permission in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data in Sams...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20984</link><description>Incorrect default permission in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to access data in Samsung Cloud for Galaxy Watch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20985 | Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20985</link><description>Improper privilege management in ThemeManager prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to reuse trial items.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20986 | Improper access control in ScreenCapture for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to take screenshots.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20986</link><description>Improper access control in ScreenCapture for Galaxy Watch prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to take screenshots.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20987 | Improper access control in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a auth_token.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20987</link><description>Improper access control in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a auth_token.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20988 | Out-of-bounds read in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20988</link><description>Out-of-bounds read in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20989 | Improper logging in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a hmac_key.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20989</link><description>Improper logging in fingerprint trustlet prior to SMR May-2025 Release 1 allows local privileged attackers to get a hmac_key.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20991 | Improper export of Android application components in Bluetooth prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to make devices discov...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20991</link><description>Improper export of Android application components in Bluetooth prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to make devices discoverable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20992 | Out-of-bound read in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20992</link><description>Out-of-bound read in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Feb-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to read out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20993 | Out-of-bounds write in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20993</link><description>Out-of-bounds write in libsecimaging.camera.samsung.so prior to SMR Jun-2025 Release 1 allows local attackers to write out-of-bounds memory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20994 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in SyncClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20994</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in SyncClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.59 allows local attackers to access read and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20995 | Improper handling of insufficient permission in ClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.5...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20995</link><description>Improper handling of insufficient permission in ClientProvider in Samsung Internet installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 28.0.0.59 allows local attackers to read and write arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-20996 | Improper authorization in Smart Switch installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 3.7.64.10 allows local attackers to read data with t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-20996</link><description>Improper authorization in Smart Switch installed on non-Samsung Device prior to version 3.7.64.10 allows local attackers to read data with the privilege of Smart Switch. User interaction is required for triggering this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-31127 | MacOS Zscaler Client Connector Local Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-31127</link><description>An improper verification of a loaded library in Zscaler Client Connector on Mac &lt; 4.2.0.241 may allow a local attacker to elevate their privileges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:59:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5561 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System view-pass-detail.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5561</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /admin/view-pass-detail.php. The manipulation of the argument viewid leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:51:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5539 | Simplify Contact Management: WP Easy Contact &amp;lt;= 4.0.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5539</link><description>The Simple Contact Form Plugin for WordPress – WP Easy Contact plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.0.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:35:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5558 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System changeimage.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5558</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /admin/changeimage.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5560 | PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System index.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5560</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Curfew e-Pass Management System 1.0. It has been classified as critical. Affected is an unknown function of the file /index.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5531 | Staff Directory – Employee Directory for WordPress &amp;lt;= 4.5.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5531</link><description>The Employee Directory – Staff Listing &amp; Team Directory Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.5.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5532 | Faculty Staff and Student Directory Plugin – Campus Directory &amp;lt;= 1.9.0 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5532</link><description>The Campus Directory – Faculty, Staff &amp; Student Directory Plugin for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'emd_mb_meta' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.9.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5557 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System edit-course.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5557</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0 and classified as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /admin/edit-course.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 04:03:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5556 | PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System edit-teacher-info.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5556</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in PHPGurukul Teacher Subject Allocation Management System 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /admin/edit-teacher-info.php. The manipulation of the argument editid leads to sql injection. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 03:40:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5554 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System pass-bwdates-reports-details.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5554</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /admin/pass-bwdates-reports-details.php. The manipulation of the argument fromdate/todate leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 03:40:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-49223 | billboard.js before 3.15.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function generate, which could allow attackers to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-49223</link><description>billboard.js before 3.15.1 was discovered to contain a prototype pollution via the function generate, which could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code or cause a Denial of Service (DoS) via injecting arbitrary properties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5552 | ChestnutCMS API Endpoint exec deserialization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5552</link><description>A vulnerability was found in ChestnutCMS up to 15.1. It has been declared as critical. This vulnerability affects unknown code of the file /dev-api/groovy/exec of the component API Endpoint. The manipulation leads to deserialization. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5553 | PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System download-pass.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5553</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in PHPGurukul Rail Pass Management System 1.0. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /download-pass.php. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5551 | FreeFloat FTP Server SYSTEM Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5551</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. It has been classified as critical. This affects an unknown part of the component SYSTEM Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5549 | FreeFloat FTP Server PASV Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5549</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component PASV Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5550 | FreeFloat FTP Server PBSZ Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5550</link><description>A vulnerability was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0 and classified as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component PBSZ Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5548 | FreeFloat FTP Server NOOP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5548</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, was found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. Affected is an unknown function of the component NOOP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5547 | FreeFloat FTP Server CDUP Command buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5547</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as critical, has been found in FreeFloat FTP Server 1.0. This issue affects some unknown processing of the component CDUP Command Handler. The manipulation leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 01:13:29 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>