<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:56:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2022-45348 | WordPress amr users Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.59.4 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45348</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in anmari amr users.This issue affects amr users: from n/a through 4.59.4.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:56:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45810 | WordPress Email Subscribers &amp;amp; Newsletters Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.5.2 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45810</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Icegram Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters and Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce.This issue affects Icegram Express – Email Marketing, Newsletters and Automation for WordPress &amp; WooCommerce: from n/a through 5.5.2.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46821 | WordPress Emails &amp;amp; Newsletters with Jackmail Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.22 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46821</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Jackmail &amp; Sarbacane Emails &amp; Newsletters with Jackmail.This issue affects Emails &amp; Newsletters with Jackmail: from n/a through 1.2.22.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:56:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46803 | WordPress Noptin Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.5 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46803</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Noptin Newsletter Simple Newsletter Plugin – Noptin.This issue affects Simple Newsletter Plugin – Noptin: from n/a through 1.9.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46804 | WordPress Export Users Data Distinct Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.3 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46804</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Narola Infotech Solutions LLP Export Users Data Distinct.This issue affects Export Users Data Distinct: from n/a through 1.3.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46809 | WordPress ReviewX Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46809</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in WPDeveloper ReviewX – Multi-criteria Rating &amp; Reviews for WooCommerce.This issue affects ReviewX – Multi-criteria Rating &amp; Reviews for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.6.7.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0898 | Uncontrolled Search Path Element in GE MiCOM S1 Agile</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0898</link><description>General Electric MiCOM S1 Agile is vulnerable to an attacker achieving code execution by placing malicious DLL files in the directory of the application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:46:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46801 | WordPress Site Reviews Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.2.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46801</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Paul Ryley Site Reviews.This issue affects Site Reviews: from n/a through 6.2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:36:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46802 | WordPress Product Reviews Import Export for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.8 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46802</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in WebToffee Product Reviews Import Export for WooCommerce.This issue affects Product Reviews Import Export for WooCommerce: from n/a through 1.4.8.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23796 | WordPress Form Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.9.9.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23796</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Muneeb Form Builder | Create Responsive Contact Forms.This issue affects Form Builder | Create Responsive Contact Forms: from n/a through 1.9.9.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36527 | WordPress Post to CSV by BestWebSoft Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.0 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36527</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in BestWebSoft Post to CSV by BestWebSoft.This issue affects Post to CSV by BestWebSoft: from n/a through 1.4.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:36:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45357 | WordPress 1003 Mortgage Application Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.75 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45357</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Lenderd 1003 Mortgage Application.This issue affects 1003 Mortgage Application: from n/a through 1.75.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23678 | WordPress WP Cookie Notice for GDPR, CCPA &amp;amp; ePrivacy Consent Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.5 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23678</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in WPEkaClub WP Cookie Consent ( for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy ).This issue affects WP Cookie Consent ( for GDPR, CCPA &amp; ePrivacy ): from n/a through 2.2.5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:57:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22719 | WordPress GiveWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.25.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22719</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in GiveWP.This issue affects GiveWP: from n/a through 2.25.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:47:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4295 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver allows improper GPU memory processing operations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4295</link><description>A local non-privileged user can make improper GPU memory processing operations to gain access to already freed memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:47:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3889 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver exposes sensitive data from freed memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3889</link><description>A local non-privileged user can make improper GPU memory processing operations. If the operations are carefully prepared, then they could be used to gain access to already freed memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41425 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Wonder CMS v.3.2.0 thru v.3.4.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted scrip...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41425</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Wonder CMS v.3.2.0 thru v.3.4.2 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted script uploaded to the installModule component.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47359 | Videolan VLC prior to version 3.0.20 contains an incorrect offset read that leads to a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow in function GetPacket() an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47359</link><description>Videolan VLC prior to version 3.0.20 contains an incorrect offset read that leads to a Heap-Based Buffer Overflow in function GetPacket() and results in a memory corruption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47360 | Videolan VLC prior to version 3.0.20 contains an Integer underflow that leads to an incorrect packet length.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47360</link><description>Videolan VLC prior to version 3.0.20 contains an Integer underflow that leads to an incorrect packet length.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4272 | Mali GPU Kernel Driver exposes sensitive data from freed memory</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4272</link><description>A local non-privileged user can make GPU processing operations that expose sensitive data from previously freed memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:37:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-25983 | WordPress KB Support Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.84 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-25983</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in WPOmnia KB Support.This issue affects KB Support: from n/a through 1.5.84.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42659 | WS_FTP Server Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42659</link><description>In WS_FTP Server versions prior to 8.7.6 and 8.8.4, an unrestricted file upload flaw has been identified.  An authenticated Ad Hoc Transfer user has the ability to craft an API call which allows them to upload a file to a specified location on the underlying operating system hosting the WS_FTP Server application.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5179 | An issue was discovered in Open Design Alliance Drawings SDK before 2024.10. A corrupted value for the start of MiniFat sector in a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5179</link><description>An issue was discovered in Open Design Alliance Drawings SDK before 2024.10. A corrupted value for the start of MiniFat sector in a crafted DGN file leads to an out-of-bounds read. This can allow attackers to cause a crash, potentially enabling a denial-of-service attack (Crash, Exit, or Restart) or possible code execution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45350 | WordPress Simple History Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.3.1 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45350</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in Pär Thernström Simple History – user activity log, audit tool.This issue affects Simple History – user activity log, audit tool: from n/a through 3.3.1.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47442 | WordPress UsersWP Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.3.9 is vulnerable to CSV Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47442</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Formula Elements in a CSV File vulnerability in AyeCode Ltd UsersWP.This issue affects UsersWP: from n/a through 1.2.3.9.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33480 | RemoteClinic 2.0 contains a critical vulnerability chain that can be exploited by a remote attacker with low-privileged user credentials to ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33480</link><description>RemoteClinic 2.0 contains a critical vulnerability chain that can be exploited by a remote attacker with low-privileged user credentials to create admin users, escalate privileges, and execute arbitrary code on the target system via a PHP shell. The vulnerabilities are caused by a lack of input validation and access control in the staff/register.php endpoint and the edit-my-profile.php page. By sending a series of specially crafted requests to the RemoteClinic application, an attacker can create admin users with more privileges than their own, upload a PHP file containing arbitrary code, and execute arbitrary commands via the PHP shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33481 | RemoteClinic 2.0 is vulnerable to a time-based blind SQL injection attack in the 'start' GET parameter of patients/index.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33481</link><description>RemoteClinic 2.0 is vulnerable to a time-based blind SQL injection attack in the 'start' GET parameter of patients/index.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33478 | RemoteClinic 2.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the ID parameter of /medicines/stocks.php.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33478</link><description>RemoteClinic 2.0 has a SQL injection vulnerability in the ID parameter of /medicines/stocks.php.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33479 | RemoteClinic version 2.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /staff/edit.php file.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33479</link><description>RemoteClinic version 2.0 contains a SQL injection vulnerability in the /staff/edit.php file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47455 | Tenda AX1806 V1.0.0.1 contains a heap overflow vulnerability in setSchedWifi function, in which the src and v12 are directly obtained from h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47455</link><description>Tenda AX1806 V1.0.0.1 contains a heap overflow vulnerability in setSchedWifi function, in which the src and v12 are directly obtained from http request parameter schedStartTime and schedEndTime without checking their size.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:59:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47456 | Tenda AX1806 V1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow vulnerability in function sub_455D4, called by function fromSetWirelessRepeat.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47456</link><description>Tenda AX1806 V1.0.0.1 contains a stack overflow vulnerability in function sub_455D4, called by function fromSetWirelessRepeat.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:59:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-0436 | Secret logging may occur in debug mode of Atlas Operator </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-0436</link><description>The affected versions of MongoDB Atlas Kubernetes Operator may print sensitive information like GCP service account keys and API integration secrets while DEBUG mode logging is enabled. This issue affects MongoDB Atlas Kubernetes Operator versions: 1.5.0, 1.6.0, 1.6.1, 1.7.0.

Please note that this is reported on an EOL version of the product, and users are advised to upgrade to the latest supported version.
Required Configuration: 

DEBUG logging is not enabled by default, and must be configured by the end-user. To check the log-level of the Operator, review the flags passed in your deployment configuration (eg.  https://github.com/mongodb/mongodb-atlas-kubernetes/blob/main/config/manager/manager.yaml#L27 https://github.com/mongodb/mongodb-atlas-kubernetes/blob/main/config/manager/manager.yaml#L27 )</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:58:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4842 | The Social Sharing Plugin - Social Warfare plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'social_warfare' shortcode ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4842</link><description>The Social Sharing Plugin - Social Warfare plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'social_warfare' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 4.4.3 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4888 | The Simple Like Page Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'sfp-page-plugin' shortcode in versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4888</link><description>The Simple Like Page Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'sfp-page-plugin' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.5.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5567 | The QR Code Tag plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'qrcodetag' shortcode in versions up to, and including...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5567</link><description>The QR Code Tag plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'qrcodetag' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5577 | The Bitly's plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpbitly' shortcode in all versions up to, an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5577</link><description>The Bitly's plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpbitly' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5659 | The Interact: Embed A Quiz On Your Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'interact-quiz' s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5659</link><description>The Interact: Embed A Quiz On Your Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'interact-quiz' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.0.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5660 | The SendPress Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5660</link><description>The SendPress Newsletters plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode(s) in all versions up to, and including, 1.22.3.31 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5661 | The Social Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'socialfeed' shortcode in all versions up...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5661</link><description>The Social Feed plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'socialfeed' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.5.4.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with author-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5669 | The Featured Image Caption plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode and post meta in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5669</link><description>The Featured Image Caption plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's shortcode and post meta in all versions up to, and including, 0.8.10 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5703 | The Gift Up Gift Cards for WordPress and WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'gif...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5703</link><description>The Gift Up Gift Cards for WordPress and WooCommerce plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'giftup' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.20.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5709 | The WD WidgetTwitter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5709</link><description>The WD WidgetTwitter plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to SQL Injection via the plugin's shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.0.9 due to insufficient escaping on the user supplied parameter and lack of sufficient preparation on the existing SQL query. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to append additional SQL queries into already existing queries that can be used to extract sensitive information from the database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:38:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4431 | msyk FMDataAPI FMDataAPI_Sample.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4431</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in msyk FMDataAPI up to 22. Affected is an unknown function of the file FMDataAPI_Sample.php. The manipulation leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. Upgrading to version 23 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 3bd1709a8f7b1720529bf5dfc9855ad609f436cf. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-244494 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46819 | Apache OFBiz: Execution of Solr plugin queries without authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46819</link><description>Missing Authentication in Apache Software Foundation Apache OFBiz when using the Solr plugin.
This issue affects Apache OFBiz: before 18.12.09. 

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 18.12.09</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5506 | The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'imgmap_delete_area...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5506</link><description>The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to unauthorized loss of data due to a missing capability check on the 'imgmap_delete_area_ajax' function in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with subscriber-level permissions and above, to delete arbitrary posts and pages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5507 | The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'imagemap' shortcode in versions up to, and including,...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5507</link><description>The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via 'imagemap' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5532 | The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This is due to mis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5532</link><description>The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'imgmap_save_area_title' function. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the post title and inject malicious JavaScript via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5658 | The WP MapIt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_mapit' shortcode in all versions up to, ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5658</link><description>The WP MapIt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wp_mapit' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5743 | The Telephone Number Linker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'telnumlink' shortcode in all...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5743</link><description>The Telephone Number Linker plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'telnumlink' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers with contributor-level and above permissions to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5975 | The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This is due to mis...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5975</link><description>The ImageMapper plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in versions up to, and including, 1.2.6. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on multiple functions. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update the plugin settings via a forged request, granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:17:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47510 | Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WPSolutions-HQ WPDBSpringClean plugin &lt;= 1.6 versions.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47510</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in WPSolutions-HQ WPDBSpringClean plugin &lt;= 1.6 versions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 10:31:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46851 | Apache Allura: sensitive information exposure via import</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46851</link><description>Allura Discussion and Allura Forum importing does not restrict URL values specified in attachments. Project administrators can run these imports, which could cause Allura to read local files and expose them.  Exposing internal files then can lead to other exploits, like session hijacking, or remote code execution.

This issue affects Apache Allura from 1.0.1 through 1.15.0.

Users are recommended to upgrade to version 1.16.0, which fixes the issue.  If you are unable to upgrade, set "disable_entry_points.allura.importers = forge-tracker, forge-discussion" in your .ini config file.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 09:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43885 | Missing error handling in the HTTP server component of Tenda RX9 Pro Firmware V22.03.02.20 allows authenticated attackers to arbitrarily loc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43885</link><description>Missing error handling in the HTTP server component of Tenda RX9 Pro Firmware V22.03.02.20 allows authenticated attackers to arbitrarily lock the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:30:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-43886 | A buffer overflow in the HTTP server component of Tenda RX9 Pro v22.03.02.20 might allow an authenticated attacker to overwrite memory.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-43886</link><description>A buffer overflow in the HTTP server component of Tenda RX9 Pro v22.03.02.20 might allow an authenticated attacker to overwrite memory.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:30:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42527 | Improper input validation vulnerability in ProcessWriteFile of libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to expose s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42527</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in ProcessWriteFile of libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to expose sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42528 | Improper Input Validation vulnerability in ProcessNvBuffering of libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42528</link><description>Improper Input Validation vulnerability in ProcessNvBuffering of libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42529 | Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42529</link><description>Out-of-bound write vulnerability in libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42530 | Improper access control vulnerability in SecSettings prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to enable Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi Direct witho...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42530</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SecSettings prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attackers to enable Wi-Fi and Wi-Fi Direct without User Interaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42531 | Improper access control vulnerability in SmsController prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release1 allows attacker to bypass restrictions on starting act...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42531</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in SmsController prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release1 allows attacker to bypass restrictions on starting activities from the background.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42532 | Improper Certificate Validation in FotaAgent prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release1 allows remote attacker to intercept the network traffic includin...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42532</link><description>Improper Certificate Validation in FotaAgent prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release1 allows remote attacker to intercept the network traffic including Firmware information.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42533 | Improper Input Validation with USB Gadget Interface prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42533</link><description>Improper Input Validation with USB Gadget Interface prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows a physical attacker to execute arbitrary code in Kernel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42534 | Improper input validation vulnerability in ChooserActivity prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary files wi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42534</link><description>Improper input validation vulnerability in ChooserActivity prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attackers to read arbitrary files with system privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42535 | Out-of-bounds Write in read_block of vold prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42535</link><description>Out-of-bounds Write in read_block of vold prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42536 | An improper input validation in saped_dec in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read and write.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42536</link><description>An improper input validation in saped_dec in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read and write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42537 | An improper input validation in get_head_crc in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read and wri...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42537</link><description>An improper input validation in get_head_crc in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read and write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42538 | An improper input validation in saped_rec_silence in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read an...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42538</link><description>An improper input validation in saped_rec_silence in libsaped prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows attacker to cause out-of-bounds read and write.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42539 | PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in ChallengeNotificationManager in Samsung Health prior to version 6.25 allows local attackers to acce...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42539</link><description>PendingIntent hijacking vulnerability in ChallengeNotificationManager in Samsung Health prior to version 6.25 allows local attackers to access data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42540 | Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.01.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via imp...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42540</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.01.1 allows attackers to access sensitive information via implicit intent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42541 | Improper authorization in PushClientProvider of Samsung Push Service prior to version 3.4.10 allows attacker to access unique id.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42541</link><description>Improper authorization in PushClientProvider of Samsung Push Service prior to version 3.4.10 allows attacker to access unique id.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42542 | Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Push Service prior to 3.4.10 allows local attackers to get register ID to identify the devi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42542</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Samsung Push Service prior to 3.4.10 allows local attackers to get register ID to identify the device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42543 | Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Bixby Voice prior to version 3.3.35.12 allows attackers to access arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42543</link><description>Improper verification of intent by broadcast receiver vulnerability in Bixby Voice prior to version 3.3.35.12 allows attackers to access arbitrary data with Bixby Voice privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42544 | Improper access control vulnerability in Quick Share prior to 13.5.52.0 allows local attacker to access local files.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42544</link><description>Improper access control vulnerability in Quick Share prior to 13.5.52.0 allows local attacker to access local files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42545 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in Phone prior to versions 12.7.20.12 in Android 11, 13.1.48, 13.5.28 in An...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42545</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in Phone prior to versions 12.7.20.12 in Android 11, 13.1.48, 13.5.28 in Android 12, and 14.7.38 in Android 13 allows attackers to access location data.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42546 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startAgreeToDisclaimerActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42546</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startAgreeToDisclaimerActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42547 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startEmailValidationActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42547</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startEmailValidationActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42548 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startMandatoryCheckActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42548</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startMandatoryCheckActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42549 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startNameValidationActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42549</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startNameValidationActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42550 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startSignIn in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attacke...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42550</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startSignIn in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42551 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startTncActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows at...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42551</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in startTncActivity in Samsung Account prior to version 14.5.00.7 allows attackers to access arbitrary file with Samsung Account privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42552 | Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Firewall application prior to versions 12.1.00.24 in Android 11, 13.1.00.16 in Android 12 and 14....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42552</link><description>Implicit intent hijacking vulnerability in Firewall application prior to versions 12.1.00.24 in Android 11, 13.1.00.16 in Android 12 and 14.1.00.7 in Android 13 allows 3rd party application to tamper the database of Firewall.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42553 | Improper authorization verification vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.90.4 allows attackers to read sandbox data of email.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42553</link><description>Improper authorization verification vulnerability in Samsung Email prior to version 6.1.90.4 allows attackers to read sandbox data of email.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42554 | Improper Authentication vulnerabiity in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42554</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerabiity in Samsung Pass prior to version 4.3.00.17 allows physical attackers to bypass authentication.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42555 | Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.13 allows attackers to get the bluetooth...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42555</link><description>Use of implicit intent for sensitive communication vulnerability in EasySetup prior to version 11.1.13 allows attackers to get the bluetooth address of user device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:59:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-30739 | Arbitrary File Descriptor Write vulnerability in libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-30739</link><description>Arbitrary File Descriptor Write vulnerability in libsec-ril prior to SMR Nov-2023 Release 1 allows local attacker to execute arbitrary code.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:49:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46845 | EC-CUBE 3 series (3.0.0 to 3.0.18-p6) and 4 series (4.0.0 to 4.0.6-p3, 4.1.0 to 4.1.2-p2, and 4.2.0 to 4.2.2) contain an arbitrary code exec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46845</link><description>EC-CUBE 3 series (3.0.0 to 3.0.18-p6) and 4 series (4.0.0 to 4.0.6-p3, 4.1.0 to 4.1.2-p2, and 4.2.0 to 4.2.2) contain an arbitrary code execution vulnerability due to improper settings of the template engine Twig included in the product. As a result, arbitrary code may be executed on the server where the product is running by a user with an administrative privilege.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:49:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5076 | The Ziteboard Online Whiteboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ziteboard' shortcode in versions ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5076</link><description>The Ziteboard Online Whiteboard plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the 'ziteboard' shortcode in versions up to, and including, 2.9.9 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:39:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42283 | Blind SQL injection in api_id parameter in Tyk Gateway version 5.0.3 allows attacker to access and dump the database via a crafted SQL query...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42283</link><description>Blind SQL injection in api_id parameter in Tyk Gateway version 5.0.3 allows attacker to access and dump the database via a crafted SQL query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42284 | Blind SQL injection in api_version parameter in Tyk Gateway version 5.0.3 allows attacker to access and dump the database via a crafted SQL ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42284</link><description>Blind SQL injection in api_version parameter in Tyk Gateway version 5.0.3 allows attacker to access and dump the database via a crafted SQL query.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:18:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38547 | A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unauthenticated user to gain information about the SQL server connection Veeam ONE uses to access its...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38547</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unauthenticated user to gain information about the SQL server connection Veeam ONE uses to access its configuration database. This may lead to remote code execution on the SQL server hosting the Veeam ONE configuration database.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38548 | A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unprivileged user who has access to the Veeam ONE Web Client the ability to acquire the NTLM hash of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38548</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unprivileged user who has access to the Veeam ONE Web Client the ability to acquire the NTLM hash of the account used by the Veeam ONE Reporting Service.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38549 | A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unprivileged user who has access to the Veeam ONE Web Client the ability to acquire the NTLM hash of ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38549</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows an unprivileged user who has access to the Veeam ONE Web Client the ability to acquire the NTLM hash of the account used by the Veeam ONE Reporting Service. Note: The criticality of this vulnerability is reduced as it requires interaction by a user with the Veeam ONE Administrator role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41723 | A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows a user with the Veeam ONE Read-Only User role to view the Dashboard Schedule. Note: The criticality of t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41723</link><description>A vulnerability in Veeam ONE allows a user with the Veeam ONE Read-Only User role to view the Dashboard Schedule. Note: The criticality of this vulnerability is reduced because the user with the Read-Only role is only able to view the schedule and cannot make changes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2019-25156 | dstar2018 Agency search.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2019-25156</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in dstar2018 Agency up to 61. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file search.php. The manipulation of the argument QSType/QuickSearch leads to cross site scripting. The attack can be launched remotely. The patch is named 975b56953efabb434519d9feefcc53685fb8d0ab. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244495.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-21671 | Improper Input Validation in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-21671</link><description>Memory Corruption in Core during syscall for Sectools Fuse comparison feature.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-22388 | Use of Out-of-range Pointer Offset in Multi-mode Call Processor</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-22388</link><description>Memory Corruption in Multi-mode Call Processor while processing bit mask API.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-24852 | Improper Authentication in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-24852</link><description>Memory Corruption in Core due to secure memory access by user while loading modem image.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28545 | Improper Restriction of Operations within the Bounds of a Memory Buffer in TZ Secure OS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28545</link><description>Memory corruption in TZ Secure OS while loading an app ELF.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28553 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Host</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28553</link><description>Information Disclosure in WLAN Host when processing WMI event command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28554 | Buffer Over-read in Qualcomm IPC</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28554</link><description>Information Disclosure in Qualcomm IPC while reading values from shared memory in VM.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28556 | Improper Authorization in HLOS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28556</link><description>Cryptographic issue in HLOS during key management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28563 | Buffer Over-read in IOE Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28563</link><description>Information disclosure in IOE Firmware while handling WMI command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28566 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28566</link><description>Information disclosure in WLAN HAL while handling the WMI state info command.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28568 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28568</link><description>Information disclosure in WLAN HAL when reception status handler is called.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28569 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HAL</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28569</link><description>Information disclosure in WLAN HAL while handling command through WMI interfaces.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28570 | Buffer Copy without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28570</link><description>Memory corruption while processing audio effects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28572 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN HOST</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28572</link><description>Memory corruption in WLAN HOST while processing the WLAN scan descriptor list.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28574 | Improper Input Validation in Core</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28574</link><description>Memory corruption in core services when Diag handler receives a command to configure event listeners.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33031 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Automotive Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33031</link><description>Memory corruption in Automotive Audio while copying data from ADSP shared buffer to the VOC packet data buffer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33045 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33045</link><description>Memory corruption in WLAN Firmware while parsing a NAN management frame carrying a S3 attribute.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33047 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33047</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware while parsing no-inherit IES.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33048 | Buffer over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33048</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware while parsing t2lm buffers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33055 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33055</link><description>Memory Corruption in Audio while invoking callback function in driver from ADSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33056 | NULL Pointer dereference in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33056</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware when firmware receives beacon including T2LM IE.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33059 | Buffer Copy Without Checking Size of Input in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33059</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio while processing the VOC packet data from ADSP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33061 | Buffer Over-read in WLAN Firmware</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33061</link><description>Transient DOS in WLAN Firmware while parsing WLAN beacon or probe-response frame.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33074 | Use After Free in Audio</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33074</link><description>Memory corruption in Audio when SSR event is triggered after music playback is stopped.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47102 | UrBackup Server 2.5.31 allows brute-force enumeration of user accounts because a failure message confirms that a username is not valid.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47102</link><description>UrBackup Server 2.5.31 allows brute-force enumeration of user accounts because a failure message confirms that a username is not valid.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:27:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46998 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in BootBox Bootbox.js v.3.2 through 6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46998</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in BootBox Bootbox.js v.3.2 through 6.0 allows a remote attacker to execute arbitrary code via a crafted payload to alert(), confirm(), prompt() functions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35140 | The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel GS1900-24EP switch firmware version V2.70(ABTO.5) could allow an authenticated ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35140</link><description>The improper privilege management vulnerability in the Zyxel GS1900-24EP switch firmware version V2.70(ABTO.5) could allow an authenticated local user with read-only access to modify system settings on a vulnerable device.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 02:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5976 | Improper Access Control in microweber/microweber</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5976</link><description>Improper Access Control in GitHub repository microweber/microweber prior to 2.0.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 02:07:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36409 | Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Information Disclosure Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36409</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 23:22:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-36769 | Microsoft OneNote Spoofing Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-36769</link><description>No english description</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45556 | Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Mybb Mybb Forums v.1.8.33 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the theme Name paramet...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45556</link><description>Cross Site Scripting vulnerability in Mybb Mybb Forums v.1.8.33 allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code via the theme Name parameter in the theme management component.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 21:49:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47004 | Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Redis RedisGraph v.2.x through v.2.12.8 and fixed in v.2.12.9 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47004</link><description>Buffer Overflow vulnerability in Redis RedisGraph v.2.x through v.2.12.8 and fixed in v.2.12.9 allows an attacker to execute arbitrary code via the code logic after valid authentication.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 21:29:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4810 | Responsive Pricing Table &amp;lt; 5.1.8 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scriping</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4810</link><description>The Responsive Pricing Table WordPress plugin before 5.1.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4858 | WP Simple Table Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.6 - Admin+ Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4858</link><description>The Simple Table Manager WordPress plugin through 1.5.6 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4930 | Front End PM &amp;lt; 11.4.3 - Sensitive Data Exposure via Directory Listing</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4930</link><description>The Front End PM WordPress plugin before 11.4.3 does not block listing the contents of the directories where it stores attachments to private messages, allowing unauthenticated visitors to list and download private attachments if the autoindex feature of the web server is enabled.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5082 | History Log by click5 &amp;lt; 1.0.13 - Admin+ Time-Based Blind SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5082</link><description>The History Log by click5 WordPress plugin before 1.0.13 does not properly sanitise and escape a parameter before using it in a SQL statement, leading to a SQL injection exploitable by admin users when using the Smash Balloon Social Photo Feed plugin alongside it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5181 | WP Discord Invite &amp;lt; 2.5.2 - Admin+ Stored Cross Site Scripting </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5181</link><description>The WP Discord Invite WordPress plugin before 2.5.2 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5228 | User Registration &amp;lt; 3.0.4.2 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5228</link><description>The User Registration WordPress plugin before 3.0.4.2 does not sanitize and escape some of its settings, which could allow high-privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5352 | Awesome Support &amp;lt; 6.1.5 - Insufficient permission check in wpas_edit_reply</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5352</link><description>The Awesome Support WordPress plugin before 6.1.5 does not correctly authorize the wpas_edit_reply function, allowing users to edit posts for which they do not have permission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5354 | Awesome Support &amp;lt; 6.1.5 - Reflected Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5354</link><description>The Awesome Support WordPress plugin before 6.1.5 does not sanitise and escape a parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5355 | Awesome Support &amp;lt; 6.1.5 - Submitter+ Arbitrary File Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5355</link><description>The Awesome Support WordPress plugin before 6.1.5 does not sanitize file paths when deleting temporary attachment files, allowing a ticket submitter to delete arbitrary files on the server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5454 | Templately &amp;lt; 2.2.6 - Arbitrary post trashing via Missing Authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5454</link><description>The Templately WordPress plugin before 2.2.6 does not properly authorize the `saved-templates/delete` REST API call, allowing unauthenticated users to delete arbitrary posts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5530 | Ninja Forms &amp;lt; 3.6.34 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5530</link><description>The Ninja Forms Contact Form WordPress plugin before 3.6.34 does not sanitize and escape its label fields, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored XSS attacks. Only users with the unfiltered_html capability can perform this, and such users are already allowed to use JS in posts/comments etc however the vendor acknowledged and fixed the issue</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5601 | WooCommerce Ninja Forms Product Add-ons &amp;lt; 1.7.1 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5601</link><description>The WooCommerce Ninja Forms Product Add-ons WordPress plugin before 1.7.1 does not validate the file to be uploaded, allowing any unauthenticated users to upload arbitrary files to the server, leading to RCE.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5605 | URL Shortify &amp;lt;= 1.7.8 - Admin+ Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5605</link><description>The URL Shortify WordPress plugin through 1.7.8 does not sanitise and escape some of its settings, which could allow high privilege users such as admin to perform Stored Cross-Site Scripting attacks even when the unfiltered_html capability is disallowed (for example in multisite setup)</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:46:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5771 | HTML injection in AdminUI through email subject</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5771</link><description>Proofpoint Enterprise Protection contains a stored XSS vulnerability in the AdminUI. An unauthenticated attacker can send a specially crafted email with HTML in the subject which triggers XSS when viewing quarantined messages.  This issue affects Proofpoint Enterprise Protection: from 8.20.0 before patch 4796, from 8.18.6 before patch 4795 and all other prior versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:23:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48192 | Cross-site scripting vulnerability in Softing smartLink SW-HT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48192</link><description>Cross-site Scripting vulnerability in Softing smartLink SW-HT before 1.30, which allows an attacker to execute a dynamic script (JavaScript, VBScript) in the context of the application.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:57:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-48193 | Weak ciphers vulnerability in Softing smartLink SW-HT</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-48193</link><description>Weak ciphers in Softing smartLink SW-HT before 1.30 are enabled during secure communication (SSL).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:57:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5719 | Red Lion Crimson Improper Neutralization of Null Byte or NUL Character</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5719</link><description>The Crimson 3.2 Windows-based configuration tool allows users with administrative access to define new passwords for users and to download the resulting security configuration to a device. If such a password contains the percent (%) character, invalid values will be included, potentially truncating the string if a NUL is encountered. If the simplified password is not detected by the administrator, the device might be left in a vulnerable state as a result of more-easily compromised credentials. Note that passwords entered via the Crimson system web server do not suffer from this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:36:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5777 | Weintek EasyBuilder Pro Use of Hard-coded Credentials</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5777</link><description>Weintek EasyBuilder Pro contains a vulnerability that, even when the private key is immediately deleted after the crash report transmission is finished, the private key is exposed to the public, which could result in obtaining remote control of the crash report server.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:36:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46731 | Remote code execution through the section parameter in Administration as guest in XWiki Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46731</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki doesn't properly escape the section URL parameter that is used in the code for displaying administration sections. This allows any user with read access to the document `XWiki.AdminSheet` (by default, everyone including unauthenticated users) to execute code including Groovy code. This impacts the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki instance. This vulnerability has been patched in XWiki 14.10.14, 15.6 RC1 and 15.5.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unablr to upgrade may apply the fix in commit `fec8e0e53f9` manually. Alternatively, to protect against attacks from unauthenticated users, view right for guests can be removed from this document (it is only needed for space and wiki admins).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:15:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46732 | Reflected Cross-site scripting through revision parameter in content menu in XWiki Platform</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46732</link><description>XWiki Platform is a generic wiki platform offering runtime services for applications built on top of it. XWiki is vulnerable to reflected cross-site scripting (RXSS) via the `rev` parameter that is used in the content of the content menu without escaping. If an attacker can convince a user to visit a link with a crafted parameter, this allows the attacker to execute arbitrary actions in the name of the user, including remote code (Groovy) execution in the case of a user with programming right, compromising the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the whole XWiki installation. This has been patched in XWiki 15.6 RC1, 15.5.1 and 14.10.14. The patch in commit `04e325d57` can be manually applied without upgrading (or restarting) the instance. Users are advised to upgrade or to manually apply the patch. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:51:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46254 | Service accounts can see namespaces of other tenants in capsule-proxy</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46254</link><description>capsule-proxy is a reverse proxy for Capsule kubernetes multi-tenancy framework. A bug in the RoleBinding reflector used by `capsule-proxy` gives ServiceAccount tenant owners the right to list Namespaces of other tenants backed by the same owner kind and name. For example consider two tenants `solar` and `wind`. Tenant `solar`, owned by a ServiceAccount named `tenant-owner` in the Namespace `solar`. Tenant `wind`, owned by a ServiceAccount named `tenant-owner` in the Namespace `wind`. The Tenant owner `solar` would be able to list the namespaces of the Tenant `wind` and vice-versa, although this is not correct. The bug introduces an exfiltration vulnerability since allows the listing of Namespace resources of other Tenants, although just in some specific conditions: 1. `capsule-proxy` runs with the `--disable-caching=false` (default value: `false`) and 2. Tenant owners are ServiceAccount, with the same resource name, but in different Namespaces. This vulnerability doesn't allow any privilege escalation on the outer tenant Namespace-scoped resources, since the Kubernetes RBAC is enforcing this. This issue has been addressed in version 0.4.5. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:41:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-39345 | Unauthorized Access to Private Fields in User Registration API in strapi</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-39345</link><description>strapi is an open-source headless CMS. Versions prior to 4.13.1 did not properly restrict write access to fielded marked as private in the user registration endpoint. As such malicious users may be able to errantly modify their user records. This issue has been addressed in version 4.13.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:30:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46251 | Visual editor persistent Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in MyBB</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46251</link><description>MyBB is a free and open source forum software. Custom MyCode (BBCode) for the visual editor (_SCEditor_) doesn't escape input properly when rendering HTML, resulting in a DOM-based XSS vulnerability. This weakness can be exploited by pointing a victim to a page where the visual editor is active (e.g. as a post or Private Message) and operates on a maliciously crafted MyCode message. This may occur on pages where message content is pre-filled using a GET/POST parameter, or on reply pages where a previously saved malicious message is quoted. The impact is be mitigated when: 1. the visual editor is disabled globally (_Admin CP → Configuration → Settings → Clickable Smilies and BB Code: [Clickable MyCode Editor](https://github.com/mybb/mybb/blob/mybb_1836/install/resources/settings.xml#L2087-L2094)_ is set to _Off_), or 2. the visual editor is disabled for individual user accounts (_User CP → Your Profile → Edit Options_: _Show the MyCode formatting options on the posting pages_ checkbox is not checked). MyBB 1.8.37 resolves this issue with the commit `6dcaf0b4d`. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade may mitigate the impact without upgrading MyBB by changing the following setting (_Admin CP → Configuration → Settings_):
- _Clickable Smilies and BB Code → [Clickable MyCode Editor](https://github.com/mybb/mybb/blob/mybb_1836/install/resources/settings.xml#L2087-L2094)_: _Off_. Similarly, individual MyBB forum users are able to disable the visual editor by diabling the account option (_User CP → Your Profile → Edit Options_) _Show the MyCode formatting options on the posting pages_.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-44398 | Out-of-bounds write in exiv2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-44398</link><description>Exiv2 is a C++ library and a command-line utility to read, write, delete and modify Exif, IPTC, XMP and ICC image metadata. An out-of-bounds write was found in Exiv2 version v0.28.0. The vulnerable function, `BmffImage::brotliUncompress`, is new in v0.28.0, so earlier versions of Exiv2 are _not_ affected. The out-of-bounds write is triggered when Exiv2 is used to read the metadata of a crafted image file. An attacker could potentially exploit the vulnerability to gain code execution, if they can trick the victim into running Exiv2 on a crafted image file. This bug is fixed in version v0.28.1. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds for this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:39:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4700 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4700</link><description>An authorization issue affecting GitLab EE affecting all versions from 14.7 prior to 16.3.6, 16.4 prior to 16.4.2, and 16.5 prior to 16.5.1, allowed a user to run jobs in protected environments, bypassing any required approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:39:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45827 | Prototype Pollution vulnerability in @clickbar/dot-diver</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45827</link><description>Dot diver is a lightweight, powerful, and dependency-free TypeScript utility library that provides types and functions to work with object paths in dot notation. In versions prior to 1.0.2 there is a Prototype Pollution vulnerability in the `setByPath` function which can leads to remote code execution (RCE). This issue has been addressed in commit `98daf567` which has been included in release 1.0.2. Users are advised to upgrade. There are no known workarounds to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:27:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46728 | SQUID-2021:8 Denial of Service in Gopher gateway</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46728</link><description>Squid is a caching proxy for the Web supporting HTTP, HTTPS, FTP, and more. Due to a NULL pointer dereference bug Squid is vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack against Squid's Gopher gateway. The gopher protocol is always available and enabled in Squid prior to Squid 6.0.1. Responses triggering this bug are possible to be received from any gopher server, even those without malicious intent. Gopher support has been removed in Squid version 6.0.1. Users are advised to upgrade. Users unable to upgrade should reject all gopher URL requests.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:27:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40660 | Potential pin bypass when card tracks its own login state</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40660</link><description>A flaw was found in OpenSC packages that allow a potential PIN bypass. When a token/card is authenticated by one process, it can perform cryptographic operations in other processes when an empty zero-length pin is passed. This issue poses a security risk, particularly for OS logon/screen unlock and for small, permanently connected tokens to computers. Additionally, the token can internally track login status. This flaw allows an attacker to gain unauthorized access, carry out malicious actions, or compromise the system without the user's awareness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:27:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40661 | Multiple memory issues with pkcs15-init (enrollment tool)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40661</link><description>Several memory vulnerabilities were identified within the OpenSC packages, particularly in the card enrollment process using pkcs15-init when a user or administrator enrolls cards. To take advantage of these flaws, an attacker must have physical access to the computer system and employ a custom-crafted USB device or smart card to manipulate responses to APDUs. This manipulation can potentially allow &#13;
compromise key generation, certificate loading, and other card management operations during enrollment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4535 | Out-of-bounds read in myeid driver handling encryption using symmetric keys</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4535</link><description>An out-of-bounds read vulnerability was found in OpenSC packages within the MyEID driver when handling symmetric key encryption. Exploiting this flaw requires an attacker to have physical access to the computer and a specially crafted USB device or smart card. This flaw allows the attacker to manipulate APDU responses and potentially gain unauthorized access to sensitive data, compromising the system's security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:27:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5678 | Excessive time spent in DH check / generation with large Q parameter value</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5678</link><description>Issue summary: Generating excessively long X9.42 DH keys or checking
excessively long X9.42 DH keys or parameters may be very slow.

Impact summary: Applications that use the functions DH_generate_key() to
generate an X9.42 DH key may experience long delays.  Likewise, applications
that use DH_check_pub_key(), DH_check_pub_key_ex() or EVP_PKEY_public_check()
to check an X9.42 DH key or X9.42 DH parameters may experience long delays.
Where the key or parameters that are being checked have been obtained from
an untrusted source this may lead to a Denial of Service.

While DH_check() performs all the necessary checks (as of CVE-2023-3817),
DH_check_pub_key() doesn't make any of these checks, and is therefore
vulnerable for excessively large P and Q parameters.

Likewise, while DH_generate_key() performs a check for an excessively large
P, it doesn't check for an excessively large Q.

An application that calls DH_generate_key() or DH_check_pub_key() and
supplies a key or parameters obtained from an untrusted source could be
vulnerable to a Denial of Service attack.

DH_generate_key() and DH_check_pub_key() are also called by a number of
other OpenSSL functions.  An application calling any of those other
functions may similarly be affected.  The other functions affected by this
are DH_check_pub_key_ex(), EVP_PKEY_public_check(), and EVP_PKEY_generate().

Also vulnerable are the OpenSSL pkey command line application when using the
"-pubcheck" option, as well as the OpenSSL genpkey command line application.

The OpenSSL SSL/TLS implementation is not affected by this issue.

The OpenSSL 3.0 and 3.1 FIPS providers are not affected by this issue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5969 |  Denial of Service via Link Preview in /api/v4/redirect_location</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5969</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly sanitize the request to /api/v4/redirect_location allowing an attacker, sending a specially crafted request to /api/v4/redirect_location, to fill up the memory due to caching large items.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:58:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5968 | Password hash in response body after username update</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5968</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly sanitize the user object when updating the username, resulting in the password hash being included in the response body.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:38:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5967 | Denial of Service via crashing the Calls Plugin</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5967</link><description>Mattermost fails to properly validate requests to the Calls plugin, allowing an attacker sending a request without a User Agent header to cause a panic and crash the Calls plugin</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41378 | Calico Typha hangs during unclean TLS handshake</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41378</link><description>In certain conditions for Calico Typha (v3.26.2, v3.25.1 and below), and Calico Enterprise Typha (v3.17.1, v3.16.3, v3.15.3 and below), a client TLS handshake can block the Calico Typha server indefinitely, resulting in denial of service. The TLS Handshake() call is performed inside the main server handle for loop without any timeout allowing an unclean TLS handshake to block the main loop indefinitely while other connections will be idle waiting for that handshake to finish.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 15:26:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5950 | Rapid7 Velociraptor Reflected XSS </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5950</link><description>Rapid7 Velociraptor versions prior to 0.7.0-4 suffer from a reflected cross site scripting vulnerability. This vulnerability allows attackers to inject JS into the error path, potentially leading to unauthorized execution of scripts within a user's web browser. This vulnerability is fixed in version 0.7.0-04 and a patch is available to download. Patches are also available for version 0.6.9 (0.6.9-1).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 14:41:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4910 | Logged out users tokens can be accessed</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4910</link><description>A flaw was found In 3Scale Admin Portal. If a user logs out from the personal tokens page and then presses the back button in the browser, the tokens page is rendered from the browser cache.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45163 | 1E-Exchange-CommandLinePing instruction before v18.1 allows for arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45163</link><description>The 1E-Exchange-CommandLinePing instruction that is part of the Network product pack available on the 1E Exchange does not properly validate the input parameter, which allows for a specially crafted input to perform arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM permissions.

To remediate this issue download the updated Network product pack from the 1E Exchange and update the 1E-Exchange-CommandLinePing instruction to v18.1 by uploading it through the 1E Platform instruction upload UI</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5963 | Improper Input Validation in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5963</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE with Advanced Search affecting all versions from 13.9 to 16.3.6, 16.4 prior to 16.4.2 and 16.5 prior to 16.5.1 that could allow a denial of service in the Advanced Search function by chaining too many syntax operators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5964 | 1E-Exchange-DisplayMessage instruction allows for arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5964</link><description>The 1E-Exchange-DisplayMessageinstruction that is part of the End-User Interaction product pack available on the 1E Exchange does not properly validate the Caption or Message parameters, which allows for a specially crafted input to perform arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM permissions.

To remediate this issue DELETE the instruction “Show dialogue with caption %Caption% and message %Message%” from the list of instructions in the Settings UI, and replace it with the new instruction 1E-Exchange-ShowNotification instruction available in the updated End-User Interaction product pack. The new instruction should show as “Show %Type% type notification with header %Header% and message %Message%” with a version of 7.1 or above.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3399 | Improper Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3399</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions starting from 11.6 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. It was possible for an unauthorised project or group member to read the CI/CD variables using the custom project templates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3909 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3909</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 12.3 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. A Regular Expression Denial of Service was possible by adding a large string in timeout input in gitlab-ci.yml file.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45161 | 1E-Exchange-URLResponseTime instruction before v20.1 allows arbitrary code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45161</link><description>The 1E-Exchange-URLResponseTime instruction that is part of the Network product pack available on the 1E Exchange does not properly validate the URL parameter, which allows for a specially crafted input to perform arbitrary code execution with SYSTEM permissions.

To remediate this issue download the updated Network product pack from the 1E Exchange and update the 1E-Exchange-URLResponseTime instruction to v20.1 by uploading it through the 1E Platform instruction upload UI</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-3246 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-3246</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE/CE affecting all versions starting before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1 which allows an attackers to block Sidekiq job processor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:57:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47186 | WordPress Kadence WooCommerce Email Designer Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47186</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Kadence WP Kadence WooCommerce Email Designer plugin &lt;= 1.5.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:29:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46781 | WordPress Current Menu Item for Custom Post Types Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46781</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Roland Murg Current Menu Item for Custom Post Types plugin &lt;= 1.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:29:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5823 | WordPress TK Google Fonts GDPR Compliant Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.2.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5823</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in ThemeKraft TK Google Fonts GDPR Compliant plugin &lt;= 2.2.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46778 | WordPress Auto Limit Posts Reloaded Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46778</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in TheFreeWindows Auto Limit Posts Reloaded plugin &lt;= 2.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46779 | WordPress EasyRecipe Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.3251 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46779</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in EasyRecipe plugin &lt;= 3.5.3251 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46780 | WordPress Alter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46780</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Alter plugin &lt;= 1.0 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46776 | WordPress Auto Excerpt everywhere Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46776</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Serena Villa Auto Excerpt everywhere plugin &lt;= 1.5 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46777 | WordPress Feather Login Page Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46777</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Custom Login Page | Temporary Users | Rebrand Login | Login Captcha plugin &lt;= 1.1.3 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46775 | WordPress Original texts Yandex WebMaster Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.18 is vulnerable to Cross Site Request Forgery (CSRF)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46775</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) vulnerability in Djo Original texts Yandex WebMaster plugin &lt;= 1.18 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47185 | WordPress wpDiscuz Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.6.11 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47185</link><description>Unauth. Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in gVectors Team Comments — wpDiscuz plugin &lt;= 7.6.11 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5090 | Improper check in svm_set_x2apic_msr_interception allows direct access to host x2apic msrs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5090</link><description>A flaw was found in KVM. An improper check in svm_set_x2apic_msr_interception() may allow direct access to host x2apic msrs when the guest resets its apic, potentially leading to a denial of service condition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 11:18:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5825 | Uncontrolled Resource Consumption in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5825</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.2 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, all versions starting from 16.5 before 16.5.1. A low-privileged attacker can point a CI/CD Component to an incorrect path and cause the server to exhaust all available memory through an infinite loop and cause Denial of Service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:33:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-5831 | Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-5831</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 16.0 before 16.3.6, all versions starting from 16.4 before 16.4.2, and all versions starting from 16.5.0 before 16.5.1 which have the `super_sidebar_logged_out` feature flag enabled. Affected versions with this default-disabled feature flag enabled may unintentionally disclose GitLab version metadata to unauthorized actors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4996 | Local privilege escalation </title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4996</link><description>Netskope was made aware of a security vulnerability in its NSClient product for version 100 &amp; prior where a malicious non-admin user can disable the Netskope client by using a specially-crafted package. The root cause of the problem was a user control code when called by a Windows ServiceController did not validate the permissions associated with the user before executing the user control code. This user control code had permissions to terminate the NSClient service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 10:33:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47182 | WordPress Login Screen Manager Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.5.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47182</link><description>Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) leading to a Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Nazmul Hossain Nihal Login Screen Manager plugin &lt;= 3.5.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47184 | WordPress Admin Bar &amp;amp; Dashboard Access Control Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.8 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47184</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Proper Fraction LLC. Admin Bar &amp; Dashboard Access Control plugin &lt;= 1.2.8 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:57:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47177 | WordPress Linker Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47177</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Yakir Sitbon, Ariel Klikstein Linker plugin &lt;= 1.2.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:57:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46824 | WordPress Slick Popup Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7.14 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46824</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Om Ak Solutions Slick Popup: Contact Form 7 Popup Plugin plugin &lt;= 1.7.14 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-23702 | WordPress Comments Ratings Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.7 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-23702</link><description>Auth. (admin+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Pixelgrade Comments Ratings plugin &lt;= 1.1.7 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:47:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46822 | WordPress WooCommerce – Store Exporter Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.2 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46822</link><description>Unauth. Reflected Cross-Site Scripting') vulnerability in Visser Labs Store Exporter for WooCommerce – Export Products, Export Orders, Export Subscriptions, and More plugin &lt;= 2.7.2 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:36:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46783 | WordPress Pre-Orders for WooCommerce Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.13 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46783</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Bright Plugins Pre-Orders for WooCommerce plugin &lt;= 1.2.13 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46782 | WordPress MomentoPress for Momento360 Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.1 is vulnerable to Cross Site Scripting (XSS)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46782</link><description>Auth. (contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Chris Yee MomentoPress for Momento360 plugin &lt;= 1.0.1 versions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46823 | WordPress ImageLinks Interactive Image Builder Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46823</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Avirtum ImageLinks Interactive Image Builder for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects ImageLinks Interactive Image Builder for WordPress: from n/a through 1.5.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46084 | WordPress Icons Font Loader Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.2 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46084</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in bPlugins LLC Icons Font Loader allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Icons Font Loader: from n/a through 1.1.2.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46821 | WordPress GD Security Headers Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46821</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Milan Petrovic GD Security Headers allows auth. (admin+) SQL Injection.This issue affects GD Security Headers: from n/a through 1.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45657 | WordPress Nexter Theme &amp;lt;= 2.0.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45657</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in POSIMYTH Nexter allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Nexter: from n/a through 2.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45830 | WordPress Accessibility Suite by Online ADA Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.11 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45830</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Online ADA Accessibility Suite by Online ADA allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Accessibility Suite by Online ADA: from n/a through 4.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-35911 | WordPress Contact Form Generator Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.6.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-35911</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Creative Solutions Contact Form Generator : Creative form builder for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact Form Generator : Creative form builder for WordPress: from n/a through 2.6.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:51:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45069 | WordPress Video Gallery – YouTube Gallery Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.1.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45069</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Video Gallery by Total-Soft Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery Plugin allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Video Gallery – Best WordPress YouTube Gallery Plugin: from n/a through 2.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:51:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45074 | WordPress Advanced Page Visit Counter Plugin &amp;lt;= 7.1.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45074</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Page Visit Counter Advanced Page Visit Counter – Most Wanted Analytics Plugin for WordPress allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Advanced Page Visit Counter – Most Wanted Analytics Plugin for WordPress: from n/a through 7.1.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:41:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28748 | WordPress Copy Or Move Comments Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28748</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in biztechc Copy or Move Comments allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Copy or Move Comments: from n/a through 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45055 | WordPress MStore API Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45055</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in InspireUI MStore API allows SQL Injection.This issue affects MStore API: from n/a through 4.0.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:41:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45001 | WordPress Seriously Simple Stats Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.0 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45001</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Castos Seriously Simple Stats allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Seriously Simple Stats: from n/a through 1.5.0.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-45046 | WordPress Pressference Exporter Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-45046</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Pressference Pressference Exporter allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Pressference Exporter: from n/a through 1.0.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-27605 | WordPress WP Reroute Email Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.4.6 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-27605</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Sajjad Hossain WP Reroute Email allows SQL Injection.This issue affects WP Reroute Email: from n/a through 1.4.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40609 | WordPress Contact form 7 Custom validation Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.1.3 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40609</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Aiyaz, maheshpatel Contact form 7 Custom validation allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Contact form 7 Custom validation: from n/a through 1.1.3.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-41685 | WordPress Woocommerce Support System Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-41685</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in ilGhera Woocommerce Support System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Woocommerce Support System: from n/a through 1.2.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-33924 | WordPress SIS Handball Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.45 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-33924</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Felix Welberg SIS Handball allows SQL Injection.This issue affects SIS Handball: from n/a through 1.0.45.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38382 | WordPress Subscribe to Category Plugin &amp;lt;= 2.7.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38382</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Daniel Söderström / Sidney van de Stouwe Subscribe to Category allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Subscribe to Category: from n/a through 2.7.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-40207 | WordPress Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.0.12 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-40207</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in RedNao Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Donations Made Easy – Smart Donations: from n/a through 4.0.12.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46849 | WordPress Coming Soon Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.5.9 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46849</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Weblizar Coming Soon Page – Responsive Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance Mode allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Coming Soon Page – Responsive Coming Soon &amp; Maintenance Mode: from n/a through 1.5.9.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-45373 | WordPress Slimstat Analytics Plugin &amp;lt;= 5.0.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-45373</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Jason Crouse, VeronaLabs Slimstat Analytics allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Slimstat Analytics: from n/a through 5.0.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-46860 | WordPress Short URL Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-46860</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in KaizenCoders Short URL allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Short URL: from n/a through 1.6.4.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:31:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47430 | WordPress The School Management – Education &amp;amp; Learning Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.1 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47430</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Weblizar The School Management – Education &amp; Learning Management allows SQL Injection.This issue affects The School Management – Education &amp; Learning Management: from n/a through 4.1.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:51:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47432 | WordPress Shortcode IMDB Plugin &amp;lt;= 6.0.8 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47432</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Kemal YAZICI - PluginPress Shortcode IMDB allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Shortcode IMDB: from n/a through 6.0.8.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47420 | WordPress Accessibility Suite by Online ADA Plugin &amp;lt;= 4.11 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47420</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Online ADA Accessibility Suite by Online ADA allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Accessibility Suite by Online ADA: from n/a through 4.11.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:51:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-47428 | WordPress Booking calendar, Appointment Booking System Plugin &amp;lt;= 3.2.7 is vulnerable to SQL Injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-47428</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in WpDevArt Booking calendar, Appointment Booking System allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Booking calendar, Appointment Booking System: from n/a through 3.2.7.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2021-4430 | Ortus Solutions ColdBox Elixir ENV Variable defaultConfig.js information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2021-4430</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in Ortus Solutions ColdBox Elixir 3.1.6. This affects an unknown part of the file src/defaultConfig.js of the component ENV Variable Handler. The manipulation leads to information disclosure. Upgrading to version 3.1.7 is able to address this issue. The identifier of the patch is a3aa62daea2e44c76d08d1eac63768cd928cd69e. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier VDB-244485 was assigned to this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-28794 | PAC Files Exposed to Internet Websites</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-28794</link><description>Origin Validation Error vulnerability in Zscaler Client Connector on Linux allows Privilege Abuse. This issue affects Zscaler Client Connector for Linux: before 1.3.1.6.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-42669 | &amp;quot;rpcecho&amp;quot; development server allows denial of service via sleep() call on ad dc</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-42669</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Samba's "rpcecho" development server, a non-Windows RPC server used to test Samba's DCE/RPC stack elements. This vulnerability stems from an RPC function that can be blocked indefinitely. The issue arises because the "rpcecho" service operates with only one worker in the main RPC task, allowing calls to the "rpcecho" server to be blocked for a specified time, causing service disruptions. This disruption is triggered by a "sleep()" call in the "dcesrv_echo_TestSleep()" function under specific conditions. Authenticated users or attackers can exploit this vulnerability to make calls to the "rpcecho" server, requesting it to block for a specified duration, effectively disrupting most services and leading to a complete denial of service on the AD DC. The DoS affects all other services as "rpcecho" runs in the main RPC task.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47253 | Qualitor through 8.20 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via PHP code in the html/ad/adpesquisasql/request/processVariavel.ph...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47253</link><description>Qualitor through 8.20 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via PHP code in the html/ad/adpesquisasql/request/processVariavel.php gridValoresPopHidden parameter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38406 | bgpd/bgp_flowspec.c in FRRouting (FRR) before 8.4.3 mishandles an nlri length of zero, aka a "flowspec overflow."</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38406</link><description>bgpd/bgp_flowspec.c in FRRouting (FRR) before 8.4.3 mishandles an nlri length of zero, aka a "flowspec overflow."</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:27:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-38407 | bgpd/bgp_label.c in FRRouting (FRR) before 8.5 attempts to read beyond the end of the stream during labeled unicast parsing.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-38407</link><description>bgpd/bgp_label.c in FRRouting (FRR) before 8.5 attempts to read beyond the end of the stream during labeled unicast parsing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4699 | Denial-of-Service (DoS) Vulnerability in MELSEC Series</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4699</link><description>Insufficient Verification of Data Authenticity vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC-F Series main modules and MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU modules allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to reset the memory of the products to factory default state and cause denial-of-service (DoS) condition on the products by sending specific packets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:27:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-4625 | Denial-of-Service（DoS） Vulnerability in Web server function on MELSEC Series CPU module</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-4625</link><description>Improper Restriction of Excessive Authentication Attempts vulnerability in Mitsubishi Electric Corporation MELSEC iQ-F Series CPU modules Web server function allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to prevent legitimate users from logging into the Web server function for a certain period after the attacker has attempted to log in illegally by continuously attempting unauthorized login to the Web server function. The impact of this vulnerability will persist while the attacker continues to attempt unauthorized login.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:27:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-20702 | In 5G NRLC, there is a possible invalid memory access due to lack of error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if UE rece...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-20702</link><description>In 5G NRLC, there is a possible invalid memory access due to lack of error handling. This could lead to remote denial of service, if UE received invalid 1-byte rlc sdu, with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: MOLY00921261; Issue ID: MOLY01128895.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32818 | In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32818</link><description>In vdec, there is a possible out of bounds write due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08163896 &amp; ALPS08013430; Issue ID: ALPS07867715.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32825 | In bluethooth service, there is a possible out of bounds reads due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32825</link><description>In bluethooth service, there is a possible out of bounds reads due to improper input validation. This could lead to local information disclosure with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07884130; Issue ID: ALPS07884130.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32832 | In video, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32832</link><description>In video, there is a possible memory corruption due to a race condition. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08235273; Issue ID: ALPS08235273.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32834 | In secmem, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32834</link><description>In secmem, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08161762; Issue ID: ALPS08161762.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32835 | In keyinstall, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32835</link><description>In keyinstall, there is a possible memory corruption due to type confusion. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08157918; Issue ID: ALPS08157918.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32836 | In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32836</link><description>In display, there is a possible out of bounds write due to an integer overflow. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08126725; Issue ID: ALPS08126725.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32837 | In video, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no ad...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32837</link><description>In video, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with no additional execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS08235273; Issue ID: ALPS08250357.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32838 | In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing valid range checking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32838</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing valid range checking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07310805; Issue ID: ALPS07310805.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32839 | In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing valid range checking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32839</link><description>In dpe, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing valid range checking. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction is not needed for exploitation. Patch ID: ALPS07262576; Issue ID: ALPS07262576.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-32840 | In modem CCCI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-32840</link><description>In modem CCCI, there is a possible out of bounds write due to a missing bounds check. This could lead to local escalation of privilege with System execution privileges needed. User interaction may be also needed for exploitation Patch ID: MOLY01138425; Issue ID: MOLY01138425 (MSV-862).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-46802 | e-Tax software Version3.0.10 and earlier improperly restricts XML external entity references (XXE) due to the configuration of the embedded ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-46802</link><description>e-Tax software Version3.0.10 and earlier improperly restricts XML external entity references (XXE) due to the configuration of the embedded XML parser. By processing a specially crafted XML file, arbitrary files on the system may be read by an attacker.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 02:09:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25093 | Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 Tag access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25093</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 up to 2.10.2. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the component Tag Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Upgrading to version 2.10.3 is able to address this issue. The name of the patch is cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244484.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 02:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47272 | Roundcube 1.5.x before 1.5.6 and 1.6.x before 1.6.5 allows XSS via a Content-Type or Content-Disposition header (used for attachment preview...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47272</link><description>Roundcube 1.5.x before 1.5.6 and 1.6.x before 1.6.5 allows XSS via a Content-Type or Content-Disposition header (used for attachment preview or download).</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 02:09:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47271 | PKP-WAL (aka PKP Web Application Library or pkp-lib) before 3.3.0-16, as used in Open Journal Systems (OJS) and other products, does not ver...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47271</link><description>PKP-WAL (aka PKP Web Application Library or pkp-lib) before 3.3.0-16, as used in Open Journal Systems (OJS) and other products, does not verify that the file named in an XML document (used for the native import/export plugin) is an image file, before trying to use it for an issue cover image.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 23:42:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25092 | Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 Command Mention access control</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25092</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Vaerys-Dawn DiscordSailv2 up to 2.10.2. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the component Command Mention Handler. The manipulation leads to improper access controls. Upgrading to version 2.10.3 is able to address this issue. The patch is named cc12e0be82a5d05d9f359ed8e56088f4f8b8eb69. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. The associated identifier of this vulnerability is VDB-244483.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 21:16:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20187 | Magnesium-PHP Base.php formatEmailString injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20187</link><description>** UNSUPPORTED WHEN ASSIGNED ** A vulnerability was found in Magnesium-PHP up to 0.3.0. It has been classified as problematic. Affected is the function formatEmailString of the file src/Magnesium/Message/Base.php. The manipulation of the argument email/name leads to injection. Upgrading to version 0.3.1 is able to address this issue. The patch is identified as 500d340e1f6421007413cc08a8383475221c2604. It is recommended to upgrade the affected component. VDB-244482 is the identifier assigned to this vulnerability. NOTE: This vulnerability only affects products that are no longer supported by the maintainer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 20:43:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47258 | Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS in a Markdown formatter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47258</link><description>Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS in a Markdown formatter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 03:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47259 | Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS in the Textile formatter.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47259</link><description>Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS in the Textile formatter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2023-47260 | Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS via thumbnails.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2023-47260</link><description>Redmine before 4.2.11 and 5.0.x before 5.0.6 allows XSS via thumbnails.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>