<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>New CVE from cve.org feed</title><link>https://github.com/test.xml</link><description>Last 2 days CVE feed!</description><atom:link href="https://github.com/test.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:30:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>CVE-2025-7745 | Modbus TCP buffer overread</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7745</link><description>: Buffer Over-read vulnerability in ABB AC500 V2.This issue affects AC500 V2: through 2.5.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8107 | In OceanBase's Oracle tenant mode, a malicious user with specific privileges can achieve privilege escalation to SYS-level access by executi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8107</link><description>In OceanBase's Oracle tenant mode, a malicious user with specific privileges can achieve privilege escalation to SYS-level access by executing carefully crafted commands.




This vulnerability only affects OceanBase tenants in Oracle mode. Tenants in MySQL mode are unaffected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:30:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-0765 | Incorrect Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-0765</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 17.9 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed an unauthorized user to access custom service desk email addresses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-1299 | Missing Authorization in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-1299</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 15.4 before 18.0.5, all versions starting from 18.1 before 18.1.3, all versions starting from 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under circumstances, could have allowed an unauthorized user to read deployment job logs by sending a crafted request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41240 | Mounted Kubernetes Secrets under a predictable path located within the web server document root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41240</link><description>Three Bitnami Helm charts mount Kubernetes Secrets under a predictable path (/opt/bitnami/*/secrets) that is located within the web server document root.
In affected versions, this can lead to unauthenticated access to sensitive credentials via HTTP/S. A remote attacker could retrieve these secrets by accessing specific URLs if the application is exposed externally. The issue affects deployments using the default value of usePasswordFiles=true, which mounts secrets as files into the container filesystem.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4976 | Exposure of Sensitive Information Due to Incompatible Policies in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4976</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab EE affecting all versions from 17.0 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under certain circumstances, could have allowed an attacker to access internal notes in GitLab Duo responses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7001 | Insufficient Granularity of Access Control in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7001</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.0 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed priviledged users to access certain resource_group information through the API which should have been unavailable.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7437 | Ebook Store &amp;lt;= 5.8012 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7437</link><description>The Ebook Store plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the ebook_store_save_form function in all versions up to, and including, 5.8012. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7852 | WPBookit &amp;lt;= 1.0.6 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Upload via image_upload_handle Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7852</link><description>The WPBookit plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the image_upload_handle() function hooked via the 'add_new_customer' route in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.6. The plugin’s image‐upload handler calls move_uploaded_file() on client‐supplied files without restricting allowed extensions or MIME types, nor sanitizing the filename. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected site's server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4393 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Deserialization Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4393</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor has an internal service that deserializes data, which allows a local attacker to interact with the service by crafting a binary payload to crash the service or elevate privileges. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4394 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Unencrypted Filesystem Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4394</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor uses an unencrypted filesystem on internal storage, which allows an attacker with physical access to read and modify files. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4395 | Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor Empty Password Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4395</link><description>Medtronic MyCareLink Patient Monitor has a built-in user account with an empty password, which allows an attacker with physical access to log in with no password and access modify system functionality. 

This issue affects MyCareLink Patient Monitor models 24950 and 24952: before June 25, 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4968 | WPBakery Page Builder &amp;lt;= 8.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Multiple Page Builder Elements</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4968</link><description>The WPBakery Page Builder for WordPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via multiple Page Builder elements (Copyright Element,  Hover Box, Separator With Text, FAQ, Single Image, Custom Header, Button, Call To Action, Progress Bar, Pie Chart, Round Chart, and Line Chart) in all versions up to, and including, 8.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54365 | fastapi-guard patch contains bypassable RegEx</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54365</link><description>fastapi-guard is a security library for FastAPI that provides middleware to control IPs, log requests, detect penetration attempts and more. In version 3.0.1, the regular expression patched to mitigate the ReDoS vulnerability by limiting the length of string fails to catch inputs that exceed this limit. This type of patch fails to detect cases in which the string representing the attributes of a</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15044 | Kaltura &amp;lt; 11.1.0-2 PHP Object Injection RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15044</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists in Kaltura versions prior to 11.1.0-2 due to unsafe deserialization of user-controlled data within the keditorservices module. An unauthenticated remote attacker can exploit this issue by sending a specially crafted serialized PHP object in the kdata GET parameter to the redirectWidgetCmd endpoint. Successful exploitation leads to execution of arbitrary PHP code in the context of the web server process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-32019 | Harbor&amp;#x27;s repository description page allows for XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-32019</link><description>Harbor is an open source trusted cloud native registry project that stores, signs, and scans content. Versions 2.11.2 and below, as well as versions 2.12.0-rc1 and 2.13.0-rc1, contain a vulnerability where the markdown field in the info tab page can be exploited to inject XSS code. This is fixed in versions 2.11.3 and 2.12.3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47281 | Kyverno&amp;#x27;s Improper JMESPath Variable Evaluation Leads to Denial of Service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47281</link><description>Kyverno is a policy engine designed for cloud native platform engineering teams. In versions 1.14.1 and below, a Denial of Service (DoS) vulnerability exists due to improper handling of JMESPath variable substitutions. Attackers with permissions to create or update Kyverno policies can craft expressions using the {{@}} variable combined with a pipe and an invalid JMESPath function (e.g., {{@ | non_existent_function }}). This leads to a nil value being substituted into the policy structure. Subsequent processing by internal functions, specifically getValueAsStringMap, which expect string values, results in a panic due to a type assertion failure (interface {} is nil, not string). This crashes Kyverno worker threads in the admission controller and causes continuous crashes of the reports controller pod. This is fixed in version 1.14.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53537 | LibHTP&amp;#x27;s memory leak with lzma can lead to resource starvation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53537</link><description>LibHTP is a security-aware parser for the HTTP protocol and its related bits and pieces. In versions 0.5.50 and below, there is a traffic-induced memory leak that can starve the process of memory, leading to loss of visibility. To workaround this issue, set `suricata.yaml app-layer.protocols.http.libhtp.default-config.lzma-enabled` to false. This issue is fixed in version 0.5.51.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53942 | authentik has an insufficient check for account active status during OAuth/SAML authentication</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53942</link><description>authentik is an open-source Identity Provider that emphasizes flexibility and versatility, with support for a wide set of protocols. In versions 2025.4.4 and earlier, as well as versions 2025.6.0-rc1 through 2025.6.3, deactivated users who registered through OAuth/SAML or linked their accounts to OAuth/SAML providers can still retain partial access to the system despite their accounts being deactivated. They end up in a half-authenticated state where they cannot access the API but crucially they can authorize applications if they know the URL of the application. To workaround this issue, developers can add an expression policy to the user login stage on the respective authentication flow with the expression of return request.context["pending_user"].is_active. This modification ensures that the return statement only activates the user login stage when the user is active. This issue is fixed in versions authentik 2025.4.4 and 2025.6.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54377 | Roo Code Lacks Line Break Validation in its Command Execution Tool</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54377</link><description>Roo Code is an AI-powered autonomous coding agent that lives in users' editors. In versions 3.23.18 and below, RooCode does not validate line breaks (\n) in its command input, allowing potential bypass of the allow-list mechanism. The project appears to lack parsing or validation logic to prevent multi-line command injection. When commands are evaluated for execution, only the first line or token may be considered, enabling attackers to smuggle additional commands in subsequent lines. This is fixed in version 3.23.19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8058 | The regcomp function in the GNU C library version from 2.4 to 2.41 is 
subject to a double free if some previous allocation fails. It can be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8058</link><description>The regcomp function in the GNU C library version from 2.4 to 2.41 is 
subject to a double free if some previous allocation fails. It can be 
accomplished either by a malloc failure or by using an interposed malloc
 that injects random malloc failures. The double free can allow buffer 
manipulation depending of how the regex is constructed. This issue 
affects all architectures and ABIs supported by the GNU C library.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-44109 | A URL redirection in Pinokio v3.6.23 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-44109</link><description>A URL redirection in Pinokio v3.6.23 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50477 | A URL redirection in lbry-desktop v0.53.9 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50477</link><description>A URL redirection in lbry-desktop v0.53.9 allows attackers to redirect victim users to attacker-controlled pages.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46686 | Redis through 7.4.3 allows memory consumption via a multi-bulk command composed of many bulks, sent by an authenticated user. This occurs be...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46686</link><description>Redis through 7.4.3 allows memory consumption via a multi-bulk command composed of many bulks, sent by an authenticated user. This occurs because the server allocates memory for the command arguments of every bulk, even when the command is skipped because of insufficient permissions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-47187 | A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, coul...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-47187</link><description>A vulnerability in the Mitel 6800 Series, 6900 Series, and 6900w Series SIP Phones, including the 6970 Conference Unit through 6.4 SP4, could allow an unauthenticated attacker to perform a file upload attack due to missing authentication mechanisms. A successful exploit could allow an attacker to upload arbitrary WAV files, which may potentially exhaust the phone's storage without affecting the phone's availability or operation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4439 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4439</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that could have allowed an authenticated user to perform cross-site scripting attacks when the instance is served through certain content delivery networks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4700 | Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (&amp;#x27;Cross-site Scripting&amp;#x27;) in GitLab</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4700</link><description>An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 15.10 before 18.0.5, 18.1 before 18.1.3, and 18.2 before 18.2.1 that, under specific circumstances, could have potentially allowed a successful attacker to trigger unintended content rendering leading to XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50481 | A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /blog/blogpost/add of Mezzanine CMS v6.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50481</link><description>A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the component /blog/blogpost/add of Mezzanine CMS v6.1.0 allows attackers to execute arbitrary web scripts or HTML via injecting a crafted payload into a blog post.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2633 | Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability in NI LabVIEW when loading fonts</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2633</link><description>Out of bounds read vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in NI LabVIEW in lvre!UDecStrToNum that may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-2634 | Out of Bounds Read Vulnerability in NI LabVIEW when building font map</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-2634</link><description>Out of bounds read vulnerability due to improper bounds checking in NI LabVIEW in fontmgr may result in information disclosure or arbitrary code execution.  Successful exploitation requires an attacker to get a user to open a specially crafted VI.  This vulnerability affects NI LabVIEW 2025 Q1 and prior versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8069 | Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in AWS Client VPN Windows Client</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8069</link><description>During the AWS Client VPN client installation on Windows devices, the install process references the C:\usr\local\windows-x86_64-openssl-localbuild\ssl directory location to fetch the OpenSSL configuration file. As a result, a non-admin user could place arbitrary code in the configuration file. If an admin user starts the AWS Client VPN client installation process, that code could be executed with root-level privileges. This issue does not affect Linux or Mac devices. 

We recommend users discontinue any new installations of AWS Client VPN on Windows prior to version 5.2.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46171 | vBulletin 3.8.7 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service condition via the misc.php?do=buddylist endpoint. If an authenticated user has a suffic...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46171</link><description>vBulletin 3.8.7 is vulnerable to a denial-of-service condition via the misc.php?do=buddylist endpoint. If an authenticated user has a sufficiently large buddy list, processing the list can consume excessive memory, exhausting system resources and crashing the forum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6018 | Pam-config: lpe from unprivileged to allow_active in pam</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6018</link><description>A Local Privilege Escalation (LPE) vulnerability has been discovered in pam-config within Linux Pluggable Authentication Modules (PAM). This flaw allows an unprivileged local attacker (for example, a user logged in via SSH) to obtain the elevated privileges normally reserved for a physically present, "allow_active" user. The highest risk is that the attacker can then perform all allow_active yes Polkit actions, which are typically restricted to console users, potentially gaining unauthorized control over system configurations, services, or other sensitive operations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33020 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody information disclosure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33020</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 transmits sensitive information without encryption that could allow an attacker to obtain highly sensitive information.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33076 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33076</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-33077 | IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody code execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-33077</link><description>IBM Engineering Systems Design Rhapsody 9.0.2, 10.0, and 10.0.1 is vulnerable to a stack-based buffer overflow, caused by improper bounds checking. A local user could overflow the buffer and execute arbitrary code on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40597 | A Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Ser...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40597</link><description>A Heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially results in code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40598 | A Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SMA100 series web interface, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker t...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40598</link><description>A Reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in the SMA100 series web interface, allowing a remote unauthenticated attacker to potentially execute arbitrary JavaScript code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40596 | A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Se...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40596</link><description>A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SMA100 series web interface allows remote, unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS) or potentially results in code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36116 | IBM Db2 Mirror for i cross-site websocket hijacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36116</link><description>IBM Db2 Mirror for i 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 GUI is affected by cross-site WebSocket hijacking vulnerability.  By sending a specially crafted request, an unauthenticated malicious actor could exploit this vulnerability to sniff an existing WebSocket connection to then remotely perform operations that the user is not allowed to perform.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36117 | IBM Db2 Mirror for i session fixation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36117</link><description>IBM Db2 Mirror for i 7.4, 7.5, and 7.6 does not disallow the session id after use which could allow an authenticated user to impersonate another user on the system.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2010-10012 | httpdASM 0.92 Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2010-10012</link><description>A path traversal vulnerability exists in httpdasm version 0.92, a lightweight Windows HTTP server, that allows unauthenticated attackers to read arbitrary files on the host system. By sending a specially crafted GET request containing a sequence of URL-encoded backslashes and directory traversal patterns, an attacker can escape the web root and access sensitive files outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10141 | Xdebug Remote Debugger Unauthenticated OS Command Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10141</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists within Xdebug versions 2.5.5 and earlier, a PHP debugging extension developed by Derick Rethans. When remote debugging is enabled, Xdebug listens on port 9000 and accepts debugger protocol commands without authentication. An attacker can send a crafted eval command over this interface to execute arbitrary PHP code, which may invoke system-level functions such as system() or passthru(). This results in full compromise of the host under the privileges of the web server user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2016-15045 | Deepin lastore-daemon Privilege Escalation via Unsigned .deb Installation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2016-15045</link><description>A local privilege escalation vulnerability exists in lastore-daemon, the system package manager daemon used in Deepin Linux (developed by Wuhan Deepin Technology Co., Ltd.). In versions 0.9.53-1 (Deepin 15.5) and 0.9.66-1 (Deepin 15.7), the D-Bus configuration permits any user in the sudo group to invoke the InstallPackage method without password authentication. By default, the first user created on Deepin is in the sudo group. An attacker with shell access can craft a .deb package containing a malicious post-install script and use dbus-send to install it via lastore-daemon, resulting in arbitrary code execution as root.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2017-20198 | DC/OS Marathon UI &amp;lt; 1.9.0 Unauthenticated RCE via Docker Mount Abuse</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2017-20198</link><description>The Marathon UI in DC/OS &lt; 1.9.0 allows unauthenticated users to deploy arbitrary Docker containers. Due to improper restriction of volume mount configurations, attackers can deploy a container that mounts the host's root filesystem (/) with read/write privileges. When using a malicious Docker image, the attacker can write to /etc/cron.d/ on the host, achieving arbitrary code execution with root privileges. This impacts any system where the Docker daemon honors Marathon container configurations without policy enforcement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25113 | Dicoogle PACS Web Server 2.5.0 Unauthenticated Path Traversal</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25113</link><description>An unauthenticated path traversal vulnerability exists in Dicoogle PACS Web Server version 2.5.0 and possibly earlier. The vulnerability allows remote attackers to read arbitrary files on the underlying system by sending a crafted request to the /exportFile endpoint using the UID parameter. Successful exploitation can reveal sensitive files accessible by the web server user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2018-25114 | osCommerce 2.3.4.1 Installer Unauthenticated Configuration File Injection PHP Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2018-25114</link><description>A remote code execution vulnerability exists within osCommerce Online Merchant version 2.3.4.1 due to insecure default configuration and missing authentication in the installer workflow. By default, the /install/ directory remains accessible after installation. An unauthenticated attacker can invoke install_4.php, submit crafted POST data, and inject arbitrary PHP code into the configure.php file. When the application later includes this file, the injected payload is executed, resulting in full server-side compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2022-4978 | Steppschuh Remote Control Server 3.1.1.12 Unauthenticated RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2022-4978</link><description>Remote Control Server, maintained by Steppschuh, 3.1.1.12 allows unauthenticated remote code execution when authentication is disabled, which is the default configuration. The server exposes a custom UDP-based control protocol that accepts remote keyboard input events without verification. An attacker on the same network can issue a sequence of keystroke commands to launch a system shell and execute arbitrary commands, resulting in full system compromise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46099 | In Pluck CMS 4.7.20-dev, an authenticated attacker can upload or create a crafted PHP file under the albums module directory and access it v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46099</link><description>In Pluck CMS 4.7.20-dev, an authenticated attacker can upload or create a crafted PHP file under the albums module directory and access it via the module routing logic in albums.site.php, resulting in arbitrary command execution through a GET parameter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-40599 | An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the SMA 100 series web management interface. A remote attacker with administr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-40599</link><description>An authenticated arbitrary file upload vulnerability exists in the SMA 100 series web management interface. A remote attacker with administrative privileges can exploit this flaw to upload arbitrary files to the system, potentially leading to remote code execution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54090 | Apache HTTP Server: &amp;#x27;RewriteCond expr&amp;#x27; always evaluates to true in 2.4.64</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54090</link><description>A bug in Apache HTTP Server 2.4.64 results in all "RewriteCond expr ..." tests evaluating as "true".



Users are recommended to upgrade to version 2.4.65, which fixes the issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4411 | XSS in Dataprom Informatics&amp;#x27; PACS-ACSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4411</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Dataprom Informatics PACS-ACSS allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects PACS-ACSS: before 16.05.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-12310 | Bypass of Login Screen on Shared Kiosk Workstations</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-12310</link><description>A vulnerability in Imprivata Enterprise Access Management (formerly Imprivata OneSign) allows bypassing the login screen of the shared kiosk workstation and allows unauthorized access to the underlying Windows system through the already logged-in autologon account due to insufficient handling of keyboard shortcuts.
This issue affects Imprivata Enterprise Access Management versions 5.3 through 24.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4296 | Open Redirect in HotelRunner&amp;#x27;s B2B</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4296</link><description>URL Redirection to Untrusted Site ('Open Redirect') vulnerability in HotelRunner B2B allows Forceful Browsing.This issue affects B2B: before 04.06.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40682 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40682</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local user to cause a denial of service due to improper validation of specified type of input.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-40686 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis HOST header injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-40686</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 is vulnerable to HTTP header injection, caused by improper validation of input by the HOST headers. This could allow an attacker to conduct various attacks against the vulnerable system, including cross-site scripting, cache poisoning or session hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41750 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41750</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local, authenticated attacker to bypass client-side enforcement of security to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-41751 | IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis security bypass</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-41751</link><description>IBM SmartCloud Analytics - Log Analysis 1.3.7.0, 1.3.7.1, 1.3.7.2, 1.3.8.0, 1.3.8.1, and 1.3.8.2 could allow a local, authenticated attacker to bypass client-side enforcement of security to manipulate data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-50127 | Extension - dj-extensions.com - SQLi vulnerability in DJ-Flyer component 1.0-3.2 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-50127</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in DJ-Flyer component 1.0-3.2 for Joomla was discovered. The issue allows privileged users to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54294 | Extension - stackideas.com - SQLi vulnerability in Komento component 4.0.0-4.0.7 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54294</link><description>A SQLi vulnerability in Komento component 4.0.0-4.0.7for Joomla was discovered. The issue allows unprivileged users to execute arbitrary SQL commands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54295 | Extension - dj-extensions.com - Reflected XSS vulnerability in DJ-Reviews component 1.0-1.3.6 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54295</link><description>A Reflected XSS vulnerability in DJ-Reviews component 1.0-1.3.6 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54296 | Extension - mooj.org - Stored XSS vulnerability in ProFiles component 1.0-1.5.0 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54296</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in ProFiles component 1.0-1.5.0 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54297 | Extension - compojoom.com - Stored XSS vulnerability in CComment component 5.0.0-6.1.14 for Joomla</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54297</link><description>A stored XSS vulnerability in CComment component 5.0.0-6.1.14 for Joomla was discovered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-27930 | Stored XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-27930</link><description>Zohocorp ManageEngine Applications Manager versions 176600 and prior are vulnerable to stored cross-site scripting in the File/Directory monitor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53882 | python-mailmans logrotate configuration allows potential escalation from mailman to root</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53882</link><description>A Reliance on Untrusted Inputs in a Security Decision vulnerability in the logrotate configuration for openSUSEs mailman3 package allows potential escalation from mailman to root. This issue affects openSUSE Tumbleweed: from ? before 3.3.10-2.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41683 | Weidmueller: Root Command Injection via Unsanitized Input in event_mail_test Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41683</link><description>An authenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on affected devices due to lack of improper sanitizing of user input in the Main Web Interface (endpoint event_mail_test).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41684 | Weidmueller: Root Command Injection via Unsanitized Input in tls_iotgen_setting Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41684</link><description>An authenticated remote attacker can execute arbitrary commands with root privileges on affected devices due to lack of improper sanitizing of user input in the Main Web Interface (endpoint tls_iotgen_setting).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41687 | Weidmueller: Unauthenticated Stack-Based Buffer Overflow in u-link Management API</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41687</link><description>An unauthenticated remote attacker may use a stack based buffer overflow in the u-link Management API to gain full access on the affected devices.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8070 | Windows service registered with an unquoted ImagePath vulnerability in the system registry</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8070</link><description>The Windows service configuration of ABP and AES contains an unquoted ImagePath registry value vulnerability. This allows a local attacker to execute arbitrary code by placing a malicious executable in a predictable location such as C:\Program.exe. If the service runs with elevated privileges, exploitation results in privilege escalation to SYSTEM level. This vulnerability arises from an unquoted service path affecting systems where the executable resides in a path containing spaces.
Affected products and versions include: ABP 2.0.7.6130 and earlier as well as AES 1.0.6.6133 and earlier.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31700 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31700</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted malicious packets, potentially causing service disruption (e.g., crashes) or remote code execution (RCE). Some devices may have deployed protection mechanisms such as Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR), which reduces the likelihood of successful RCE exploitation. However, denial-of-service (DoS) attacks remain a concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31701 | A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted mali...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31701</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Dahua products.

Attackers could exploit a buffer overflow vulnerability by sending specially crafted malicious packets, potentially causing service disruption (e.g., crashes) or remote code execution (RCE). Some devices may have deployed protection mechanisms such as Address Space Layout Randomization (ASLR), which reduces the likelihood of successful RCE exploitation. However, denial-of-service (DoS) attacks remain a concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6174 | WordPress Qwizcards &amp;lt;= 3.9.4 - Reflected XSS</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6174</link><description>The Qwizcards | online quizzes and flashcards WordPress plugin through 3.9.4 does not sanitise and escape the "_stylesheet" parameter before outputting it back in the page, leading to a Reflected Cross-Site Scripting which could be used against high privilege users such as admin or any other user.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54438 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54438</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54439 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54439</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54440 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54440</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54441 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54441</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54442 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54442</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54443 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54443</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54444 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54444</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54445 | Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Server Side Request For...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54445</link><description>Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Server Side Request Forgery.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54446 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54446</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Upload a Web Shell to a Web Server.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54447 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54447</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54448 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54448</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54451 | Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54451</link><description>Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:00:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54452 | Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54452</link><description>Improper Authentication vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54453 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54453</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54449 | Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue aff...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54449</link><description>Unrestricted Upload of File with Dangerous Type vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54450 | Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allow...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54450</link><description>Improper Limitation of a Pathname to a Restricted Directory ('Path Traversal') vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Code Injection.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54454 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54454</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54455 | Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicI...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54455</link><description>Use of Hard-coded Credentials vulnerability in Samsung Electronics MagicINFO 9 Server allows Authentication Bypass.This issue affects MagicINFO 9 Server: less than 21.1080.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8020 | All versions of the package private-ip are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide an IP or hostname ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8020</link><description>All versions of the package private-ip are vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) where an attacker can provide an IP or hostname that resolves to a multicast IP address (224.0.0.0/4) which is not included as part of the private IP ranges in the package's source code.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8021 | All versions of the package files-bucket-server are vulnerable to Directory Traversal where an attacker can traverse the file system and acc...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8021</link><description>All versions of the package files-bucket-server are vulnerable to Directory Traversal where an attacker can traverse the file system and access files outside of the intended directory.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8022 | Versions of the package bun after 0.0.12 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command In...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8022</link><description>Versions of the package bun after 0.0.12 are vulnerable to Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') in the $ shell API due to improper neutralization of user input. An attacker can exploit this by providing specially crafted input that includes command-line arguments or shell metacharacters, leading to unintended command execution.&#13;&#13;**Note:** This issue relates to the widely known and actively developed 'Bun' JavaScript runtime. The bun package on NPM at versions 0.0.12 and below belongs to a different and older project that happened to claim the 'bun' name in the past.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43881 | Improper validation of specified quantity in input issue exists in Real-time Bus Tracking System versions prior to 1.1. If exploited, a deni...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43881</link><description>Improper validation of specified quantity in input issue exists in Real-time Bus Tracking System versions prior to 1.1. If exploited, a denial of service (DoS) condition may be caused by an attacker who can log in to the administrative page of the affected product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53286 | Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in DDNS Record functionality in Syn...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53286</link><description>Improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in DDNS Record functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to execute arbitrary code via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53287 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VPN Setting functionality in Synology ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53287</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in VPN Setting functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-53288 | Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NTP Region functionality in Synology R...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-53288</link><description>Improper neutralization of input during web page generation ('Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in NTP Region functionality in Synology Router Manager (SRM) before 1.3.1-9346-11 allows remote authenticated users with administrator privileges to inject arbitrary web script or HTML via unspecified vectors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-42947 | Code Injection vulnerability in SAP FICA ODN framework</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-42947</link><description>SAP FICA ODN framework allows a high privileged user to inject value inside the local variable which can then be executed by the application. An attacker could thereby control the behaviour of the application causing high impact on integrity, low impact on availability and no impact on confidentiality of the application.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5753 | Valuation Calculator &amp;lt;= 1.3.2 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via link Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5753</link><description>The Valuation Calculator plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘link’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 1.3.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5818 | Featured Image Plus – Quick &amp;amp; Bulk Edit with Unsplash &amp;lt;= 1.6.4 - Authenticated (Admin+) Server-Side Request Forgery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5818</link><description>The Featured Image Plus – Quick &amp; Bulk Edit with Unsplash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Server-Side Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.4 via the fip_get_image_options() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with administrator-level access and above, to make web requests to arbitrary locations originating from the web application and can be used to query and modify information from internal services.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6054 | YANewsflash &amp;lt;= 1.0.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6054</link><description>The YANewsflash plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'yanewsflash/yanewsflash.php' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6190 | Realty Portal – Agent &amp;lt;= 0.3.9 - Missing Authorization to Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation via rp_user_profile() Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6190</link><description>The Realty Portal – Agent plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization within the rp_user_profile() AJAX handler in versions 0.1.0 through 0.3.9. The handler reads the client-supplied meta key and value pairs from $_POST and passes them directly to update_user_meta() without restricting to a safe whitelist. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to overwrite the wp_capabilities meta and grant themselves the administrator role.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6214 | Omnishop &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Arbitrary User Deletion via /users/delete REST Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6214</link><description>The Omnishop plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery on its /users/delete REST route in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. The route’s permission_callback only verifies that the requester is logged in, but fails to require any nonce or other proof of intent. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary user accounts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6215 | Omnishop &amp;lt;= 1.0.9 - Missing Registration Restriction to Unauthenticated Account Creation via /users/register REST Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6215</link><description>The Omnishop plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Unauthenticated Registration Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.9. Its /users/register endpoint is exposed to the public (permission_callback always returns true) and invokes wp_create_user() unconditionally,  ignoring the site’s users_can_register option and any nonce or CAPTCHA checks. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to create arbitrary user accounts (customer) on sites where registrations should be closed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6261 | Fleetwire Fleet Management Plugin &amp;lt;= 1.0.19 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via fleetwire_list Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6261</link><description>The Fleetwire Fleet Management plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's fleetwire_list shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.19 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7722 | Social Streams &amp;lt;= 1.2.1 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Privilege Escalation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7722</link><description>The Social Streams plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to privilege escalation in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.1. This is due to the plugin not properly validating a user's identity prior to updating their user meta information in the update_user_meta() function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to change their user type to that of an administrator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8060 | Tenda AC23 httpd setMacFilterCfg sub_46C940 stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8060</link><description>A vulnerability has been found in Tenda AC23 16.03.07.52 and classified as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is the function sub_46C940 of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54120 | PCL Community Edition exposes login credentials in logs</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54120</link><description>PCL (Plain Craft Launcher) Community Edition is a Minecraft launcher. In PCL CE versions 2.12.0-beta.5 to 2.12.0-beta.9, the login credentials used during the third-party login process are accidentally recorded in the local log file. Although the log file is not automatically uploaded or shared, if the user manually sends the log file, there is a risk of leakage. This is fixed in version 2.12.0-beta.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43489 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43489</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The vulnerability could deserialize untrusted data without validation. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43486 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43486</link><description>A potential stored cross-site scripting vulnerability has been
identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The
website allows user input to be stored and rendered without proper
sanitization. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43487 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43487</link><description>A potential privilege escalation through Sudo vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.2. The firmware flaw does not properly implement access controls. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43488 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43488</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.2. The vulnerability could allow a bypass of the application's XSS filter by submitting untrusted characters. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54139 | HAX CMS&amp;#x27; application pages are vulnerable to clickjacking</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54139</link><description>HAX CMS allows users to manage their microsite universe with a NodeJS or PHP backend. In haxcms-nodejs versions 11.0.12 and below and in haxcms-php versions 11.0.7 and below, all pages within the HAX CMS application do not contain headers to prevent other websites from loading the site within an iframe. This applies to both the CMS and generated sites. An unauthenticated attacker can load the standalone login page or other sensitive functionality within an iframe, performing a UI redressing attack (clickjacking). This can be used to perform social engineering attacks to attempt to coerce users into performing unintended actions within the HAX CMS application. This is fixed in haxcms-nodejs version 11.0.13 and haxcms-php 11.0.8.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43483 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43483</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been
identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The
vulnerability could allow the retrieval of hardcoded cryptographic keys. HP has
addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43484 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43484</link><description>A potential reflected cross-site scripting vulnerability has been
identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The
website does not validate or sanitize the user input before rendering it in the
response. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43485 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43485</link><description>A potential security
vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions
prior to 10.12.2. The vulnerability could potentially allow a privileged
user to retrieve credentials from the log files. HP has addressed the issue in
the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43021 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43021</link><description>A potential security vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The vulnerability could allow the use and retrieval of the default password. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43022 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43022</link><description>A potential SQL injection vulnerability has been identified in the Poly
Clariti Manager for versions prior to 10.12.1. The vulnerability could allow
a privileged user to execute SQL commands. HP has addressed the issue in
the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-43020 | Poly Clariti Manager - Multiple Security Vulnerabilities</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-43020</link><description>A potential command
injection vulnerability has been identified in the Poly Clariti Manager for
versions prior to 10.12.2. The vulnerability could allow a privileged user
to submit arbitrary input. HP has addressed the issue in the latest software update.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-41425 | DuraComm DP-10iN-100-MU Cross-site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-41425</link><description>DuraComm SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU

 is vulnerable to a cross-site scripting attack. This could allow an attacker to prevent legitimate users from accessing the web interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7766 | Lantronix Provisioning Manager Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7766</link><description>Lantronix Provisioning Manager is vulnerable to XML external entity attacks in configuration files supplied by network devices, leading to unauthenticated remote code execution on hosts with Provisioning Manager installed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48733 | DuraComm DP-10iN-100-MU Missing Authentication for Critical Function</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48733</link><description>DuraComm SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU

 lacks access controls for a function that should require user authentication. This could allow an attacker to repeatedly reboot the device.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53538 | Suricata&amp;#x27;s mishandling of data on  HTTP2 stream 0 can lead to resource starvation</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53538</link><description>Suricata is a network IDS, IPS and NSM engine developed by the OISF (Open Information Security Foundation) and the Suricata community. In versions 7.0.10 and below and  8.0.0-beta1 through 8.0.0-rc1, mishandling of data on HTTP2 stream 0 can lead to uncontrolled memory usage, leading to loss of visibility. Workarounds include disabling the HTTP/2 parser, and using a signature like drop http2 any any -&gt; any any (frame:http2.hdr; byte_test:1,=,0,3; byte_test:4,=,0,5; sid: 1;) where the first byte test tests the HTTP2 frame type DATA and the second tests the stream id 0. This is fixed in versions 7.0.11 and 8.0.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53703 | DuraComm DP-10iN-100-MU Cleartext Transmission of Sensitive Information</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53703</link><description>DuraComm SPM-500 DP-10iN-100-MU

 transmits sensitive data without encryption over a channel that could be intercepted by attackers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54072 | yt-dlp allows `--exec` command injection when using placeholder on Windows</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54072</link><description>yt-dlp is a feature-rich command-line audio/video downloader. In versions 2025.06.25 and below, when the --exec option is used on Windows with the default placeholder (or {}), insufficient sanitization is applied to the expanded filepath, allowing for remote code execution. This is a bypass of the mitigation for CVE-2024-22423 where the default placeholder and {} were not covered by the new escaping rules. Windows users who are unable to upgrade should avoid using --exec altogether. Instead, the --write-info-json or --dump-json options could be used, with an external script or command line consuming the JSON output. This is fixed in version 2025.07.21.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54137 | NodeJS version of the HAX CMS application is distributed with Default Secrets</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54137</link><description>HAX CMS NodeJS allows users to manage their microsite universe with a NodeJS backend. Versions 11.0.9 and below were distributed with hardcoded default credentials for the user and superuser accounts. Additionally, the application has default private keys for JWTs. Users aren't prompted to change credentials or secrets during installation, and there is no way to change them through the UI. An unauthenticated attacker can read the default user credentials and JWT private keys from the public haxtheweb GitHub repositories. These credentials and keys can be used to access unconfigured self-hosted instances of the application, modify sites, and perform further attacks. This is fixed in version 11.0.10.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54138 | LibreNMS has Authenticated Local File Inclusion in ajax_form.php that Allows RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54138</link><description>LibreNMS is an auto-discovering PHP/MySQL/SNMP based network monitoring which includes support for a wide range of network hardware and operating systems. LibreNMS versions 25.6.0 and below contain an architectural vulnerability in the ajax_form.php endpoint that permits Remote File Inclusion based on user-controlled POST input. The application directly uses the type parameter to dynamically include .inc.php files from the trusted path includes/html/forms/, without validation or allowlisting. This pattern introduces a latent Remote Code Execution (RCE) vector if an attacker can stage a file in this include path — for example, via symlink, development misconfiguration, or chained vulnerabilities. This is fixed in version 25.7.0.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54140 | pyLoad has Path Traversal Vulnerability in json/upload Endpoint that allows Arbitrary File Write</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54140</link><description>pyLoad is a free and open-source Download Manager written in pure Python. In version 0.5.0b3.dev89, an authenticated path traversal vulnerability exists in the /json/upload endpoint of pyLoad. By manipulating the filename of an uploaded file, an attacker can traverse out of the intended upload directory, allowing them to write arbitrary files to any location on the system accessible to the pyLoad process. This may lead to: Remote Code Execution (RCE), local privilege escalation, system-wide compromise, persistence, and backdoors. This is fixed in version 0.5.0b3.dev90.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-54141 | ViewVC&amp;#x27;s standalone server exposes arbitrary server filesystem content</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-54141</link><description>ViewVC is a browser interface for CVS and Subversion version control repositories. In versions 1.1.0 through 1.1.31 and 1.2.0 through 1.2.3, the standalone.py script provided in the ViewVC distribution can expose the contents of the host server's filesystem though a directory traversal-style attack. This is fixed in versions 1.1.31 and  1.2.4.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8010 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 138.0.7204.168 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8010</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 138.0.7204.168 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8011 | Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 138.0.7204.168 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8011</link><description>Type Confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 138.0.7204.168 allowed a remote attacker to potentially exploit heap corruption via a crafted HTML page. (Chromium security severity: High)</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8027 | On 64-bit platforms IonMonkey-JIT only wrote 32 bits of the 64-bit return value space on the stack. Baseline-JIT, however, read the entire 6...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8027</link><description>On 64-bit platforms IonMonkey-JIT only wrote 32 bits of the 64-bit return value space on the stack. Baseline-JIT, however, read the entire 64 bits. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.26, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8028 | On arm64, a WASM `br_table` instruction with a lot of entries could lead to the label being too far from the instruction causing truncation ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8028</link><description>On arm64, a WASM `br_table` instruction with a lot of entries could lead to the label being too far from the instruction causing truncation and incorrect computation of the branch address. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.26, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8029 | Thunderbird executed `javascript:` URLs when used in `object` and `embed` tags. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8029</link><description>Thunderbird executed `javascript:` URLs when used in `object` and `embed` tags. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8030 | Insufficient escaping in the “Copy as cURL” feature could potentially be used to trick a user into executing unexpected code. This vulnerabi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8030</link><description>Insufficient escaping in the “Copy as cURL” feature could potentially be used to trick a user into executing unexpected code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8031 | The `username:password` part was not correctly stripped from URLs in CSP reports potentially leaking HTTP Basic Authentication credentials. ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8031</link><description>The `username:password` part was not correctly stripped from URLs in CSP reports potentially leaking HTTP Basic Authentication credentials. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8032 | XSLT document loading did not correctly propagate the source document which bypassed its CSP. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Fire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8032</link><description>XSLT document loading did not correctly propagate the source document which bypassed its CSP. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8033 | The JavaScript engine did not handle closed generators correctly and it was possible to resume them leading to a nullptr deref. This vulnera...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8033</link><description>The JavaScript engine did not handle closed generators correctly and it was possible to resume them leading to a nullptr deref. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.26, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8034 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.25, Firefox ESR 128.12, Thunderbird ESR 128.12, Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Fire...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8034</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 115.25, Firefox ESR 128.12, Thunderbird ESR 128.12, Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 115.26, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8035 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 128.12, Thunderbird ESR 128.12, Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Firefox 140 and Thunderb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8035</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 128.12, Thunderbird ESR 128.12, Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 128.13, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, Thunderbird &lt; 128.13, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8036 | Thunderbird cached CORS preflight responses across IP address changes. This allowed circumventing CORS with DNS rebinding. This vulnerabilit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8036</link><description>Thunderbird cached CORS preflight responses across IP address changes. This allowed circumventing CORS with DNS rebinding. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8037 | Setting a nameless cookie with an equals sign in the value shadowed other cookies. Even if the nameless cookie was set over HTTP and the sha...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8037</link><description>Setting a nameless cookie with an equals sign in the value shadowed other cookies. Even if the nameless cookie was set over HTTP and the shadowed cookie included the `Secure` attribute. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8038 | Thunderbird ignored paths when checking the validity of navigations in a frame. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140....</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8038</link><description>Thunderbird ignored paths when checking the validity of navigations in a frame. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8039 | In some cases search terms persisted in the URL bar even after navigating away from the search page. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 14...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8039</link><description>In some cases search terms persisted in the URL bar even after navigating away from the search page. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8040 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8040</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox ESR 140.0, Thunderbird ESR 140.0, Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141, Firefox ESR &lt; 140.1, Thunderbird &lt; 141, and Thunderbird &lt; 140.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8043 | Focus incorrectly truncated URLs towards the beginning instead of around the origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141 and Thunderbir...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8043</link><description>Focus incorrectly truncated URLs towards the beginning instead of around the origin. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141 and Thunderbird &lt; 141.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8044 | Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that w...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8044</link><description>Memory safety bugs present in Firefox 140 and Thunderbird 140. Some of these bugs showed evidence of memory corruption and we presume that with enough effort some of these could have been exploited to run arbitrary code. This vulnerability affects Firefox &lt; 141 and Thunderbird &lt; 141.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7723 | Authenticated command injection on VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1 and VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7723</link><description>A command injection vulnerability exists that can be exploited after authentication in VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1 and VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2.This issue affects VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1: before 1.1.5 Build 250518; VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2: before 1.3.1 Build 250407.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7724 | Unauthenticated command injection on VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1 and VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7724</link><description>An unauthenticated OS command injection vulnerability exists in VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1 and VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2.This issue affects VIGI NVR1104H-4P V1: before 1.1.5 Build 250518; VIGI NVR2016H-16MP V2: before 1.3.1 Build 250407.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51462 | Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in api.apps.dialog_app.set_dialog in RAGFlow 0.17.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbit...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51462</link><description>Stored Cross-site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in api.apps.dialog_app.set_dialog in RAGFlow 0.17.2 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript via crafted input to the assistant greeting field, which is stored unsanitised and rendered using a markdown component with rehype-raw.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51472 | Code Injection in AgentTemplate.eval_agent_config in TransformerOptimus SuperAGI 0.0.14 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary Python ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51472</link><description>Code Injection in AgentTemplate.eval_agent_config in TransformerOptimus SuperAGI 0.0.14 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary Python code via malicious values in agent template configurations such as the goal, constraints, or instruction field, which are evaluated using eval() without validation during template loading or updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31511 | An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can bypass manager approval by changing the user ID in a Request%20Bui...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31511</link><description>An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can bypass manager approval by changing the user ID in a Request%20Building%20Access requestSubmit API call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31512 | An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can bypass manager approval via isAddedByApprover in a Request%20Build...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31512</link><description>An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can bypass manager approval via isAddedByApprover in a Request%20Building%20Access requestSubmit API call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-31513 | An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can elevate to administrator privileges via the IsAdminApprover parame...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-31513</link><description>An issue was discovered in AlertEnterprise Guardian 4.1.14.2.2.1. One can elevate to administrator privileges via the IsAdminApprover parameter in a Request%20Building%20Access requestSubmit API call.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51458 | SQL Injection in editor_sql_run and query_ex in eosphoros-ai DB-GPT 0.7.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51458</link><description>SQL Injection in editor_sql_run and query_ex in eosphoros-ai DB-GPT 0.7.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary SQL statements via crafted input passed to the /v1/editor/sql/run or /v1/editor/chart/run endpoints, interacting with api_editor_v1.editor_sql_run, editor_chart_run, and datasource.rdbms.base.query_ex.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51475 | Arbitrary File Overwrite (AFO) in superagi.controllers.resources.upload in TransformerOptimus SuperAGI 0.0.14 allows remote attackers to ove...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51475</link><description>Arbitrary File Overwrite (AFO) in superagi.controllers.resources.upload in TransformerOptimus SuperAGI 0.0.14 allows remote attackers to overwrite arbitrary files via unsanitised filenames submitted to the file upload endpoint, due to improper handling of directory traversal in os.path.join() and lack of path validation in get_root_input_dir().</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51459 | File Upload vulnerability in agent.hub.controller.refresh_plugins in eosphoros-ai DB-GPT 0.7.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51459</link><description>File Upload vulnerability in agent.hub.controller.refresh_plugins in eosphoros-ai DB-GPT 0.7.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary code via a malicious plugin ZIP file uploaded to the /v1/personal/agent/upload endpoint, interacting with plugin_hub._sanitize_filename and plugins_util.scan_plugins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51479 | Authorization bypass in update_user_group in onyx-dot-app Onyx Enterprise Edition 0.27.0 allows remote authenticated attackers to modify arb...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51479</link><description>Authorization bypass in update_user_group in onyx-dot-app Onyx Enterprise Edition 0.27.0 allows remote authenticated attackers to modify arbitrary user groups via crafted PATCH requests to the /api/manage/admin/user-group/id endpoint, bypassing intended curator-group assignment checks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51471 | Cross-Domain Token Exposure in server.auth.getAuthorizationToken in Ollama 0.6.7 allows remote attackers to steal authentication tokens and ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51471</link><description>Cross-Domain Token Exposure in server.auth.getAuthorizationToken in Ollama 0.6.7 allows remote attackers to steal authentication tokens and bypass access controls via a malicious realm value in a WWW-Authenticate header returned by the /api/pull endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48964 | ping in iputils before 20250602 allows a denial of service (application error in adaptive ping mode or incorrect data collection) via a craf...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48964</link><description>ping in iputils before 20250602 allows a denial of service (application error in adaptive ping mode or incorrect data collection) via a crafted ICMP Echo Reply packet, because a zero timestamp can lead to large intermediate values that have an integer overflow when squared during statistics calculations. NOTE: this issue exists because of an incomplete fix for CVE-2025-47268 (that fix was only about timestamp calculations, and it did not account for a specific scenario where the original timestamp in the ICMP payload is zero).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2024-38335 | IBM Security QRadar Network Threat Analytics denial of service</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2024-38335</link><description>IBM Security QRadar Network Threat Analytics 1.0.0 through 1.3.1 could allow a privileged user to cause a denial of service due to improper allocation of resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51464 | Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in aimhubio Aim 3.28.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims browsers via malicious ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51464</link><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) in aimhubio Aim 3.28.0 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary JavaScript in victims browsers via malicious Python code submitted to the /api/reports endpoint, which is interpreted and executed by Pyodide when the report is viewed. No sanitisation or sandbox restrictions prevent JavaScript execution via pyodide.code.run_js().</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51481 | Local File Inclusion in dagster._grpc.impl.get_notebook_data in Dagster 1.10.14 allows attackers with access to the gRPC server to read arbi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51481</link><description>Local File Inclusion in dagster._grpc.impl.get_notebook_data in Dagster 1.10.14 allows attackers with access to the gRPC server to read arbitrary files by supplying path traversal sequences in the notebook_path field of ExternalNotebookData requests, bypassing the intended extension-based check.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6523 | Use of weak credentials in emergency authentication component in Devolutions Server allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass authenticat...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6523</link><description>Use of weak credentials in emergency authentication component in Devolutions Server allows an unauthenticated attacker to bypass authentication via brute forcing the short emergency codes generated by the server within a feasible timeframe.

This issue affects the following versions :

  *  Devolutions Server 2025.2.2.0 through 2025.2.3.0
  *  
Devolutions Server 2025.1.11.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6741 | Improper access control in secure message component in Devolutions Server allows an authenticated user to steal unauthorized entries via the...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6741</link><description>Improper access control in secure message component in Devolutions Server allows an authenticated user to steal unauthorized entries via the secure message entry attachment feature


This issue affects the following versions :

  *  Devolutions Server 2025.2.2.0 through 2025.2.4.0
  *  
Devolutions Server 2025.1.11.0 and earlier</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51482 | Remote Code Execution in letta.server.rest_api.routers.v1.tools.run_tool_from_source in letta-ai Letta 0.7.12 allows remote attackers to exe...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51482</link><description>Remote Code Execution in letta.server.rest_api.routers.v1.tools.run_tool_from_source in letta-ai Letta 0.7.12 allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary Python code and system commands via crafted payloads to the /v1/tools/run endpoint, bypassing intended sandbox restrictions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5042 | RFA File Parsing Out-of-Bounds Read Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5042</link><description>A maliciously crafted RFA file, when parsed through Autodesk Revit, can force an Out-of-Bounds Read vulnerability. A malicious actor can leverage this vulnerability to cause a crash, read sensitive data, or execute arbitrary code in the context of the current process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51480 | Path Traversal vulnerability in onnx.external_data_helper.save_external_data in ONNX 1.17.0 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files by...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51480</link><description>Path Traversal vulnerability in onnx.external_data_helper.save_external_data in ONNX 1.17.0 allows attackers to overwrite arbitrary files by supplying crafted external_data.location paths containing traversal sequences, bypassing intended directory restrictions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7371 | Okta On-Premises Provisioning (OPP) agents log certain user data during administrator-initiated password resets. This vulnerability allows a...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7371</link><description>Okta On-Premises Provisioning (OPP) agents log certain user data during administrator-initiated password resets. This vulnerability allows an attacker with access to the local servers running OPP agents to retrieve user personal information and temporary passwords created during password reset. You are affected by this vulnerability if the following preconditions are met: Local server running OPP agent with versions &gt;=2.2.1 and &lt;= 2.3.0, and User account has had an administrator-initiated password reset while using the affected versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-35966 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the CDB2SQLQUERY protocol buffer message handling of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A specially cr...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-35966</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the CDB2SQLQUERY protocol buffer message handling of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A specially crafted protocol buffer message can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can simply connect to a database instance over TCP and send the crafted message to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36512 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1 database when handling a distributed transaction heartbeat. A specially...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36512</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1 database when handling a distributed transaction heartbeat. A specially crafted protocol buffer message can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can simply connect to a database instance over TCP and send the crafted message to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-36520 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the net_connectmsg Protocol Buffer Message functionality of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A speci...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-36520</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the net_connectmsg Protocol Buffer Message functionality of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A specially crafted network packets can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send packets to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46354 | A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Distributed Transaction Commit/Abort Operation functionality of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A spec...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46354</link><description>A denial of service vulnerability exists in the Distributed Transaction Commit/Abort Operation functionality of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1. A specially crafted network packet can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can send a malicious packet to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-48498 | A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the Distributed Transaction component of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1 when processing a number of...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-48498</link><description>A null pointer dereference vulnerability exists in the Distributed Transaction component of Bloomberg Comdb2 8.1 when processing a number of fields used for coordination. A specially crafted protocol buffer message can lead to a denial of service. An attacker can simply connect to a database instance over TCP and send the crafted message to trigger this vulnerability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8019 | Shenzhen Libituo Technology LBT-T300-T310 appy.cgi sub_40B6F0 buffer overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8019</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Shenzhen Libituo Technology LBT-T300-T310 2.2.3.6. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is the function sub_40B6F0 of the file at/appy.cgi. The manipulation of the argument wan_proto leads to buffer overflow. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51463 | Path Traversal in restore_run_backup() in AIM 3.28.0 allows remote attackers to write arbitrary files to the server's filesystem via a craft...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51463</link><description>Path Traversal in restore_run_backup() in AIM 3.28.0 allows remote attackers to write arbitrary files to the server's filesystem via a crafted backup tar file submitted to the run_instruction API, which is extracted without path validation during restoration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51858 | Self Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChatPlayground.ai through 2025-05-24, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain s...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51858</link><description>Self Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChatPlayground.ai through 2025-05-24, allows attackers to execute arbitrary code and gain sensitive information via a crafted SVG file contents sent through the chat component.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51859 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Chaindesk thru 2025-05-26 in its agent chat component. An attacker can achieve arbitrary ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51859</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in Chaindesk thru 2025-05-26 in its agent chat component. An attacker can achieve arbitrary client-side script execution by crafting an AI agent whose system prompt instructs the underlying Large Language Model (LLM) to embed malicious script payloads (e.g., SVG-based XSS) into its chat responses. When a user interacts with such a malicious agent or accesses a direct link to a conversation containing an XSS payload, the script executes in the user's browser. Successful exploitation can lead to the theft of sensitive information, such as JWT session tokens, potentially resulting in account hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51860 | Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in TelegAI (telegai.com) 2025-05-26 in its chat component and character container component. An attacker c...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51860</link><description>Stored Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) in TelegAI (telegai.com) 2025-05-26 in its chat component and character container component. An attacker can achieve arbitrary client-side script execution by crafting an AI Character with SVG XSS payloads in either description, greeting, example dialog, or system prompt(instructing the LLM to embed XSS payload in its chat response). When a user interacts with such a malicious AI Character or just browse its profile, the script executes in the user's browser. Successful exploitation can lead to the theft of sensitive information, such as session tokens, potentially resulting in account hijacking.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51862 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in TelegAI (telegai.com) thru 2025-05-26 in its chat component. An attacker can exploi...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51862</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in TelegAI (telegai.com) thru 2025-05-26 in its chat component. An attacker can exploit this IDOR to tamper other users' conversation. Additionally, malicious contents and XSS payloads can be injected, leading to phishing attack, user spoofing and account hijacking via XSS.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51863 | Self Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChatGPT Unli (ChatGPTUnli.com) thru 2025-05-26 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code v...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51863</link><description>Self Cross Site Scripting (XSS) vulnerability in ChatGPT Unli (ChatGPTUnli.com) thru 2025-05-26 allows attackers to execute arbitrary code via a crafted SVG file to the chat interface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8015 | Shortcodes Ultimate &amp;lt;= 7.4.2 - Authenticated (Author+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via Image Title and Slide Link</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8015</link><description>The WP Shortcodes Plugin — Shortcodes Ultimate plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via an uploaded image's 'Title' and 'Slide link' fields in all versions up to, and including, 7.4.2 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Author-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51864 | A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in AIBOX LLM chat (chat.aibox365.cn) through 2025-05-27, allowing attackers to h...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51864</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in AIBOX LLM chat (chat.aibox365.cn) through 2025-05-27, allowing attackers to hijack accounts through stolen JWT tokens.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51865 | Ai2 playground web service (playground.allenai.org) LLM chat through 2025-06-03 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR), al...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51865</link><description>Ai2 playground web service (playground.allenai.org) LLM chat through 2025-06-03 is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR), allowing attackers to gain sensitvie information via enumerating thread keys in the URL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8018 | code-projects Food Ordering Review System reservation_page.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8018</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Food Ordering Review System 1.0. It has been declared as critical. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /user/reservation_page.php. The manipulation of the argument reg_Id leads to sql injection. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. Other parameters might be affected as well.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4878 | Libssh: use of uninitialized variable in privatekey_from_file()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4878</link><description>A vulnerability was found in libssh, where an uninitialized variable exists under certain conditions in the privatekey_from_file() function. This flaw can be triggered if the file specified by the filename doesn't exist and may lead to possible signing failures or heap corruption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4295 | Host Header Injection in HotelRunner&amp;#x27;s B2B</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4295</link><description>Improper Validation of Certificate with Host Mismatch vulnerability in HotelRunner B2B allows HTTP Response Splitting.This issue affects B2B: before 04.06.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-51867 | Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Deepfiction AI (deepfiction.ai) thru June 3, 2025, allowing attackers to chat with ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-51867</link><description>Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability in Deepfiction AI (deepfiction.ai) thru June 3, 2025, allowing attackers to chat with the LLM using other users' credits via sensitive information gained by the /browse/stories endpoint.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4294 | XSS in HotelRunner&amp;#x27;s B2B</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4294</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in HotelRunner B2B allows Cross-Site Scripting (XSS).This issue affects B2B: before 04.06.2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-8017 | Tenda AC7 httpd setMacFilterCfg formSetMacFilterCfg stack-based overflow</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-8017</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Tenda AC7 15.03.06.44. It has been classified as critical. Affected is the function formSetMacFilterCfg of the file /goform/setMacFilterCfg of the component httpd. The manipulation of the argument deviceList leads to stack-based buffer overflow. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10140 | Ajax Load More &amp;lt; 2.8.1.2 - Subscriber+ File Upload &amp;amp; Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10140</link><description>The Ajax Load More plugin before 2.8.1.2 does not have authorisation in some of its AJAX actions, allowing any authenticated users, such as subscriber, to upload and delete arbitrary files.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34140 | ETQ Reliance CG/NXG API Authorization Bypass via ;localized-text URI Suffix</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34140</link><description>An authorization bypass vulnerability exists in ETQ Reliance (legacy CG and NXG SaaS platforms). By appending a specific URI suffix to certain API endpoints, an unauthenticated attacker can bypass access control checks and retrieve limited sensitive resources. The root cause was a misconfiguration in API authorization logic, which has since been corrected in SE.2025.1 and 2025.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34141 | ETQ Reliance CG Reflected Cross-Site Scripting in `SQLConverterServlet`</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34141</link><description>A reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability exists in ETQ Reliance CG (legacy) platform within the `SQLConverterServlet` component. This vulnerability requires user interaction, such as clicking a crafted link, and may result in execution of unauthorized scripts in the user's context. The affected servlet was unnecessarily exposed to authenticated users and has since been disabled in version SE.2025.1.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34142 | ETQ Reliance CG XML External Entity (XXE) Injection in SSO SAML Handler</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34142</link><description>An XML External Entity (XXE) injection vulnerability exists in ETQ Reliance on the CG (legacy) platform within the `/resources/sessions/sso` endpoint. The SAML authentication handler processes XML input without disabling external entity resolution, allowing crafted SAML responses to invoke external entity references. This could enable attackers to retrieve sensitive files or perform server-side request forgery (SSRF). The issue was addressed by disabling external entity processing for the affected XML parser in versions SE.2025.1 and 2025.1.2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-34143 | ETQ Reliance CG Authentication Bypass via Trailing Space RCE</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-34143</link><description>An authentication bypass vulnerability exists in ETQ Reliance on the CG (legacy) platform. The application allowed login as the privileged internal SYSTEM user by manipulating the username field. The SYSTEM account does not require a password, enabling attackers with network access to the login page to obtain elevated access. Once authenticated, an attacker could achieve remote code execution by modifying Jython scripts within the application. This issue was resolved by introducing stricter validation logic to exclude internal accounts from public authentication workflows in version MP-4583.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7705 | Authentication bypass due to compatibility mode enabled by default</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7705</link><description>: Active Debug Code vulnerability in ABB Switch Actuator 4 DU-83330, ABB Switch actuator, door/light 4 DU -83330-500.This issue affects Switch Actuator 4 DU-83330: All Versions; Switch actuator, door/light 4 DU -83330-500: All Versions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4284 | Reflected XSS in Rolantis Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Agentis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4284</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation (XSS or 'Cross-site Scripting') vulnerability in Rolantis Information Technologies Agentis allows Reflected XSS, DOM-Based XSS.This issue affects Agentis: before 4.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-4285 | SQLi in Rolantis Information Technologies&amp;#x27; Agentis</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-4285</link><description>Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability in Rolantis Information Technologies Agentis allows SQL Injection.This issue affects Agentis: before 4.32.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7899 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in extension &amp;quot;powermail&amp;quot; (powermail)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7899</link><description>The powermail extension for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference resulting in download of arbitrary files from the webserver. This issue affects powermail version 12.0.0 up to 12.5.2 and version 13.0.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:01:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7900 | Insecure Direct Object Reference in extension &amp;quot;femanager&amp;quot; (femanager)</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7900</link><description>The femanager extension for TYPO3 allows Insecure Direct Object Reference resulting in unauthorized modification of userdata. This issue affects femanager version 6.4.1 and below, 7.0.0 to 7.5.2 and 8.0.0 to 8.3.0</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7427 | Uncontrolled Search Path Element in Arm Development Studio before 2025</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7427</link><description>Uncontrolled Search Path Element in Arm Development Studio before 2025 may allow an attacker to perform a DLL hijacking attack. Successful exploitation could lead to local arbitrary code execution in the context of the user running Arm Development Studio.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-46267 | Hidden functionality issue exists in WRC-BE36QS-B and WRC-W701-B. If exploited, the product's hidden debug function may be enabled by a remo...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-46267</link><description>Hidden functionality issue exists in WRC-BE36QS-B and WRC-W701-B. If exploited, the product's hidden debug function may be enabled by a remote attacker who can log in to WebGUI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-53472 | WRC-BE36QS-B and WRC-W701-B contain an improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerabil...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-53472</link><description>WRC-BE36QS-B and WRC-W701-B contain an improper neutralization of special elements used in an OS command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability in WebGUI. If exploited, an arbitrary OS command may be executed by a remote attacker who can log in to WebGUI.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6082 | Birth Chart Compatibility &amp;lt;= 2.0 - Unauthenticated Full Path Exposure</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6082</link><description>The Birth Chart Compatibility plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Full Path Disclosure in all versions up to, and including, 2.0. This is due to insufficient protection against directly accessing the plugin's index.php file, which causes an error exposing the full path. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to retrieve the full path of the web application, which can be used to aid other attacks. The information displayed is not useful on its own, and requires another vulnerability to be present for damage to an affected website.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6187 | bSecure 1.3.7 - 1.7.9 - Missing Authorization to Unauthenticated Privilege Escalation via order_info REST Endpoint</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6187</link><description>The bSecure plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Privilege Escalation due to missing authorization within its order_info REST endpoint in versions 1.3.7 through 1.7.9. The plugin registers the /webhook/v2/order_info/ route with a permission_callback that always returns true, effectively bypassing all authentication. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers who know any user’s email to obtain a valid login cookie and fully impersonate that account.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6213 | Nginx Cache Purge Preload &amp;lt;= 2.1.1 - Authenticated (Administrator+) Remote Code Execution</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6213</link><description>The Nginx Cache Purge Preload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Remote Code Execution in all versions up to, and including, 2.1.1 via the 'nppp_preload_cache_on_update' function. This is due to insufficient sanitization of the $_SERVER['HTTP_REFERERER'] parameter passed from the 'nppp_handle_fastcgi_cache_actions_admin_bar' function. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Administrator-level access and above, to execute code on the server.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7685 | Like &amp;amp; Share My Site &amp;lt;= 0.2 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7685</link><description>The Like &amp; Share My Site plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 0.2. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'lsms_admin' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7687 | Latest Post Accordian Slider &amp;lt;= 1.3 - Cross-Site Request Forgery to Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7687</link><description>The Latest Post Accordian Slider plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Cross-Site Request Forgery in all versions up to, and including, 1.3. This is due to missing or incorrect nonce validation on the 'lpaccordian' page. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to update settings and inject malicious web scripts via a forged request granted they can trick a site administrator into performing an action such as clicking on a link.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7692 | Orion Login with SMS &amp;lt;= 1.0.5 - Authenticated Bypass via Weak OTP</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7692</link><description>The Orion Login with SMS plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Authentication Bypass in all versions up to, and including, 1.0.5. This is due to the olws_handle_verify_phone() function not utilizing a strong enough OTP value, exposing the hash needed to generate the OTP value, and no restrictions on the number of attempts to submit the code. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to log in as other users, including administrators, if they have access to their phone number.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-38352 | posix-cpu-timers: fix race between handle_posix_cpu_timers() and posix_cpu_timer_del()</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-38352</link><description>In the Linux kernel, the following vulnerability has been resolved:

posix-cpu-timers: fix race between handle_posix_cpu_timers() and posix_cpu_timer_del()

If an exiting non-autoreaping task has already passed exit_notify() and
calls handle_posix_cpu_timers() from IRQ, it can be reaped by its parent
or debugger right after unlock_task_sighand().

If a concurrent posix_cpu_timer_del() runs at that moment, it won't be
able to detect timer-&gt;it.cpu.firing != 0: cpu_timer_task_rcu() and/or
lock_task_sighand() will fail.

Add the tsk-&gt;exit_state check into run_posix_cpu_timers() to fix this.

This fix is not needed if CONFIG_POSIX_CPU_TIMERS_TASK_WORK=y, because
exit_task_work() is called before exit_notify(). But the check still
makes sense, task_work_add(&amp;amp;tsk-&gt;posix_cputimers_work.work) will fail
anyway in this case.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7645 | Extensions For CF7 (Contact form 7 Database, Conditional Fields and Redirection) &amp;lt;= 3.2.8 - Unauthenticated Arbitrary File Deletion Triggered via Admin Form Submission Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7645</link><description>The Extensions For CF7 (Contact form 7 Database, Conditional Fields and Redirection) plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file deletion due to insufficient file path validation in the 'delete-file' field in all versions up to, and including, 3.2.8. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to delete arbitrary files on the server, when an administrator deletes the submission, which can easily lead to remote code execution when the right file is deleted (such as wp-config.php).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-52580 | Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in "region PAY" App for Android prior to 1.5.28. If exploited, sensitive user ...</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-52580</link><description>Insertion of sensitive information into log file issue exists in "region PAY" App for Android prior to 1.5.28. If exploited, sensitive user information may be exposed to an attacker who has access to the application logs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6585 | WP JobHunt &amp;lt;= 7.2 - Authenticated (Subscriber+) Insecure Direct Object Reference to Arbitrary Account Deletion</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6585</link><description>The WP JobHunt plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Insecure Direct Object Reference in all versions up to, and including, 7.2 via the cs_remove_profile_callback() function due to missing validation on a user controlled key. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Subscriber-level access and above, to delete accounts of other users including admins.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7495 | WP-Members &amp;lt;= 3.5.4.1 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7495</link><description>The WP-Members Membership Plugin plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's 'wpmem_login_link' shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 3.5.4.1 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7644 | Pixel Gallery Addons for Elementor – Easy Grid, Creative Gallery, Drag and Drop Grid, Custom Grid Layout, Portfolio Gallery &amp;lt;= 1.6.7 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7644</link><description>The Pixel Gallery Addons for Elementor – Easy Grid, Creative Gallery, Drag and Drop Grid, Custom Grid Layout, Portfolio Gallery plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via URLs in all widgets in all versions up to, and including, 1.6.7 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7953 | Sanluan PublicCMS viewer.html redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7953</link><description>A vulnerability, which was classified as problematic, has been found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.a. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file publiccms-parent/publiccms/src/main/webapp/resource/plugins/pdfjs/viewer.html. The manipulation of the argument File leads to open redirect. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named f1af17af004ca9345c6fe4d5936d87d008d26e75. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7952 | TOTOLINK T6 MQTT Packet wireless.so ckeckKeepAlive command injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7952</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical was found in TOTOLINK T6 4.1.5cu.748. This vulnerability affects the function ckeckKeepAlive of the file wireless.so of the component MQTT Packet Handler. The manipulation leads to command injection. The attack can be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7950 | code-projects Public Chat Room login.php sql injection</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7950</link><description>A vulnerability was found in code-projects Public Chat Room 1.0. It has been rated as critical. Affected by this issue is some unknown functionality of the file /login.php. The manipulation of the argument Username leads to sql injection. The attack may be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7951 | code-projects Public Chat Room send_message.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7951</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic has been found in code-projects Public Chat Room 1.0. This affects an unknown part of the file /send_message.php. The manipulation of the argument chat_msg/your_name leads to cross site scripting. It is possible to initiate the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2012-10020 | FoxyPress &amp;lt;= 0.4.2.1 - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2012-10020</link><description>The FoxyPress plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the uploadify.php file in versions up to, and including, 0.4.2.1. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected sites server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2015-10137 | Website Contact Form With File Upload &amp;lt;= 1.3.4 - Arbitrary File Upload</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2015-10137</link><description>The Website Contact Form With File Upload plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to arbitrary file uploads due to missing file type validation in the 'upload_file()' function in versions up to, and including, 1.3.4. This makes it possible for unauthenticated attackers to upload arbitrary files on the affected sites server which may make remote code execution possible.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-5240 | CRM and Lead Management by vcita &amp;lt;= 2.7.5 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via type Parameter</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-5240</link><description>The CRM and Lead Management by vcita plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the ‘type’ parameter in all versions up to, and including, 2.7.5 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with Contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-6831 | User Registration &amp;lt;= 4.2.4 - Authenticated (Contributor+) Stored Cross-Site Scripting via urcr_restrict Shortcode</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-6831</link><description>The User Registration plugin for WordPress is vulnerable to Stored Cross-Site Scripting via the plugin's urcr_restrict shortcode in all versions up to, and including, 4.2.4 due to insufficient input sanitization and output escaping on user supplied attributes. This makes it possible for authenticated attackers, with contributor-level access and above, to inject arbitrary web scripts in pages that will execute whenever a user accesses an injected page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7949 | Sanluan PublicCMS preview.html redirect</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7949</link><description>A vulnerability was found in Sanluan PublicCMS up to 5.202506.a. It has been declared as problematic. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file publiccms-parent/publiccms/src/main/resources/templates/admin/cmsDiy/preview.html. The manipulation of the argument url leads to open redirect. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used. The patch is named c1e79f124e3f4c458315d908ed7dee06f9f12a76/f1af17af004ca9345c6fe4d5936d87d008d26e75. It is recommended to apply a patch to fix this issue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7948 | jshERP updatePwd password recovery</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7948</link><description>A vulnerability classified as problematic was found in jshERP up to 3.5. Affected by this vulnerability is an unknown functionality of the file /jshERP-boot/user/updatePwd. The manipulation leads to weak password recovery. The attack can be launched remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7946 | PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System HTTP POST Request search-visitor.php cross site scripting</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7946</link><description>A vulnerability was found in PHPGurukul Apartment Visitors Management System 1.0. It has been rated as problematic. This issue affects some unknown processing of the file /search-visitor.php of the component HTTP POST Request Handler. The manipulation of the argument searchdata leads to cross site scripting. The attack may be initiated remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CVE-2025-7947 | jshERP Account delete improper authorization</title><link>https://www.cve.org/CVERecord?id=CVE-2025-7947</link><description>A vulnerability classified as critical has been found in jshERP up to 3.5. Affected is an unknown function of the file /user/delete of the component Account Handler. The manipulation of the argument ID leads to improper authorization. It is possible to launch the attack remotely. The exploit has been disclosed to the public and may be used.</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:02:18 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>